#761: Yuan En and Xie Xie Hundred Year is good to gather

All, in that flicker, like as transient as fleeting clouds that she shakes the head. All, in this moment, such as a handle sharp knife blade drop from the clouds, cut the day to break.

Three years of hiding time, more than 1000 day and night separations, in his heart some, only then she.

Time when he comes back, when he sees her on this Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, she even is actually not willing to uncover the surface for him.

All change into anguished, change severe pain beyond description, fills the air in the heart.

„Elder brother......” side transmits Na'er summon gently, Tang Wulin somewhat stiff turning head looks to her, smiles to her.

Na'er has tarried, she never sees Elder Brother to have such smiling face, is stiff and awkward, but also brings to wipe to despair and desolate. She suddenly thought that the heart of own is good to hurt and be quite sore. Sore is beyond description. She gripped subconsciously tightened his hand.

Brings the bamboo hat, to bring veil, she visits him from afar, he could not see that her eyes already the mist filled the air, he could not see that her long eyelash is shivering gently.

She how wants to lift the own veil, is, she is very clear, own should deserve, then breaks.

......

On Train, they were chatting ambition, had broadly like Xie Xie, had ordinary like Xu Xiaoyan, had easily and comfortably like Xu Lizhi.

Also there are......

„Marries you.”

Plays the noisy words, as if made her mood obviously low, his first time saw that she was like this desolate, just like autumn dreary.

Did her body, what exactly have? Her ambition, is very perhaps heavy and is very heavy. For those questioned and opposed by all people heavily, but must shoulder walking.

She does not want to injure this crowd of companion, therefore she has chosen with its deceit, was inferior that did not say.

„Everyone has secret, you let alone.”

„Your ambition?”

„Enlistment, I must enlist in the military.”

He must become formidable, at that time can retrieve Aunt Daddy, retrieves Na'er, he looks to out of the window, absent-minded smile.

She as if realized that his facial expression, past, had flashed before to future a moment ago in her at present......

That evening, her hair flutters in the night breeze, the eye pupil no longer is black, but sends out light purple halo.

In the palm the bunch of ray of light beats, wipe dark-purple to jump finally, dodges not to have.

She is beautiful like a riddle of moonlit night, in the eye pupil is deep Tanshui.

The life is a journey, has passenger and scenery along the way.

One day I will get out, but I leave your am the most beautiful memory.

Makes me frame in your mind, wishing me never to extinguish in that scenery.

......

In the Sea God lake the Sea God reason, being on intimate terms competition fourth segment had finished, three lived to be predestined friends ended.

May in his heart, the reason of thinking decide three to live actually only to trade shaking the head gently.

The speechless rejection, lets his intention great ash. At this moment, he even only wants quickly to leave here, looks for a place to bury own.

„Good, since No. 17 female student is not willing to choose, we do not force. Because also has last segment, therefore you have not been able to walk temporarily, invited all our female student homing. You formerly chose to be recorded. Then, is our Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting last segment, Hundred Year will be good to gather.”

„According to stipulation, Hundred Year good about this segment above, the authority will reverse, the male student will make the final choice. What if you choose just selected your female students, we will offer the most beautiful blessing, congratulated you to hold hands successfully. When this segment, formerly had chosen the Sea God fairy maidens of male student, the male student who everyone also 30 seconds of time when you select enters the stage to him said words that you want to speak. The male student who especially many female students select, our Sea God fairy maidens may probably try hard to touch your beloved men. What if the male student selects has not chosen your female students, you have one minute of vindicating time. However, I must remind your am, if you elect formerly did not select your female students, the failure probability will be then high. Failure probability of all previous Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting such choice surpasses 80%.”

„Meanwhile, believes that you also know. In this segment, holds hands finally a successful pair, might suffer others' carrying off a girl to be one's wife. Carries off a girl to be one's wife in segment, you can face together, so long as can mount near the Sea God lakeshore smoothly, even if you succeeded.”

„Good, asking everybody to be ready, Hundred Year was good to gather, immediately started.”

„We defer to the ballot to rank as before. What first presence, Xie Xie. Is quite quick, has not thought that has selected directly you. It seems like that we can congratulate ahead of time, but, wants to carry off a girl to be one's wife can also prepare to start.”

Xie Xie looked at people first wickedly, nearby male student cannot bear say: „Relax the brothers, nobody snatches with you. Some courage with Great Titan Ape in the same place, it is estimated that also you. On quick.”

Xie Xie stared his one eyes ill-humoredly, is stimulating to movement the own lotus leaf slowly emersion with joy, arrives at the forefront of male students.

„I choose Yuan En Yehui.” The lotus leaf stop, he could not bear shout.

„Feeds, has not arrived at you to elect.” Lan Muzi cannot bear say with a smile.

Xie Xie sticks out chest, righteous [say / way]: „How I elect her, has no alternative.”

Yuan En Yehui under foot lotus leaf emersion, „selects this disgraced fellow I not to know is right, I only want quickly to leave here now.”

Xie Xie laughs, „, I was your person.” The point of tip of the toe on the lotus leaf, flies is also to the Yuan En Yehui direction plunders gently.

Yuan En Yehui thinks really a palm of the hand claps him, but held her hand that to flicker in formerly him, she knows that later own impossible to treat him like before.

For these years, he has not always given up, throughout, for she tries hard, won't she be able to see? She has not accepted him, was actually not equal to that she does not pay attention to him.

He has many shortcomings, but actually wins in the special sentiment. He has not had any expression to other female student, he revolves side her every day.

Perhaps what he does not know, his genuine is moved her is not that vindicating, not for her but assiduous cultivate. But when Work Study Student Dormitory, sweeps the floor in front of her every morning, gets trough clear water for her.

She likes visiting him appearance that for she works, that time he was quiet and earnest, moreover in the look was also bringing the light gentleness.

Perhaps is side that that day saw, moved her heartstrings.

In her heart, had already chosen him, but, she has the fear, she feared that he is spur-of-the-moment.

More than 1000 day and night Test, have proven his rigid. Defended Yun Kai to see moon/month Ming, finally hugged the beautiful woman to turn over.

„Good, below I announced that this Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting first to becoming a buddhist get to know successfully, Yuan En Yehui and Xie Xie. Congratulates you. You will receive Sea God Blessing, obtains the congratulation of Academy. Wish your reason to decide three to live, Hundred Year to be good to gather.”

Selects point ray of light from Sea God lakeside take-off of distant place, from the sky blasts out enchanting eye-catching fireworks.

Under the complementing of fireworks, the smiling face and formerly bracelet on Xie Xie face completely vanished, he is pulling both hands of Yuan En Yehui, said in a soft voice: „Yuan En, I will be good to you. Certain meeting. I will protect you with my Life, for you, even if gives up the entire world I also wanting. I like you, I am sincerity, this I only like you for a lifetime.”

Yuan En Yehui visits him dull, his earnest appearance made her heart in slight(ly) was shivering, she somewhat charming lowered the head slightly, „.”

Xie Xie Control does not live in the own emotion again, fierce stretching out the arms hugs into her the bosom. But this time, has not resisted, only then that a pair of encirclement in the arm of his waist.

---------------------

Yes, Wulin, must start!( To be continued.)

#762: I am the girl of trying to outdo others

The applause such as slating resounds on the shore and level of the lake, appear(ance) of first to lover, making all people cheer for them.

The eye socket of Xie Xie was red, for this day, he waited to be too long and be too long. He is how is not easy to wait till arrival of this day!

Applause that Tang Wulin also makes an effort, on his face has been full of the smiling face, congratulates you, Yuan En and Xie Xie, congratulate you.

The fireworks diverges, Xie Xie and lotus leaf of Yuan En Yehui under foot turned into golden-colored, delivers them to go to the shore. Has not carried off a girl to be one's wife, only then blessed.

They disembark, has not actually departed, with them stands, just replaced has tried Xu Lizhi and Ye Xinglan of clothes.

„Sorry, Sister Xinglan. Is I am not good, we have not seen the fireworks.” A Xu Lizhi face apologetic looks at Ye Xinglan.

Ye Xinglan is holding his fat hand, one like childhood such.

„Here fireworks are too few, I must be more, you buy for me.”

Xu Lizhi excited [say / way]: „Good! I buy certainly the Shrek City best fireworks, only blooms for you.”

„Disgustingly don't be good.” Xie Xie cannot bear tease.

„Who can be disgusting than you!” Xu Lizhi stared his one eyes.

In this time, on the Sea God lake level of the lake is transmitting Lan Muzi sounds/voices, „next, Tang Wulin.”

Hears these six characters, four people become are suddenly peaceful, their vision could not bear go to the level of the lake, subconscious, all gripped tightened the fist.

Captain!

Captain came back, they also without enough time cheer for him. But they are very clear then regarding him and her, will be what kind important.

„Why doesn't she uncover the surface? Moreover she has not chosen Captain , because is jealous?” Xu Lizhi cannot bear say.

Xie Xie shakes the head, the brow is tight, „, should not be jealous that simple. Gu Yue character haven't you understood? If she wants to obtain anything, she will not hesitate all strives, like initially she just came the time, will always sit by Boss, even when we fold the hand, she also always chooses to place under the palm of Boss. They had certainly anything, occurred matter that some we did not know, even I suspected that Boss is missing for a long time also Transformation with them is so related.”

„Some of I also such feelings, if they cannot retrieve on Blind Date General Meeting today each other, perhaps......” Yuan En Yehui sighed, but this was actually not they desired.

Tang Wulin has not thought second will pull out own, the lotus leaf of under foot naturally drifts about forward, arrived at the male students front.

On face because of Xie Xie and Yuan En Yehui, but the appear(ance) smiling face has restrained, stands on the lotus leaf, his back supports as before straightly.

He was 18 years old, he has grown up. As a man, what matter regardless of comes across, he will not make own perish in light of this.

Even if in the heart extremely the ache, he also as before must a man such stand likely. Spiritless forever is unable to solve the problem, cannot obtain to sympathize.

„Just had chosen Wulin altogether three female students, then, then, asked these three female students to say your aspirations to him separately, made final striving. We decide your vindicating orders by ballot way (of life). Yinmeng, you come.”

Tang Yinmeng has extracted a first name, „Wu Siduo.”

Wu Siduo gains ground, is looking out float Tang Wulin on level of the lake, at this moment, she suddenly had some confidence, because, Gu Yue has not uncovered the surface, has not elected him.

More than three years of time does not see, they already thorough being cut off? Perhaps then, own also has an opportunity.

She looked at Dragon Spear Goddess Na'er, she truly compared with the own beautiful, but had never heard she and he have anything to occur together. Moreover, she is only 16 years old.

„Wulin, long time no see. Chooses you on this Blind Date General Meeting, is I passes through to think. Or if your appear(ance), perhaps my choice will not be different. But you came. Pays attention to you are when we just tested into Shrek Academy in the past. Just started that little while, said honestly that my point could not have a liking for you. I thought that you just rely on luckily were becoming Shrek, such you, why can also become Class Leader of our class?”

„But, afterward you used the motion of own to prove, you have that qualifications. Every day looks that you grow step by step, my confidence starts to vacillate, when I lose to you time and time again, your form continually is also deepening in my heart.”

„I am girl of trying to outdo others, from infancy to maturity, my anything must achieve well. Any thing must be best. In my eyes, you are best. Only then you can let my heart movement. I will not speak any talk between lovers, I can only say that I will accompany you to walk is farther.”

These words are not touching, but actually absolutely proceeds from the bottom of one's heart. Distant place shore, Luo Guixing and Xu Yucheng wet standing there, they look at each other to smile bitterly.

Yes, they had already guessed correctly she chooses his reason, because he is best.

„What Wulin had to say?” Lan Muzi asked.

Tang Wulin sighed one lightly, „was sorry very much, Wu Siduo. Love and strength not absolute relations. In my heart, we are only classmate(s). Sorry, person who I had liking.”

Wu Siduo takes a deep breath tone, „she?”

Tang Wulin eyes suddenly Great Release of Rays of Light, [say / way] without hesitation: „Yes.”

Wu Siduo nodded, she has smiled suddenly, „elects you, I did not regret. Because you are best, even if treats sentimental, you are also. Loses to her, I recognized.”

Spoke these words, she jumps leaps, has not come ashore directly, but plunges into the water. Like formerly Luo Guixing and Xu Yucheng such, submerged in the water to vanish does not see.

Gazes after her to leave, in the Tang Wulin eye has the apology, but, he can only this.

Lan Muzi sighed, „was a pity very much, then, next was.”

„Dai Yun'er!” Tang Yinmeng said this name.

The lotus leaf of Dai Yun'er drifts about, her look is somewhat desolate, when Tang Wulin said is that two characters, she understands, he said was not own.

„Third Brother, does not see for a long time, I asked you to be so long, finally met on this Blind Date General Meeting again. Do you know? Just I saw your time I was happy. More than three years, you should also just come back, finally with you in the together person should be I. Did you forget in Dragon Valley our mutual help to arrive at the Dragon Valley deep place step by step? If not you, will not have present me, in my heart, you are I have recognized the man. Even if you do not elect me, this point never will also change. I like you, is not because you are best , because you are you. I like you.”

Looks on Dai Yun'er pretty face is flowing the tears, Tang Wulin sighs one lightly, „Yun'er, sorry. You should know that in my heart already already some people. I cannot, is unable such to do. My heart many years ago had been packed by her. I can only say that you came late. I like you, although you are proud Little Princess, but your natural disposition is good. You is a good miss, what a pity, I can only say when hates not to meet by chance has not married. I do not have the means to branch out the same place the heart of own again, I can only , when you are Younger Sister, is the friend, actually cannot be Lover.”

Dai Yun'er visits him dull, listening to his persuasive rejection, the corners of the mouth place to have anguished. She does not have to open the mouth again, but has not given up like Wu Siduo, standing that but insists on lotus leaf, not having the choice to leave.

„, Last, is so invited our Dragon Spear Goddess. Na'er, this you.”

Falls with the Tang Yinmeng voice, on the entire Sea God lake level of the lake also has in the lakeside, is peaceful.

On Sky is the light of star moon/month, under the starry sky is the wave light on Sea God lake level of the lake is clear, is shining upon her that silver-haired purple eyes beautiful form, arrives at side Dai Yun'er slowly.

Her look was somewhat crazy, her pupil light ripples.

She looks at his vision, is not Younger Sister looks to the elder brother.

Tang Wulin shakes slightly, he felt the difference of her vision.

„Elder brother!” Na'er summoned one gently.

„Na'er, you......” Tang Wulin brow slightly pressed.

Na'er shows a faint smile, „does elder brother, you know? When my three years old, you gave shelter to me in the past at that moment, I have liked on you. For me, you used and not strong strong body have blocked these unprincipled people. You are incessantly good, you are braver.”

„You compare general person of same age to want strong many, six -year-old time, your Martial Soul Awakening, is Blue Silver Grass. Recognition waste Martial Soul, unfortunately lucky, you appear(ance) in Martial Soul Awakening Soul Power. Your ambition is becomes Soul Master, at that time you have not been able to think Battle Armor Master, therefore, you said that you want to control Mecha.”

---------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket!( To be continued.)

#763: Elder Brother, I like you

Na'er gentle looks at Tang Wulin, at this moment, in her eyes only then he, „but, wanting into Soul Master to need Soul Spirit, needs to spend a lot of money. In our family is not wealthy, Aunt Daddy has tried hard really very much. Therefore, you when were only six years old to choose have studied forging. I remember, just started very much clearly, after you are tired every day goes home, even including the expression cannot make. Collapses on the bed, even links me to ask you you unable to hear probably.”

„But you have not given up, as before you insist practices. Whenever you took the wages time, besides leaving behind part saves, surplus buys the candy to eat for me. These candies, but may be sweet sweetly.”

„Still remembers? Days of I have asked you, if I walked, you can think me?”

Tang Wulin dull listened to Na'er saying that his mind as if returned for ten years ago, got that time home.

......

My ambition is, stars sea

He has the youth of black becoming dark pupil fair skin, steps Eastsea City solitarily, was surmising the dream steps in the unknown road ahead.

Waste Martial Soul Blue Silver Grass, Innate Soul Power pitiful 3rd Rank. In the big city, he is ordinary, even if is tiny the grass seed that such as flutters in all directions, has fulfilled the original intention.

When other people are also bathing the inculcation of Parents, he did not have the family.

That wipes warm bright silver, goes far away in the vision, in palm slightly cool.

„If some day I left, you can think me?”

„of course can think, especially and especially thinks.”

The moist night breeze is stroking gently the cheeks, the left atrium transmits the feeling of warming up, he smiles, not anguished, only then to past remembering fondly.

In his heart, that silver-haired girl never walks away, she lives in some angle of recollection, under the setting sun, is calling Elder Brother sweetly.

I am Tang Wulin, my ambition is stars sea.

When the ordinary grass seed sprouts the luxuriant prairie, I can carry your having a heavy touch seriously before that piece of stars sea?

......

„Elder brother, I likes you, I love you. I am willing to accompany you with all time of my future, accompanies side you. Let me love how are you? I am earnest.” The Na'er expression is very serious, Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming that serious Lian Lou puts on somewhat is shocking at this time.

Tang Wulin originally dry lonesome and desperate innermost feelings at this time flood intermittent ripples. Who if most important in the female in his heart, then, mother and Na'er and she, was in the unshakeable status.

But he has not thought that in time that this is a focus of public attention, on this Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, she actually will say such words to own.

„Na'er, you are my Younger Sister!”

„No, I am not, I am only your Na'er, our any blood relationship, I have not been only your Na'er, I do not make your Younger Sister again, I only make your Na'er.” She was saying stubbornly.

Tang Wulin body slight(ly) is shivering.

„time arrived, Na'er, to be fair, I cannot make you say again.” Tang Yinmeng sounds/voices is somewhat strange, she has no alternative but to feel strange that at least compared in most this time has opened the mouth, looks at this people inconceivable, she is very good showing.

Na'er lowered the head, in the eye the tears are graceful, she said the words in own heart finally, but she had not said that Elder Brother, if you do not elect me, that......

If vindicating of Wu Siduo and Dai Yun'er, Tang Wulin can also be hard the feelings to withstand, then, Na'er these words, made his mind megascism.

He had once pledged that does not make Na'er sob again, may actually not think that at present lets that person actually own that Na'er sobs.

Na'er, you so are how silly!

But, why does not know, in his heart of hearts some feelings beyond description. Like such that Na'er said that they after all were not the biological brother and sister, Na'er are Younger Sister that he picked, is Younger Sister that he protected attentively.

Na'er gains ground suddenly, vision brilliant looks to Tang Wulin, „, if initially I had not walked, in your heart will certainly not have others.”

The Tang Wulin whole body shakes, right that she said that if initially she did not have, she continuously side own......

But said that Na'er of these words, the vision actually looked to behind, looked that was having the form of bamboo hat to not far away that.

Lan Muzi and Tang Yinmeng vision all centralized on Tang Wulin.

Lan Muzi cannot bear acclaim one, „has not thought really that Wulin Junior Brother, first time will see you unexpectedly is such magnificent scene, will have so numerous outstanding Junior Sister to like you, even has also included our small goddess. Then, now, should be you make the choice the time. As a seasoned person, I must remind your am, when breaks , then breaks, otherwise instead its chaotic. Makes your choice. Injures more people with its future, might as well make them see clearly your heart thoroughly.”

If no Na'er these words, Tang Wulin without hesitation, but, he really hesitates now. He most does not hope to injure is Na'er!

What to do, should what to do?

Some Tang Wulin delay, stand on the Sea God lake level of the lake, his first time felt that own somewhat paces back and forth.

If early knows that participates in Blind Date General Meeting is such condition, he rather does not participate.

Has a look at them quite difficultly, he.

„Wulin Junior Brother, please choose.” Lan Muzi sounds/voices was urging low and deep.

The takes a deep breath tone that Tang Wulin makes an effort, strength of whole body as if transferred in this moment.

He engages in introspection, the answer is exceptionally clear. He is not willing to injure Na'er, but is actually not willing to deceive her. Let alone, all these are that complex, he does not want to let go this time opportunity, even if the opportunity seems very uncertain.

„Sorry, Na'er. I elect No. 17 female student!” Tang Wulin said this simple several word-time, has almost exhausted own all strength.

An audience piece calls out in alarm, all Outer Court disciple this time completely cannot think that facing Dragon Spear Goddess wooing as if weeping and complaining, he has not chosen unexpectedly, but chose that not to choose him, from beginning to end No. 17 female student who even has not uncovered the surface.

This and are this possible?

Wu Siduo, Dai Yun'er and Na'er, Three Great beautiful woman! He does not elect unexpectedly, but chose that not to choose his person.

Shore.

„Really, Boss is Boss, the military might is so aggressive! Na'er......” Xie Xie has wielded the fist subconsciously.

Yuan En Yehui, Ye Xinglan and Xu Lizhi, at this time also all an anxiety of face. They know that regarding Tang Wulin, the most important time approached.

glittering of light ray of light in the air, the lotus leaf of No. 17 female student fluttered slowly, arrived at the front line.

Lan Muzi and Tang Yinmeng look at each other one, saw panic-stricken in opposite party look. They cannot think that Na'er will be rejected unexpectedly.

But in Tang Wulin said those words instant, on Na'er pretty face blood-colored shed completely, subconscious retreat one step, half foot stepped on into the water, the body shook shaking, Control lived in the personal appearance.

Lan Muzi has swallowed saliva, looks to No. 17 female student, „defers to the rule, you must take off the own bamboo hat veil now. Then listens to his one minute to vindicate.”

No. 17 female student has stopped, then lifts both hands slowly, has picked head bamboo hat veil.

That is pale white pretty face, the black hair and black pupil. Compared with Dai Yun'er and Na'er, she is not outstanding, even was covered by side two female ray of light completely.

On her face, was already full is the tears, the tears that Control does not live. She visits him, her lip continuously in gently is shivering.

Tang Wulin has smiled, looks at the tears on her face, he has smiled, she to him, is not No Love (heartless). Sees these tears, he suddenly thought that all were worth.

„You should elect her.” Gu Yue should not be excessive, looks to the Na'er direction.

Na'er has not spoken.

Gu Yue also said bewildered words, „I do not want to win.”

Na'er has actually smiled, at this moment, on the face of her pale white, has covered entirely the light smile, she sticks out chest, suddenly somewhat arrogant looks to Gu Yue, „something, are actually beyond control you.”

Gu Yue closes both eyes, tears once more to rush, „, but you may know that in this case, he will pay the how big price? Future we, meets the what kind difficulty.”

Na'er firm [say / way]: „I do not manage. I hope, can own complete gives him.”

Some Tang Wulin delay visits them, he does not know that their relations so did make closer unexpectedly? Actually were they saying what? Why his cannot understand.

Lan Muzi cannot understand, but Blind Date General Meeting must continue, „Wulin, this you, you had one minute of time.”

---------------------------------------

This was I already was actually intimate, everybody looked slowly, behind was continuous * occurred repeatedly.( To be continued.)

#764: Gu Yue, do you love me?

Tang Wulin actually shook the head, then looks at Gu Yue, „I do not take one minute, so long as I asked that her issue was enough.”

„Gu Yue, in this world, I have only loved a female student, that is you. Do you love me?”

He once some countless words wants to say to her , when he really facing, can say has these words. Also only then these words were enough, he needs, is an answer, can let his reckless answer, or makes him walk into another world the answer.

His right hand lifts, the palm turns out, shining scales the wrist place that reveals from the clothes has spread to the entire palm, shining Sharp Claws appear(ance), the five fingers back off, Sharp Claws points to above the own top of the head.

A strong courage vigor fluctuation beyond description bursts out from him suddenly, in that intense bloodline aura appear(ance) instant, presents all has Dragon-Type Martial Soul Soul Master to be all stuffy snort, complexion pale white, even if Long Yue is no exception.

How possible? His was Qi and Blood so why formidable?

The Long Yue whole face with amazement, he believes that after these three years assiduous cultivate, own has achieved another stage. Three years ago Tang Wulin, 1 vs 1 completely is not the own match. Even if the strength of his bloodline truly can suppress own some, but if no help of Gu Yue, he is impossible to defeat own.

But three years later today, that is impossible, own is Two Word Battle Armor Master, is present age Elite. Even if facing Titled Douluo, as if had strength of the spelling.

But, in this time, when that fellow blooms own bloodline aura, Long Yue actually with amazement discovered that own within the body that nearly madness the strength of bloodline under his Qi and Blood fluctuation suppression, appear(ance) the intense submitting to feeling, as if wanted his thought that own within the body the strength of bloodline to be separated from own to go unexpectedly, submits to before him.

Three years ago compares, his bloodline aura did not know formidable many times! Is this possible? bloodline aura of person formidable to so degree?

„Elder brother, does not want!” Na'er screamed one, but she actually does not dare to move. She can clear seeing, on that Golden Dragon Claw [gold/metal] turnover, Tang Wulin only need the palm to fall to below slightly, can scratch and tear the head of own.

„I only need to know the answer, that answer in your heart, clear answer. Do not deceive me, from your look, from your bloodline, I can feel you what whether said is the truth.” Tang Wulin vision brilliant looks at Gu Yue, the slightest does not let.

Gu Yue visits him dull, tears no longer flow.

Suddenly, her whole person as if collapsed, tears flood that nod that she makes an effort, just stopped, her whole person could not bear squat on the lotus leaf, she could not speak, was only the nod, was only nod of effort.

Tang Wulin has smiled, he has smiled proud, the right hand puts down, one step steps forward, he arrived in front of her.

He has drawn from lotus leaf her, drags into the bosom of own. Resounds with spirited dragon roar, appear(ance) of a colossus under the Tang Wulin body, has gone against him and her body.

That colossus sturdy powerful hind legs support under Sea God lake water, huge body, only the part of dew beside Sea God lake level of the lake, has exceeded 50 meters.

That is Tyrannosaurus, huge Tyrannosaurus, but it does not seem like Soul Spirit, but likely is real unyielding existence.

weighty black scales, the giant eye pupil of scarlet, that terrifying to the Peak huge body, appears its formidable to be incomparable all, land dragon first powerful strength.

The Long Yue strength is strong, his Mountain Dragon King is also only Martial Soul, but Tang Wulin was summons real Tyrannosaurus to be ordinary likely, moreover was not general Tyrannosaurus, under shining of light, on its jet black scales had dark-gold luster to be partly visible faintly.

Gu Yue buries pretty face in the Tang Wulin shoulder, both arms tight is hugging him. When she saw that Tang Wulin stands erect Golden Dragon Claw on his own, for many years in the innermost feelings has been tying tight that string broke finally. The thorough break, she cannot constrain that emotion of heart of hearts again, is unable the eruption of Control, incisive divulges in the tears.

How she possibly forgot that once point point Di Di, forgot with him in together that warmth time and time again. Facing the danger, keeping off that he is always duty-bound not to turn back before the own body, how all can forget?

Person non- vegetation!

If initial close because of certain goals, may along with the passage of time, all goals in influencing subtly vanishes.

Although she knows obviously own should not like this, at the beginning not care, she believes the own Control strength. When she faints from fear all already starts to be separated from Control, late, all already late.

The Tang Wulin form, already did deep taking root in her innermost feelings most deep place, want to dispel is also easier said than done?

Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, when she saw his appear(ance) in opposite that flickers, her mood nearly is unable to restrain oneself. She used how huge energy to restrain the own innermost feelings the emotion!

She knows, even if own admits defeat, should not with him in together, otherwise, all will come under his influence.

Therefore she is not willing to uncover the surface, from beginning to end is not willing. She even a little hopes that he can love another.

But when, he said that words, she knows that own made a mistake. While having tears streaming down the face, in the innermost feelings has actually filled happily.

All cannot, in he raises Golden Dragon Claw finally that flicker the collapse. At this moment, she only wants closely to hug him, walks arm in arm, in he cherishes, feels that for the past three years has not been feeling warm bosom.

She cries carefree dripping, innermost feelings all accumulating Yu in this flash as if all vanishes do not have the trail. She is not willing to think anything again, at this moment, she only wants to be a woman peacefully.

Tang Wulin closely is hugging her, his heart sudden one enriched, was seeing she had tears streaming down the face that flickered, he knows that she likes own as before, time cannot reduce the half minute she to his sentiment. Initially these injured his words, but was her mask. Why must put on these mask as for her, important? Now is important?

Dai Yun'er dull supine beginning, looks two people that in that Mighty Dragon top of the head closely supports, she suddenly thought that own appear(ance) that unnecessary. She does not hate him, just as such that he said that they know was too late.

Na'er has not cried, not sad, she is smiling, very happy is smiling, fills gratified smiling. Nobody knows that she in smiling anything, because of this time, sees on her face the person of smiling face, very few.

„Ritual becomes, congratulates Wulin and Gu Yue reason decides three to live, wishing you to be able Hundred Year to be good to gather.” Lan Muzi sounds/voices resounds through the audience.

At this time, should arrive at the time of carrying off a girl to be one's wife, but early has prepared for act Long Yue, why actually did not know, is unable to take the own step.

In front of formidable bloodline aura that on that huge Tyrannosaurus and Tang Wulin send out, his point is unable to start the thought that must begin unexpectedly.

Moreover, this is not own wants to see? He eventually not with Yun'er in the same place.

Subconscious, he looked at Xu Mi'er, looks to the young girls of that firm even some violence, he actually with amazement discovered that tears quietly falls from the Xu Mi'er eye, she looks at the two on Tyrannosaurus top of the head, has flowed off the affected tears unexpectedly. Also in this flickers, the heart of Long Yue has affected suddenly, seemed touched by any thing. But this feeling for him, is unprecedented.

----------------

Whenever quarrelled with the wife, she will ask me suddenly, did you love me? Then, I lost......

Asked the recommendation ticket. The sentimental play supports is actually not good to write, but must prepare the ground to the future. Everybody generous support Little Tang. Thank You (xiexie).( To be continued.)

#765: Gu Yue, I love you

Tyrannosaurus crawls slowly, returns to the water surface them. Gu Yue silver light dodges, the next quarter, brought Tang Wulin to vanish above the level of the lake. Moreover distance that these transmits is very far, even has not seen their forms in the shore.

In the Sea God lake the Sea God reason, this also becomes Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting previous time will make without a doubt the fine deeds that one loves to talk about.

On the Sea God lake level of the lake ray of light is as before radiant, but with their departures, slightly is gloomy. It looks like, the lead left.

Tang Wulin always does not know that Gu Yue unexpectedly becomes so blazing, like must melt him to be generally blazing.

She is kissing him unexpectedly on own initiative, that is bringing the slightly salty flavor kiss, her lip is fiery and fragrant, has the emotional outburst beyond description.

Is the sentiment in Tang Wulin heart constrains for many years? He closely is hugging her, wants all her to integrate in the body of own.

Where he does not know, only knows that surroundings is the trees. But in the own bosom, is own this life most important woman.

This kisses is very long and is very long. They are very shy, shy does not know how should continue. He in embracing tightly that her back buttocks place makes an effort, she closely is hugging his neck.

Long time and long time......

Until they have not gasped somewhat for breath, until their lips already slightly inflamed, they finally once more embrace tightly the opposite party, big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath.

„If I did not say love you, you will commit suicide really?” Some Gu Yue respites were saying.

„Why can commit suicide? I want to scratch the head to send with Golden Dragon Claw.” Tang Wulin chuckle.

Gu Yue gains ground, looks to him, he actually takes advantage of opportunity gently a kiss on her lip.

„Swindler!” [Say / Way] that Gu Yue gets angry.

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „If can deceive your heart, I would rather be the swindler for a lifetime. Gu Yue, I love you.”

Gu Yue has stagnated stagnation, after blazing complete explosion of innermost feelings, calms down slightly, the reason starts to get the winning side. She buries in his shoulder once more, on pretty face actually reveals anguished, „shouldn't you this, you know? You at ignition *. I cannot with you in the same place, we not be a passer-by, we cannot eventually in the same place.”

Tang Wulin said indifferently: „If doomed this eventually, why that must have once. Since there are once, then, all have been doomed. This is our destinies, regardless of many difficulties, regardless of we will face anything. I side you, will face with you together.”

„You are not clear.” Gu Yue pain closing both eyes.

„I understand!” Tang Wulin firm saying.

He had not asked what Gu Yue worry is anything, because he knows, if she is willing saying that sooner or later will tell own. But if she did not tell own, then, anything, he is willing to go to face with her.

Gu Yue holds his shoulder, some do not abandon leaves his bosom.

„Wulin.” She visits him earnestly.

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „Had anything to say said. I believe that you understand my regard, but you should also know that I always am a very dedicated person.”

The Gu Yue corners of the mouth place reveals to wipe anguished, „, if one day, you discovered that I am an enemy who you have to face, you will be what kind of?”

Tang Wulin said: „If arrived on that day time, you are the enemy who I have to face, you have killed me. Let me live in you. Like this we are also same can not separate.” He said is very tranquil, is not sweet words and honeyed phrases, but made the Gu Yue tears once more not by Control flowed.

Tang Wulin lifts the hand has wiped the tears on her face, both hands gently is holding her tender face, „actually to have what? Told me, let me and you faces together.”

Shaking the head of Gu Yue actually makes an effort, „, I cannot say. If there is such one day, perhaps, I will kill you . Don't you fear death? Don't you think of your family member? Puts me to walk. So long as I side you, at least I cannot Control all, if I side you, you sooner or later will have lost one's life because of me.”

Tang Wulin has smiled, „in the final analysis, because I am not very formidable. Gu Yue, you felt relieved that I will try hard become formidable, protects you well. Told me, was actually who to threaten you. Who are they? We in Shrek Academy! Also has the matter that student could not cope with on Continent?”

Shaking the head that Gu Yue makes an effort, „not and not, you not clear, you are not clear.”

Looks that her mood suddenly becomes excited, Tang Wulin hurries to hug into the own bosom her, „good, that not to say. When you want to say that when told me again. Sorry, Gu Yue, I am really good to like you, do you know? Do not leave me again, regardless of many difficulties, I side you.”

Gu Yue has not spoken again, she knows, regardless of own said anything, is impossible to affect front the determination of this man.

But, what to do should own? Attempts really for a while quick with him in the same place?

Present they, are not once they, they have grown up, they are the adults. Was not in childhood that ignorant sentiment.

After Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, if continues in the same place, she knows living own that own is impossible to dominate, can only be deeper and deeper.

They such closely are supporting.

„Walks, goes to my there.” Gu Yue said in a soft voice.

„Good. I am also happen to homeless.” The place that Tang Wulin that just came back, truly living did not have.

silver light glittering, she is not willing to leave his bosom, can only time and time again lead him to leave with teleportation quietly.

Tang Wulin surprised discovery, although own Spiritual Strength also entered Spirit Abyss Realm that stage, but when Gu Yue transfers Soul Power, actually as before gives him one type, the spiritual world vastly such as the smoke sea feeling. Actually her Spiritual Strength has achieved what kind of stage!

The place and Na'er that Gu Yue lives are similar, is a small log cabin, small log cabin on Sea God Island, but not in Inner Court. Without a doubt, this treatment is not ordinary Inner Court disciple can have. But because of her as the head of Shrek Seven Monsters, was assigned.

Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces rich degree far ultra outside on Sea God Island. Here cultivate, any type Martial Soul, has the twice the result with half the effort effect.

She hugs him to lie down, in that has only been spreading on the wooden bed of bed sheet, walks arm in arm in his bosom. He is hugging her, at this moment, does not have the half minute the thought that in his heart wants to blaspheme, some are only one type flows in the pure sentiment in hearts.

So long as can hug her like this, all became no longer seem to be important.

When does not know, her breath became even, that even that relaxes specially. Brow also gradually extend that she wrinkled comes, rests, in he cherishes like the baby.

He has smiled, exhausted also raids the heart, from coming back to the present, he never has also rested. But at this moment, all quietness, person in bosom, giving makes him very satisfied.

The closing one's eyes pupil, he also gradually falls asleep. Entered was him and her world.

Early morning Sea God lake, has the mysterious aesthetic sense, the mist fills the air, the ocean waves ripple.

She stood in the bund was very long, the shoulder was already moistened by the dew, did not have the meaning that the half minute must whisk off.

silver-haired ripples in early morning breeze, is staring at the pride of the morning of distant place, is ordinary just like the elf.

The big eye of purple produces an inverted image lake water, the corners of the mouth place is bringing to wipe the light smile throughout.

Another she comes quietly, arrives at her side to stand firm. She who the black hair flutters appears face glowing with health, on pretty face is bringing light blushing.

But when another she sees her, the smiling face on face actually vanished.

They stand shoulder to shoulder, similarly is staring at front the limpid lake water.

„You win!” Na'er in a soft voice and relaxed saying.

„You hope probably very much I win.” The Gu Yue brow is tight.

Na'er chuckle, „! I hope you to win actually very much, but I also already guessed correctly that you can win. Because I too understood his character. Do you believe? I as interlude, but existence, I think his wooing, but in order to finds an appropriate departure excuse.”

„You walked, he will be sad.” Gu Yue said.

Shaking the head of Na'er self-ridicules, „I lost, can I not walk? However, from the beginning I know that I will certainly lose, must lose, otherwise, he really will die, I said that right?”

Gu Yue was silent.

-------------------------------------------

This, everybody looks slowly, many future upholstery. I will try hard to write the following plot, behind has many ideas, I have arranged. Then, will have many everybody's unexpected plots.( To be continued.)

#766: Gu Yuena

Na'er sighed one lightly, „in the past, we made a bet, I chose with you resolutely bet, was because, I know that you wanted to look for a pretence to kill him, actually did not think the mind appear(ance) flaw. I have no alternative but to promise you, if I do not promise you, that time you, even if the mind has the flaw, without hesitation falls the homicide.”

„Do you regret now?” Na'er asked.

Gu Yue somewhat is in a daze, „regret? I do not know.” She does not know really own regretted.

Na'er said: „If you do not want all these, initially should not formulate to integrate the world way (of life). Facts showed that your such procedure is right, only then understands Humanity, can genuine find their Ruin way (of life). However, we in fact have actually discovered that Humanity does not have no merit to speak, at least, the Humanity rich emotion, is we completely does not have. Therefore had me, you of childhood time, in order to lets own really likely Humanity, has to Seal own. Good genuine fits into the Humanity society. But belonged to Humanity that some Soul born.”

„When you discovered that the Humanity mood some have not been possible Control time, wants to remove me forcefully became impossible. Will be enormous because of such degree injury you. But all these, gather my brother to be related , because my brother takes to my warmth and love, making me understand anything was the Humanity emotion.”

„But, you separate from the body me, a take shape independent individual, but is whatever, I am your part, we eventually is a body. Therefore you make a bet with me, betting my brother can like on you, can give up me because of you. If you have won, showed that the Humanity emotion is false, I naturally will also integrate you. If you lost, at that time you what said that you lost have made me forever the individual. Right. What a pity, I have your Wisdom after all, but also has the Humanity emotion, less than several years I understand that radically is impossible. I occupied you 30% strengths. If I am independent finally, then, you were not you. Therefore, you are impossible to discard my, the difference is, does not have the next fusion, is bringing slight defect that's all. Therefore, if you lost, you will certainly massacre my brother, fuses me forcefully. Did I say may be right?”

Gu Yue looks at Na'er, listening to her to speak with confidence, pretty face becomes slightly some pale white.

„Gu Yue, do you know? Reason that I am willing to make a bet with you , because you do not understand the Humanity sentiment. Believes in you that I and my brother's sentiment was that you thought plants. In fact you have made a mistake, what we are more is the kinship, perhaps I to him not completely am, but at least he to me is. But he to you, is actually not the kinship, but is Love.”

„Love and kinship are entirely different. Therefore, he has not given up me, has not betrayed me. Although he has elected you. Therefore, I lost, but, you actually cannot obtain the result that you want. Therefore, was actually who to lose, did not say.”

Gu Yue deep visits her, „you think that I do not know these that really you plan?”

Na'er has smiled, „your of course knows that intelligent such as you, to be how possibly able to look? When you try to alienate my brother , because you felt that the own emotion was affected, what a pity, Love is influences subtly, when you realize the incorrect time, already late. Because, he has been admitted to you. Therefore, you diligently have gotten rid in attempt, the attempt suppresses. May more be time grew, he actually more takes root to germinate in your heart.”

„Gu Yue, do you have the discovery, Soul Beast or Divine Beast(s), our natural dispositions were too pure. After once we contact the Humanity emotion, regardless of your energy is formidable, Spiritual Strength is vast, is actually not able to prevent that sentimental attack. It invisible does not have the nature, actually real existence.”

Gu Yue anguished [say / way]: „Did you think this unable he? Do you think really like this?”

Na'er sighed one lightly, „at least this can make his live was remote. So long as time grew, when he has enough strength, so long as you are unable to his act , I to believe that in the future nobody can kill he. Gu Yue, faces up to your own sentiment. The hatred will only make the human hoodwink both eyes.”

Gu Yue suddenly angry tunnel: „You really look like Humanity now.”

Na'er has smiled, „I am Humanity! I have thought. Therefore, I do not want Ruin Humanity, what I am willing to see is the peaceful coexistence. I love my brother, I also love our Aunt Daddy, I like the Humanity world. Humanity emotion. You have won, but, you also lost. But I am really good to hope that in the future you can have a good result, no, is you can have a good result.”

The breath of Gu Yue becomes somewhat rapid, „you think really I amn't able to firmly decide to kill him?”

Na'er shakes the head, „your of course cannot. You cannot. Even if no me, you cannot. Otherwise, will you wait till the present? When murders such as you resolute, so hesitant? When your hesitant first time, perhaps you have the opportunity, but after your so hesitant three times, impossible to his act . This point I am clear, your own also certainly is very at heart clear. After you fuse me, you are I, I am you, you will only come under a more tremendous influence. But does not set firm resolve. Loves him well, my brother is very outstanding and is very outstanding. Although we do not know that his Golden Dragon King bloodline came from where, but has to acknowledge that in the Humanity world, can be joined to our only then he.”

On the Gu Yue face full is dejected, „I decided wrongly was initially with your bet, or I should not separate you. At least such words, I can also affect subtly.”

„You lost, I also lost. You said right, my not being able to get down hand, I did not have the means to kill him. Therefore I can only leave him, making time and distance change pale our each other being in love, perhaps, only has this, some day I will kill him in the nonchalance. He grows enough quick, one day has killed me. You understand that among us the contradiction is irreconcilable, this is contradiction between Humanity and Soul Beast, is contradiction between Gods and Divine Beast(s). He is I, conflicts that is unable to solve.”

Na'er was silent, she somewhat is finally startled, „, but, I walked, you also walked, he will be sad.”

The Gu Yue body trembled trembling, „such also compared with me side him, but my these person Control do not live to kill his good again on own initiative. Present I, but also is far from all walking from Seal, Nucleus has awakened, but you know that our these under how formidable existence. Even had already should become Divine Beast(s) Elite. Even if present I, impossible to suppress them completely. Therefore, I am doomed to walk.”

Na'er white teeth bites the lower lip lightly, „perhaps you are right. Gu Yue, you really changed. You will have considered for other people, particularly for him. I understood, you must leave, to give him in a big way becomes among Zhangkong. You are the hope, in the future some day he can unable to kill him to you formidable. But you know that is impossible, God Realm existence, he is forever is no longer impossible to achieve your this realm.”

Gu Yue has smiled, „you understand that but you do not understand. You do not know that actually he in my heart is what kind of status. You are not clear, actually some present my many to belong to Humanity. You said right, I regretted, why I regretted initially to issue to integrate the order of Humanity world. However, my mission I must do, but I am not willing to injure the person who does not want to injure. Therefore, such contradiction, makes me come alone to face. I do not know how should do, but must walk forward. Comes back Na'er. Starting today, I no longer am Gu Yue, my name can be complete finally. He does not know that I called Gu Yuena!”

A flowing light sparkles, the body of Gu Yue suddenly became insightful, the insight of silvery-white, the six glow stars of under foot raised invisible knot, covered them.

If some people will discover in neighbor that in that silvery-white world, does not have the half minute energy fluctuation to overflow.

The body of Na'er also became insightful, the insight of silvery-white, she gradually moved toward Gu Yue, has actually had tears streaming down the face.

„I somewhat do not give up all these, does not give up person, does not give up Teacher(s), does not give up Elder Brother!”

--------------------------------------

Two female fusions, but starts, was not finished!( To be continued.)

#767: They walked

Gu Yue sighed, „, but you should know, many did not abandon, you did not have origin, you were doomed to come back. Otherwise can only vanish into thin air. You have said that after you return, you are I, I am you. I will let loose all, since the slight defect changed into the fissure, then, makes us accept this fissure together. Perhaps, all will be different.”

The silvery-white form overlaps, Na'er and Gu Yue open their both arms separately. Two forms start to fuse slowly, the Gu Yue black hair vanished, the black pupil turned into purple. The Na'er naivete vanished, she is growing up slowly.

When their appearances became exactly the same, when changes into grows up three -year-old Dragon Spear Goddess, silver light suddenly dodges, vanishes in the silent Sea God lakeside.

Tang Wulin does not know how long own has rested, he only thought very much own for a long time very long has not rested was so happy. That feeling, is hard to describe in the spoken language simply.

„Gu Yue!” Suddenly where he has remembered own, has not opened the eye, on the face completely satisfies. Smells fragrance that on her is in sole possession, subconscious opening arm, seeks her tender body. Last night anything had not occurred, he hugged her to rest an evening, that was blending of emotion, but at this moment, perhaps was rising sun that because early morning brought, his innermost feelings fiery. Although he does not know how should do, but the instinct is clear.

But, his hand has actually traced spatial, has not traced in the side to that moving tender body. He still clearly remembers that her tender body willowy, does not have the least bit excrescence, hugs in the bosom, comfortable of not being able to say.

„Gu Yue.” Tang Wulin summoned one again, has opened a pupil.

The sunlight sprinkles into room by the window corner, a wisp falls on him, warm particularly comfortable. In log cabin empty, neat clean. On the table, is placing a very big gift box.

Is breakfast that she gives me to prepare?

Tang Wulin jumped down from the bed, which did the Gu Yue person go? In the heart is having this thought that before he has arrived at the table, has lifted the gift box.

Immediately, the rich fragrance caresses the face.

Eats the Tang Wulin flash of numerous good food to judge, the food in this gift box is the nutritional value very high good thing.

„Oh. Good. The ruby shrimp, has not eaten to have been for a long time. Such bulk lots. Comes back! Only then on Douluo Continent so many delicious.”

The gift box altogether is divided into six, each is a flavor extremely good the good thing of nutritional value superelevation. Could see, these things do unusual is fine, has spent the thoughts absolutely.

Which Tang Wulin will be polite, immediately made chewing motions greatly quickly. Quick, full mouth fragrance at the same time, in the belly was warm, comfortable of not being able to say.

Food energy sends out all the limbs and bones, that feeling was really too wonderful.

Ate to the full comfortably! Which did Gu Yue go? Was attended class? How to have come back?

Tang Wulin shoved open the door to walk. Outside the door is a small courtyard, is not big, but actually green and luxuriant completely is the vegetation, has filled Life aura.

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, puts out the foul air again slowly. Immediately thought the whole body is changed beyond recognition.

„Which did Gu Yue go? Ok, in room she. Always compares looks to be better randomly, she knows me here, should be quick.”

Tang Wulin returns to the room, while he prepares meditation a while to wait for Gu Yue comes back. Suddenly, on bedside table hears sound.

Turns head to look that sees only exquisite Soul Guide Communication Device to lie down there.

Is Gu Yue? She has not brought communications device!

Tang Wulin walked to take in the past, hesitant, has chosen the connection.

„Hey, hello, I am the Gu Yue friend, she has not brought Soul Guide Communication Device, you have any matter, when she comes back me to pass on as soon as possible.” After Tang Wulin puts through Soul Guide Communication Device, immediately very polite saying.

But what made his surprised was, another side of communications device did not have sounds/voices.

„Hey, hello? Can you be able to hear?” Tang Wulin closely examined one.

Another side does not have sounds/voices.

Tang Wulin wrinkled frown, „, if you did not speak I when the signal was not good to hang up!”

„Wulin.” Finally, opposite somewhat difficult as has resounded a summon.

Hears this sounds/voices, why does not know, in Tang Wulin heart suddenly „thump”. On face expression also along with it dignified several points.

„Gu Yue?” Tang Wulin is probing asking.

„Um.” Gu Yue should say in a soft voice.

Tang Wulin said: „Where are you at?”

[Say / Way] that Gu Yue irrelevantly replied: „Eats to food that you did leave behind?”

„Has eaten, is delicious. You quickly come back. I just now come back, has not known how should enter Inner Court.” Tang Wulin says with a smile.

Gu Yue said: „Sorry, Wulin.”

„How?” Tang Wulin is suppressing the restlessness in own heart reluctantly.

„I must walk.” Gu Yue said finally.

„Walked? Do you want to go?” Tang Wulin rapid asking.

Gu Yue sounds/voices sobbed, „I must walk, for my own, for you, I must walk. Sorry, Wulin, I walked.”

Here, Soul Guide Communicator hung up suddenly.

Tang Wulin was silly immediately, he hurries to dial the number that Gu Yue dials, but is actually a piece of busy signal, cannot put through.

He not willingly allocates number repeatedly, attempt repeatedly. But hears has the busy signal, in addition, does not have least bit Transformation.

Walked? Did she walk? Can she go? It is not good, I must look for him.

A Tang Wulin hand is gripping Soul Guide Communication Device, flies also to resemble flushed. He just now rushes out, suddenly, a copious formidable force majeure drops from the clouds suddenly, Tang Wulin only thought that own ran upon a tenacity incomparable wall, the body rebound returned, numerous falling on the ground.

Must know, his strength very terrifying, although only started, but that impact absolutely is not weak, by the easy rebound, that counter- tension had formidable how obviously.

The form drops from the clouds together.

That is handsome youth, but on the handsome face the anger thrives at this time. He beckons toward Tang Wulin, body of Tang Wulin not by Control has flown in his hand, was held the front by him.

„Na'er? Does Na'er go?” Usually is always wind light Yun Dan, does not know Yun Ming that many years have not gotten angry, at this time are the anger soar to the heavens simply.

„Na'er?” In Tang Wulin heart anxious, time has not awakened.

Yun Ming lifts the hand, is a palm of the hand pulls out above him, Peak icy aura spreads over the Tang Wulin whole body instantaneously, making him hit to tremble smartly spirit, thus came soberly.

„Na'er? Na'er how?” Tang Wulin hurries anxious asking.

Yun Ming also calms down at this time, he is the what kind status, lets go, places the ground Tang Wulin. Then correspondence in the hand has given him.

Tang Wulin takes the letter paper to look that immediately dumbfounded.

„Teacher(s), Na'er is unfair to you. But Na'er must walk. I do not give up you, does not give up the teacher's wife, does not give up on Sea God Island all, all. But, Na'er must walk. Don't you want to be sad? Na'er has the reason that has to walk, but I must tell you, Na'er continuously you, when Father regards. Like me and Elder Brother Daddy. Teacher(s), you and teacher's wife should not be sad, Na'er is all right, Na'er all will be very good, Na'er walked. You help me look after Elder Brother, Elder Brother is specially outstanding, if possible, you also receive him for the person. Also, you passed on to Elder Brother, Na'er are all right, said that Na'er was looks for Aunt Daddy.”

The inscription is: Loves your Na'er.

This letter not many contents, but said a matter, is, Na'er walked!

-------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued.)

#768: Did not have the trail

Gu Yue just hit Soul Guide Communicator, said that she must walk, but at this moment, from the Yun Ming hand, Tang Wulin also obtained this kind of letter. In the morning when joyful and happy instantaneous nothing left, just like had been sprinkled trough cold water by the overhead.

He most important two women walked unexpectedly.

„Because of you, is you make Na'er walk sadly. If cannot retrieve Na'er, snort!” Yun Ming cold snort, entire Sea God Island as if shivered.

Tang Wulin has slapped a own face fiercely, sends out „” a resounding. Yesterday evening he truly was because has neglected Younger Sister with the Gu Yue mood eruption, at this moment, how can not the painful penetrating heart.

But after this next to long-handled fan gets down, although has left the red trace on the face, but his eyes also rapid calm.

„Hello, you are Na'er Teacher(s), you are Sea God Pavilion Master. Tang Wulin pays a visit Pavilion Master.” He salutes to Yun Ming immediately.

Yun Ming waves, „where will Na'er go to? Can you think?”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „I cannot think that I more than three years did not have. Regardless of not to be how impossible to think. Not only Na'er walked, Gu Yue just hit Soul Guide Communicator, said that she also walked. I do not know that they two departures have relations inevitably, but I thought that now we should seek for them in first time. Finds their all have possibly gone to the place. What friend does Na'er have on Sea God Island?”

Yun Ming sees him such quickly to calm down, has not lost the square inch, complexion has also relaxed several points, „does not have. Na'er usually lives in seclusion, besides with our husbands and wives, almost does not have anything to go out together. Does not have anything to walk near person. Otherwise, how possible cultivate by her age to be so fast.”

Tang Wulin said: „Their two both walked, may have some connections. The Gu Yue words, I must ask companion. Is Shrek Seven Monsters other people, perhaps they will know. Because I in Academy in Outer Court, Inner Court I was not initially familiar. Perhaps they will know. Moreover perhaps Gu Yue or the Spirit Transferring Pagoda person, she will go to Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters, I think that I should go to that side Spirit Transferring Pagoda directly first, simultaneously makes my companion seek together.”

The Yun Ming expression suddenly becomes somewhat strange, „Shrek Seven Monsters, do you know. Gu Yue is for your temporarily substituting for Shrek Seven Monsters Captain status, because she has the Spirit Transferring Pagoda background, cannot become Shrek Seven Monsters. She has believed you will come back, therefore helps your temporarily substituting for position.”

Tang Wulin stayed, „I do not know. She......”

Yun Ming sinking sound track: „First did not say these, pressed you saying that you went to Spirit Transferring Pagoda to walk first. I also mobilize the Academy person to seek. So long as they have not left Shrek City, certainly can find. Also had better be able find, otherwise I could not forgive you.”

„Um.” Tang Wulin cannot give a thought to the Yun Ming anger, although he makes own calm down reluctantly, can actually not be burning with impatience?

Ran, runs, while dials Soul Guide Communicator to companion that flies also to resemble. Luckily, everybody's Soul Guide Communicator number has not traded.

Xie Xie: „What, did Gu Yue walk? Boss, any situation. Good, Academy inside teaches us to look, you go to Spirit Transferring Pagoda first. You said right, she most has the place that the possibility goes to is Spirit Transferring Pagoda. Usually she every month will go to several times. Previous time we go to Spirit Raising Platform to promote Soul Ring the time, probably I listen to the Spirit Transferring Pagoda person to be honored to her name, she should not lower in the Spirit Transferring Pagoda status now.”

Yuan En Yehui: „Um, quickly looks. Since you are missing, the Gu Yue mood not has been right. In Academy gives us.”

Le Zhengyu, „I the place that eats meal to some outside us frequently look.”

Xu Xiaoyan, „I usually the cultivate place look to us.”

Ye Xinglan said: „I seek in the Inner Court range, Lizhi with me together.”

companion all bustle about, but Tang Wulin was actually similar to ran out of Shrek Academy that flew also to resemble, looked for one Car Rental, directly soared Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters to go.

Leaves in him soon, entire Shrek Academy starts to take action, Shrek City all official levels and transport hubs, all receive the notice, and obtained Na'er and Gu Yue picture, seeks for their trails.

Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming is the what kind character, he wants strength that finds a person to start instantaneously to be absolutely giant.

In fact, he has not sought for Na'er in Academy, takes his cultivation as, so long as spreads Spiritual Strength, can cover entire Academy easily, even is Shrek City.

But, he had not actually found the Na'er trail, even is aura. Na'er looked like vanished baseless.

No!

No!

No!

That side Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters, Tang Wulin has not obtained any useful news, first was he could not find. Next is, he is not the Spirit Transferring Pagoda person, has the material about Advanced personnel whereabouts he not to look up. When afterward, was communicated after Academy personally act and Spirit Transferring Pagoda, the news that Spirit Transferring Pagoda gave was, Gu Yue had not gone to Spirit Transferring Pagoda for half a month, now of course not.

Following three days, Tang Wulin and companion almost looked everywhere Shrek City each corner, had not actually found a wee bit clues.

Gu Yue disappears, Na'er disappears, all relation way (of life) are not all able to contact with them.

The major rises of life are mediocre, Tang Wulin watching looked for three days later, finally returned Shrek Academy.

He has not gone to Inner Court, but returned to Work Study Student Dormitory of nobody left. Here does not have freshman, all initially went to Star Luo Continent before them is the same.

Sits on the Dormitory entrance stair, Tang Wulin dull looks at the front, in his bright big eye this time had covered entirely the blood thread.

Why can such depart? Why?

Just in the same place, she just acknowledged she is loves his, actually such left. At this time Tang Wulin genuine realized, the trouble that she faces is huge, perhaps even in her heart, this trouble is unable to resist including Shrek Academy. Why otherwise does she want to walk?

Regarding Na'er, in the Tang Wulin heart has filled guilty, his quite guilty that late has not gone to accompany Na'er, comforts her heart.

Perhaps the suffering of dual pain made the Tang Wulin heart severe pain such as twist, change individual already to collapse. If no that time to spiritual wheting of willpower as well as body, perhaps he cannot withstand.

Sixth that year, Na'er walked.

16-year-old in the present, Na'er departs once more.

Na'er actually where? Gu Yue where? Why do they want to walk? What matter everybody has unable to face together?

Why can go to me?

Tang Wulin suddenly thought that is which time own Dragon Valley is quietest. Busy that every day keeping, but the heart is at least static. Even if has been full of missing to them every day, but at least not such pain.

„Wulin.” Gentle sounds/voices resounds in the side. When Tang Wulin gains ground looked, discovers arrives at side own is actually Dai Yun'er. In her behind also with two people, impressively Long Yue and Xu Mi'er.

„I heard, although does not know why she will depart, but since you are fall in love, looks. She will come back one day.” The Dai Yun'er consolation said.

Tang Wulin shook the head.

The Xu Mi'er stride arrives in front of him, „gets up, don't with good-for-nothing. I asked you, did she like you?”

Tang Wulin nod of without hesitation, regarding this, he does not doubt.

------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued.)

#769: Silver Dragon scales

„I can also visit her to like you. Why does she want bewildered departure?” [Say / Way] that Xu Mi'er lets somebody cool off or calm down: „Nothing but is you are unable to take to her the security sense. You are not very formidable! Although Shrek Academy is strong, but Academy is neutral, what formidable enemy she has certainly to need to face, is actually not willing to implicate you to walk, I guess is right?”

Tang Wulin has gawked staring, let alone, Xu Mi'er guesses as if also really almost.

„Since because of this, that is your issue, who makes you not very formidable? To retrieve her, first you must become formidable are good, otherwise, even if looks, she also same returns, will compel to have no other choice but also to walk. Small and weak must bear such pain. When you are formidable enough, who can also rob your Lover in this world?”

Xu Mi'er sounds/voices is very strong, even has been full of the satire, but is actually similar to a steelyard weight, pounding maliciously in the Tang Wulin heart.

Yes! Why will she walk? Is because own is not very formidable!

„But Na'er......”

[Say / Way] that Xu Mi'er disdains: „Na'er? You have the matter she not to have the matter, a Two Word Battle Armor Master strength don't you know? You? On that day I saw you am Four Rings, was worried that this was worried that was useful. On your this morality moral character, besides is much longer selects, has no merit to speak of simply, silver type wax spear head. Does not understand really why that many female students will like you.”

„Cannot you say him like this.” Dai Yun'er glowers to Xu Mi'er.

Xu Mi'er sincere [say / way]: „Silly thing, looks for the man, you who wants the man to protect were first good. His, gives for nothing me not to want. Walked.”

At the same time was saying, as soon as she pats Long Yue, turns around to walk.

Long Yue to Tang Wulin many sympathies, not having listened to Xu Mi'er to upbraid Tang Wulin, has not had an intense sense of joy on own initiative.

Yesterday after being on intimate terms conclusion of Tang Wulin and Gu Yue, he has chosen Xu Mi'er finally, does not dare to believe including his own some, after all, he and Xu Mi'er just knew!

However, he more and more thought now that the choice of own is correct. Xu Mi'er this miss character is frank, advocates strength. But own are most, isn't strength? He likes Xu Mi'er this surface crabby in fact innermost feelings having the miss in exquisite place very much.

„Mi'er, waits for me.” The Long Yue half step pursued.

„Mi'er, did you know Tang Wulin before?” Long Yue asked.

Xu Mi'er shot a look at his one eyes, „does not know! Why I must know this type of soft egg. The present woman, is face controls, the face is much longer is useful. I am the pragmatism, you grow, although ugly, but the good and evil is solid.”

The Long Yue expression is instantaneous, „you praise me?”

Xu Mi'er stared his one eyes, „of course! You think.”

The Long Yue forced smile said: Matter that „you should hear me. Shrek Seven Monsters defeats our matters in Star Luo Empire entire Great Continental Youth's Advanced Soul Master Elite Competition.”

Xu Mi'er nodded, „has heard. I also thought somewhat exaggeratingly, but yesterday and you hit one to come to see. Gu Yue they truly are some skills.”

Long Yue said: „At that time led is not Gu Yue.”

Xu Mi'er has gawked, „? What interests haven't I to these matter, been Gu Yue am who?” Her also really not clear these, as Inner Court disciple, she every so often are close up are studying own Soul Guidance Device.

„Was you just scolded of soft egg. Initially my Six Rings, Two Word Battle Armor Master. He and Gu Yue One Word Battle Armor Master is not, is Four Rings, their joint effort, has defeated me. Although I am not willing to acknowledge very much, but I must say that Tang Wulin is not the soft egg, he is very strong. Although he seems Four Rings, but, Seven Rings I have been able to feel the threat from him as before.”

„?”

......

Dai Yun'er somewhat anxious said to Tang Wulin: „Do not listen her, she definitely does not know that you had formidable say.”

Tang Wulin is smiling bitterly shaking the head, „she said also right. In the final analysis, is I am weak, I cannot protect them. Therefore they left me. Am I failed very much?”

Dai Yun'er holds his arm, „do not think, even if they walked, at least your side also has me, I will not walk. So long as you want, I have remained to accompany you.”

Tang Wulin shakes the head, „Yun'er, you is a good miss. However, on that day I said clearly on Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, could not accommodate the second individual in my heart, now is not at least good. But you could rest assured that I not because this matter perishes. I have many and a lot to do. They walked, I look for them. Xu Mi'er Senior Sister said right, they have the enough strong strength, in the normal condition protects own not to have the issue certainly, the one who has the issue is I, I was too small and weak. I must promote the own strength to be good as soon as possible. When my strength is enough, certainly will look for them.”

Tang Wulin character always tenacity, particularly when facing difficulties.

This time to his attack was really too big, just came back, the most important two people actually left him to go, but the Xu Mi'er words made him awaken, although in heart as before ache, but he actually very clear was telling own, whatever, the promotion strength was first is important.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin stands up, „Yun'er, I must go to that side Inner Court. I will buoy up. No matter, when I you is a friend, even is Younger Sister. However, we really possibly are not Lover. Sorry.”

Spoke these words, Tang Wulin starting to walk stride, directly soars the Inner Court direction to go. He does not want to injure a miss again, but the words actually must talk clearly, otherwise, will only cause many misunderstanding.

Stands there, Dai Yun'er visits him to leave dull, in a time heart five senses mixed Chen.

Tang Wulin Dormitory has assigned, of course not on Sea God Island. Departure of Na'er, making Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming be furious, although has not punished to Tang Wulin anything eventually, but his any will not give favored treatment.

The Inner Court main classroom building is big, the following Dormitory area is broad, the Inner Court disciple quantity little must be more than Outer Court, therefore, here has not been filled up with, each person room.

Tang Wulin returns to the own room, 2-3 take off the clothes, entered the bathroom directly.

several days has not taken a bath, he must clean the body of own, rests well, then starts the All-Out promotion strength.

Since could not find them, first promotion own diligently, making own more formidable, when they come back. Tang Wulin deeply believed that Na'er and Gu Yue will certainly come back, after or he was formidable, asks them to come back.

Blind seeking any objection, Xu Mi'er has not said right, he is insufficiently formidable, has caused all these.

The goal in heart reappears once more, strength of person was too tiny, he needs, is more formidable strength.

Opens water Dragon's Head of bathroom, when Tang Wulin prepares to flush the body of own, he actually with amazement discovered that on the own neck, does not know were when many a necklace.

Before during several days has been, anxious, pain, to rebuke oneself anxiously. He has not discovered unexpectedly on own was unexpectedly many same thing.

The necklace is a careful silver chain, under this silver chain, is hanging pendant, oval pendant, that unexpectedly is together exquisite scales, only then the pigeon egg size, Can silver, above has a close pattern layer upon layer all over the body. This clearly is together silver scales! Moreover, by understanding of Tang Wulin regarding own bloodline and Dragon Clan aura in Dragon Valley, this clearly is together dragon scales, silver dragon scales.

Silver Dragon scales! This and are this Gu Yue leave my?

Tang Wulin careful picks scales, some look delay, slightly why do not know, is touching this piece of scales, he really has Gu Yue in the present feeling.

Approaches carefully to look at present that will discover, scales is in itself not the pure ellipse, one side is oval, another side receives upwardly, the whole looks like, somewhat is similar to a small shield. The above altogether four patterns, layer upon layer covered to fold have felt the stereoscopic effect. Rear the pattern all upwardly bends, but slightly has the ray to shine on this scales, ray of light that this projects will present the three-dimensional shape.

Tang Wulin subconscious rotation scales, making the reflection ray of light fall on the wall, unexpectedly take shape small dragon-shaped, extremely strange.

Gu Yue loves my, she has no other choice but to leave.

In Tang Wulin eye moved removes gradually, what replaces it is a firmness.

In Love, most was worried that is the opposite party does not love own. When Tang Wulin sees this scales, he understood finally firmly.

-----------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued.)

#770: Gu Yue, is waiting for me!

Departure of Gu Yue is stems from has no recourse, otherwise, she formerly not according to pain. Xu Mi'er Senior Sister said right, reason that cannot defend her , because the own strength is not very formidable.

Subconscious grips in the tight hand silver scale, is feeling the sharpness of its edge, the Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, formidable, is own must first pursue now.

Gu Yue, is waiting for me. Regardless of many difficulties are placed in front of us, I will accompany certainly you to overrun. When I become formidable!

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin takes out own Soul Guide Communication Device, has dialed a number.

„Xinglan, can you come my one? Simultaneously told everybody, did not need to look again. This several days gets down, the place that can find we had looked, she is hiding us intentionally, we were impossible to find her.”

......

Looks into the distance, the white fog is confused.

Gu Yue static standing there. This is Platform, a baseless conjecture in Platform of upper air, in her behind, is Spirit Transferring Pagoda that towers palatially.

Here is the Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters roof. Was called Lingyun Platform.

She has stood here was very long, her right hand places the own front throughout, in the palm, is grasping anything.

„Although is very painful, but why, I actually like this painful feeling. Is this Love?”

This time she, restored originally the appearance of black becoming dark pupil, a white long skirt, can see from the golden-colored trace as well as front of long skirt edge badge that she rose very high degree in the Spirit Transferring Pagoda status.

She spreads out the palm slowly, in the own palm place, together shining diamond-shaped scales presents there, the golden-colored thin link connection it, on scales the pattern is magnificent, stack-up four, scales one side receives, presents to be similar in the shape of shield.

Her cautiously treats it on the neck of own, follows the collar place to send in the own most personal place it again.

Direction that she looks into, is Shrek.

„What's wrong? Doesn't give up?” Gentle sounds/voices behind is resounding.

Gu Yue turns round fast, who simply has not gone looks like the human is, already respectful saluting, „Teacher(s).”

Heavenly Phoenix Douluo Leng Yaozhu arrives at side her gradually, „Shrek truly is an appealing place. However, since has chosen departure, do not regret. You do not give up that Academy, doesn't give up somebody?”

The body of Gu Yue has shaken shaking, „did you know?”

Heavenly Phoenix Douluo shows a faint smile, „possibly doesn't know? That is Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting! Once I also......”

Here, she has stopped, tender face revealed disappointed.

„Is only, I do not understand why you will choose to leave. Can make you settle on, he is very inevitably outstanding. I have also seen him, truly is a rare talented person. You should try, making him join us.”

Gu Yue is smiling bitterly shaking the head, „I do not want to make him feel embarrassed. He is the Tang Sect person. If not depart, I think that I he will haul in Tang Sect may be much more than me the possibility that he will draw. You know my ambition. I cannot be hobbled by the sentiment.”

In the Heavenly Phoenix Douluo eye reveals a applause, but also flashes through moved similarly, „child, you make own shoulder was too heavy. Although I happily see all these very much, is, for your own words, sentimental matter, very possible one time to miss will not obtain. Moreover, walks according to our plans, your road can skyrocket, when some day you stand in the Continent summit top, perhaps you had discovered that he and you have the insurmountable distance, at that time, you impossible in the same place. You are young, even if you choose and him now are many in together time, Teacher(s) will not blame your.”

Gu Yue somewhat rapid shaking the head, „does not use suddenly. Teacher(s), my heart not like firmness that you imagine, if continues again, I was very perhaps difficult to set firm resolve.”

Leng Yaozhu sighed, „good. Then, all defer to our plans. Match altogether four that you will face, each, is Spirit Transferring Pagoda talent extremely, defeats them, you will become Spirit Transferring Pagoda in the future the Pagoda Master first cis-position successor. Every time loses one time, your cis-position will drop. Following time, Teacher(s) will bring a more tremendous pressure to you, stimulates your potential. However I believe that you are best. After all, you are Spirit Transferring Pagoda in history, only under 20-year-old age, Spiritual Strength already cultivate to Spirit Abyss Realm peak person. Once breaks through, then, your world sea extravagant Sky. Before 30 years old, must become Titled Douluo.”

......

„Thank You (xiexie).” Tang Wulin looks in front of own on the table, that glittering light golden-colored ray of light armor, heartfelt said to Ye Xinglan.

companion came, side him.

Not only this several days Tang Wulin All-Out to go to is seeking for Gu Yue, they also similarly so.

Xie Xie lifts the hand to hold the shoulder of Tang Wulin, „Boss, should not be sad, Gu Yue has certainly any matter to go, she will certainly come back.”

„Um, I know that she will certainly come back. Therefore, I must make own stronger. Otherwise, was fallen by her is too far, but how also to lead the way with her shoulder to shoulder?” On the Tang Wulin face is having the light smile, at least in the companion eye, could not see that on him has any difference.

Yuan En Yehui vents anger lightly, „you so are always strong, can always be bolder with each setback. This is I am inferior to your place.”

Ye Xinglan said: „I think that you need to adjust the condition to carry on the fusion again.”

Tang Wulin shakes the head, „does not use. I do not have am so vulnerable. If including One Word Battle Armor fusion difficulties, how I also to make your Captain?”

Yes, is placed in front of him on the table, is his complete set One Word Battle Armor surplus Component. Is these years Ye Xinglan personally for his manufacture. All Battle Armor have prepared, misses, is only the fusion.

Fused Battle Armor, he can become One Word Battle Armor Master. This once was his long-awaited matter, but at this moment, on his face actually only then smiled, not excited.

At the same time was saying, Tang Wulin has first taken up own breastplate, breastplate is biggest one, is whole set Battle Armor Nucleus. breastplate puts succinctly greatly, the both sides have a rectangular Armor piece to cover respectively, is the overall clothing, takes to be heavy with the hand.

Tang Wulin said: „Your retreat several steps.”

The people hurry to spread out some, leaves he bigger spatial.

Next flickers, they noticed that the eye pupil of Tang Wulin has shone, intense golden-colored ray of light bursts out from his eyes, the strong Qi and Blood fluctuation just liked the essence erupts generally instantaneously.

reaction biggest is Xie Xie, he stuffy snort, subconscious retreat one step, complexion one white, unexpectedly sits falls to the ground. The Battle Armor stress in within the body, covers the whole body rapidly, his complexion then attractive several points, cannot help but a piece with amazement.

Not only he, the feelings of other person also some varying degrees, they only thought that on Tang Wulin erupts an incomparably formidable pressure suddenly, that completely is superior that oppression strength to lower position. When that thick golden-colored mist gushes out from him, this feeling also became even more obvious.

In the people, Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan situation is best, was only retreat one step, other person at least retreat two steps.

The look on each face exceptionally shocks.

Must know that their each people on the scene, cultivate to be stronger than Tang Wulin, is Five Rings Soul King Elite, is One Word Battle Armor Master!

But under such strength disparity, Tang Wulin they of bloodline aura unexpectedly oppression has to plant feeling irresistibly.

------------------------------------

The new year's celebration, wish everybody Happy New Year, wishes coming true, good luck in everything!( To be continued.)

#771: The One Word Battle Armor fusion is completed

More than three years in the past, his Soul Power seemed did not have the least bit to promote, why can his pressure not know strong how many times compared with before?

If they know that Tang Wulin has been having to do with Dragon Clan in Dragon Valley, knows him, whenever Dragon Burying consumes the huge time will have dragon bone(s) nature take shape dragon spirit(s) to supplement that will not be shocking.

Right, Tang Wulin Soul Power does not have many promotion. However, the strength of his bloodline obtained unprecedented moistening in the past three years.

pure the strength of True Dragon is infiltrating his body unceasingly, even if his own , the strength of not completely clear own present bloodline has been actually what degree.

But what without a doubt is, has Mountain Dragon King Martial Soul Long Yue to continually by his aura thorough suppression.

bloodline promoted this stage, he started really genuine showed Golden Dragon King aura.

Four golden-colored ring of light raise from the Tang Wulin under foot successively, circles regarding his body up and down. The golden-colored light fog that bursts out from him infiltrates to that breastplate in slowly.

Immediately, breastplate starts to send out brilliantly, light golden-colored luster turned into Can golden-colored rapidly, Tang Wulin eyes is getting more and more bright, the rich golden-colored light fog has swept across his body surroundings diameter three meters range, all golden-colored Battle Armor Battle Armor Master slight(ly) on table shivers, then float, float in midair, regarding in Tang Wulin body surroundings.

Tang Wulin begins supinely, golden-colored scales reappears slowly, covers the whole body rapidly, his both arms and shoulders Battle Armor originally also along with it reappearing.

„Receives!” Tang Wulin gives a loud shout.

All Battle Armor like all were adsorbed by that golden-colored light fog generally, changed into golden light (Jin Guang) instantaneously to his body fusion in the past. time that several times breathe, on complete with his body fitting in the same place.

One Word Battle Armor, complete absorb!

light golden-colored armor piece covers the whole body, pattern does not calculate too, is only light dragon pattern(s), the both arms shoulders have the sharp knife blade to stick out slightly, when Tang Wulin Qi and Blood to rush, the Battle Armor surface reappears the light scales pattern.

helmet covers the entire forehead, the both sides have just like the dragon horn general bulge, the helmet center has crest line together to stick out slightly upwardly, golden-colored mask has blocked the face of Tang Wulin together, eye pupil dew that be only golden light (Jin Guang) four shoot outside.

This set of Battle Armor most remarkable characteristics are helmet both sides that to sharp dragon horn, as well as similar style, appear(ance) by the double small arm and double calf punctures suddenly, these puncture the edge to be sharp suddenly, carefully looked that also slightly presents is the dragon horn appearance, light golden-colored halo is mixing face armor piece ray of light glittering, to human a strange sense of reality.

Tang Wulin only thought the body of own instantaneously anything, but was quick, they as if turned into part of body, strength of Soul Power and bloodline pour into, flowed the body of own again, as if the whole person has increased, this was this time feeling. That huge amplification makes him unable to bear want to look to vent to erupt.

„You need to be familiar with Battle Armor strength, do we compare notes to strike?” Ye Xinglan said to Tang Wulin.

„Good!” Tang Wulin also wants to try, puts on One Word Battle Armor own, can actually be what kind of degree.

Inner Court has exclusive comparing notes to strike, this is different from Outer Court. Comparing notes of Outer Court strikes also needs the defray expenses to use, the Inner Court completely need, does not compare notes to strike, so long as empties can momentarily use. After all, regarding cultivation to achieve the student of certain extent, can compare notes to strike to promote own through the use is very important. Actual combat experience even is most times more important than own Soul Power rank, particularly regarding the Shrek Academy student.

Intensity that without a doubt, Inner Court compares notes to strike must go far beyond Outer Court, particularly protects the intensity.

weighty Guard Screen raises, including under foot, although is not quite comfortable on Soul Guidance energy feeling some, but this can also guarantee as far as possible is insufficient to destroy here.

Xu Lizhi in comparing notes to strike beside, in other people in comparing notes to strike.

„Who comes?” Tang Wulin looks to companion.

Ye Xinglan just about to opens the mouth, nearby Yuan En Yehui one step has stepped forward, „I come.”

„Good!” Cultivates on Soul Power is, Yuan En Yehui is in them strongest one.

„My Soul Power has achieved 57th Rank, you must be careful.” Yuan En Yehui said to Tang Wulin.

Three years promote 10th Rank, this speed seems is not quick. However, regarding is 19-year-old her, 57th Rank Soul Power is quite shocking.

Initially, Long Yue at age 20, is 60th Rank raises one's head that's all.

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „good.”

Both sides are separated by 50 meters, other people fall back on the distant place, Xie Xie cannot bear shout: „Boss, you cannot under the heavy hand!”

„Shuts up you.” Yuan En Yehui ill-humored saying.

Xie Xie smiles, „I also care about you.”

Yuan En Yehui no longer manages him, in the eye ray of light dodges, quick release own Martial Soul, Soul Ring ray of light rapid ascension, two purple three black, without a doubt, she promotes is not only Soul Power, but is comprehensive, in Soul King this stage, was considered as on Super Rank formidable absolutely.

Because on Tang Wulin is dressing directly One Word Battle Armor, Yuan En Yehui without hesitation also released own Battle Armor, covered the whole body just like earth dignified yellow Battle Armor, after collecting one set, the color saw when Star Luo Continent initially Tang Wulin wanted to be profounder.

This does not have the matter of means that after all, Yuan En Yehui itself also has Fallen Angel Martial Soul, but Battle Armor actually can only have one set. Therefore, when manufacture Battle Armor, she must the well distributed Two Martial Souls cut between as far as possible. Therefore, her Battle Armor in fact is the earth and darkness Dual Attributes.

When uses different Martial Soul, Battle Armor will cut the different conditions voluntarily. This itself in fact is a flaw, because to care about different Martial Soul, on sole Martial Soul, the amplification will be relative to normal One Word Battle Armor to be smaller.

Why this is also Yuan En Yehui is the Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor faithful supporter, because gives Battle Armor to strengthen through Spiritual Metal from the beginning, for her is most important.

Her Battle Armor manufacture gets up is most troublesome, if Two Word Battle Armor time does over to delay too long time again completely, let alone Spiritual Metal can also carry on more multiple Harmonizing Refinement alloy forging, thus makes own Battle Armor stronger, weakens the Dual Attributes Battle Armor negative effect.

Face upwards a long and loud cry, a Yuan En Yehui both arms show, two ray of light shine separately in her hands, her Soul Ring has shone, the body inflates rapidly, in an instant changed into height six meters Great Titan Ape.

Copes with Tang Wulin, without a doubt, Great Titan Ape Martial Soul is most appropriate. Can be able to see from this time Martial Soul altitude that compared with before, her Great Titan Ape Martial Soul was more formidable.

Two ray of light of that appear(ance) on both hands, initially Tang Wulin gave her two handle alloy Giant Hammer(s) impressively. And initially compared with, aura on Giant Hammer(s) was slightly different, the Soul Power fluctuation clearly increased. This underwent certain transformation obviously, making it more formidable.

Six meters high, stature incomparably majestic Great Titan Ape, takes such one pair again is being five meters, terrifying Giant Hammer(s) of giant non- Péng, that might, makes Mecha see that absolutely wants to turn around runs.

The Tang Wulin corners of the mouth also twitched, looked at Xie Xie of distant place, in the heart acclaimed. Xie Xie this fellow, has certainly being abused tendency.

Yuan En Yehui will be impolite to Tang Wulin, although he has Four Rings, but, Tang Wulin in initially, the overall strength was far from Soul Power cultivated for can show. After let alone this time comes back, Soul Power has not promoted many, but bloodline aura actually does not know that was more formidable than many before. Facing such Tang Wulin, Yuan En Yehui will not have the least bit to keep the hand.

The left leg one step steps forward, the body jumped over, a pair of Giant Hammer(s) brandishes, drops from the clouds. Tandem, just like at top speed general.

Giant Hammer(s) has not fallen, two giant hammer shades have dropped from the clouds. That is two groups just likes the essence generally is more like giant artillery shell attack. Presents all over the body is yellow, the diameter with the Giant Hammer(s) hammer head same size.

Is this Air Artillery?

Tang Wulin was startled. Meanwhile he also profoundly understands that yesterday Xie Xie can defeat Yuan En Yehui, others are what kind showing mercy.

Several years do not see, Yuan En Yehui has applied so the degree Air Artillery. Giant Hammer(s) and in hand under One Word Battle Armor amplification. These two groups of Giant Hammer(s) Air Artillery terrifying of explosive force, the general Soul Guide Cannon ball by far cannot compare!

------------------------------------------

Today New Year's Day, was one year passed, I wrote a book also nearly for 13 years. This month will have 13 years of special gift to give to everybody, the new book big carapace master soft hardbound will promote. Year later and everybody meets. We hope that you like. Clip clop, Happy New Year!( To be continued.)

#772: Yuan En strength not strong?

However, Tang Wulin stands in the meaning that same place actually do not fend, the both arms lift, puts up above the own top of the head. The a pair of arm inflates several points suddenly, the Battle Armor surface all presents the dragon scales shape, Golden Dragon Claw along with it reappearing.

Saw that two groups of hammer shades arrived, both hands that Tang Wulin builds also hold, stresses into that pair of hammer shade outrageously.

The people noticed that his a pair of Golden Dragon Claw jumps to project radiant ray of light suddenly, on Tang Wulin has the golden-colored light fog to fill the air obviously. Next flickers, that two groups of hammer shades were scratched and torn unexpectedly stiffly.

„Puff and puff” two, two groups of hammer shade dispersing, the formidable assault strength falls on Tang Wulin, he actually continually shakes has not shaken.

Yuan En Yehui a pair of Giant Hammer(s) follows on somebody's heels, falls above the Tang Wulin top of the head like lightning. Tang Wulin eyes becomes glistens suddenly. Does not dodge as before does not evade, a pair of Golden Dragon Claw gets hold of turned into a fist suddenly, gives a loud shout, double fist bombardment, unexpectedly that by double fist to dual hammers.

Must know, that pair of Giant Hammer(s) weight enough over ten thousand jin (0.5 kg)! In the entire Shrek Seven Monsters team, besides Tang Wulin, has Yuan En Yehui to use. At this time, in addition Vajra Titan formidable strength, terrifying of its mighty energy, if Yellow Rank Mecha does not release Soul Guide Screen, crushing that directly pounded. But Tang Wulin actually relies on the a pair of fist of own to plan that must meet the tough head-on with toughness.

Yuan En Yehui also thinks inconceivable, she does not believe in the same rank, some people can meet own dual hammers by the body hardly, subconscious, she received a strength slightly, this is to the situation of Tang Wulin absolute trust.

„Bang!” The collision of dual hammers double fist, but erupts one to thunder. An intense air wave is centered on them to collide to locate erupts instantaneously.

In this flash, in the feelings of all people, Tang Wulin as if changed into the palatial mountain, he has not used any Soul Skill and Qi and Blood Soul Ring technique, whole body golden light (Jin Guang) puts greatly, that One Word Battle Armor released brilliantly.

Comparing notes of Tang Wulin under foot strikes Soul Guide Screen also bursts out intense halo.

Blocked?

Other people stared in a big way eye, worried for Tang Wulin. Yuan En Yehui strength strong, everybody is clear. Tang Wulin not in the time, she is first Assault System Battle Soul Master of entire team, is the mainstay of team.

However, they saw that does not dare to believe.

Yuan En Yehui dual hammers by raising of Tang Wulin double fist bombardment, then stood up from failure unexpectedly falls on the ground, she by Control retreat one after another, first company retreat several steps, then unexpectedly Control was not occupied by the body of own unexpectedly, sat falls down.

This......

dual hammers „dang” pounds in the ground. The Yuan En Yehui a pair of arm soft sagging, hides eyes under helmet, fills look that has not dared to believe.

Although she received the strength at the final moment slightly, strength that but took back also during own control!

But when she pounded the Tang Wulin double fist, she actually felt own faced at all likely was not a person, but was Ferocious Beast, terrifying instead shook the strength just like the tide. Moreover she also obviously noticed that Tang Wulin has one to receive the movement of fist, this means that he has not used All-Out.

Tang Wulin stands in same place, mark silk has not moved, has not pursued. Other people is a delay of face.

The Xie Xie personal appearance dodges, plunged Yuan En Yehui, the Ye Xinglan tranquil face at this time also has always opened the mouth.

This is......

Tang Wulin also fast arrives in front of Yuan En Yehui, „is all right?”

Yuan En Yehui discarded in the hand at this time dual hammers, smiles bitterly, „is all right, is only the both arms dislocation. If no Battle Armor, perhaps......”

„Dislocation? Boss, you were too ruthless, I spelled with you!” Xie Xie grief and indignation has beaten two on Tang Wulin Battle Armor.

Tang Wulin said apologetically: „Sorry! I do not know like this, I just finally felt your strength not strong time, received the strength fast, may be late.”

Solemnly silent, surroundings suddenly becomes solemnly silent.

strength not strong time......

strength not strong time?

strength not strong time!

heavens! That is Great Titan Ape, that is one pair is ten thousand jin (0.5 kg) Giant Hammer(s).

That is Yuan En Yehui is bringing Air Artillery attack.

At least except for him, other person absolutely nobody hardly will meet such attack. His back coupling is actually, strength not strong......

This......

Yuan En Yehui is also dumbfounded looks at Tang Wulin, „speaks the truth, how many strengths had you just used?”

Tang Wulin thinks that said: „Approximately, 50% to 60%.”

Yuan En Yehui is also speechless, her body reduced the normal shape, Xie Xie helps her, as soon as pushes the both arms, has joined the arm of dislocation.

Her earnest [say / way]: „Captain, I thought that you should examine your strength degree first. I thought that purely from strength, even if that Long Yue, should not compare you. How your does strength become so formidable?”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Should be these three years absorb has moistened the body energy reason. Thinks that you want to know where very much I was missing this time to go, was such......”

At that moment, he conceals nothing whatsoever, in Dragon Valley spoke matter of own.

„True Dragon skeleton? Buries the bone three years. Boss, you won!” Xie Xie does not dare to believe looks at Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „, but asked to feel at ease. You know that my Martial Soul is Blue Silver Grass, in fact, if no Golden Dragon King bloodline, my radically anything is not, even if I again diligently also useless. Therefore, I thanked bloodline to take to my thing very much. To Dragon Valley, it is helps me be able absorb to many Dragon Clan energy. Dragon Clan were too many to my help, can I be cruel enough to visit them to expose the corpse wilderness? I have not thought that will use such long time. Every day is digging a pit, transports dragon bone(s), this may be the heavy work. Especially places the original appearance these heavy dragon bone(s), is some difficulties. dragon bone(s) is heavy, um, compared with heaviness that you imagine, that very possible absorb Dragon Clan own essence energy.”

„Every day some absorb dragon spirit(s), in addition unceasing practical training. My strength possibly promotion naturally. Some of my own also feelings, but has not thought of promotion big of such. However, my Control. At least does not affect forging.”

Xu Xiaoyan said: „It seems like, Soul Power does not have the promotion is not the misdemeanor. Boss, your body intensity was more fearful. Your this strength, has surmounted most Soul Skill simply, is not good Yuan En. Compared with strength, whose your match! Perhaps you can compare with Titled Douluo.”

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „That is impossible, Titled Douluo Soul Power on relaxed crush I. However I also believe that should go to test own strength to have many. After being advantageous better Control. If not dress Battle Armor, should so not be strong. Yuan En, you will use Gigantic Demon Titan next time, then I do not put on Battle Armor, we try again.”

Tang Wulin strength, has shocked all people without doubt. This has to plant to hate the day simply not to have, hates the ringless feeling! Likely is not Humanity can have.

The body of Inner Court measured that room all equipment are most advanced, the Inner Court student must examine the own physical condition every three months here, cultivates including accurate Soul Power is, strength, speed, Spiritual Strength and reaction strength wait / etc.. Very careful. In order to help the students act according to own different conditioning own.

When Tang Wulin and companion arrive body measures the room, there is a person actually to stand here is waiting for them.

---------------------------------------------

Wish everybody Happy New Year, tomorrow's three!( To be continued.)

#773: test

Wu Zhangkong seems before more than three years compares does not have no Transformation, the years unable on this Icily Arrogant Prince Charming face to leave any trace. aura became longer.

Sees him, Tang Wulin hurries to go forward several steps, respectful [say / way]: „Teacher Wu, I came back.”

Wu Zhangkong goes forward suddenly several steps, has given him beyond expectation a hug, „, your situation is at least better than me.”

Tang Wulin gawked, in mind reappeared initially Wu Zhangkong to lead him to go to Heaven Dou City suddenly, enters the situation in that piece of Graveyard seeing, mind slightly shocked, „Teacher Wu......”

Wu Zhangkong loosens him, „comes back well, anything was needless to say. Come, I lead you to carry on the body to measure.”

Xie Xie grinning collects, has referred to the nose of own. Without doubt, is he informs Wu Zhangkong.

After Tang Wulin since returns to Academy, because the Gu Yue matter whole person is a little chaotic, has thought through until today, is better.

However, after sobering, he suddenly discovered that seeks for Gu Yue the several days in him anxiously, has prevented him without any Teacher(s). Zhuo Shi or Feng Wuyu, or Wu Zhangkong, does not have.

„Teacher Wu, sorry, after I come back,......”

Wu Zhangkong shook the head, „perhaps, your also not clear Inner Court situation. Then, I told you simply. After entering Inner Court, you by the Academy default to grow up. You remote are responsible for own all behaviors, but similarly, Academy will again not restrain you like you when Outer Court. Besides the regular inspection, Inner Court in fact to the binding force of students is very small. You handle matter that own wants to handle, nobody will stop. Let alone, you with the Gu Yue sentiment, passed through Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting to be definite, Academy will certainly support you in this aspect, even helped you look for her, had her news to meet first time to inform you. According to the situation at present seeking, Gu Yue was very possible to be hidden by Spirit Transferring Pagoda, otherwise, we were impossible unable to find. But Academy and Spirit Transferring Pagoda subtle relationship, only if Pavilion Master requests forcefully, otherwise, our also very difficult office. But Pavilion Master to some of your as if resentment.”

Yun Ming of course had the resentment to Tang Wulin, best disciple lost the trail because of Tang Wulin, if this did not have the resentment to blame.

Tang Wulin listened to the Wu Zhangkong words, in heart a warmth, Teacher Wu, although has not come to look for own, but, he also has been helping without a doubt own seek for Gu Yue! Otherwise, he is impossible to know is so clear.

Did Gu Yue go to Spirit Transferring Pagoda? Between I and her issue on Spirit Transferring Pagoda? In this world, can make Academy dread that also had Spirit Transferring Pagoda. Yes, certainly is this.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin feels suddenly that own had the goal. The goal that although must resist is that palatial huge, but there is a goal always to compare is not much stronger, at least lets the direction that he had must try hard.

The body measured that the room is big, is much bigger than the imagination , the volume of each machine is also exceptionally huge.

„You must carry on comprehensive test, makes us know that by being advantageous your present genuine body condition, good to arrange following cultivate for you.” Wu Zhangkong said to Tang Wulin.

„Yes!” Tang Wulin complies with one.

„First test one your Soul Power.” Before Wu Zhangkong brings he arrives at an instrument, on the instrument has two spheroidites, Tang Wulin has used similarly, hurries to go forward to grip.

Wu Zhangkong start instrument, quick, digital fast appear(ance).

„Soul Power rank, 47. Soul Ancestor rank. Soul Power degree of compression, six degrees.” The electronic sound gets up.

Hears six degrees these two characters time, the eyebrow of Wu Zhangkong slightly has selected selecting, some surprise looks to Tang Wulin.

„Soul Power degree of compression, what is this?” Asking of Tang Wulin doubts. Before he when carried on similar test, but did not have Soul Power degree of compression data.

Wu Zhangkong said: „After Soul Power has been the certain extent, the quantity is not absolutely important, but must look at the nature. The degree of compression is the nature. Simply speaking, similarly is Nine Rings Titled Douluo , to promote Soul Power to achieve through Heaven and Earth Treasure, with achieves entirely different of 90th Rank by own cultivate little accumulation. The degree of compression at least differs over three degrees. The degree of compression is higher, proves the Soul Power congealing reality. Each once corresponded stage. Your Soul Power degree of compression six degrees, mean, although you are Four Rings cultivate are, but in fact your Soul Power congealing solid degree sufficiently compares favorably with normal cultivate Soul Emperor level Soul Master. The words of two coefficient multiplications, your actual stage can compared with fifty levels of Soul King.”

Tang Wulin or first time hear this concept, cannot bear look to companion, in the eye is revealing inquiry ray of light.

Xie Xie shrugs the arm, „our cultivate Mysterious Heaven Skill, the Soul Power degree of compression compares to have the superiority. I was also six degrees, but I cultivated but for Five Rings. Everybody should be similar.”

„He he, my seven degrees!” Chubby Xu Lizhi collects, saying with a laugh.

Xie Xie ill-humored [say / way]: „You are different from the normal person. You can wholly absorbed cultivate Soul Power, compress them!”

„What is different from the normal person?” Ye Xinglan shot a look at Xie Xie one.

Xie Xie stares, comes on reaction, complexion strange looks to Yuan En Yehui.

Yuan En Yehui likely has not actually seen expression that he seeks help, Xie Xie coughs, „with the normal person different meaning is, the talent different reported. Lizhi, you looked I said is right.”

„He he!”

Wu Zhangkong said: „In this regard, Lizhi truly can say that the talent different reported. The promotion of Soul Power degree of compression even compared with cultivate Soul Power difficulties. Especially after five degrees, wanted to promote the degree of compression difficult ratio once to ascend to heaven. I 77th Rank Soul Power, degree of compression also reluctantly has been seven degrees now. Walks, next test.”

After everybody's explanation, Tang Wulin is understands that Soul Power degree of compression judgment has many significances. Without doubt, Four Rings achieves six degrees him, in the future will promote spatial is very big. This is a very good data.

„Spiritual Strength examines first.”

The giant instrument, Tang Wulin sits below, helmet falls, covers above him.

Wu Zhangkong said: „Inner Court here instrument intensity is quite big, but the security is very high, you can relax the mind, release Spiritual Strength naturally in own forehead surroundings, the instrument will record.”

Closed both eyes, Tang Wulin also very much wants to know that now own Spiritual Strength has been any degree, in Dragon Valley, he was the initial judgment, own Spiritual Strength should break through Spirit Sea Realm, has achieved Spirit Abyss Realm stage. But has not undergone the examination of genuine, he is unable to affirm that the judgment of own is whether correct.

After all, Spiritual Strength request of Spirit Sea Realm, only then 500 points, but Spirit Abyss Realm is actually reaches as high as 5000 points! Once enters Spirit Abyss Realm, that completely is another world. Very formidable Soul Master, Spiritual Strength also in this stage.

According to Tang Wulin knows, initially they when went to Star Luo Empire, Teacher Wu should not achieve this stage.

The machine starts to work, lights shine. Each light is representing 100 Spiritual Strength. speed that the light raises is quick, in an instant surpassed ten lamps to shine.

The people are not strange, after all, they already know that Tang Wulin Spiritual Strength achieved Spirit Sea Realm. After is so long, achieves 1000 Spiritual Strength to be very normal. In fact, they basically have also reached this Spiritual Strength level. Xu Xiaoyan Spiritual Strength is strongest, topped 3000 points, above the Spirit Sea Realm intermediate stage.

As for Gu Yue, she always no longer Academy carries on test, that side Spirit Transferring Pagoda, therefore, nobody knows her accurate Spiritual Strength intensity.

However, meaning that the viewpoint on instrument has not stopped obviously , to continue to skyrocket, quick, is ten lamps shines.

2000!

On the people face started to reveal surprisedly, after all, Tang Wulin was Assault System Battle Soul Master! 2000 Spiritual Strength, this is quite considerable. If when chooses Soul Spirit to restrain some, this stage Spiritual Strength sufficiently supported to Titled Douluo stage.

Then is......, 3000!

When data to 3000. The surprise on people face turned into the shock.

3000, Spirit Sea Realm High Rank.

Xu Xiaoyan loses the sound track: „Boss won't Spiritual Strength surpass me?” Her voice also declines, saw the 34 th lamp shines, but her Spiritual Strength is more than 3300.

This......

Tang Wulin Spiritual Strength surpassed 3000, this in Inner Court disciple was very rare situation. Spiritual Strength is very important regarding Soul Master, but the development level cannot compare with Soul Power obviously, therefore, only if to fuse High Rank Soul Spirit, otherwise few people can specially cultivate Spiritual Strength.

4000!

------------------------------

Happy New Year, first! Today three, the new year of first week, Bai Qiu recommends the vote support!( To be continued.)

#774: terrifying strength

Shock! All people were shocked. 4000 mean Spirit Abyss Realm Top Rank, after achieving this stage, in the future will have opportunity assault Spirit Abyss Realm!

What is Spirit Abyss Realm?

Spirit Abyss Realm, As Deep as a Prison, the blue sky underground spring, on under the poor blue sky the underground spring, the thought to the myriad things thoughts of returning home, Top Rank Spiritual Strength has legendary Soul Spirit foundation, can fuse any stage Soul Spirit, orange Soul Spirit and red Soul Spirit only may fuse are one, in having these two Soul Spirit any situations, fuses other Soul Spirit ability to be equal to Spirit Sea Realm again. If no red and orange Soul Spirit, may hold other stage Soul Spirit upper limits is five, but the rank does not limit. Normal, Spirit Abyss Realm is the Humanity limit.

But, the light is shining as before, moreover is firm, but uniform speed shines, this means that Tang Wulin has not reached the limit.

„Drop!” The instrument has made a sound suddenly. Formerly all lights unexpectedly simultaneously went out.

When all people think the examination of Tang Wulin ended, side, purple light has shone.

„Spirit Abyss Realm!” Wu Zhangkong blurted out, on the face full is shocking. In fact, until now, his Spiritual Strength cannot break through Spirit Abyss Realm!

What is Spirit Abyss Realm? It looks like the speed sonic barrier, above the Spirit Abyss Realm following and Spirit Abyss Realm, completely is the concepts of two stage.

Tang Wulin was repairing to unexpectedly break through Spirit Abyss Realm, this simply was too inconceivable.

yellow lights then shine, had not finished, test is continuing as before.

The people no longer shock, they were somewhat numb. 47th Rank Soul Ancestor, Spiritual Strength cultivates is Spirit Abyss Realm. Even if Spiritual System Soul Master, Spiritual Strength is also not necessarily able to be this degree?

They had guessed, Gu Yue Spiritual Strength should achieves Spirit Abyss Realm. But, has not confirmed. Meanwhile, Gu Yue Martial Soul, but the Element(s) control, requests to be high to Spiritual Strength.

But Tang Wulin is Assault System, is counted Control System at most again. Why his Spiritual Strength can high to so the degree. Everybody cultivate Purple Demon Eyes! Is the disparity so why big?

6000!

7000!

The light is still shining, has not stopped, Tang Wulin Spiritual Strength has clearly been over Xu Xiaoyan one time. Then, some Wu Zhangkong delay, this situation, he has not seen in Academy. In the Inner Court student, Spiritual Strength cultivates for can surpass Tang Wulin absolutely is extremely rare.

According to Wu Zhangkong knows, in entire Academy, spiritual cultivate to strongly, of course is Present Generation Sea God Pavilion Pavilion Master, one generation of Limit Douluo Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming.

Old Yun Spiritual Strength has achieved legend existence Divine Origin Realm, but also is Shrek Academy only Divine Origin Realm.

Besides him, even if Light and Dark Douluo Spiritual Strength cultivates for also in Spirit Domain Realm stage.

Spirit Domain Realm and Spirit Abyss Realm are only the one pace! 20,000 Spiritual Strength, are the Spirit Domain Realm thresholds.

Tang Wulin Spiritual Strength has surpassed 7000 now, he now is only 18 years old, this means in the future him in the Spiritual Strength stage aspect, certainly can assault Spirit Domain Realm. This was unable to describe with talent.

Wu Zhangkong also knows that Spiritual Strength in the Soul Master cultivate earlier period, regarding does not walk to strive to excel spiritual kind of Martial Soul Soul Master to affect is not that obvious, after may arrive at Titled Douluo stage, Spiritual Strength has the decisive function. Wants to be farther, Spiritual Strength that the Titled Douluo level walks strives certainly to excel, is stronger , to promote possibly is bigger.

Limit Douluo must have Divine Origin Realm spiritual to cultivate is, but this point, has caught many Super Rank Douluo most important place.

Reason that Light and Dark Douluo cannot achieve that stage , because, her Spiritual Strength is unable to break through the Divine Origin Realm bottleneck.

Now world, can have Divine Origin Realm spiritual to cultivate is, coming of palm of the hand number.

of course, is high stage, as if in having the God Realm age existence Godking Realm Spiritual Strength, already vanished. It is said that only if genuine Becomes a God, otherwise, Spiritual Strength is impossible to achieve that realm.

speed that the light shines finally started to slow down, this means that the examination reached the final stage, when the second 18 yellow lights shone, finally stopped.

A purple lamp, 28 yellow lights.

„7800 Spiritual Strength.”

Feelings of some people having a parched mouth, 7800! Really fully has 7800!

This is what kind inconceivable.

7800 Spiritual Strength, mean that any they are very clear. Spirit Abyss Realm, As Deep as a Prison Spirit Abyss Realm! Moreover just did not cross the threshold. From the 10,000 points of Spirit Abyss Realm intermediate stage is not that remote.

Wears helmet Tang Wulin unable to hear outside sounds/voices, reminded after the prompt sound, he took off helmet. Looks that is gazing at own companion glassy-eyed, asking of doubts: „You how?”

„7800!” Xie Xie to Tang Wulin compared with the act potential, the left hand is seven, the right hand is eight.

Tang Wulin has gawked, then „”.

„? Ended? Boss, aren't you surprised? Your Spiritual Strength has reached 7800 points, Spirit Abyss Realm!” Xie Xie excited saying.

Tang Wulin said: „Gu Yue already is Spirit Abyss Realm. This has anything.”

The people were all speechless.

Wu Zhangkong vision brilliant visits him, „you already know that own did break through this stage?”

Tang Wulin nodded, „breakthrough time as if has to feel, as if entire world became clear, moreover sensation large scale promotion. Looked like has shoved open a leafed door, entered another world.”

Wu Zhangkong has gawked, after long time, he nodded to Tang Wulin, „Thank You (xiexie).” Without doubt, the sensibility of Tang Wulin has the help to affect for him.

Tang Wulin said: „What is?”

„strength test.” Wu Zhangkong said that although he unemotionally, but the fluctuation of look appears this time mood not to have in the surface to be so tranquil.

The Strength Testing Tool volume has surpassed the imagination of Tang Wulin, seems looks like a hill. Above has over 30 to stroke Placement, each size and shape are not same.

Wu Zhangkong said: „strength test is comprehensive, can test unusual is careful. For example, you can test own palm strength, fist strength, shoulder assault strength, can test Battle Armor strength, weapon attack strength wait / etc.. I suggested that you can carry on fist strike strength test, then after dressing Battle Armor, test one time, was OK again.”

Tang Wulin is he, as soon as strips, regarding Tang Wulin ability, nobody was clearer than him.

„Good.” Tang Wulin complies with one.

People subconscious draws back several steps. Compares in Spiritual Strength, everybody is without doubt more curious regarding Tang Wulin strength. Thinks including Yuan En Yehui formidable strength Tang Wulin light, then, can actually his own strength limit be what kind of degree?

Fist strike target appear(ance). Tang Wulin moved the body of own, strength of to rush within the body Qi and Blood, the whole body has warmed up immediately. His eyes starts to send out light golden-colored halo.

„Starts!”

Drinks with Wu Zhangkong one greatly, the Tang Wulin body half revolution, then like lightning strikes a fist.

Right fist!

„Bang” the entire target vibrated fiercely, then that is similar to hill shivered several to return to extremely unexpectedly fiercely normal.

„Right strikes strength sincerely, 104,000 kilograms.” The electronic sound has given the answer!

Tang Wulin own was shocked, 104,000 kilograms? What concept is this?

One ton is 1000 kilograms, 104,000 kilograms mean that own this fist, has 100 tons strength fully.

The audience are silent, Wu Zhangkong is also.

--------------------------------------

second, asked the recommendation ticket!( To be continued.)

#775: Sky Dragon Roars

Tang Wulin looked at the right hand of own, then has turned around, is embarrasedly typical to companion: „Explosive force and explosive force.”

Wu Zhangkong sobers at this time, standard strength that „Black Rank Mecha All-Out strikes is, 35,000 kilograms. Meets this standard, can be evaluated as Black Rank. Because red level Mecha is extremely special, does not carry on the strength evaluation.”

In other words, strength of Tang Wulin right fist has been over Black Rank Mecha three times.

„Boss, you simply are the human form monster. I understand that now you just showed mercy to Yuan En.”

Yes, besides the human form monster, cannot find out also has anything to describe Tang Wulin. Don't forget, he has not dressed now Battle Armor. Has not used his all amplification strength Soul Skill, for example Golden Dragon Body.

„Was good, did not need to continue test.” Wu Zhangkong beckoned with the hand.

[Say / Way] of Tang Wulin doubts: „Why Teacher Wu?”

On Wu Zhangkong face unusual revealed very user-friendly expression, ill-humored [say / way]: „The limit carrying capacity of this instrument is 200,000 kilograms. I worried that you put on Battle Armor All-Out to attend a meeting to exceed this strength limit. However, I must give you a suggestion, you need to promote own Soul Power as soon as possible, and promoted Battle Armor stage as soon as possible. Otherwise, by your present strength, One Word Battle Armor cannot withstand. If you have come across very intense collision, Battle Armor will possibly damage.”

Can't Battle Armor withstand Tang Wulin strength?

The Yuan En Yehui forced smile said: „This thinks that has exceeded you, who knows that the distance seemed to be farther.”

strength regarding Soul Master, does not fear facing very much one ability. After all, the pure strength limitation was too big.

However, any type ability, after achieving certain Peak. Cannot judge with the common sense.

Wu Zhangkong has given a data, „Strength Type Titled Douluo, when breaks through 90th Rank, 100,000 kilograms fist strike strength are foundation. Generally speaking, Strength Type Three Word Battle Armor Master can also achieve this strength stage. Wulin, are you really Humanity?”

Always ice-cold Teacher Wu suddenly emits such one, Tang Wulin is somewhat awkward, but he cannot bear look to both hands of own. After absorb Golden Dragon King Seal energy, could own be Humanity really?

However, this also similarly verifies Tang Wulin present strength to be fearful, even if is Wu Zhangkong of Shrek Academy classroom, was startled because of his strength.

Wu Zhangkong looks at Tang Wulin, in the look reveals the unusual gentleness, „you have grown up, I have had nothing to teach you. Future you, what are more is taught by Academy Titled Douluo Elite.”

In Tang Wulin heart one anxious, „Teacher Wu.”

Wu Zhangkong beckons with the hand, „you, Gu Yue, Xiaoyan and Xie Xie are I bring from Eastsea City, saw that you can have today's result I to be very gratified. I resigned from the work of teacher to Academy temporarily, shortly after must start to close up cultivate. This time my closes up time at least not to be lower than one year.”

Here, he stopped, the vision following the crowd person has swept, „was you takes to me to hope that making me ignite the upward heart. Wulin, the matter about Gu Yue I thought that you do not need too to be worried, Gu Yue ability enough, I think, among you impediment, came from certain competitive relations between Spirit Transferring Pagoda and Tang Sect mainly. You like her, diligently makes own formidable. In this world, strength forever is all bases, when you have enough strength, all will be impossible become possible. I was very happy that from you had not seen dispirited and gives up. You biggest merit can always be bolder with each setback and grasp the nettle. This is also your successful root. For Gu Yue, for your own and your companion, forwards diligently.”

„Yes, my certain meeting.” Tang Wulin gripped tightened the fist, forceful replied.

Following test is smooth, but all have test about body, Tang Wulin has given the extremely astonishing data. His skin tenacity degree compared favorably with Thousand Years above stage Defense System Soul Beast this too to be astonishing unexpectedly sufficiently. From the overall data, he completely likely is a human form monster, but is not Humanity.

„Was good, test arrived here, this data I will submit directly to Sea God Pavilion. You just returned to Inner Court, by your talent, believes that Sea God Pavilion will appoint instruct Teacher(s) to you directly, in my opinion, your Ancestral Master possibility should be biggest. After all before you, is studying with him. You should go to Spirit Transferring Pagoda now, the Battle Armor name of own.”

One Word Battle Armor name!

This regarding all Soul Master, the matter that most yearns for absolutely, only then after having complete set One Word Battle Armor, has this qualifications.

Although One Word Battle Armor time, name can only be a character, but only then a character, is all Soul Master is anticipating, because this was proving their strength, is the unequalled glory.

Tang Wulin subconscious looks to companion, the people are also visiting him.

Xie Xie said with a smile: „Boss, we have known you will come back, therefore we, although already had complete set One Word Battle Armor, actually continuously not to Two Word Battle Armor diligently. You may probably quickly help us start forging! Well our Battle Armor integral liftings.”

People as if by prior agreement smiled.

Yuan En Yehui said: „Blacksmith that we trust only then you, only then you most understand our Battle Armor metal(s) need.”

Tang Wulin said: „Your did Battle Armor name?”

Yuan En Yehui nodded, „generally speaking, the One Word Battle Armor name is related with own Martial Soul. Or the first two characters are related with Martial Soul.”

Xie Xie smiles, said: „Number of words more often, can be related with Lover, Yuan En, you thought that and other later Battle Armor rank was high, which character in your name is good!”

Yuan En Yehui elegant blushing face, „as you like.”

Xie Xie smiles, „that I may probably think well.”

Tang Wulin somewhat is slightly absent-minded, Battle Armor name. He has remembered the Wu Zhangkong Battle Armor name suddenly, Sky Ice, two words Battle Armor time, his Battle Armor is called Sky Ice, Sky Ice Wu Zhangkong. Sky Frost Sword day, Long Bing ice.

What a pity, own Battle Armor can only name with a character now, then on having nothing selectivity. When can use two characters time......

„I register now.” Tang Wulin said.

Left Academy, everybody went to cultivate respectively, Tang Wulin left Shrek Academy Inner Court, on Car Rental, directly soared Spirit Transferring Pagoda General Headquarters.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda regarding his Soul Master, is considered as absolutely on is the colossus. When the distant place has been able to see that huge tower-shaped construction, in the Tang Wulin heart surges suddenly a heroic feelings.

If one day, must face the entire Spirit Transferring Pagoda organization for Gu Yue, how? So long as own is formidable enough, does not have anything is impossible.

Gu Yue, is waiting for me. I certainly become formidable, not only my own, I will certainly have formidable the enough influence. When one day needs, I will stand side you, even if snatches, I must snatch you.

Enters Spirit Transferring Pagoda, although was not first time comes to here, actually still here shocked broadly.

Staff driving approaches, „please ask that what matter you do have?”

Tang Wulin said: „I must carry on Battle Armor name registration.”

In the staff eyes flashes through surprised, high and low has sized up his several eyes, „do you come from Shrek Academy?”

„Um.” Tang Wulin nodded.

The expression of staff immediately becomes respectful, „asked you to come with me.”

Tang Wulin went to a specially spacious elevator with him, outside the elevator unexpectedly is the glass, can see outside scenery.

Quick, the elevator skyrockets, speed is quick, the ground rapidly changes in the field of vision is small, this feeling looks like flies suddenly.

„Bites!” When the digital of elevator on 101, the elevator stopped.

„Welcome to Spirit Transferring Pagoda 101, Sky Dragon Roars.” Hand signal that the staff make invitation.

Goes out of the elevator, another staff welcomed immediately, is different from the beforehand attire ordinary staff. At present this staff is a young girl, the look are sweet and pretty, a white long skirt, above has the fog and partly visible dragon pattern(s), the makings excellent. The age is also at about 20 years old.

She sees Tang Wulin is also at present bright, good charming youth!

Can be brought to mean that to 101 any she is very clear, very respectful salutes the hand signal that to Tang Wulin and makes to invite, „respect Battle Armor Master, please come with me.”

In the Tang Wulin heart moves slightly, the Battle Armor Master treatment is really different. Really, Teacher(s) said right, in the Soul Master world, the strength is all.

Meanwhile he also starts to size up this behavior 101 Sky Dragon Roars.

----------------------

Three finished, asks recommendation ticket.( To be continued.)

#776: Battle Armor stage, Black Rank

This is a very high hall, the spatial feeling is comfortable. The hall ground is black, in the black ground has to have the mica luster white dragon pattern(s) design.

The hall is divided into regions, the arc counter orderly arrangement, top the hall has 20 meters high from the ground fully, the surroundings wall is the glass composition, can clear seeing outside fog. Really worthily is Sky Dragon Roars.

„, Are you first time arrive at our 101?” The young girls are smiling asking.

Tang Wulin nodded, „, my first time arrived here.”

„Is honored at your service very much, you can call me Shui Yu (Water Fish).” The young girls smile to nod the head.

„Shui Yu (Water Fish), very unusual name.” Tang Wulin somewhat surprisedly visits her.

The young girls unfold the face to smile, „, everybody said. Our staff have title, I live in the coastal city, my Martial Soul is Fish-Type. I usually always like crying, everybody said that my water were too many, therefore called me Shui Yu (Water Fish).”

Tang Wulin smiles, this smiles, immediately Shui Yu (Water Fish) looks slightly one dull, in the heart mused that this youth is much longer leads! He smiles as if to be able the vision of person to hold.

„You, since is first time arrived here, I simply introduced for you. Spirit Transferring Pagoda attaches great importance to all Battle Armor Master, therefore, gave the service of Battle Armor Master to set up this special region. We hope that each Battle Armor Master can be similar to True Dragon sends out own sounds/voices in the Soul Master world generally, therefore here is called, Sky Dragon Roars.”

„Battle Armor Master after our Spirit Transferring Pagoda registers, will obtain a series of courteous reception. First we will provide the distinguished guest service that ordinary Soul Master does not have for you. Every year you can enter Intermediate Spirit Raising Platform free two, Soul Spirit Pagoda one time. Simultaneously can the half price enter Advanced Spirit Raising Platform one time. This is to the foundation service of One Word Battle Armor Master. If you can promote to higher stage, then, will also obtain a higher courteous reception.”

In Tang Wulin heart one startled, he knows that Spirit Raising Platform enters needs many resources. Intermediate can Spirit Raising Platform actually enter free twice? Takes his present cultivation as, Intermediate Spirit Raising Platform should be able the wanderer one. But there , to promote the own Soul Ring age limit is very appropriate.

„What that need do I pay?” Asking that Tang Wulin maintains composure.

Shui Yu (Water Fish) said with a smile: „Anything does not need. So long as you completed the registration to be OK here. Meanwhile, Spirit Transferring Pagoda has special provides to Battle Armor Master some task, if you are interested to receive. The task reward that we give certainly is highest. Soul Master or Battle Armor Master, we are Platform. As the Platform side, we will certainly give you such honored distinguished guest all convenience services. In order to help you be able to arrive at higher stage in the future.”

Tang Wulin and Spirit Transferring Pagoda had to do had not short time, but he was first time knows that the service of Spirit Transferring Pagoda can actually achieve so the degree.

No wonder they can become now the Continent first big organizations, only bosses around the Soul Master method, is other organizations does not have.

Tang Wulin cannot bear ask: „If provides to us facilitates and welfare, has not actually requested, this is not quite as if reasonable.”

Shui Yu (Water Fish) has spat under the tongue, appears very adorable, „actually we have our working methods, after your became a habit welfare of Spirit Transferring Pagoda, naturally hope to enjoy many welfare. For example enters Advanced Spirit Raising Platform, for example obtains High Rank Soul Spirit wait / etc.. But not only these need to pay money, the services of some high stage also need certain task points to take payment way (of life) beyond money. In other words, when you need the service of some higher stage, you need to help Spirit Transferring Pagoda complete some task.”

In the Tang Wulin heart suddenly, not having the space to fall the meat pie the matter.

„Meanwhile, you must maintain must wear the communication watch that our Spirit Transferring Pagoda provides every day, to help us provide some task detailed lists to you, you can not receive, but needs to wear it. Only then wears the watch to achieve certain time every day, can enjoy all welfare benefits.”

Tang Wulin has smiled, Spirit Transferring Pagoda is really fierce! This seems is the minor matter, but, makes Spirit Transferring Pagoda have ability to be able, in same time will want to provide to Soul Master particularly Battle Armor Master who on Soul Master news first time transmits all registrations. This point was too formidable.

In other words, so long as Spirit Transferring Pagoda thinks that it can disseminate the news immediately to massive Soul Master Elite, can provide some task in massive Soul Master Elite. Although the Control strength is not very strong, but at least can boss around Soul Master. But regarding Soul Master, Spirit Transferring Pagoda Soul Spirit is each Soul Master is impossible to give up, therefore, Soul Master will have the dependence to Spirit Transferring Pagoda.

Tang Sect inheritance is no wonder longer than Spirit Transferring Pagoda, will have substituted for the status of first big organization by Spirit Transferring Pagoda. This is the monopoly was fierce.

„I understood, then, can we carry on Battle Armor to register now?” Tang Wulin asked.

„of course, you come with me.” Before Shui Yu (Water Fish) brings Tang Wulin is arriving at a counter, after the counter said with her attire same beautiful woman staff: „Battle Armor Master of this respect must name his Battle Armor.”

The staff after counter stand up saying: „Please first evaluate to the testing room with us.”

Evaluated the Battle Armor Master status the method to be simple, released Battle Armor, and carried on energy to scan, confirmed that Battle Armor amplification effect as well as Battle Armor complete set, was enough.

Testing room behind counter, this is a room of hexagon, in the ground is the complex Soul Guidance Method Array mark. The research in Tang Wulin not anything this aspect, but thinks very magnificently. Above the top of the head is hanging a circular instrument.

„Please release Battle Armor.” Shui Yu (Water Fish) said.

The Tang Wulin thought moves, selects point ray of light to shine in various body places.

„Two Word Battle Armor?” Shui Yu (Water Fish) and another staff simultaneously lose one's voice to say.

golden-colored Battle Armor reappears, but covers whole body, when golden-colored mask falls covers the face of Tang Wulin, aura that on his whole person sends out made two staff both surprised has covered the mouth.

Very strong dignity.

They as the Sky Dragon Roars staff, were many, but Battle Armor also saw dignity such heavy Battle Armor actually first like Tang Wulin that time saw.

In fact, is not in Battle Armor dignity, but when Battle Armor and Tang Wulin own aura fuses in together, after having brought back his bloodline aura, will send out the so intense dignity.

Light beam drops from the clouds, shines on Tang Wulin. Tang Wulin only thought that had any thing as if to pass over gently and swiftly from own.

Quick, electronic sound gets up.

„Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor, Battle Armor stage, Black Rank.”

Had about Battle Armor stage, Tang Wulin had already heard. Like Mecha, on Douluo Continent, has the stage appraisal about Soul Master, is with the Soul Ring same color system that uses, from low to high, white, yellow, purple, black and red! Most adds golden-colored again.

What Battle Armor stage finger is, Battle Armor of same rank, some different stage differentiate. For example, similarly is One Word Battle Armor, Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor and ordinary One Word Battle Armor definitely is not stage, this point is without a doubt.

Regarding Battle Armor Master, One Word Battle Armor can only say crosses the threshold, therefore, what everybody when manufacture One Word Battle Armor is more important accumulates experience, after all, Two Word Battle Armor must again manufacture.

Therefore, the One Word Battle Armor majority are White Rank and Yellow Rank. Can achieve Purple Rank is very rare. But generally speaking, Purple Rank is also the One Word Battle Armor limit. Because of by One Word Battle Armor metal(s) itself, the appraisal also arrived here.

-----------------

Sought the recommendation vote support again! ~( to be continued.)

#777: One Word Battle Armor: Dragon

Only if, like Tang Wulin, makes successful One Word Battle Armor with Spiritual Metal, may achieve higher stage. Also wants Battle Armor amplification degree and manufacture is good enough, metal(s) itself enough.

Without a doubt, Tang Wulin One Word Battle Armor absolutely is very formidable, is over 85% Harmonizing Refinement Spiritual Alloy forging, in addition design of Gu Yue, Ye Xinglan manufacture.

Then appear(ance) rare One Word Battle Armor Black Rank appraisal.

Hears this result, two beautiful woman staff both like yes damn look at Tang Wulin, this even them formerly think that Tang Wulin is Two Word Battle Armor Master is more surprised.

Black Rank stage One Word Battle Armor, that means that this Battle Armor Master background is absolutely deep, Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor, is extremely rare in entire Soul Master! Moreover Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor can promote directly, does not need again manufacture, so long as increases metal(s) to complete higher stage alloy, redesigns again makes. Is easier to Two Word Battle Armor that makes completely, mighty energy is also higher.

Therefore, Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor these characters, almost quite in the future.

Let alone Tang Wulin seems also so young handsome, how can not let in two feminine staff beautiful pupils the extraordinary splendor again and again?

„Was OK?” Tang Wulin continually asked two, two beautiful woman staff reaction comes.

Shui Yu (Water Fish) hurries saying: „Was OK. You carry on to register with us.”

The registration is only filling out a form standard, comes colleges, age and any stage Battle Armor Master, most important is, to the name of Battle Armor.

„Dragon!” Shui Yu (Water Fish) surprised looks at Tang Wulin.

Names Battle Armor by the dragon, means that Martial Soul is related with the dragon, the person of name are so many, but Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor Master are not many. This made ability of Shui Yu (Water Fish) to Tang Wulin have many guesses.

Yes, Tang Wulin to the Battle Armor name of own is the dragon, is willing to be a True Dragon clan buries the bone like him, was the Golden Dragon King bloodline achievement he. Battle Armor One Word he had already decided to use the dragon.

Therefore, as Battle Armor Master, he has been able to use now: Dragon Tang Wulin called own.

Generally of course, in the Battle Armor Master world, must arrive at Two Word Battle Armor the time so will call, one is because, One Word is too frail, is, many Battle Armor Master believe that only then Two Word, is genuine Battle Armor Master. of course, Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor is an exception.

Under the look gaze of Shui Yu (Water Fish) hope, Tang Wulin rides the elevator to return to the ground, he will not have the mood to go with others to exchange communication number anything. But the Spirit Transferring Pagoda staff also really very much have the quality, had not demanded on own initiative that is looks at most his look somewhat longs for that's all.

Left Spirit Transferring Pagoda, Tang Wulin subconscious turning head looked that in the look was bringing several points of confusedness. Gu Yue, you in? You in Spirit Transferring Pagoda? You where?

Is waiting for me, quick, I will have the name of second character. At that time, your name, is my only choice.

Shrek Academy Inner Court has finally made to the arrangement of Tang Wulin, first confirmed his Inner Court disciple status, in the meantime, confirmed he for Shrek Seven Monsters new Captain, has replaced originally temporarily substituting for of Gu Yue. Before this is more than three years, has arranged.

In addition, Tang Wulin was allowed to be occupied by, instruct who assigns in Sea God Island, is his Ancestral Master, Zhuo Shi.

Obviously, Na'er to Sky Raising Douluo keeps the letter not to make him decide to accept Tang Wulin. Even because of the relations of Na'er, he also has the obvious loathing feeling to Tang Wulin.

Sky Raising Douluo is the person of special sentiment, in his opinion, Tang Wulin one attracted that many female students, certainly has handled any appealing matter. Then causes departure of Na'er. Regarding this he is unhappy. May, Tang Wulin be the contribution that Shrek Academy makes is for all this indelible. Therefore, even if he, cannot cancel the Tang Wulin Shrek Seven Monsters title, only if he makes the huge mistake.

Let alone, the body of Tang Wulin measured that in the Sea God Pavilion conference, played the role of considerable degree......

„Young fellow!” A Zhuo Shi palm of the hand arranges on the Tang Wulin shoulder. Straight grinning that even if Tang Wulin such physical quality, was patted by this palm of the hand.

„Makes every effort to succeed to me. Your that physical quality evaluation what's the matter? Right fist strength is over 100,000 kilograms, ha! You do not know at that time met numerous position Ancient expression. Light and Dark Douluo Old Long is surprised. Very good, from now on, you keep on Sea God Island to continue to pursue advanced studies with me. You must do now, my Scarlet Dragon Nine Styles study entire. Is quickly promotes your this low pitiful Soul Power. Soul Power and your companion have missed big stage, how do you make Shrek Seven Monsters Captain?”

„Yes, my certainly assiduous study.”

Zhuo Shi naturally turned into Golden Dragon Nine Styles Scarlet Dragon Nine Styles to Tang Wulin here, so far, what he learns and can achieve mastery through a comprehensive study is Golden Dragon Shocks the Heavens and Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth.

This can be said as strength of utilization Tang Wulin Qi and Blood best way (of life). Regarding Scarlet Dragon Douluo Scarlet Dragon Nine Styles he was hope for a long time. Because cultivates for limits, before cannot continue to study.

Now his Soul Power compared with had initially promoted much, at least achieved Four Rings, what was more important, his strength of present within the body Qi and Blood just like the thick liquid quicksilver, extreme congealing is thick. cultivate has this Golden Dragon Nine Styles naturally to have the effect of wasted effort.

Those who made Zhuo Shi not think, assiduous study these four characters that Tang Wulin said sounded to be very simple, but he used Peak assiduous two words.

Under the instruction of Zhuo Shi, Tang Wulin started the practice quickly, practice that does not stand still.

What does not stand still, simply has not rested.

He only does three matters, practices Golden Dragon Nine Styles, meditation, forging!

Every day did these three matters, meditation has rested, so long as a Soul Power restoration , to continue to practice immediately. forging three double-hour, surplus time are used for meditation every day and practices Golden Dragon Nine Styles.

If one day two days, of course regarding the Inner Court student is very normal, but Tang Wulin such practices, is the entire three months.

The strength in within the body formidable bloodline was transferred finally in Golden Dragon Nine Styles cultivate, is relying on the strength of formidable Qi and Blood, he does not know that what is weary.

In the Zhuo Shi eye, this time Tang Wulin completely likely changed a person, three years ago entirely different. The cultivate Golden Dragon Nine Styles talent has exceeded his imagination good.

Three months of time is very short regarding Soul Master cultivate, but the Tang Wulin three months are used for cultivate time to be actually equal in ordinary Soul Master one year. Even if Shrek Academy most diligent Inner Court disciple, cultivate time also only then his half.

Therefore, the short three months, his whole person looked like was reborn generally.

„Ancestral Master!” Tang Wulin respectful salutes to Zhuo Shi.

Zhuo Shi benign [say / way]: „What has not clearly?”

Tang Wulin shook the head, „does not have, Ancestral Master. I want to suspend Golden Dragon Nine Styles cultivate.”

If traded other disciple saying that perhaps by the Zhuo Shi irritable temperament, already a palm of the hand patted, scolded one not diligently.

But Tang Wulin said that makes him have the feeling of relaxing. This boy knew finally tired, can rest?

„Um, good. You should relax. Moderate relaxation helps following cultivate.”

Tang Wulin actually shook the head, „is not Ancestral Master, I do not rest. I plan the assault 50th Rank bottleneck. I already Soul Power cultivate to the 49th Rank peak.”

From 47th Rank to the 49th Rank peak, he has used for three months!

The stimulation of method of Innate Body Sect cultivate to body, Blue Silver Emperor awakened, making Tang Wulin Soul Power cultivate speed promote finally. Has been the unprecedented degree. In addition his so assiduous effort, Soul Power finally arrives at the threshold that must break through.

Zhuo Shi opened mouth, „I thought that you should slow several days, adjust own to start to break through slightly again.”

Tang Wulin said: „Ancestral Master, my body condition is good. I have the feeling, should. The 50th Rank bottleneck is not anything. Makes me exceed. Even if must rest, broke through 50th Rank to say again.”

Zhuo Shi slightly hesitant, then has selected, „that good, I help your guard.”

„Thank You (xiexie) Ancestral Master.”

Regarding Tang Wulin, Zhuo Shi is very difficult to say the non- character, three months, what has he made? Soul Power cultivate to the 49th Rank peak, in the meantime, Golden Dragon Nine Styles he has practiced four types, not simple grasps, but is achieving mastery through a comprehensive study of genuine.

But Soul Power that in Zhuo Shi Golden Dragon Nine Styles, the latter three types need to transfer is extremely huge, even is not the strength of Qi and Blood can replace.

Therefore, Tang Wulin gave the feeling of Zhuo Shi somewhat to teach not to have recently to be possible unexpectedly to teach.

Has the similar feeling also has Feng Wuyu.

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued.)

#778: In dream old man

Tang Wulin forging arrived at 6th Rank Blacksmith peak stage, only misses one step to be among the 7th Rank Blacksmith ranks. But 7th Rank Blacksmith needs to complete Soul Refinement.

Feng Wuyu own, but he also can only experience lecture of own in Soul Refinement aspect to Tang Wulin, Tang Wulin attempt, but has not succeeded at present. Feng Wuyu gives his suggestion is, making him look for Divine Craftsman Zhen Hua. Can carry on Heavenly Refinement one generation of Divine Craftsman, wants certainly profound many regarding the understanding of Soul Refinement. Even if Feng Wuyu is a little not willing to acknowledge, but for the future of own Darling apprentice, has to make him go.

Three months, the heart of Tang Wulin was tranquil. Or busy cultivate makes him simply not have the thoughts to care about other.

Three months of time, relies on massive rare metal(s) to accumulate and his own 6th Rank Blacksmith peak stage, he has completed four metal(s) Harmonizing Refinement. And also includes his own to all companion, has made the Battle Armor metal(s) transformation.

In other words, now their One Word Battle Armor has completed the promotion on material quality, on difference following Battle Armor again manufacture.

Design, Gu Yue had already completed, like same has promoted 6th Rank Mecha Manufacture Master Ye Xinglan, momentarily can carry on Two Word Battle Armor manufacture.

But when like initially their manufacture One Word Battle Armor, currently the manufacture Two Word Battle Armor difficulty has. Cultivates to be insufficient.

Meanwhile, normal, wants to dress completely Two Word Battle Armor, needs Six Rings to cultivate is.

Zhuo Shi said: „Since breaks through Five Rings, I lead you to go to a place.” At the same time was saying, he holds the Tang Wulin shoulder, soars. They disappear in the midair rapidly.

Tang Wulin only thought that the neglected advice sound howls, seemed only several seconds of time already again conscientious.

This is small valley, obviously is a place on Sea God Island, surroundings is the green and luxuriant vegetation, rich Life aura and Plant fragrant fill the air to flow in the air.

Is Blue Silver Grass Tang Wulin is overjoyed as Martial Soul, here natural aura is so rich, broke through of course to be good regarding him.

He hurries to sit cross-legged sits down same place, starts to enter the meditation condition.

Zhuo Shi stands side him, is feeling his Soul Power fluctuation Transformation.

The wind has blown in the ear, was breathing the fragrance and Plant of soil delicate fragrance, the heart of Tang Wulin quickly peaceful. In the world of nature, so is always easy absorbed.

Soul Power naturally according to the line operation of Mysterious Heaven Skill, in the Tang Wulin spiritual world, as if some green luminous spots quietly shines, that is side Plant.

They felt Tang Wulin Blue Silver Emperor aura, immediately sent out the kind signal, echoed with him mutually.

Light blue halo sends out from Tang Wulin, his black hair also gradually turned into blue, aura melted, unexpectedly to the human he was a feeling of nature member.

If only depends on the feeling not to need eye to look that Zhuo Shi this cultivated to not discover his existence easily.

The Zhuo Shi secret nod, Tang Wulin the condition, means him already the understanding of genuine own Martial Soul mystery.

This is good!

Golden Dragon King bloodline aura restrains completely, some are only Blue Silver Emperor., Expands gradually to a farther place to the Plant sensation. More and more green luminous spots join to the Tang Wulin spiritual world.

His Soul Power in promotion of influencing subtly, is sending out many sounds/voices. More and more Plant send out own aura, even if slightly a wee bit energy, must release, integrates in Tang Wulin aura. But with the Tang Wulin breath turnover, Blue Silver Emperor aura that releases from him will return nurturing to parents to these Plant, they will send out the mood of jumping for joy immediately. Because comes under the influence of Blue Silver Emperor aura, they will be easier born to belong to own Spirit Wisdom.

On the Tang Wulin face reappears a smiling face, in the Plant world, he looked like had found many family members, grew with these family members and companion together. His spiritual world can also a larger scale spread, even covers to entire Sea God Island.

Suddenly, the Tang Wulin body has shaken shaking, he as if feels a difference beyond description to transmit from numerous Plant. Different with Plant of other place, Plant on Sea God Island obviously is much higher on Life stage, takes to him to be also more. May at this moment, in these Plant, as if some special characteristics send out.

That green luminous spot turned into golden-colored in his spiritual world unexpectedly gradually, each other blends with his Blue Silver Emperor aura as before, but what is more important, returned nurturing to parents to his energy promotes suddenly.

Also at this time, Tang Wulin suddenly felt in own spiritual world „bang”, as if the colossus stiffly intrudes, makes his body megascism.

Then he with amazement discovered that were many a huge golden-colored light group in the own spiritual world, big enough to supports fully the own entire spiritual world.

Next flickers, the consciousness of Tang Wulin blurred. Under flickers again, he discovered surprised that own arrived in a golden-colored world.

surroundings is all kinds of Plant, rich varied. But these Plant actually all are light golden-colored, all sends out Life aura that Tang Wulin is hearing something never heard of before.

That thick Life strength made him unable to bear the breath of greed(y), but each breath seemed promoting his Life stage.

„Kid. Your aura is Blue Silver Emperor.” Old sounds/voices suddenly resounds, then Tang Wulin saw an old person slowly from the woods.

He seems is very special, the body the rickets, the whole body has presented for scarlet golden-colored, the long beard has hung the ground, a white hair was so, the eyebrow is also also long the sagging ground. The a pair of eye pupil is actually extremely clear light golden-colored, looks that in the Tang Wulin look has filled surprisedly.

„Hello, where is this?” Tang Wulin surprised asking.

The old men said: „You have not replied me, your Blue Silver Emperor does aura come from where?”

Tang Wulin said: „My Martial Soul is Blue Silver Emperor!”

The old men have smiled, he shakes the head, „is impossible, Humanity is impossible to have Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul. Said to look how it does come?”

Tang Wulin stares, „why is Humanity impossible to have Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul?”

The old men said: „Because, Blue Silver Emperor is the same with me, belongs to Plant world highest stage Life. This is impossible to unify with another Life. Only if, you have Blue Silver Emperor part. Has to belong to Blue Silver Emperor bloodline. Said is straightforward, part of your body belongs to Plant. Understood?”

Tang Wulin dull [say / way]: „I am not clear. Part of body belongs to Plant, what is this?”

The old men said: „Stupid you. That is, gives birth to your Parents to have a side is Plant. Humanity and Plant union, has given birth to you.”

Tang Wulin loses the sound track: „Is this possible? How Humanity and are Plant possible to unify?”

The old men said: „Anything is impossible. Gaining Spirit Wisdom Plant is Soul Beast, they can also pass long years cultivate. After Hundred-thousand Years cultivate, Plant can also change into Humanity, why can't unify with Humanity? Right, on you are his aura. Skip-generation hereditary aura. Yes! Blue Silver Emperor , can only have this [lineage/vein] inheritance on Continent. Your aura is so rich, can awaken Blue Silver Emperor, should be his direct line bloodline. Really inconceivable!”

Tang Wulin is confused, „you meant that my Parents has a side is Plant System Soul Beast, is the Hundred-thousand Years Plant System Soul Beast person? Is impossible, this is how possible! My Aunt Daddy are most common Humanity.”( To be continued.)

#779: Five Rings Soul King!

The old man light [say / way] of: „I am unable to discuss these with you, because I was not clear on you to have anything. But I can actually feel Transformation of your body, can feel your Blue Silver Emperor bloodline. Initially, is he transplants me, has given my this good fortune, making me vertical take root, finally awakened completely, became such Life shape, since you were his descendant. Then, I give you a good fortune.”

„You......” Tang Wulin just said a character, suddenly, surroundings all turned into rich and bright golden-colored, he only thought that has innumerable golden-colored to integrate own within the body instantaneously, Blue Silver Emperor swarm from his body, but this time Blue Silver Emperor actually all turned into Can golden-colored.

Their dig in the ground, turned into golden-colored the surroundings earth. On the Tang Wulin forehead golden light (Jin Guang) dodges, a golden-colored trace of crotch shape reappears.

Next flickers, he immersed in this golden-colored sea.

Whole body is warm, comfortable of not being able to say. Especially the spiritual world, the Tang Wulin surprised discovery, own spiritual sea turned into bright golden-colored completely. Many that too Spiritual Strength itself has not promoted, even also reduced most probably, but his spiritual sea not only liquefies completely, has the type viscous to feel appear(ance). What is more important, he felt that the heart of own became insightful, the unprecedented insight, in cultivate all sorts think before not the clear thing achieved mastery through a comprehensive study instantaneously.

This feeling was very marvelous, looks like own suddenly becomes intelligent. Although Tang Wulin own is very clear this is how inconceivable. May in fact, the feeling be so.

The Soul Power 50th Rank bottleneck does not know when has broken through naturally, Soul Power rises to another stage, is washing out his body, but his Soul Power is unexpectedly same as the strength of Qi and Blood, unexpectedly also turned into golden-colored, but is actually slightly blanch golden-colored, slightly has the difference with pure gold-colored of strength of Qi and Blood.

Was this? Actually have I met what?

Soul Power flows, all rivers run into sea. Tang Wulin exhales foul air slowly, then has opened eyes.

When he opens the flash of both eyes, immediately was surprised, frightens to jump from the ground directly.

Because, he discovered surprised, in his side , is not only promising his guard Scarlet Dragon Douluo Zhuo Shi Ancestral Master, really also has several people. On everyone is sending out unequalled terrifying aura. Stands in him directly, impressively is that Sea God Pavilion Master, Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming Old Yun, is Na'er Teacher(s).

The vision of people all centralized on him, moreover seems also the somewhat bad flavor.

Tang Wulin has a look at Yun Ming, turns head to have a look around Zhuo Shi again, time was shocked.

The Zhuo Shi expression is somewhat strange, at least from his facial expression, Tang Wulin cannot judge him now is any condition.

„Said, what's the matter?” The Yun Ming sinking sound said.

Tang Wulin somewhat dumbfounded [say / way]: „I and I do not know what's the matter. Old Yun, how? I broke through the 50th Rank bottleneck a moment ago! Your this is......”

The corners of the mouth of Yun Ming twitched, „is only? Breaks through the 50th Rank bottleneck?” His sounds/voices raised several points obviously, moreover has the obvious anger flavor.

Tang Wulin has swallowed saliva, he does not know really that actually own has made anything, has initiated this Sky Raising Douluo so intense anger unexpectedly.

Zhuo Shi coughs, said in a low voice: „Wulin, actually had you just made what? You start shortly after meditation, all Plant on entire Sea God Island all turned into golden-colored......”

Tang Wulin surprised looks at Zhuo Shi, „what? Plant on Sea God Island turned into golden-colored, is the same with my dream in?”

Yes, on Sea God Island all Plant all turned into golden-colored. It seems looks like the islands that a gold casts. Inner Court disciple of Sea God lakeside all looked to stay. But this is also since Sea God Island has constructed, more than 10,000 years never have grand picture.

„In dream?” Yun Ming looks at Tang Wulin, in the eye flashes through the color of thinking, „what did you see in the dream?”

Tang Wulin has hesitated slightly, formerly own in simply will say that in the meditation process saw.

Yun Ming as well as surroundings several oldest Titled Douluo complexion become somewhat is strange.

Light and Dark Douluo Long Yeyue sighed one lightly, „was his act . However, is really quite strange, is the outcome that he refers to what? Pavilion Master, do you want to communicate with him?”

Suddenly, Yun Ming complexion changes, vision brilliant looks to Tang Wulin, „you said a moment ago that your Martial Soul is Blue Silver Emperor, did the old man also such ask your?”

„Yes!” Tang Wulin saying without hesitation.

„Blue Silver Emperor and bloodline, are impossible to have Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul inheritance. What he refers to is......” time, the expression of Yun Ming whole person becomes shocks.

By his status, does not know how long did not have appear(ance) such expression. Light and Dark Douluo Long Yeyue as if has also thought of anything, on the face the expression is similarly splendid. In two big Titled Douluo looks is even bringing shock.

[Say / Way] that Tang Wulin is confused: „Pavilion Master, what you said is what meaning?”

Yun Ming takes a deep breath tone, sinking sound track: „In Shrek Academy historical, you are not first have the Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul student, but is actually the second person. But before you, who has Blue Silver Emperor, you should know.”

In the Tang Wulin heart moves, then a [say / way] of face respect: „You said should found Tang Sect that big energy? Also is Shrek Academy first generation of Shrek Seven Monsters that?”

Yun Ming nodded, „is that. According to the meaning of Old Gold, your bloodline, very possible is inheritance from that......”

A shock of Tang Wulin face, „this and are this possible? That was existence before Twenty-thousand Years. If he has inheritance, I should not be second have the Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul person. Moreover, Pavilion Master, my Martial Soul is Blue Silver Grass, was some time ago because of the promotion of own bloodline, Blue Silver Emperor that the stimulation becomes. Should be Martial Soul two times awakens.”

Yun Ming eye including profound meaning visits him, „before Twenty-thousand Years, that ancestor, similarly is Blue Silver Grass Martial Soul, Blue Silver Emperor that afterward was awakening. Because his Mother is a Hundred-thousand Years Blue Silver Emperor cultivate adult. Therefore had this bloodline. Old Gold will not speak incorrectly, nobody understands the Plant System Martial Soul world compared with him, therefore, your bloodline really may be inheritance from that. Although has separated many generations, but you are also surnamed Tang.”

Tang Wulin was somewhat ignorant, „you meant that old person in my dream is genuine existence?”

Yun Ming cold snort, „you may know, in you a moment ago in meditation process, Sea God Island genuine center, because your energy sharp decline surpasses 30%.”

Doubts of Tang Wulin face, his of course does not understand. Does not know that Yun Ming was saying anything.

„Everybody comes with me.” At the same time was saying, Yun Ming wields toward the Tang Wulin big sleeve, Tang Wulin only thought that body of own instantaneously not by Control, becomes dark, at present a fuzziness, but also does not have what ill place.

ray of light dodges, when he at present the scenery becomes clear, he went to another place.

First what heaves in sight is a lofty tree, this great tree was really too big, some crown could not look at the feeling of boundary unexpectedly, under the big tree, the giant tree room, depended on it unexpectedly completely, but existence. Sets up in the room to be hanging together inscribed horizontal tablet, above has three large characters.

Sea God Pavilion!

The Tang Wulin heart shakes, he is first time arrived here, what without a doubt is, here is Shrek Academy, is as for Shrek City most Nucleus location, Sea God Pavilion! Place that Sea God Pavilion Ancient can live.( To be continued.)

#780: green-gold Soul Ring

Tang Wulin only thought that surroundings Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces surges, compared with beforehand own location Sea God Island on does not know that wanted richly many, particularly that rich Life aura, making him unable to bear the takes a deep breath tone, immediately felt Soul Power flowed, comfortable that the whole body could not say. Especially his Martial Soul Blue Silver Emperor, transmits the exhilaration faintly.

Yun Ming said to Tang Wulin: „Here is Sea God Pavilion, Sea God Pavilion depends on this big tree construction, here is also entire Shrek Nucleus. This big tree named Golden Tree, Twenty-thousand Years comes, is its continuously Blessing Shrek, whenever Shrek faced with enormous crisis time, it is always protecting us. Whenever has outstanding talent appear(ance) time, it also always takes to us Wisdom, points out the direction for us. But before you, Old Gold that sees, is this Golden Tree tree spirits, even if we, misses to see, genuine Shrek protector. We do not know that actually Old Gold has made anything to you, but can actually feel the Golden Tree energy sharp decline 30%. But Sea God Island all vegetation change into golden-colored this grade of sign, since existence first time.”

Here, after Yun Ming has stopped one next, said: „I can also tell you a point, initially, the first generation of Shrek Seven Monsters genuine Soul character, Thousand Hands Douluo Tang San after cultivate Becomes a God, before leaving Douluo Continent went to God Realm, has constructed this Sea God Island, was it transfers personally the golden old tree. Now you should understand why we will recognize, your body was flowing his bloodline.”

Tang Wulin dumbfounded after listening to Yun Ming to narrate these, slightly had the doubts including his own heart, own was Martial Soul really related with Tang Sect ancestor Tang San? But, the Tang San ancestor is able to move unhindered the big energy before Twenty-thousand Years! This is how possible.

Zhuo Shi he he smiles, said: „Whether or not bloodline of older generation, but this at least is the good deed. Old Gold act , naturally can Wulin helps very much.”

„Good deed?” Yun Ming shot a look at Zhuo Shi one, „was meddlesome to this boy of course. But you may know how many years golden old tree 30% energy do need to accumulate? Three Thousand Years, entire three Thousand Years. But 30% energy, can resist one time devastating the disaster regarding Shrek Academy. Therefore, to Academy, big of loss, is hard to count simply.”

„......” Tang Wulin looks at expression very serious Yun Ming, a forced smile of face, „, but, I do not know how should also go back this energy!”

Yun Ming said: „You release Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul to make us look.”

„Yes.”

Tang Wulin does not dare to neglect, hurries to stimulate to movement Soul Power, inspires the Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul release of own.

blue-gold thick Vine swarm, Soul Ring also raise from his along with it. Three Purple One are black, Four Soul Rings first ascends.

But, strange picture appear(ance). Behind Tang Wulin, huge blue-gold phantom reappears slowly, was initially appear(ance) of Tang Wulin when Martial Soul Variation Blue Silver Emperor.

Side Blue Silver Emperor, phantom shines together, that is an all over the body Can golden-colored big tree, simply looks like the Golden Tree diminished version.

When these two phantom appear(ance), Tang Wulin only thought that own within the body Soul Power madness surges, the Blue Silver Emperor fierce tremor that all releases, the color also starts appear(ance) strange Transformation. From blue-gold originally, turned into blue and golden-colored alternate glittering.

Two big phantom approach slowly, then mutually fuses unexpectedly, Blue Silver Emperor the branch of sturdy Vine and Golden Tree blends mutually. blue and golden-colored fuse to produce strange green-gold, strong Life aura erupts, even if surroundings is Titled Douluo, they can also feel obviously has rich Life energy to burst out to pour into to their within the body.

Feeling most profound was Light and Dark Douluo, she was in all Titled Douluo oldest one, like such that her own said that she already date and time infinite. But at this moment, she actually obviously felt that own that approached Life origin that withers to pour into vigor unexpectedly likely, the Life fluctuation starts to be strengthened slowly, although are not many are not quick, but that is the promotion of Life origin, but is not the promotion of instantaneous Life strength. This two biggest difference is, former's promotion can permanent retain, but the latter will be only among the moment will diverge.

Two mirage finally closely coincides in together, strange appear(ance), Blue Silver Emperor and Golden Tree vanished, displaces, is together the green-gold form, although that green-gold form is somewhat fuzzy, but roughly in the shape and Tang Wulin are exactly the same, it float in Tang Wulin behind, a take shape diameter ten meters giant corona, the both arms open to the body, have to plant to hug the feeling of entire world.

This is......

„Soul Skill Variation? Martial Soul Variation?” Even if is Sea God Pavilion Master Yun Ming, is unable to judge this outcome to mean anything completely at present.

But at this moment, Tang Wulin behind that green-gold figure swings the body in a flash, changes into green-gold ring of light to drop from the clouds suddenly, the set on Tang Wulin, fell after that black Soul Ring, became Tang Wulin Fifth Soul Ring.

Light and Shadow vanishes, Tang Wulin Blue Silver Emperor is also peaceful. They turned into blue-gold, seemed with formerly did not have what difference. On Tang Wulin, actually solid were many glittering and translucent carving green-gold Soul Ring, Life aura that floods, is similar to the essence is simply ordinary.

Yun Ming as well as audiences Titled Douluo stared in a big way the eye, the Light and Dark Douluo surprised [say / way]: „Ten years of life, just that Life strength poured into, at least has promoted my ten years of life.”

She is so, other Titled Douluo of course are also so.

Ten years of life! This is regardless of cannot trade with much money. Moreover, Light and Dark Douluo already last years of life, so direct judgment own income, but regarding other Titled Douluo, their Life strength is very strong, after obtaining this fresh and rich Life strength poured into, after the overall adjustment, the advantage that gained will be only bigger.

But at this moment, they have no interest to feel own Life energy Transformation, those who most make them shock is front this green-gold Soul Ring.

Soul Ring color normal is the white, yellow, purple, black and red five colors, this was inheritance several Ten-thousand Years came, the Soul Master most basic Soul Ring color, separately was representing for ten years, Hundred Year, Thousand Years, Ten-thousand Years and Hundred-thousand Years. Until before Ten-thousand Years, Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao appears, Creation Soul Spirit system. Surpasses above Hundred-thousand Years cultivates for Soul Spirit, might take shape orange-gold Soul Ring, thus Creation one generation of brand-new Soul Ring appear(ance).

But, their present green-gold, actually absolutely hear something never heard of before, moreover numerous position Titled Douluo can definitely affirm, green-gold in Humanity historical absolutely does not have appear(ance). After being unprecedented, does not have the future. Tang Wulin has done such a matter.

But as brand-new color Soul Ring Creation, on one is Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao, the big energy of sidewise compression first!

„Tries your fifth Soul Skill.” Yun Ming sinking sound track.

Soul Master spies on other people Soul Skill is the matter of unusual taboo, but the situation obviously is here different, presents all people can be said as the Tang Wulin division commander, must think that his Soul Skill naturally cannot have any issue.

Tang Wulin hurries to nod, the thought moves, stimulates to movement Soul Power to pour into to own Fifth Soul Ring.

In an instant, green-gold Soul Ring Great Release of Rays of Light, Tang Wulin only thought that Soul Power of own within the body swarms to enter. His whole person on green-gold ray of light by that Soul Ring was shone the homochromy.

Then......

Did not have then......

Tang Wulin Soul Power weakens rapidly, is almost only time that several times breathe, his Soul Power completely has exhausted, unexpectedly by that green-gold Soul Ring just like heavy drinker absorbing water absorb completely.

The Tang Wulin body in a flash, the strength of his bloodline is luckily formidable most enough, has not thrown down.

„Soul Skill?” Zhuo Shi asked.

A Tang Wulin face is ignorant, „I and I do not know! I thought that Soul Power suction by that Soul Ring, then does not have on any Transformation......”

The expression of people immediately becomes strange.

This situation hears something never heard of before similarly. Soul Master Soul Skill acts according to different rank consumptions is truly different, may not have Soul Master not to have the means to stimulate to movement Soul Skill, and condition of also Soul Power all suction.

Yun Ming lifts the hand according to the Tang Wulin shoulder, is feeling his body Transformation precisely. Right, his Soul Power all suction, the brook drop not saves.

Traded ordinary Soul Master, Soul Power has exhausted will directly perhaps faint, at least is unable to maintain stands, Tang Wulin relied on the formidable physical quality to be not affected.

-------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued.)

#781: The child of nature

Yun Ming frown said: „Should be he cultivate to insufficient, Soul Power is not enough to stimulate to movement Soul Skill, therefore does not have the Soul Skill effect to appear. I help your helping hand to try.”

At the same time was saying, he moves sideways to arrive at behind Tang Wulin, pressed the right hand on his shoulder, shifted the Tang Wulin vest place.

Tang Wulin only thinks one extremely gentle, but exceptionally vigorous Soul Power pours into to own within the body slowly, rapid brace completely own dry meridians.

Mysterious Heaven Skill!

This absolutely is purest Mysterious Heaven Skill. Being startled of Tang Wulin face, he has not thought that Pavilion Master unexpectedly cultivate is also Mysterious Heaven Skill.

„Calm, concentrates spiritual. Stimulates to movement your Soul Ring to try!”

Does Yun Ming cultivate is? Itself cultivate is also Mysterious Heaven Skill, wanted to imitate Tang Wulin Soul Power to be easy. Tang Wulin hurries to transfer Soul Power, pours into to own Fifth Soul Ring.

green-gold ray of light again appear(ance), as before just like swallowing up general, absorb Soul Power of Tang Wulin within the body.

The genuine contact, can feel a Super Rank Elite strength to be fearful. Tang Wulin only thought Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power that own behind transmits rolling flows just like long stream grand river generally, that green ring of light Devour, although quick, but cannot affect the own within the body Soul Power fill degree.

green-gold ring of light became more and more radiant, Tang Wulin only thought that in own spiritual sea, as if had any thing to bloom slowly. When looks with rapt attention, spiritual sea also turned into green-gold unexpectedly.

He begins slightly supinely, center the forehead, green light pattern reappears together quietly. This light pattern seems like the sprout that was just born, green-gold halo blooms from the Tang Wulin forehead place.

That encircles halo to send out a diameter ten meters range, then falls to the ground slowly.

Other Titled Douluo subconsciously have fallen back on the far place, looks at this time this mysterious Transformation.

green-gold halo falls to the ground, changes into green ring of light, in ring of light, shone grotesque and gaudy green-gold, marvelous green-gold rune reappeared slowly, not only they appear(ance) in ground, float in airborne.

Peak rich Life aura is centered on it bursts out outward, but this time, was actually not Humanity can the absorb Life strength, but belonged to the Life strength of Plant world specially.

Both arms of Tang Wulin subconscious opens to the body, before appear(ance) green corona appear(ance) in him behind, that reappears once again with his same green-gold figure.

Is centered on that green-gold figure, huge green-gold Vine swarm, in addition just right 12, each root has the water jar to be thick or thin, drops from the clouds, straight insertion above ground.

Immediately, the earth turned into green-gold, that thick green-gold is also extending the earth outward diffusion. The place visited, all Plant rapidly turned into golden-colored.

What is more fearful, these golden-colored swinging of Plant slight(ly), sent out exceptionally rich energy fluctuation.

Tang Wulin completely immersed in the own spiritual world at this time, he only thought that the own thinking feeling has covered instantaneously entire Sea God Island, then starts to extend the Sea God lake to spread outward, the next quarter has covered entire Shrek City Inner City. All Shrek City Inner City Plant also turned into golden-colored.

They look like the arm of eye and Tang Wulin of Tang Wulin, so long as is his thought everywhere one visit, can actually Control live in these Plant to do any matter.

What is more astonishing, the Tang Wulin surprised discovery, own really has a thought, can transmit the feeling to any place through these Plant, a strength feeling unceasing promotion beyond description. Each Plant as if in investing gives him energy that own has, so long as his body can unable to withstand, energy of his within the body continually will promote.

But all Plant in madness absorb Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces in air, are changing into most pure Life to moisten own, is returning nurturing to parents Tang Wulin.

Is feeling all these silently, suddenly, Tang Wulin at present one black, anything does not know.

When he wakes up once more, outside weather was black. Tang Wulin only thought that the own headache wants to crack, as if has any thing to the head of own rip open.

The severe pain made him unable to bear the groan make noise.

„Awoke?” Gentle sounds/voices resounds in his side.

Tang Wulin subconscious turning head looks that somewhat is at present fuzzy, but actually as before can distinguish, is Sky Raising Douluo Sea God Pavilion Master Yun Ming.

„Pavilion Master.” Tang Wulin struggles to do, actually discovered that a own strength cannot use unexpectedly. It is not the body does not have strength, but was spiritual was too weak, actually some Control did not live in the body of own.

„Is I am inconsiderate. You are lying down.” Yun Ming arrives at side Tang Wulin, pastes a golden-colored bead on his forehead.

Tang Wulin only thought that forehead transmitted cool, the headache feeling weakened immediately.

Yun Ming said: „Your very possible Creation history, to have extraordinary Soul Skill.”

„?” Tang Wulin visits him surprisedly, along with the restoration of spiritual, at present finally became clear.

Yun Ming said: „If I have not guessed that wrong, your fifth Soul Skill, should be Blue Silver Grass and Golden Tree unifies take shape. Actually it is what kind of shape, actually to use any age limit to judge, we cannot reach an agreement now. But I can tell you am, your this Soul Skill is Domain kind of Soul Skill, moreover ultra range Domain kind. In other words, it can cover the Super Rank huge range. At least in me at present in known Soul Skill, your this should be range biggest existence.”

„Through your then Transformation, we can judge some, but also wants you to supplement. We can feel at that time that all was covered by your this Soul Skill with Plant of sensation turned into golden-colored. But various Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces and Element(s) in these golden-colored Plant Devour air naturally. In other words, can play close even surpasses the Element Peeling effect. All Elemental-Type Soul Master, in your Domain, the strength extremely will be limited. of course, the premise is, has enough many Plant existence in this position.”

„Is. At that time your own Soul Power obtained suddenly has come from returning nurturing to parents of Soul Skill, making cultivation of your own to promote rapidly. In the high point, raised the standard of close 80th Rank, in other words, enhanced ten times to continue your own Soul Power.”

Soul Power from 40 as multistage as 80th Rank, has not promoted 70%. A higher rank , to promote Soul Power are more. Ten times of conservative estimates. Tang Wulin compression Soul Power, ten times also more.

„Behind we are unable to feel. Because I discovered at that time, not only this Soul Skill needs extremely huge Soul Power to promote to display, in displaying process, will also have the huge consumption to your Spiritual Strength. At that time that situation, you altogether had insisted for 13 seconds. Over 7000 Spiritual Strength have been able to insist for 13 seconds by you. This was too fearful.”

„Generally speaking, this Soul Skill we currently speaking, but also cannot investigate thoroughly its ability by far completely. What your does own have to feel?”

Tang Wulin thinks that said: „At that time I thought that the own spiritual world all turned into green-gold, is the same with that Soul Ring color. Then I can see very far place through the own spiritual world. All Plant as if turned into my eye, moreover as if can also to me Localization, transmit me. I even can Control they do any matter. energy that you said returned nurturing to parents me also to feel. So long as my body can withstand, as if has had pure Life to pour into, changes into my Soul Power.”

------------------------------------

Sorry, everybody, today in family a little anxious matter, therefore renewed late.( To be continued.)

#782: Penalty?

„Localization? Plant Control. Very good, many two aspects.” Yun Ming [say / way] looking pensive: „In other words, if you can Control this Soul Skill, in fact you be able momentarily to transmit to any Plant there that own this Soul Skill controls, and after sending out the own Soul Power violent increases attack. Right?”

Tang Wulin said: „Probably is this. But my a little Control not. I feel these, then anything does not know.”

Yun Ming nodded, „can feel these not to be very easy. Um, from now on, in your oneself has not promoted before Eight Rings, Spiritual Strength has not broken through before Spirit Domain Realm, do not consider to use this Soul Power matter.”

Tang Wulin one dull, „you meant that does not have Soul Power of Eight Rings rank, isn't able to inspire this Soul Skill?”

Yun Ming said: „Yes. Poured into according to me to the Soul Power total quantity of your within the body at that time, should be this. Luckily, what your cultivate is Mysterious Heaven Skill. If wants to use this Soul Skill forcefully, needs enough many cultivate Mysterious Heaven Skill person to pour into Soul Power for you, has inspiring to be possible. But when most people are unable the Soul Power output of Control own is pure Soul Power, but does not dope own Martial Soul properties. Therefore, do not attempt easily, because in that case, other people's Martial Soul properties will affect you, will cause you to overstate.”

Yun Ming of course is not other person of this categories, takes his cultivation as, wants own Soul Power in unnecessary some strips the nature without question. But changes individual not to be likely good.

Has Tang Wulin swallowed saliva, Spirit Domain Realm Spiritual Strength? Then is very as if remote from own! Eight Rings say nothing. Has not known how long wants to achieve Eight Rings. But this Soul Skill is unable to inspire through the strength of Qi and Blood obviously.

He does not have, because own obtained formidable Soul Skill to be excited, what polarity was, Tang Wulin somewhat was depressed.

Fifth Soul Skill, this is only fifth Soul Skill!

Fifth is Soul Skill good, what meaning has no way with having? Wants fifth Soul Skill when Eight Rings can use, means that now cannot increase many strengths to him. Simply is the weak.

Moreover, in the future can use, wants own Spiritual Strength to achieve Spirit Domain Realm. Spirit Domain Realm so is good to achieve?

Spirit Abyss Realm is most Soul Master Peak, but Spirit Domain Realm and Spirit Abyss Realm, although has missed big stage, but effect but different.

Tang Wulin Spiritual Strength can promote Spirit Abyss Realm, that is because he buries the bone in Dragon Valley, obtained the asylums of numerous Dragon Clan, in unknowingly promotes. But such chance is not that easily can obtain obviously.

In other words, if own Spiritual Strength cannot achieve Spirit Domain Realm, this Soul Skill is not likely able to use.

This kind of weak, is the food tastelessly hates to discard something simply. Can Tang Wulin not be depressed?

However, Yun Ming does not think obviously, he has thought in the time of Tang Wulin stupor, pupil light glittering, looks at Tang Wulin, said: „To display this Soul Skill, the Soul Power promotion can proceed in an orderly way, but I think that you should promote Spiritual Strength emphatically. The method of Spiritual Strength cultivate is limited, you can focus on cultivate Tang Sect Purple Demon Eyes at present. But Purple Demon Eyes is unable to act with undue haste. I will help you seek for cultivate Spiritual Strength Method as far as possible.”

„Yes, Thank You (xiexie) you.”

Yun Ming complexion sank suddenly, „, but, because you caused Golden Tree energy to weaken 30% this matters, you must give a Academy confession. Discussed after the Sea God Pavilion conference that had decided gives your penalty.”

Penalty? Tang Wulin heart one tight.

What can be? But anything, so long as did not affect own cultivate on the line.

Yun Ming sinking sound track: „You later must leave Academy time, goes out to gain experience, not only you, your Shrek Squad must go out to gain experience. You also young, cultivates to have, what now most needs is disciplines. You will be delivered to the Federation army by Academy. In there, you will be under the severest training. When obtained there approval, you can come back.”

The training of army as penalty? The Tang Wulin look is somewhat strange. In army, even if the Mecha army, what was also considered as?

They may be the Shrek Academy outstanding student, One Word Battle Armor Master! Such strength, places outside, that was assuming sole responsibility for an important task existence. What can the army have to train lives rarely their?

In the Tang Wulin heart has doubts.

But he saw the smiling face on Yun Ming face quickly, his smiling face is somewhat strange, but why does not know, Tang Wulin always thought that in this Sea God Pavilion Master smiling face, is having such cruel flavor. Or is to rejoice in other people's misfortunes.

„This army, named Federation's Flag. But in fact, is actually not pure subordinates in Federation. Said accurately that Federation is not clear, what strength this kind of army has. After you went, knows. But wants to enter this army, is not that easy. You rest here, tomorrow spiritual will restore some to go back. Gives you several days preparation time, waits for you fully to restore, immediately set off.”

Sky Raising Douluo has not explained the words, Tang Wulin naturally cannot ask anything. An army can make Sea God Pavilion Master such attach great importance, this is not simple! Definitely is not the ordinary army. Actually can be what?

He does not have what understanding to the army, how even if wants not to be impossible to get the answer again! Tang Wulin does not think simply. Is ready to cope with anything to resist by whatever means available, do they walk has experienced the matter to be few? It is not the army training, anything could not have passed.

Sea God Island as well as Shrek City appear(ance) Plant turns into golden-colored this matter to subside quickly. In most people opinion, this should be the Shrek Academy elders is carrying on any formidable ability cultivate. of course, this also made Shrek Academy cover a mysterious veil.

Five days later. Tang Wulin and his companion were ordered to build up in the Shrek Inner Court square.

The person who the Sea God Pavilion aspect, comes is Old Cai.

Sees Old Cai, the premonition in Tang Wulin heart was poorer, each time Old Cai to the matter that they arranged, is not easy to complete.

„military training? At least one year of military training?” Other people received the news, but is the same with Tang Wulin, they are not clear, actually this military training means anything.

Tang Wulin looks to companion, people are also visiting him. Tang Wulin beforehand these days continuously on Sea God Island, moreover did not have appear(ance). Said accurately that since recent a half year of time, besides has provided forging rare metal(s) to them, Tang Wulin does not have appear(ance).

Original Tang Wulin planned that looks for own that Divine Craftsman Senior Teacher, but this time did not have time. Only after can wait for this behavior military training to finish, said again. Feng Wuyu already taught Soul Refinement some skill, request and cultivate Method to him. What are more is needs to try to find out.

„Captain, what situation?” Le Zhengyu asked to Tang Wulin in a low voice. He stands side Tang Wulin, but Xu Xiaoyan stands in another side of team, can see from this point, among them the relations have not recovered. In the surface seems does not have what different that's all.

Tang Wulin shakes the head, said: „I do not know the military training specific situation, but I can tell you. This was Old Yun says personally to my penalty.”

Such remarks, Le Zhengyu has opened mouth immediately.

Who is Yun Ming? Said that is the Douluo Continent first person is not overrated certainly, this said personally to the penalty of Tang Wulin, that can be simple military training blames.

At this time, Old Cai arrived at their front. Looks at the Tang Wulin seven people, Old Cai coughs.

„You have grown up, takes military service is the responsibility of each Federation citizen. Therefore, you arrived have taken the military service age. This military training, is equal to your military service times. time is uncertain. Longest two years. We hope that after you can complete two years of military service, comes back again.”

We hope that can complete? How this saying sounds that shen hurriedly!

Xie Xie cannot bear ask: „Old Cai, is actually any military service! Can you divulge the details to us?”

Old Cai shot a look at his one eyes, „can military secret, say casually? I can tell you am. At present in Academy, has participated in this military service person, less than 30 people, can complete complete two years of military service. Has four people. In these four people, excluding me.”

Tang Wulin surprised [say / way]: „In 30 people that you said that includes including Sea God Pavilion Ancient?”

Old Cai nodded, „of course, but is not complete. It is not all Ancient has participated in this military service. Good, you think now many also useless. Because will not obtain too many things from here you, lets one's thoughts wander with it, would rather prepares. We hope that you can harvest in this military service. Now what I must say is the matters needing attention.”( To be continued.)

#783: military service? military training?

The people become vigilant! All vision brilliant looks at Old Cai.

Old Cai sinking sound track: „First, this military service is your own goes. Arrives smoothly is you must first do. I to you one point of map, by the map, you need to find there.”

„Next, for in line with exercising goal. You besides Battle Armor, all things and money will be confiscated. of course, is used for the manufacture Battle Armor goods to be an exception.”

„Third, after arriving, you want the passive obedience order. If who without allowing to be separated from the training in the midway, will be regarded as the military deserter, will also be dismissed to process Academy.”

Tang Wulin more listens more to think that , „Old Cai, that did not say, if we want the midway to withdraw, what means needs to use?”

Old Cai said: „Handed in the application, in situation that in proof body truly is unable to continue to insist, can withdraw. Understood?”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Sounds, this is really a difficult situation.”

Old Cai has smiled, smiles seemed compared with that day Mu also cruel, „difficult? You also underestimated this military training. Is ready. Goes to military training the road, was used in the past Ice Spirit Douluo and Dragon-Butterfly Douluo Martial Soul Fusion Technique by us names, is called: Golden Road. You must first do, through this Golden Road, arrives in the military training place. As for other, when you arrived will be clear. Now, Tang Wulin, goes forward to take map.”

The Tang Wulin stride arrives in front of Old Cai, Old Cai gives him a map, „gives you a half hour of time, all takes with the thing that Battle Armor has nothing to do with, the weapon is an exception. After a half hour, inspects, then set off. Money of course cannot bring. All must depend upon your own.”

Tang Wulin and Shrek Seven Monsters people quickly did the preparatory work. Zhuo Shi walks from the dark corner of distant place, arrives at side Old Cai, „was too cruel?”

Old Cai shrugs the arm, „this time is not I, is the order of Pavilion Master. However, to these kids, the cruel point is also the good deed. At least can ask them to leave is farther. Right, initially you had insisted how long is coming?”

Zhuo Shi shrugs the arm, „nine months, you?”

Old Cai snort, had not spoken.

Zhuo Shi smiles, „not my long is right? Nine months are very good result. Besides these anomalies, who can persist in completing all projects!”

Old Cai has smiled, „you said right, but your words, I will pass on that several anomalies in mouth to you.”

„Flatters, now in the evening you want to eat anything, I treat.”

Tang Wulin does not have any many things to need to carry, besides Battle Armor, had forging hammer. These are related with Battle Armor. As for other, stays behind is.

Luckily, he came out companion manufacture Battle Armor metal(s) all forging before, rare metal(s) he also brought, is used to practice own forging.

military training sounds to be so simple, but in fact, in the Tang Wulin heart was not worried specially. After all, he gives the training program of own formulation hard already. He believes that so long as some people can insist military training that own certainly can also be good.

Leaves the inspection before Academy, is more careful than the imagination. However the Tang Wulin seven people have not stolen the plan that acts slippery deceitfully obviously, quick have completed all inspections, and leaves Academy.

According to the request, they must rush to the military training place in 15 days, will otherwise not have the qualifications to carry on military training. But does not have the qualifications military training consequence is, will be dismissed by Academy, will be taken back including the Shrek Seven Monsters title.

Goes out of Academy, Tang Wulin somewhat just likes separates the world feeling, because, he a half year of time had not left here.

The extension of effort a body of own, suddenly, an exhausted feeling arose spontaneously.

Regardless of his body is strong , to continue over six months assiduous cultivate and study, every day forces the Peak effort own, in fact massively is consuming his energy. Spiritual Strength and physical strength cannot be equal to a complete mental effort of person completely, exhausted of that inner world.

Left Academy, is tying tight the string as if relaxed, Tang Wulin naturally has had the exhausted feeling.

„Captain, we now what to do? Walk?” Le Zhengyu asked. They have changed the own clothes, Le Zhengyu is a white sportswear, is joined to his golden-haired, very somewhat natural flavor.

On his face has been short of the beforehand smile, in the half year, his whole person appeared calm was more reserved. Like Tang Wulin closing up, his most time similarly are also closing up.

Tang Wulin said: „Walk is not definitely realistic, shows according to the map on, even if our All-Out to go , is also impossible to rush to the place in 15 days. Walks, I have the means to get so far as money, we make a money first, then immediately set off.”

Makes money regarding Tang Wulin is a very simple matter, the technique industry studies, forging forever not two choices. Let alone, he must have a look at own that Teacher(s).

When Tang Wulin arrives at Shrek City Blacksmith Association, warm feelings arise spontaneously. After coming back, he is closing up goes to see Mu Chen Teacher(s), then started a half year of closing up. Mu Chen has given him the own Soul Refinement experience note, Tang Wulin was just about also to accumulate one collection of issues to inquire.

Different Saint Craftsman, on Soul Refinement this road the path completely is also different, Feng Wuyu has the Feng Wuyu road, road on the other hand legitimate of Mu Chen. Qi is coinciding, the mutual verification, making understanding of Tang Wulin to Soul Refinement more several points.

Regarding the arrival of Tang Wulin, Mu Chen is very pleasantly surprised. Looks to stand in the front, is youth that Yushu faces the wind, on the Mu Chen face has shown the smiling face.

„Probably grew a point, moreover seemed is also stronger. How seems somewhat weary.” Mu Chen smiles was saying.

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „I do not know that left Academy, exhausted feeling on appear(ance). Teacher(s), Academy has arranged vice minister time trial to us, this time could go to be very long, before departure, I comes to see you. Is......”

Here, his flexure scratching the head, „Academy were many to our motion limits, rich can only keep Academy. Therefore I want forging task that comes our Association to have a look at to have anything to receive immediately, gains a travel expense.”

Mu Chen laughs, „this is not any matter. However, since is the request of Shrek Academy, Teacher(s) cannot give you directly money, this, your own chooses metal(s), then carries on forging with the maximum degree that you can be now, makes me have a look, you in the half year the forging level has achieved any stage. The metal(s) that then your forging leaves, Association purchases according to the market price. The travel expense definitely came out.”

„Good.” Tang Wulin hurries to comply with one.

In this time, familiar sounds/voices is transmitting from out of the door, „Daddy, I come back!”

Has not waited for Tang Wulin to turn round, fragrant wind has crashed in the room, that has fragrance body passing through the gate to see that in the Mu Chen office is standing these many people, has gawked immediately somewhat, but is quick, she looks to arrive in of front line.

Her footsteps stopped immediately, the expression on face also along with some it freeze.

Tang Wulin had turned round at this time, looks at front young girl, shows a faint smile, „Senior Sister.”

Yes, comes person Mu Xi. Tang Wulin previous time sees her time, before going to Star Luo Empire, after coming back, he participated in Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, then searches high and low Gu Yue, again, closed up.

--------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. The writing nearly 13 years, never like so was immediately difficult recently. Not because of writing's matter, but is some family work, did not tell everybody defeated energy. Hopes that the Tang Sect brothers and sisters can share hardships with me. I diligently maintain the writing , to continue maintains we unceasingly. Thank You (xiexie) everybody.( To be continued.)

#784: Immovable as a Mountain

Had not seen Mu Xi. In the impression of Tang Wulin, Mu Xi in Shrek Academy Outer Court, could not be admitted to Inner Court. She now over 20 years old, wanted to enter the Inner Court possibility to be getting more and more low. Only if she can become Two Word Battle Armor Master before 30 years old.

Regarding Mu Xi, Tang Wulin discovered that own fully did not understand unexpectedly, does not know Senior Sister present cultivation completely has been any degree for and other aspects. In heart an apology.

„You also know that has my this Senior Sister?” Saying that Mu Xi both hands fork waist, lets somebody cool off or calm down.

Four years have not seen Mu Xi fully, past she is a big beautiful woman, this year Mu Xi 22 years old nearly 23 years old, is a girl happiest time. Her stature grown unusual is perfect, passing through the gate, the Shrek Seven Monsters male noticed that she could not bear good the eye salute.

flaming-red long skirt, big wave long hair, beautiful strength, beautiful blazing. Like her character.

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Sorry, Senior Sister I made a mistake.”

Sees Tang Wulin suddenly, in the Mu Xi heart complex mood are almost come up on to rush instantaneously, she good to throw, maliciously cursed angrily this fellow. More than three years of disappears without a word, after coming back, in Inner Court, she cannot enter Inner Court, cannot see him. Sees only his one time, is on Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting.

But, she cannot attend that congress on the level of the lake, can only in the shore, look that he makes love to Gu Yue, looks they are good to gather in the blessing that to leave because of Hundred Year. At that moment, the mood in Mu Xi heart is extremely complex.

Time saw from initially first disdaining, to afterward approval, arrived at gradual looking up to again, this in own front fellow, became the person of same age genuine outstanding person with short ten years of time, even was in Shrek Academy the dazzling star. But, between he and her the distance also seems becoming more and more.

Some aspects, the idea of Mu Xi is the same with Wu Siduo, they are willing to pursue perfectly, had well, is not willing to look at other again.

By the Mu Xi appearance, is the pursuer are naturally innumerable in Shrek Academy, even there is Inner Court disciple in pursuing her, but she actually does not look encouragingly, because has had that together the form in her heart.

She has pursued him on forging, has cherished a hope. But, she actually discovered that own and he more has walked is farther.

Mu Xi is not the girl who can only have a dream, when she saw that Tang Wulin after on Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting has chosen others, she in the heart told own, this man eventually is own not any relations, when she has put down gradually, that fellow actually on such appear(ance) in front of own.

An apology, admits mistakes, is makes Mu Xi a lot of grievance somewhat unable to vent unexpectedly unexpectedly.

„cough cough!” Mu Chen coughs, melted the awkward atmosphere slightly. As Father, can he unable to see the idea in daughter heart?

But this time Tang Wulin, has been similar to True Dragon peeps roams through to nine days generally, sentimental matter is not the manpower can about. Only can say that is predestined friends unqualified.

Mu Chen had selected Mu Xi in secret, her character was too strong, but Tang Wulin is not that type is willing by the Control person. They try to outdo others, two people of trying to outdo others in the same place, could become the friends, but was too difficult becomes the companion.

„Wulin makes me examine his forging cultivate level. Happen to you came back, has a look together.” Mu Chen arrives at side the daughter, has patted her shoulder.

The complex mood in Mu Xi eye restrains gradually, after all, she is the 23-year-old girl, regardless of character is how stubborn, is working as these many people, is in front of Father, she also has to restrain the own mood.

„Good.”

Tang Wulin is sweated by forehead that a little Mu Xi that somewhat blazing vision looks, formerly exhausted feeling in instantaneously was burnt does not have.

Mu Chen said: „Goes to Forging Room!”

The people arrived at Forging Room with Mu Chen, in his own personal Forging Room has almost on now Douluo Continent all type rare metal(s).

Mu Chen to Tang Wulin compared with the hand signal, after Tang Wulin slightly makes the ponder, as before moved toward he most familiar that type.

Heavy Silver of standard size took by him. Then has placed on the forging stage.

The Mu Xi eyebrow has selected selecting, [say / way] that somewhat satirized: „Is only Heavy Silver?”

Tang Wulin smiles, „I most am familiar with this.”

Yes, his most familiar Heavy Silver, not only rare metal(s) that because earliest has to do is it, is because he too understood it.

Tang Wulin forging hammer throughout is Heavy Silver Hammer, but each time he when forging has broken through, choice is Heavy Silver. Has him to the Heavy Silver most familiar reason, his reposing at heart. The breakthrough is Heavy Silver brings each time, will let the feeling of his subconscious, Heavy Silver takes to his help to be biggest, most has the good luck.

Therefore, he has chosen Heavy Silver once again.

Mu Xi has not said anything again, but careful looks. These years she continuously very diligently, if no Tang Wulin, she absolutely is the talent that the Blacksmith Association non- world leaves.

Was 23-year-old she, can definitely inherit own legacy by the Mu Chen acknowledgment. 6th Rank! Present Mu Xi is also 6th Rank Blacksmith. Although she entered 6th Rank compared with Tang Wulin late, but also not late were too many. If there is not placed on more energy forging, she is also insufficient a point to enter the Inner Court opportunity not to have.

But the promotion of forging also has very great benefit for her, she has prepared own all manufacture Two Word Battle Armor metal(s), Spirit Refinement metal(s)! Moreover is Spirit Refinement alloy.

Is prepares to be well-prepared, must become Two Word Battle Armor Master before 30 years old, becomes in Shrek Academy Inner Court.

Cultivation of Mu Xi to also break through Five Rings, was Soul King stage. Various aspects, she is that outstanding.

Her effort to the own pays is very confident, therefore she wants to have a look, own trained hard was so long, separated for four years with him, actually own to overtake him in the forging aspect.

Tang Wulin puts in Heavy Silver the forging stage the calcine, simultaneously took out own that pair of Spirit Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer, on the face the look sank to congeal, eyes closed, calmness silently.

Looks at his earnest appearance, Mu Xi, although in the heart has felt suffocated, but actually also has to acknowledge that Tang Wulin truly is she biggest the competitor in the forging world, even is the goal of chase.

He became 6th Rank Blacksmith has over four years, but can also maintain in forging so calm calm. He is only 19 years old, mentality has planting to make her see own Father stably in the feeling of forging time.

Immovable as a Mountain! Palatially like mountain!

Mu Chen also looks in side that other Shrek Seven Monsters six people stand in slightly far point place, in order to avoid affects Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin forging hammer places on the forging stage, both hands hang by the body, the slender arm, the slender ten fingers, give people all a strange feeling. Is full of the sense of reality, is flooding one makings beyond description.

This moment he, on aura as if turned into this Forging Room part, but is not Humanity.

Heavy Silver forging time was too easy to judge, suddenly, Tang Wulin patted the button, was raised by calcine red Heavy Silver.

Tang Wulin was almost under flickers opens eyes, both hands has simultaneously gripped own that pair of forging hammer. Then a pair of forging hammer also finds out.

Yes, is finds out, but is not wields to pound to fall.

Mu Xi surprised seeing, Tang Wulin stretched out straight in front of oneself above a pair of forging hammer that Heavy Silver, then started striking.

He has not brandished forging hammer All-Out to pound to fall like normal forging, but is dual hammers float above Heavy Silver, but is relying on the movement of wrist, Control a pair of forging hammer unceasing rap gently above that Heavy Silver.

This forging way (of life) Mu Xi or first time see, even if own that 8th Rank Saint Craftsman Father cannot like this forging!

But Tang Wulin actually such does. His a pair of forging hammer dexterous and stable is rapping gently. But like this raps, can forging succeed?

This thought just reappeared in the Mu Xi mind, next quarter, her pupil light on freeze.

Because of her clear seeing, that Heavy Silver in Tang Wulin this seems under the dexterous incomparable rap, the volume swiftly reduces. What stranger is, it becomes more and more bright. Indistinct, Mu Xi even saw that on this Heavy Silver has some close and orderly trace appear(ance).

This......

Dexterous can the so rap actually refining?

Tang Wulin wrist vibration speed is quick, raps speed to bring one after another hits the Japanese banana crowded sound just like the rain. What is more unusual, that stormy knocking has the rhythm, seems like rapping percussion interesting to listen.( To be continued.)

#785: Peak Thousand Refinements

Because Heavy Silver his a pair of forging hammer speed is too quick, had been hammered the shade to cover unexpectedly. This time Tang Wulin to the feeling of person likely is not Blacksmith, but is more like a carver, seems cautiously is carving that metal(s).

Because is familiar, therefore is easier to control. Tang Wulin forging arrived at receiving and dispatching by the degree of heart. Wish lets together the display of rare metal(s) genuine its oneself completely properties, even said that makes its own be promoted, entrusted with Life. Then, must first maintain its properties originally, cannot have any injury.

In the past all forging way (of life) were the direct dispelling impurity and refining. But in fact, looks like in Tang Wulin, metal(s) itself has Life, even if Life has not entrusted with before Spirit Refinement also same has. Each rare metal(s) own is the body, in the refining mixed qualitative time, the thump will strike to damage its internal structure vigorously inevitably. Although behind will let its to become strong through various way (of life), may in fact, when most origin, actually cannot his refining to Peak.

Therefore, wants together good of rare metal(s) forging, from the beginning must carve, must going refining cautiously.

For example, if in meridians of human body has the impurity, the extrusion of effort can push the impurity. Because overstrain likely lets meridians appear(ance) certain damage. But if with gentler way (of life), opening bit by bit, then washes out with pure blood cleanly, the impurity has removed, meridians was unobstructed, itself also perfect.

Before Tang Wulin present forging , the different places also lie in this. He very carefully Control in the forging process own Spirit Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer, careful is combing Heavy Silver, when each rap, quietly pours into own bloodline aura to go. Let this Heavy Silver be able a better feeling his own aura.

By his present strength, if brandished a hammer to pound, Heavy Silver turned into the metal(s) cake directly, his Spirit Refinement can Heavy Silver Hammer unable to withstand is very difficult to say.

This is also he when the important reason that forging must be careful.

This time he completely immersed, Hundred Refinements purification that should rapidly complete, he has used enough three times of time, completes to comb. If can survey at this time carefully will discover that similarly is Hundred Refinements purification, Tang Wulin with Heavy Silver that this method purification comes out, in fact the volume be bigger than the normal condition. In other words, normal purification to exit some good thing also refining, but he does not have.

Mu Chen vision brilliant looks at Tang Wulin each movement, in the eye is revealing the gratified color.

Tang Wulin present hammer method is not he teaches, similarly is not Feng Wuyu teaches. This is his own hammer method, own Creation comes out.

Although Tang Sect Disorder Splitting Wind Hammer Method is good, but too violence, is too strong to metal(s) destructiveness. Although can forging have very good effect, but wants difficultly further actually.

Without a doubt, Tang Wulin found was own the road of forging. Moreover is going forward with steady steps.

Has used time of quarter, suddenly, radiant silver light selects for promotion together.

When that silver light appear(ance), in Forging Room obviously has even resounded dragon roar. That said that silver light soars to the heavens just like the flood dragon generally.

Thousand Refinements Gains Spirit!

But, normal Thousand Refinements Gains Spirit can raise five feet quite to be shocking, but Tang Wulin this silver light actually raised had a zhang (3.33 m) surplus fully, skyrocketed . Moreover the swing brandished, looked like Silver Dragon is waving against the wind.

Mu Xi stared in a big way the eye, she was also 6th Rank Blacksmith, but she actually can definitely affirm that own cannot achieve Tang Wulin absolutely now this point.

„Peak!” Mu Chen muttered said two characters.

Yes, Tang Wulin has achieved Peak Heavy Silver Thousand Refinements, the matter that metal(s) Thousand Refinements can achieve together has achieved most peak.

Let alone was Mu Xi, even if were Mu Chen own, has not grasped can achieve this point. Perhaps has Divine Craftsman Zhen Hua.

forging needs strength, but strength uses are more, does not control on exceed easily. Mu Chen impossible to rely on strength of wrist to carry on forging like Tang Wulin merely. Because his strength is insufficient, if uses Soul Power directly, involves the Control issue similarly, was inferior that pure strength is more controllable.

But Tang Wulin yes, his strength already had exceeded obviously 100,000 jin (0.5 kg), even if only strength of wrist is also extremely fearful. From forging now, his Soul Power has not used, but has used the strength of bloodline slightly, what are more is relying on pure strength. Can so carve together Heavy Silver forging to this degree.

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, a pair of Heavy Silver Hammer with that silver light raises, but launches by the body. His eyes also becomes bright.

In both hands Heavy Silver Hammer in the airborne arc, does not wait for that silver light to fall, his Heavy Silver Hammer once more has wielded.

Two ray of light also fall, pounds on Thousand Refinements Heavy Silver, sent out compared with formerly the bright many sounds.

At this time looks at that Heavy Silver again, above has close cloud pattern. cloud pattern is in itself sending out brilliantly, the halo circulation, looked like changed metal(s).

Tang Wulin no longer with strength of wrist, after the Thousand Refinements Gains Spirit Peak refining process, this Heavy Silver internal structure had been combed completely, does not know that was harder than many times before. Also can withstand Tang Wulin strength finally.

eyes is bright, the spiritual world launches completely, Tang Wulin Spiritual Strength starts to swarm, with own a pair of forging hammer gentle injection to this Heavy Silver.

Spiritual Strength and Qi and Blood fuse. The Mu Chen ear moves, he hears obviously, this Heavy Silver every time by the Tang Wulin rap time, Heavy Silver itself will send out the slight(ly) dragon roar sound. Its above cloud pattern also meets appear(ance) adjustment slightly.

Soul Power pours into, Spiritual Strength pours into! Tang Wulin started the Spirit Refinement most important process, the Life inspiration.

Spirit Refinement and Thousand Refinements biggest difference is the intelligence, together the rare metal(s) intelligence is without a doubt fuller, its exceed is valuable.

Most five 6th Rank Blacksmith, do not have the means to guarantee that own each forging certainly can complete Spirit Refinement.

But Tang Wulin, even Mu Xi, because they are the 6th Rank Blacksmith outstanding people, not only their goals 6th Rank.

But Mu Xi actually felt that Tang Wulin Spirit Refinement and own are entirely different, his summon way (of life) consumes to be much bigger than own. Soul Power pours into normally, Spiritual Strength that but he releases were too probably many, moreover indistinct also has other things. That dragon roar sound is the certificate. Normally, at least in this stage should not appear(ance) this special sound.

This can only mean that a matter, that was Tang Wulin own feeds in raw material in the forging process.

Tang Wulin very steady is wielding own Spirit Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer, like formerly was not dexterous, but did not seem that heavy like before. Is a normal hammer hammer wields falls. Falls above that Heavy Silver.

silver cloud pattern on Heavy Silver distorts gradually, from turns into the distortion smoothly, is indistinct, with injection of Tang Wulin Soul Power, it starts to have rhythm halo to fluctuate.

Did this start the Gains Spirit nature? Too quick!

With formerly Hundred Refinements and Thousand Refinements slow compared with, Tang Wulin the astonishment of Spirit Refinement speed block, at least lets Mu Xi surprised grinning with ear to ear.

If she, Spirit Refinement this process, even if uses most common rare metal(s), at least must nearly one hour be able to complete, searches to observe together the rare metal(s) Life strength, and is not easy its stimulation. But this time Tang Wulin has not completed Spirit Refinement, but metal(s), since already appear(ance) intelligence Transformation, naturally means that Spirit Refinement will soon complete.( To be continued.)

#786: Soul Refinement echo

This was also too quick, altogether also five minutes!

Let alone was Mu Xi, knew according to Mu Xi, even if were these stayed dozens years of old Blacksmith in 6th Rank Blacksmith realm, impossible to complete Spirit Refinement in short five minutes of time!

Spirit Refinement arrives at Soul Refinement, is together the insurmountable gap, the innumerable Blacksmith cards cannot pass in this pass. Otherwise Saint Craftsman will not be scarce.

But the Spirit Refinement five minutes, Mu Chen cannot achieve. He is impossible to be so quick! Tang Wulin this......

Is this function that Peak Thousand Refinements brings?

Mu Xi had completely forgotten at this time the complex mood of own to Tang Wulin, completely immerses in Tang Wulin forging.

„Buzz” at this moment, that Heavy Silver sends out slight(ly) buzz the cry, that Heavy Silver itself vibrated gently, above cloud pattern looks like lives general circulation Transformation, has dragon-shaped indistinctly. The slight(ly) dragon roar sound instantaneously becomes obvious.

Mood of joy excitedly!

Has succeeded, Spirit Refinement completes! Seven minutes!

Completes to Spirit Refinement from Thousand Refinements Gains Spirit, Tang Wulin has only used for seven minutes.

This time, Mu Chen stared in a big way the eye, subconscious gripping tightened the fist. From Tang Wulin forging, he obtained some inspirations, but regarding Saint Craftsman, this inspiration was really too important.

Mu Chen thinks own this whole life wanted assault Divine Craftsman is the impossible matter, but in just this flickered, he suddenly thought that as if had such one possibly. Thus it can be seen, Tang Wulin this time forging is huge to his touching.

Tang Wulin this time has stopped, on his face is having the light smile, as if in listening to joy of that Heavy Silver, after small Life is born to own Father is showing off general.

Next quarter, Tang Wulin aura big change. The strong Qi and Blood fluctuation, diamond-shaped scales reappeared excitedly, making his whole person seem had a feeling of formidable.

Skin that can see only then neck and both arms, scales densely covered on the neck of Tang Wulin, to lower jaw place. Both hands are covered by golden-colored scales completely, but does not have appear(ance) Golden Dragon Claw. But the strong Qi and Blood fluctuation made Mu Chen and Mu Xi was startled.

The formidable pressure on that bloodline the Martial Soul exciting release of Mu Xi, Soul Ring raised from the under foot directly.

Although Mu Chen is insufficient so, but also had a scare.

This aura......

Tang Wulin Qi and Blood fluctuated they long before to feel, but never has actually felt so intensely.

His aura such? Moreover, they also impressively see, Tang Wulin under foot, golden-colored ring of light along with it raising, entire four.

Previous Mu Xi sees Tang Wulin this Qi and Blood Soul Ring time, he also has two.

The both arms launch, Tang Wulin slight(ly) shakes, the whole body Qi and Blood fluctuation immediately became richer, golden-colored light fog dense in his body surroundings, his eyes also turned into golden-colored.

But that Heavy Silver as if also felt the aura fluctuation of Tang Wulin, joy originally as if turned curiously.

At this moment, Tang Wulin Spirit Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer moved, these time starts, his Heavy Silver Hammer had been exaggerated golden-colored by the strength of Qi and Blood. Pounds to fall outrageously, was not formerly dexterous, but became incomparably heavy.

Each hammer falls, entire Blacksmith even along with it slight(ly) trembles, low and deep thundering are ordinary just like the Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery list explosion.

That was withstood a hammer to send out sobs the groan by forging Spirit Refinement Heavy Silver every time, as if has a pain is joyful the feeling.

But Mu Xi saw that a Tang Wulin hammer falls, that Heavy Silver was exaggerated golden-colored unexpectedly instantaneously, although under will flicker will remove, but without a doubt, it will be is receiving being contaminated of Tang Wulin Spirit Refinement Heavy Silver Hammer.

Spirit Refinement and Soul Refinement biggest difference is, Spirit Refinement entrusts with Life, but Soul Refinement entrusts with metal(s) own inheritance. It looks like Soul Inheritance is ordinary.

Therefore, when One Word Battle Armor Master and Two Word Battle Armor Master, Vice Profession is Mecha Manufacture Master will be quite good. Because most can manufacture leave to conform to own Mecha. After all nobody understands own compared with own.

But to Three Word Battle Armor Master above, metal(s) that Blacksmith forging left became most important. That because of Soul Refinement.

If own is Saint Craftsman Rank Blacksmith, metal(s) that itself then, forging leaves had own Soul Power, has own Martial Soul even is Life properties. The nature and own conjunction are highest. This point even compared with Nucleus method also important.

What a pity, Blacksmith is in all Vice Profession most difficult cultivate one, Saint Craftsman that on entire Douluo Continent has is also several. Divine Craftsman has Zhen Hua one person.

It can be imagined, this is hard cultivate.

At this time, Tang Wulin started without a doubt from Spirit Refinement to the process that Soul Refinement sets out, he to that Heavy Silver that own bloodline aura All-Out to go to is pouring into, in the meantime, is also pouring into own Soul as well as own aura.

Not only Soul Refinement from forging of outside to metal(s), is from inside to outside, pours into own aura and own Soul Power and Spiritual Strength to metal(s), through and this metal(s) relation, carries on certain forging from the interior to him. The inside and outside unions, making metal(s) properties be stimulated completely, infiltrates to belong to own Soul strength again.

A view, Soul Refinement metal(s) is doing several things at the same time of Saint Craftsman.

Although this view some exaggeration, but itself also makes some sense. Spirit Refinement can make metal(s) have very unique intelligence, thus produces some ordinary metal(s) impossible appear(ance) special effect, for example Self-Restoration, for example promotion of some special effect. But Soul Refinement is different, Soul Refinement metal(s) will make Soul Master have to plant multi- a feeling of companion.

Soul Refinement metal(s) forging Battle Armor, itself looks like Soul Master second Life. Even itself can carry out some orders.

of course, if oneself is not Blacksmith, in Three Word Battle Armor this stage, is own Battle Armor metal(s) that must first complete communicates. Because of came from Two Word Battle Armor, itself had own density, although this process is long, but can achieve. But Blacksmith will save this process.

After starting the Soul Refinement process, Tang Wulin obviously became discrete, each hammer fell that heavily, injection that his intense bloodline fluctuation was actually outspoken, but did not have the meaning that the least bit weakened.

With extension of time, golden-colored on that Heavy Silver steelyard weight exaggeration by time that removes each time also becomes slow. Often is previous golden-colored has not removed completely, the Tang Wulin second hammer arrived.

Gradually, Heavy Silver completely maintains in the golden-colored condition. Tang Wulin looks like the mechanization is wielding hammer, speed that the thump strikes starts becomes more and more slow.

„Works as! Bites!”

Suddenly, after a Tang Wulin hammer falls, the Heavy Silver interior spreads clear echo.

Hears this sounds/voices, the Mu Chen body shakes fiercely.

echo! This seems a very ordinary matter, regarding is not the matter that Blacksmith other Shrek Seven Monsters six people does not even have excessively to pay attention, listens in his ear, actually likely heard in this world the most wonderful matter to be ordinary.

His too clear this means anything.

The Soul Refinement difficulty is so big, echo is the initial victory of Soul Refinement! This means that oneself pours into metal(s) various energy the integration to get up, can assist forging from the interior.

This function was really too big!

Many 6th Rank Blacksmith cannot achieve this point for a lifetime, but this point is Soul Refinement is also most difficult! Soul Refinement echo also means that Blacksmith itself regarding the understanding of rare metal(s), means that the front all preparatory work have not wasted.

On the Tang Wulin face the expression is invariable , to continue forging. Really, each drop hammer, will have echo appear(ance). Moreover becomes more and more clear.

Mu Xi stared in a big way the eye.

He and he cannot be able......

own thinks approached him, but , he if bridged over that step, was not and own same stage existence.

Mu Chen had said to Mu Xi, according to the Mu Xi present progress and assiduous degree, if quick, at age 30, she can try assault Saint Craftsman stage.

But Tang Wulin? Now he is only 19 years old! He has achieved Soul Refinement echo. But own has not actually traced including the Soul Refinement echo gate.

Qi and Blood and Soul Power of everyone are impossible completely same. Spiritual Strength is also. Therefore, Soul Refinement echo can only teaches the feeling, does not have the skill to say, needs Blacksmith own to realize from experience.

Mu Xi is in this process now, but she actually absolutely cannot think that Tang Wulin walked such far unexpectedly, can grasp this most difficult one.

----------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued.)

#787: Half-step Soul Refinement

Then? Is Soul Refinement Solidization. Once completes Solidization, Soul Refinement has completed 70%, arrives at final Rousing the Soul again, completed Rousing the Soul, Soul Refinement means successfully.

Without doubt, Heavy Silver is one of the easiest forging rare metal(s), may together Soul Refinement Heavy Silver, if appear(ance), as before is the sky-high price! Because to Soul Refinement this stage, rare metal(s) no longer is rare metal(s). But is genuine Heaven and Earth Treasure!

Tang Wulin drop hammer speed starts to speed up, strength of formidable his Qi and Blood, did not have the sign that the least bit weakens to this time extremely. The body surroundings golden-colored light fog instead became stronger and stronger.

Heavy Silver turned into golden-colored completely, intermittent dragon roar sound reverberation, that clear Soul Refinement echo sound. Means that all in develop toward a good direction.

Suddenly, that golden-colored Heavy Silver rocked fiercely, then unexpectedly jumped from the forging stage.

This is......

„Has been careful, is Life fluctuation. It must run away!”

Entrusted with Life metal(s), once after the Life degree receives the stimulation of Soul Refinement is the certain extent, will have own Spirit Wisdom. But to this time, it became startled, it does not want Control, appear(ance) to be similar to the situation of escaping. Once it has been separated from the control of Blacksmith, Soul that because just promoted by Solidization, Soul fast will not have been diverged, thus returns to the Spirit Refinement stage, at that time, this metal(s) was impossible to carry on Soul Refinement.

Tang Wulin is unhurriedly, drinks one coldly, „comes back!”

Drinks with this lowly, third golden-colored ring of light fierce dodges. That golden-colored Heavy Silver trembled trembling, „working as”, fell returned to the forging stage.

Golden Dragon Roars!

On this Heavy Silver had Tang Wulin bloodline aura, but Golden Dragon King bloodline is formidable, under frightening of Tang Wulin, this Heavy Silver already return again irresistibly.

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, both hands steelyard weight brandishes once more, falls outrageously. Started the next stage, Soul Solidization!

Tang Wulin eyes turned into purple-gold from golden-colored, each hammer wields, bloodline aura release has been short, but Spiritual Strength actually promotes. Two ruler Yu Chang suddenly to launch of purple-gold ray of light from eyes. Used Purple Demon Eyes Spirit Assault above metal(s) directly.

Immediately, the scope of that golden-colored Heavy Silver tremor started changes small, received spiritual assault and forging dual Control, it in shivering above golden-colored started the toe-, formerly trace also started to reappear.

But that is not lines, but is lifelike diamond-shaped scales appearances, unexpectedly and Tang Wulin scales is exactly the same.

Mu Chen and Mu Xi father and daughter's aura starts becomes loud. Soul Solidization seems similarly is also very smooth, according to this trend, he may complete Soul Refinement really!

Even if completes time Soul Refinement, Tang Wulin also official promotes 7th Rank from 6th Rank Blacksmith. Once to 7th Rank, then, he became new Saint Craftsman.

Must know, even if in Shrek Academy, has Feng Wuyu this Saint Craftsman! Once Tang Wulin becomes Saint Craftsman, then, he social position on entire Douluo Continent will become entirely different, will become that part of genuine top layer. Even can become Metropolis Blacksmith Association Association President.

What is more important, he is only 19 years old now, is 19-year-old he, can definitely have the opportunity to continue to promote, to go to the assault Divine Craftsman world.

Zhen Hua in Continent high of status, even if Federation Parliament, even if will be Spirit Transferring Pagoda and Shrek Academy easily will not offend.

After previous Zhen Hua assassination, Spirit Transferring Pagoda with Federation coordinates to initiate an elimination action, Evil Soul Master goes into hiding, did not have appear(ance) until several years later today. Obvious Saint Craftsman means anything regarding the entire Soul Master world.

golden-colored dragon scales reappears are getting more and more, to covers entire Heavy Silver completely. golden-colored halo starts reserved, Heavy Silver ray of light starts orderly glittering.

Solidization succeeds! Mu Chen could not bear has waved the arm that made an effort.

Must know that this Soul Refinement echo or Soul Refinement Solidization, these two processes are extremely difficulties, but can complete these two processes, means that Blacksmith must become Saint Craftsman. Although the final Rousing the Soul process is difficult, but this process can practice through time.

Tang Wulin in forging , to continue Solidization as before. His Qi and Blood fluctuation finally started to have the weaken.

But at this time, Tang Wulin does not dare to stop.

Reason that he choice completes Soul Refinement with the strength of Qi and Blood, but not with own Soul Power , because, his Soul Power is insufficient!

Normal Soul Refinement, the entire process gets down, at least needs Seven Rings to cultivate for can complete. Tang Wulin apparently does not have. The strength of his Qi and Blood is unable to be equal to the strength of Seven Rings, what is different, his bloodline is Golden Dragon King bloodline, stage is high enough, in carrying on the Soul Refinement process, the strength of Qi and Blood is easier than to fuse and Control Soul Power. For example Soul Refinement echo this step, if by Soul Power forging, Tang Wulin could not have achieved now, but used the strength of Qi and Blood he to be OK.

This distinguishes location!

dual hammers falls, „bites!” In the crisp whining noise, radiant golden light (Jin Guang) jumps to shoot suddenly from that Heavy Silver, in golden light (Jin Guang) has dragon-shaped halo to circle regarding metal(s) faintly.

Tang Wulin does not dare to neglect, the takes a deep breath tone, drinks lightly, aura of his whole person becomes intense. The pupil light glistens! Both hands slight(ly) trembles, a pair of Heavy Silver Hammer raps before the body mutually. On him has resounded the resonant dragon roar sound suddenly. first golden-colored ring of light Great Release of Rays of Light, is Golden Dragon Body.

When behavior Rousing the Soul, must with own forging energy that pours into summoned Soul Refinement metal(s), with its take shape mutual echoing. As the matter stands, metal(s) internal Soul is genuine was activated.

Has Spirit Refinement of Life strength to look like Plant, but will have Soul Soul Refinement to make metal(s) is similar to Soul Beast is ordinary. This is genuine Soul Refinement.

In other words, once Soul Refinement succeeds, metal(s) turned into life form on genuine. Wonderful lies in this. Why this was also Soul Refinement such difficult reason location.

The spirited dragon roar sound reverberates in Forging Room, that metal(s) also unceasing exudes buzz the whining noise. But the brow of Tang Wulin wrinkled quickly.

Rousing the Soul this process was too difficult, in fact, his own has not attempted several times. Can complete Soul Refinement echo and Soul Refinement Solidization these two processes like today, he before altogether also only then 2-3 times.

Rousing the Soul does not have the means to teach similarly, when everyone forging process is different, this is the process that can only get an idea unable to explain, can only own look for the feeling.

„Buzz”

golden-colored Heavy Silver trembled fiercely, then suddenly became peaceful.

Dejected of Tang Wulin face, was defeated.

Rousing the Soul only then very short time carries on, after Soul Solidization completes, metal(s) Soul has the instantaneous liveliness, if at this time can make it sublimate through Rousing the Soul, it has completed Soul Refinement, bringing the metal(s) body to become the brand-new Life body. If not good, that consolidates in the Soul Refinement Solidization condition.

golden-colored is bringing on scales Heavy Silver, golden light (Jin Guang) is and out, is smart. What a pity, it eventually is actually not able to become is similar to the Soul Beast complete Life body.

A big hand powerful holds the shoulder of Tang Wulin, „you have done very well, do not give the own too tremendous pressure.”

Tang Wulin turns head to look that what sees is the smile of Mu Chen whole face.

„If you can Soul Refinement be successful, I may want ashamed could not work as this Association President. Can achieve Solidization this step, this metal(s) can be said as Half-step Soul Refinement. Even if made your Senior Teacher know, will certainly raise up the thumb for you. In several years time, you a foot strided in Saint Craftsman large door, our judgments right, developed according to this speed, in the future you can certainly become one generation of Divine Craftsman.”

Tang Wulin flexure scratching the head, „Teacher(s), you overpraised. I also some insufficient, I have not traced to the present to the Rousing the Soul threshold. Energy that front several need to consume is too big, were few to the last step opportunity . Moreover, whenever some of my energy will be bad at this time.”

Mu Chen sinking sound track: „forging lies in the accumulation. In the Soul Refinement Three Great difficulty, what is actually most difficult is first closes Soul Refinement echo, this is not can achieve really diligently. What the need are more is the luck and talent. Can achieve this point Blacksmith, so long as there is an enough time accumulation, almost can become Saint Craftsman finally. But your Soul Refinement Solidization achieved. What needs is only the accumulation of time, what need is to the experience of Soul Refinement. Continually promotes to cultivate is, your cultivation to be higher, when including Spiritual Strength, you will be at the Rousing the Soul feeling to be clearer. You certainly become Saint Craftsman, currently speaking, but is time issue that's all.”( To be continued.)

#788: Takes care, Wulin

Tang Wulin nodded, said with a smile: „Thank You (xiexie) Teacher(s). Teacher(s), you looked how much money my this Heavy Silver can sell?”

Mu Xi cannot bear curl the lip in side, „this has not changed, you fell to the square hole in the center.” She does not know that Tang Wulin their trip of task need.

Mu Chen stared daughter one eyes, then he he said with a smile: „Also sells anything! This Half-step Soul Refinement I collected. You are I most outstanding disciple, this metal(s) I, so long as takes away that side General Headquarters to show off, even if your Senior Teacher, must envy serious. Ha! To Half-step Soul Refinement this stage, you qualifications have named to own metal(s).”

In the Tang Wulin heart moves, hurries saying: „Teacher(s), was inferior that you help my giving a name character.”

Mu Chen surprised looks at Tang Wulin, regarding Saint Craftsman, is the metal(s) name of own is the extremely glorious matter, some people will give others this qualifications.

Looks at the sincerity in Tang Wulin look, Mu Chen also in hesitant, Tang Wulin said: „Teacher(s), does not have my today without your guidance. Do not decline.”

Mu Chen laughs, „good, good and good! Any ratio has not let my happy matter. That Teacher(s) gives a name to you. Looked that your forging leaves on this Heavy Silver dragon scales to cover, might as well call Dragon-scaled Heavy Silver! Later all your Soul Refinement metal(s), on so as to dragon scales prestige, how? In your name also has the Qilin large male deer, is the harmonics.”

„Good!”

From that moment on, Tang Wulin future Half-step Soul Refinement above metal(s) had was the own name, Heavy Silver was Dragon-scaled Heavy Silver, Adamantite is Dragon-scaled Adamantite.

Once rare metal(s) had the name, its value to imagine highly difficult. Moreover, each Saint Craftsman Soul Refinement metal(s) properties is different. It is not all Soul Master can use same position Saint Craftsman Soul Refinement metal(s).

Tang Wulin this Soul Refinement has injection of his Golden Dragon King bloodline, high of its quality, once genuine completes Soul Refinement, in the Saint Craftsman world absolutely is most Top Rank existence. Almost for all Battle Armor Master. Especially Assault System and Strength Type Battle Armor Master, matches certainly.

Tang Wulin had experimented, metal(s) that own this Half-step Soul Refinement leaves, even can isolate his own Golden Dragon King bloodline aura pressure. Because is in itself common origin location.

In the future if his companion puts on dragon scales metal(s) Battle Armor that his forging leaves, then, at least can let them in the fight not by the influence of own bloodline aura.

Mu Chen has given Tang Wulin 5 million federation coin(s), enough their all expenses all the way. If Dragon-scaled Heavy Silver must sell, value also incessantly so. This is in the Half-step Soul Refinement situation. But Mu Chen accepts this metal(s) to collect, the significance is different!

„Senior Sister, I walked.” Tang Wulin to delivering to entrance Mu Xi waved.

Although Mu Xi continuously to his sarcastic comments , but when he and companion must leave, she has actually delivered to out of the door.

Looks that smiles to Tang Wulin that own waves, Mu Xi nips the lower lip, suddenly, she overruns fiercely, grasps him.

Tang Wulin is gawked, the ear that she hugs transmits Mu Xi to bring sobbing sounds/voices, „takes care, Wulin.”

Has not waited for him to open the mouth, Mu Xi loosened him, flies is also has run back Blacksmith Association.

Fragrance still , a thick sense of being lost and lonely along with it appear(ance). Not only because this losing must separate , because, Tang Wulin feels suddenly in this moment that own is not the beforehand youth, is not a child. He is an adult, when is young the youth will be gone forever, but the responsibility of his shoulder actually becomes more and more heavy.

„Doesn't give up?” Xie Xie smiles near the Tang Wulin ear lowly.

The Tang Wulin ill-humored lifting hand has knocked in his head.

Can hold 20 people of Bus to stop before them, this is Mu Chen specially for the car(riage) that they arrange. Will deliver directly them to Soul Guide Train Station.

Said honestly that Tang Wulin natural has a little conflicted the psychology regarding Soul Guidance Train, is really because before , the several peculiar circumstances of encountering, making him very speechless.

But he must acknowledge that Soul Guidance Train goes to the military training direction quickest transportation vehicle at present.

Since Academy has stipulated time, moreover can see from the Old Cai expression expression that wants to arrive in the destination not to be perhaps easy. Front naturally can save time is frugal good.

Moreover now they were not the initial youth, everybody all was One Word Battle Armor Master, seven One Word Battle Armor Master! in addition strength already quite formidable.

Therefore, Tang Wulin after careful ponder, the decision is called as Soul Guidance High-speed Train.

Arrives at Soul Guide Train Station, buying a ticket. Tang Wulin has not used initial privilege. Buying a ticket boards, Train has not opened, the breath of Tang Wulin became even.

On Train is a they row of achievement. Tang Wulin and Le Zhengyu sit together, Xu Lizhi and Ye Xinglan, Xie Xie and Yuan En Yehui have Xu Xiaoyan to sit in another side row of three people of position.

Le Zhengyu hears the Tang Wulin even breathing to turn head to look, the surprised discovery, he has fallen asleep.

Yes, he was too weary, was too tired in Academy cultivate in the half year, in addition formerly Soul Refinement, Tang Wulin , is not only tired, heart also tired is not good.

He sits in the position by the window, sleeps soundly. The handsome face appears very quiet, the long eyelash builds below eyelid. Even if has fallen asleep, as before is a handsome man.

Le Zhengyu looked at Tang Wulin, own sat there starts to be in a daze.

In the half year, he feels similarly exhausted. Since Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting was rejected by Xu Xiaoyan, his whole person changed.

That attack for him was really too big. After helping Tang Wulin sought for Gu Yue not to find, his entire one month has not gone out. Closes own in the room. He thought that own does not have the face to see human. The pride of innermost feelings does not allow him to have such frustration.

, He starts to understand where the own issue gradually of that day leaves, is, even if so, innermost feelings proud is not willing to make him admit mistakes as before.

In his subconscious believes throughout that Xu Xiaoyan can look his, will make him have the opportunity of explanation.

What may be contrary to what expects, six months have passed, Xu Xiaoyan has not arrived at side him throughout, among them the distance also as if becomes more and more.

If not like not being painful. These words use on Le Zhengyu are appropriate. He liked Xu Xiaoyan, liked that spirit demon also being gentle such as the miss of jade.

But, Holy Angel Family made him unable to make own proud say the apology words. This is he most painful place.

Le Zhengyu dull sitting there, perhaps, this exiting, own should find an opportunity and she chats well.

He turns head to look at Xu Xiaoyan subconsciously, the surprised discovery, Xu Xiaoyan is also actually visiting him, four items of docking, they have avoided the vision of opposite party subconsciously.

But at this moment, impulsion suddenly appear(ance) beyond description in the Le Zhengyu heart, he fiercely has also stood.

Bridges over the corridor, Le Zhengyu arrives by three people of row of chairs. What here sits in the outermost is Xie Xie, is Yuan En Yehui, Xu Xiaoyan sits in the innermost.

Le Zhengyu said to Yuan En Yehui: „Can Yuan En, change a position with you first? I had the words to say to Xiaoyan.”

„Hey!” Has not waited for the Yuan En Yehui start to talk somewhat discontentedly, Xie Xie looks to Le Zhengyu. But when he sees the Le Zhengyu somewhat gloomy look, eventually is helpless standing up.

Yuan En Yehui has not said anything, stands up, arrives at side Tang Wulin to sit down, Xie Xie stands side her simply, has given Le Zhengyu another side position.

Xu Xiaoyan hears Le Zhengyu sounds/voices, after gaining ground looked at his one eyes, immediately turns to out of the window direction.

------------------------

The new week, sought the recommendation vote support.( To be continued.)

#789: It is not willing to forgive

Le Zhengyu walks, sits down in her side.

„Xiaoyan.”

Xu Xiaoyan has not turned head.

„Sorry. If you for Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting matter offended, I again were still apologizing to you. Was I was too at that time impulsive, was too arrogant. I apologized to you. Over six months, I have thought very much clearly, you are very important to me, I am willing to put down the pride of own, we......”

He just spoke of here, Xu Xiaoyan on fierce turning head, looks at Le Zhengyu that lets somebody cool off or calm down, said: „You in giving charity? I do not need your giving charity. I do not need noble Holy Angel Family giving charity. Le Zhengyu, I saw clearly you on that day actually, I have thought own very joyfully with you in the same place, but I was clear on that day, in your eyes, my radically anything is not, but in your heart should come as soon as called that sigh goes to with the woman who maidservant anything has not distinguished.”

„You are very outstanding, are gentle, the strength excels. But I told you, I was not rare. My radically not rare these. You with I apologize? If you realized really own has made a mistake, not after over six months today looks for me. You are impossible to put down the pride in heart, is impossible. In your innermost feelings forever keeps aloof. I will never find one not to be the boyfriend the person who I and he place the same social stratum, will be the future husband. Therefore, we consider as finished.”

Xu Xiaoyan sounds/voices somewhat is obviously excited, other row of passengers look askance.

The [say / way] of some Le Zhengyu short of breath hundred flowers: „Actually do you also make me what kind of? I apologized to you. Xiaoyan, who said in my heart you are not and my social stratum? I like you, I am sincerity likes you.”

Xu Xiaoyan lifts the hand, indifferent gives a hand signal of suspension, „I said that we consider as finished. Please leave here, you sit in my side will make me uncomfortable.”

Because Le Zhengyu is angry, chest fluctuating obviously becomes fierce, he has not thought of the Xu Xiaoyan so sarcastic comments rejection own. Let him say the apology words, is not actually easy to his own. Securable is actually the so direct rejection.

„Xu Xiaoyan, I know that you reject me are because feels inferior. You are feeling inferior is right? Why can't you face up among us the issue? Yes, I over six months have not gone to look for you, that is because of me is unable the returning to normal mood. Right, I attach great importance to face-saving, therefore on that day after that many people you to reject me my very offended also is very painful. But in the half year I want to understand, I understood for me Love is more important than the face. I also came to apologize to you, did you also want what kind of?”

Xu Xiaoyan cold snort, „I do not cherish your this giving charity Love. Moreover, I told you, I also never felt inferior. Do not forget, I am also one of the Shrek Seven Monsters, do I have something to feel inferior? You get out of the way!”

Le Zhengyu fierce standing up, „do not regret!”

Xu Xiaoyan stubborn turning head, looked that does not look at his one eyes.

Le Zhengyu enraged returning said that by own position, Xie Xie and Yuan En Yehui are listening to their dialog, frowned.

„Can't you calm?” The Xie Xie helpless [say / way], „girl must roar.”

Le Zhengyu roared: „Your don't mind/care I.”

„Who cherished to manage you?” Yuan En Yehui stands up, draws Xie Xie, returned to own formerly position, was comforting eye socket red Xu Xiaoyan in a low voice.

Le Zhengyu sits returns to side Tang Wulin, in heart as before extremely angry difficult draw. As if the big stones press in the chest, breathes difficulties.

Xie Xie not because of his scolding, but offended, instead somewhat sympathized with Le Zhengyu.

Is too close to the problem, the onlooker is clear-headed. Xu Xiaoyan said right, Le Zhengyu was too proud, his pride is in the bone, is gradually influences from infancy to maturity in Holy Angel Family. That is not one day two days of matters, in his heart likes Xu Xiaoyan being without a doubt, but without a doubt, on Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, his words have had very profound stimulation to Xu Xiaoyan. If he can awaken to look for Xu Xiaoyan at that time to talk clearly promptly immediately, perhaps also has the opportunity. But he does not have, has hoodwinked his heart proud, the point of honor is to let he entire over six months time has not paid attention to Xu Xiaoyan.

Perhaps Xu Xiaoyan does not have him to be so proud, but others is a miss! Had been such treated coldly for a half year, in the heart can not have the anger and anger? At this time Le Zhengyu should do only, is hear that the soft and gentle words, even is brazen-faced and shameless encouraging, the opportunity naturally was much bigger. Must make the miss vent the anger.

But in the Le Zhengyu own heart also thinks suffering from injustice, had gone against several after by Xu Xiaoyan, naturally erupted. This can only be without doubt makes contradiction intensify.

This matter, who the bystander persuaded to be also useless. Instead makes them ossify.

Tang Wulin is very weary, therefore he rests is very fragrant, Le Zhengyu and Xu Xiaoyan loud dialog cannot awaken by noise him.

Le Zhengyu looked at Tang Wulin, suddenly some same life connected feelings, Gu Yue bewildered walked, Na'er has also been missing, is so big regarding the attack of Tang Wulin. own? Where also very to goes.

Soul Guidance High-speed Train is speeding along, steadily and quickly. The place that they must go to is very far, in the entire Douluo Continent northeast seashore. Even if called as Train, wants entire three days of time to arrive. Therefore, this is a far way travels.

Quick, daytime must pass, the world outside glass falls into darkness gradually.

Xu Xiaoyan and Le Zhengyu is not very happy, they are one day have not eaten the thing. Other people have not urged, at this time, in the fit of temper, urged also uselessly.

Tang Wulin the money of Teacher(s) there obtaining has apportioned everybody, far way Train has the dining car to dispose. After having had the dinner, some Xu Lizhi worries asked to Ye Xinglan, „Sister Xinglan, Boss has rested entire the day, can awaken him?”

The far way Train chair wants spacious many compared with ordinary Train, the seat back recedes, almost can partly lie down, comfort level not anything issue.

Ye Xinglan shook the head, „do not call him, he should not be the weariness on body, but is on spiritual. Since Gu Yue walked, he a little spelled. Let him rest well, he is the person who in us most needs to relax.”

Xu Lizhi touches the fat face of own, „does not understand really why Gu Yue must walk, Boss such good person. What matter has unable to discuss? Even if because Spirit Transferring Pagoda has the relations, but between we and Spirit Transferring Pagoda do not have any contradiction!”

Ye Xinglan shakes the head, „I am not clear, but should not be simple. The Captain missing that several years, the Gu Yue whole person became silent, so long as did not attend class, she will not keep Academy. She even in desirably maintains the distance with us. specific because of anything, perhaps only then their own is clear, even not completely is clear Captain. Let him rest well, nothing could not solve. The association faces.”

In free time who they spoke, suddenly, Soul Guidance Train vibrated fiercely. The people stare, the next quarter, entire Soul Guidance Train goes to one side suddenly crookedly, the ear-piercing chaffing sound and frightened squeal almost flood in the entire compartment instantaneously.

Slender Soul Guidance Train as if horizontally had been flung in High-speed, threw to fly directly.

Its travel speed is extremely quick, suddenly appear(ance) Transformation almost let have Soul Guidance Train of 16 compartments to disintegrate instantaneously fully.

What situation?

All people are all surprised, even if Shrek Seven Monsters strengths are astonishing, this sudden Transformation also makes them be caught off guard. All was almost is flung from the position instantaneously.( To be continued.)

#790: It is not the accident

At this time demonstrated the function of Assault System Battle Soul Master. Selects point starlight to burst out from Ye Xinglan, dazzling sword light suddenly to launch, instantaneous Body and Sword Unity, her hand draws Xu Lizhi together, the automobile body transverse shift is tumbling, but she actually slightly float in compartment palatial motionless. Is revolving the compartment is cut directly by sword light that on her bursts out, bringing Xu Lizhi to jump.

Other people also similarly made reaction, Le Zhengyu back pair of wings have launched, that the body while was flinging horizontally, the a pair of wing has protected oneself. Meanwhile, Sacred Light bursts out, changes into light to cover him covers.

Another side, the Yuan En Yehui body inflates suddenly, the both arms open, separately hugs into the own bosom to change into the huge body of Great Titan Ape to roll up Xie Xie and Xu Xiaoyan, protects inside two by oneself. Is relying on the body formidable defense strength in the compartment, although collides, but cuts the compartment to speak with Ye Xinglan, was the instantaneous ball flew.

Most miserable Tang Wulin actually, because he in the deep sleep, that absolutely is a protection does not have. Even if the vibration under automobile body first cannot make him wake. The automobile body flings horizontally, the body of Tang Wulin was flung to fly directly, numerous pounding one side of compartment.

Until at this moment, him has opened the eye. Happen to saw that companion flung to fly from compartment.

Tang Wulin body not by Control is rolling in the compartment, his some sleepy eyes dim finding out both hands, grasped rapidly on the wall of compartment.

golden-colored scales along with it reappearing, Tang Wulin shook the head, diligently lets the own sober several points, then a both hands point, ripping open compartment stiffly, body, although was flung, but to outside, was instead more relaxed.

The body was flung to fly in airborne, he can see clearly the present aspect.

Entire Soul Guidance Train has been derailed, was flung to fly directly in airborne, compartment from the sky breaks a successively, scatters in all directions to flutter about. What is more fearful, many people were flung from the crack.

These average people are not Soul Master, does not have Tang Wulin their adapting ability, those were flung to fly, in the event of the collision is almost instantaneous blood light Beng Xian, pitiful.

In Tang Wulin heart speechless, why? Why is this? Why own sits Soul Guidance High-speed Train each time time, will encounter this grade of rarely seen situation. In the Federation history all Soul Guidance Train have an accident is related with own! own simply is Soul Guidance Train bearer of bad luck, moreover this broom (bad luck) was also too fierce a point.

The body rolls up in airborne, the instance before landing, the Tang Wulin whole body catches up, a fist bombardment in ground, with the aid of formidable instead shakes the strength to melt strength that own had been flung to fly, a tumbling, falls on the ground.

Did not stop by defense strength of course of his body in has been injured in just process, but a person was awakened from the deep sleep, always not good feeling.

But Tang Wulin does not dare to neglect at this time, his first time is seeking for the companion trail.

Luckily, everybody is quite striking, particularly Ye Xinglan point point starlight. Tang Wulin hurries to run to the companion direction. He must confirm the first companion security is good.

Shrek Seven Monsters of course will not have matter, Tang Wulin is last gathers.

Seven people look at each other in blank diamay, finally vision all centralized on Tang Wulin, reveals to perform in the look that does not call the turn.

Tang Wulin has coughed, „quickly saves others.”

„First waits.” Ye Xinglan sinking sound said suddenly that „this is not normal. The Soul Guidance Train security is extremely high, how to go off track suddenly? Can create artificially?”

At this time, entire Soul Guidance Train has all been separated from the track, was flung to fly wilderness in all directions, 16 compartments succeeded in giving up 78, time, various pitiful yell sounds continuously.

Soul Guidance Train can accommodate over 500 people, the so significant accident, the casualty figure must have.

Listened to the Ye Xinglan words, Tang Wulin is also vigilant that sinking sound track: „Everybody receives Martial Soul first.”

He had had faced the experience of Evil Soul Master, but that experience was unhappy. This time is derailed , if not accident, but thinks that then, not only definitely went off track is so simple.

In this time, they were noticing that distant place ray of light shine quietly, that ray of light and not strong are fierce, seems purple.

Xie Xie said in a low voice: „I had a look in the past. You hide.”

At the same time was saying, he swings body in a flash, the body rapidly becomes illusory, looked like integrates in the air, vanished without the trace.

Agility System Battle Soul Master, must hide own to be responsible for investigating at this time.

Tang Wulin has given a hand signal, people speedily found the bunker in surroundings, camouflages the body of own.

The life-saving is necessary, but if there is an enemy, then, must solve the enemy more important first.

Was less than one minute, Xie Xie came back, „was artificial. Some people are slaughtering the wounded. They have 50-60 people, is taking Soul Guide Ray Gun, sees the human to kill. Boss, what to do?”

Tang Wulin said: „What strength can see clearly is?”

Xie Xie said: „What can affirm is Soul Master, but specific cultivates for is unable to see clearly, only uses the Soul Guide Ray Gun words, they have not released Martial Soul. But from speed, is not weak.”

„Walks! On us.” The unnecessary words, can't this situation, facing these terrifying members, how sit by and do nothing?

Tang Wulin flushed fast, other people follow behind. His left and right separately are Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui, behind with Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi, Le Zhengyu and Xie Xie in behind.

Xu Lizhi muttered talked over several soul incantations, Steamed Stuffed Bun came out to give companion by his fast manufacture.

The agile little dragon(s) package, can make everybody's speed quicker. When Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun as the preparation, erupts uses.

Quick, Tang Wulin saw the enemy in Xie Xie mouth. These people all is a black clothed, in the curtain of night just like the spirit, purple rays projects from Soul Guide Ray Gun in their hand, falls into the compartment.

black-clothed person is bringing helmet, helmet covered the face.

When Tang Wulin they clash, immediately some people have discovered them. From near three and five black-clothed person turn against one's associates immediately, launched Soul Guidance rays to them.

Tang Wulin one step steps forward, Golden Scales takes possession. Meanwhile, Blue Silver Emperor suddenly to launch, take shape barrier before the body.

Soul Guidance rays falls on Blue Silver Emperor can only bring piece by piece halo. A Tang Wulin tip of the toe place, the human is similar to artillery shell generally suddenly to launch.

People also in airborne, his both hands void have grasped. Two huge suctions erupt from his both hands, is ordinary, two black-clothed person that just like two vortex pulls falls to fly in his direction.

Both hands Golden Dragon Claw finds out, simultaneously grasps to them.

That two black-clothed person reaction are quick, immediately releases own Martial Soul, one is three yellow Soul Ring, another is one white two yellow. Unexpectedly is Soul Elder.

Left Soul Master is Beast Martial Soul, the body suddenly becomes the strong several points, in the top of the head also grows two buffalo and cow horns, with the aid of the Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Claw suction, lowers the head, has hit toward Tang Wulin.

Moreover that black-clothed person Martial Soul is a handle broadsword, the abandonment hand in without hesitation Ray Gun, brandishes the broadsword to divide to Tang Wulin.

„Puff!” Left hand Golden Dragon Claw flies a Cattle-Type Martial Soul Soul Master palm of the hand racket, terrifying strength made the body of that black-clothed person in airborne disintegrate directly.

Right hand Golden Dragon Claw holds broadsword that looks like, broadsword instantaneous to shatter, Martial Soul and Soul Master mind is connected, that Soul Master is stuffy immediately snort. Tang Wulin right hand Golden Dragon Claw grip turned into a fist, shelled directly on his chest.

The dorsal instantaneous bulge, the human is similar to artillery shell departs, similarly from the sky blows out one group of blood fog.

Tang Wulin most hates is these cruel terrifying members, starts not to be forgiving. After solves them like lightning, he overran toward distant place population many black-clothed person immediately.

By him, Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan also launched attack, in the Ye Xinglan hand Star Divine Sword outlined [say / way] sword thread(s), selected point Star Grain(s), in she held on the Divine sword to burst out, where these were about Soul Elder cultivated for black-clothed person can block her attack, did not have the Tang Wulin that violence, but was almost one sword one.

What Yuan En Yehui releases is Fallen Angel changes the body, transforms from Great Titan Ape as Fallen Angel that to favor in darkness battles, Satanic Demon Sword cuts purple glow, similarly has solved the own enemy rapidly.

The following four people absolutely do not have the act opportunity, Tang Wulin, Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui three people of speed were too quick. Puts in an appearance, five and six black-clothed person completely perished.

----------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. Today three. Thank everybody's support!( To be continued.)

#791: Golden Dragon reveals the prestige

Here sound attracted black-clothed person of distant place immediately. Soul Guidance rays immediately crowded launches in their directions.

„Be careful, Soul Guide Cannon!” Xie Xie sounds/voices resounds.

Tang Wulin subconscious turning head looks that sees only on a black-clothed person shoulder to carry a gun tube, happen to aims at own.

Next flickers, howls with one, one group of bright purple ray of light directly soars own to fly to shoot.

Tang Wulin cold snort, body golden light (Jin Guang) dodges, four golden-colored ring of light upper bodies, first ring of light shines, Golden Dragon Body!

The whole body was covered by golden-colored scales, his left hand Golden Dragon Claw finds out instantaneously, grasps unexpectedly directly toward that only group.

„Bang” a bang, Soul Guide Cannon unexpectedly directly grasping exploded by Tang Wulin. Formidable explosive force assault on him, can only make his golden dragon scales piece sparkle shine, makes him withdraw unable to achieve continually.

Meanwhile, that launched Soul Guide Cannon Soul Master already softly. Xie Xie when reminded Tang Wulin already act .

On speed, in the entire team Xie Xie is second to none without doubt, but copes with these to cultivate for about black-clothed person in Soul Elder, Agility System Soul Master obviously is preponderant.

Shadow Dragon Dagger shuttles back and forth in illusory and reality, black forms cannot fall to the ground.

Tang Wulin assumes the center, protects following Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi, looks over the audience. Xie Xie, Yuan En Yehui, Le Zhengyu and Ye Xinglan clash to cope with these black-clothed person.

Has not discovered anything to threaten, dozens black-clothed person just like easily accomplished drop down in the face of the Shrek Seven Monsters formidable offensive generally.

Suddenly, a sense of fear flashes through in the Tang Wulin heart imperceptibly suddenly, he is almost turning round without hesitation, one grasped behind Xu Lizhi and Xu Xiaoyan, is having their body crosswise tumblings.

gray-black Light and Shadow dodges not to have together, in the ground leaves behind one has been five meters, width one meter gap, deeply did not see the bottom unexpectedly.

What terrifying is, by that gap, is corroding unexpectedly rapidly.

„Evil Soul Master!” Tang Wulin drinks one lowly.

„Dares to prevent our motions. Your Soul can by sacrificed and refined.” Ice-cold sounds/voices reverberates in the air.

Together form also slowly reappears, he float in midair. The whole body covers in the grey clothes. Whole person seemed has been full of haze flavor.

The body altogether has seven Soul Ring, two yellow, three purple, two black!

Soul Saint!

This unexpectedly is Evil Soul Master of Soul Saint rank. The ash-gray form also continues this together. In darkness, as if appear(ance) the gate of space and time, ash-gray forms quietly reappeared, adds to have more than ten completely unexpectedly. Their Soul Ring least also four, Seven Rings has in front of Tang Wulin this. In addition four Six Rings, surplus are Four Rings and Five Rings.

The Tang Wulin heart sinks, what if the grey clothes represent is Evil Soul Master, then, simultaneously appear(ance) several Evil Soul Master, to them without doubt are the huge threats.

Reason that Evil Soul Master Evil , because they can promote own with some cruel way (of life), not only promotion speed is quick, but also their ability are virtually impossible to guard against. Soul Master of same level rank, Evil Soul Master be much more formidable than ordinary Soul Master.

Their existence, aimed at destroying and Ruin, Evil cultivate way (of life) will definitely cause their character distortions, even not by Control.

„You help other people. Here gives me.” Tang Wulin waved to behind Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi.

They understood Tang Wulin strength, without hesitation runs in the directions of other people.

Shrek Seven Monsters coordinates long-standingly, other people after discovering Evil Soul Master, is rapid converges toward Tang Wulin.

The Evil Soul Master offensive has also launched at this time, they absolutely do not have any meaning of exchange. Formerly black-clothed person also remaining twenty, saw Evil Soul Master appear(ance), immediately disperses, threw in the Train direction.

Their this slaughter motions obviously are early deliberate, what the functions of numerous Evil Soul Master seem to be more is to bring up the rear.

Airborne Evil Soul Master both hands open by the body, dusky mist bursts out from him suddenly, the personal appearance dodges, plunged Tang Wulin, a pair of gray-black Sharp Claws directly soared the Tang Wulin overhead to grasp.

Good quick speed!

speed of this grey clothes man also wanted compared with Xie Xie quickly, Tang Wulin almost thought that at present a flower, Sharp Claws arrived in front of own, grasped to his face, another grasped to his chest.

Once were grasped, finally can be imagined.

Agility System Evil Soul Master?

Tang Wulin does not have retreat, facing speed such quick match, even if will be retreat will not have anything to affect.

golden light (Jin Guang) glittering, Tang Wulin a pair of Golden Dragon Claw keeps off in the own face front alternately.

Seven Rings how? His Four Rings time dares to shake Six Rings Long Yue hardly. Let alone cultivates for already Five Rings now, overall strength has qualitative to leap.

second golden-colored Soul Ring shines, Tang Wulin whole body scales instantaneously was changing into the mirror surface shape.

„Bites!” Two resounding, Evil Soul Master Sharp Claws grasps in the Tang Wulin chest, another grasps on his arm.

Tang Wulin only thought that the air/Qi of two yin cold well up to drill generally to own within the body just like the spring, but his huge Golden Dragon King bloodline aura erupts instantaneously, blocked actually has not let that icy aura invasion.

That Evil Soul Master only thought that own pair of claws was similar to grasps above the sheet iron, then front this person of scales got up on glittering rapidly.

„Raises!” In the dragon roar sound, gigantic Golden-colored Dragon Head jumps to shoot from Tang Wulin both hands, at the same time, on him Third Soul Ring also along with it bright.

„Raises -” Frantic dragon roar resounds. That Evil Soul Master only thinks whole body one, within the body Qi and Blood as if not by galloping of Control. The next quarter, that Golden-colored Dragon Head arrived front.

Golden Dragon Shocks the Heavens adds Tang Wulin Qi and Blood Soul Ring technique Golden Dragon Roars.

Facing Seven Rings cultivates for Evil Soul Master, Tang Wulin must fight a battle to force a quick decision, is good to help other companion, therefore he comes up not to have any to keep the hand.

Golden Dragon Roars stops the skill, has strong Control strength. Especially when Martial Soul of match is Dragon-Type the effect is best.

This Evil Soul Master Martial Soul is not Dragon-Type, itself cultivates to be also higher than Tang Wulin. But present Tang Wulin was not four years ago he, he obtained that many dragon spirit(s) in addition to hold in Dragon Valley, thick of bloodline aura, surpassed the past. This Golden Dragon Roars shocks the audience, all Evil Soul Master speed are one slow, let alone near at hand.

However this Evil Soul Master strength also truly formidable, Golden Dragon Shocks the Heavens directly hits the flash of his body, although his person hit flying upside down, but also rapid reaction comes, Fifth Soul Ring ray of light dodges, then the whole person changed into one group of ash-gray mist unexpectedly, Golden Dragon Shocks the Heavens has put from that mist, cannot hit the reality.

Mist distant place condense, this Seven Rings Evil Soul Master was enraged again obviously, in the mouth sends out a keenly blowing, the body surroundings ash-gray mist suddenly becomes intense.

On him Three Soul Rings shines, purple Soul Ring in the sparkle, as if has strong bloody aura to greet the nostrils.

Tang Wulin only thought that brain dizziness, blood in within the body as if generally does not become by Control manic, as if must seize the body, but.

„Well!” This situation he is first time meets. Soul Skill of match as if can Control his blood.

Tang Wulin while surprised, cold snort! Qi and Blood misfortune, forcefully Control within the body blood. Whole body golden light (Jin Guang) puts greatly, receives the Soul Skill stimulation of opposite party, strength of reassignment his bloodline seemed to be easier for several points, the light golden-colored light fog reappears in body surroundings.

------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#792: Golden Dragon Soars

One step steps forward, Tang Wulin jumped over, he has not released Martial Soul, because can change into the mist Soul Skill to see from formerly the match that his Martial Soul will not play anything to affect. Such being the case, was inferior that does not use.

Void , a Tang Wulin fist rumbles, the sound of body dragon roar begins. It seems like an unadorned fist rumbles instantaneous, his whole person from the under foot to the coccygeal vertebra, follows the entire vertebra to extend again upwardly, to the human whole body extend, regains consciousness the general feeling just like Mighty Dragon.

All that extend comes, all converge above this fist finally.

The right fist of Golden Dragon Claw rumbles, is centered on the Tang Wulin body, in a diameter three meters range, turned into bright golden-colored suddenly, next one flickers, his whole body under lead of right fist, suddenly in airborne glittering.

In Sky appear(ance) has been dozens meters golden-colored band of light, a diameter three meters band of light almost dodges to pass.

That Evil Soul Master can only change into one group of mist promptly, but so, called out pitifully, again condense became human form time, the body swayed is crashing in the place.

Golden Dragon Soars!

The strength of bloodline erupts in the compression, the flash that the use erupts leads the body, in that condition, Tang Wulin itself is almost at the Tyrant Body condition strongly, whole body strength at 1 : 00, a little likely is the person sword unites, attack 30 meters in diameter, can only straight line attack, these be the limit. The assault strength that but is erupting instantaneously is actually three times of his normal attack strength.

The Scarlet Dragon Douluo Zhuo Shi Scarlet Dragon Nine Styles third type, Dragon Soars! Said accurately, he teaches Tang Wulin should be Divine Dragon Nine Styles, affects on Tang Wulin, is Golden Dragon Nine Styles. Therefore is, Golden Dragon Soars!

That flickers, Tang Wulin looks like extend opens dragon claw Golden Dragon King, under personal appearance assault, has Blocks God, Kills God and Blocks Buddha, Kills Buddha might greatly.

This is the Tang Wulin first time uses Golden Dragon Soars this type in the fight of genuine, the effect is very tangible.

Because this type, not only has strength of Soul Power and bloodline, also has integration of Spiritual Strength. Therefore is all-around attack. Even if that Evil Soul Master changes into the mist, received assault similarly.

After falling to the ground Evil Soul Master not to dare to pull rank finally again, body grey ray of light shone, covered the whole body just like leaf armor, the back, one pile of ash-gray wing extend came, seemed looks like gigantic bat.

Battle Armor! Has Wings Battle Armor, Two Word Battle Armor!

Without a doubt, Evil Soul Master of this Seven Rings Soul Saint rank, similarly is also Two Word Battle Armor Master!

Battle Armor takes possession, Evil Soul Master aura immediately becomes entirely different.

Must know that Battle Armor can promote Soul Master two stage, although Seven Rings Soul Saint put on Two Word Battle Armor to the Titled Douluo standard, but absolutely has also surpassed Eight Rings Soul Douluo stage.

surroundings world suddenly gloomy, that Evil Soul Master face upwards to send out a keenly blowing, immediately, Tang Wulin only thought that was similar the sharp acupuncture to enter the own spiritual world, the forehead severe pain. Meanwhile, within the body bloodline in his Control galloped suddenly, madness to rush.

Those who make Tang Wulin with amazement is, because of bloodline appear(ance) short out-of-control, had overrun toward Golden Dragon King ninth Seal unexpectedly.

This is fighting! How can clash ninth Seal at this time, this and suicide anything have not distinguished.

Tang Wulin hurries to nip the tip of tongue, as far as possible lets the own sober several points. Body point golden light (Jin Guang) shines, released own Battle Armor.

golden-colored Battle Armor cover whole body, immediately, to rush bloodline aura received the suppression from outside, Soul Power obtains the formidable amplification, Tang Wulin Control lived in own bloodline finally again. mask falls, covers his handsome face. The Tang Wulin right hand wipes on the forehead, Golden Dragon Spear rises suddenly against the wind, was grasped by him in the hand.

gold helmet gold armor gold mask! Begins again grasps Golden Dragon Spear. When the Tang Wulin floating body falls to the ground, martial-looking extraordinary.

In hand Golden Dragon Spear one horizontal, in his look ray of light blooms, the body under squats slightly, the next quarter, once more overran toward that Evil Soul Master.

Golden Dragon Spear punctures like lightning, changes into the (spear|gun) glow. But strange appear(ance), body of that Evil Soul Master under Golden Dragon Spear covers, actually when just like not having the weight in airborne glittering, can always not allow sends to avoid Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Spear attack in the middle generally rapidly.

His that a pair of Sharp Claws had the Two Word Battle Armor amplification, becomes has foot Yu Chang fully, presents for the grey Crystallized Body shape, while fending, often attacks a claw.

His speed was really too quick, Tang Wulin is unable to fend completely. A claw falls, on Tang Wulin One Word Battle Armor will leave several white traces.

But at this time Tang Wulin this was named as Battle Armor of dragon showed the formidable defense strength, whenever Evil Soul Master attack fell on his Battle Armor, Battle Armor of that part will reappear light pattern of scales shape, enormous degree melted that Sharp Claws attack strength.

Generally speaking, Two Word Battle Armor suppresses to One Word Battle Armor absolutely, but this Evil Soul Master cannot achieve this point obviously. This no doubt is Spiritual Metal builds with Tang Wulin One Word Battle Armor related, what is more important is Tang Wulin defense strength is astonishing.

However, this time Tang Wulin does not feel better, opposite party speed is too quick, drifts from place to place, his attack is unable to fall on the tangible, place that huge strength has not vented. This match for him is hard to deal with, the superiority cannot display.

But Evil Soul Master of that Soul Saint rank wants to take Tang Wulin not to be easy, the Tang Wulin defense strength is too strong, and has formerly Golden Dragon Soars to the deep impression that he makes, at this time this Two Word Battle Armor Evil Soul Master is discrete, is unceasing You Dou, attempts to weaken Tang Wulin Soul Power, seeks unceasingly initiates attack emptily.

They fell into here have entangled war, but other one side, Shrek Seven Monsters other six people of situations were also less optimistic.

Altogether 11 Evil Soul Master have sphered Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui they. And initiated madness attack.

Evil Soul Master in the Soul Master world completely is another system, even if Martial Soul is the same, if took the Evil Soul Master cultivate route, ability that cultivate comes out is also entirely different.

Forefront Six Rings Evil Soul Master is hardest to deal with, is One Word Battle Armor Master, Martial Soul that releases is also one by one rarely seen.

Four Six Rings Evil Soul Master Martial Soul was one turned into Skeleton respectively, was dressing armor piece Skeleton. The personal appearance is huge, eight meters high, the whole body skeleton is extremely fully sturdy, in addition protection of One Word Battle Armor. The frontage attacks hardly. Grasps a handle is seven meters giant chopper.

Luckily, Shrek Seven Monsters also has Yuan En Yehui, Great Titan Ape Martial Soul releases, a pair of had not been launched by Giant Hammer(s) of Academy confiscation, meets the tough head-on with toughness, has blocked the attack of this huge Skeleton.

second Six Rings Evil Soul Master, is one seems is similar to the person of clown general appearance, his face side is white, side is black, seems very strange. In the mouth sends out villainous smile unceasingly. Body unceasing in revolving, is similar to slowly, frightened and so on curse ability is falling on Shrek unceasingly strangely six, is weakening them. Moreover he also hides behind other Evil Soul Master, cannot suffice him.

Third Six Rings Evil Soul Master turned into a giant wolf appearance, the whole body has been sending out the bloody air/Qi, fought, while picked up formerly the black-clothed person corpse unexpectedly, ate the hearts of these black-clothed person specially, every time ate a heart, his attack strength will promote several points. The whole body superficial knowledge presents is the iron grey, invulnerability. Ye Xinglan Star Divine Sword is unable to puncture he is dressing Battle Armor.

fourth 6th Rank Evil Soul Master is in these four people seems most normal one, his normalcy is because he seems also looks like individual, rides a whole body to brave the black flame bone horse, a little likely is the nightmare in legend. The whole body is covering weighty black armor piece, grasps the heavy sword, chops the delight of cutting with Le Zhengyu mutually.

Yuan En Yehui to Skeleton Evil Soul Master, Ye Xinglan to giant wolf Evil Soul Master, Le Zhengyu confronts horseman Evil Soul Master. Three people of frontages shoulder somewhat to be strenuous hardly.

The same level rank, Evil Soul Master is stronger than ordinary Soul Master, but Shrek Seven Monsters obviously is not ordinary Soul Master. But front these Evil Soul Master in cultivation are also higher than them for the aspect on stage! Let alone behind also Control System Evil Soul Master unceasingly weakens them through various curses.

Xie Xie thinks actually very much act solves that clown Evil Soul Master, but the issue is, he must stay in behind, protects Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi.

Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi direct combat ability was too weak, if he also walked, other Evil Soul Master certainly will go then to enter.

In other seven Evil Soul Master, five Five Rings Evil Soul Master, two are also One Word Battle Armor Master, another four are 4th Rank Evil Soul Master.

---------------------------------------------

Thank You (xiexie) everybody's blessing, although this is in my this life most is unable a happy birthday, but there are you, I have strong foundation and power. Thank your for 13 years companion. I try hard, I support certainly am continue write a book for everybody. Thank You (xiexie) you.

#793: Fights vigorously Evil Soul Master

These seven people attack from four surroundings, Xie Xie is the busy delight. A person branches out three to do several things at the same time, is equal to fighting from four directions. In all people, is the pressure that he bears is instead biggest.

At this time can see that Xie Xie cultivate was usually assiduous. Four forms face the different enemies separately, is carrying on the different fights, he can unexpectedly Control also good.

Although deals to be strenuous, but also has Xu Xiaoyan Control luckily.

Xu Xiaoyan has not displayed own strongest Control Soul Skill eagerly, but whenever Xie Xie deals with difficulties time, Star Wheel Ice Chain can always help Xie Xie solve many problems.

„Bang!” On the Yuan En Yehui right hand hammer pulls up, parry the Skeleton Evil Soul Master broadsword, the left hand hammer has swept away, directly soars the opposite party chest place bombardment in the past.

That Skeleton Evil Soul Master lowers roars, in the eye socket as if Gains Spirit soul flame is beating. The body squats to below, drives the great blade to keep off by the body before the body.

Also is a dull thumping sound, Skeleton Evil Soul Master and Yuan En Yehui simultaneously retreat one step, the strength aspect, they unexpectedly have the feeling of rival in chess.

Ye Xinglan slightly gets the advantage, although her Star Divine Sword is very difficult to break through giant wolf Evil Soul Master defense, but, her Star Divine Sword not only has sword qi also to have sword intent. That sharp sword intent is oppressing that giant wolf Evil Soul Master throughout, after discovering the opposite party eats the heart to be able the amplification own, Ye Xinglan is relying on own assault, has not made that giant wolf Evil Soul Master eat to have been to a heart again.

Le Zhengyu here situation is in evenly matched. That horseman under the warhorse with the aid of cross, darkness energy is thick, but has happen to met mutual restraint Holy Angel Martial Soul. darkness and light two clearly opposite energy assault, in airborne erupt piece by piece terrifying energy storm mutually unceasingly.

But the present is in the evening, is obviously disadvantageous regarding a Sacred energy side.

darkness horseman has a feeling of troops body, that nightmare warhorse, completely is back and forth interlinked with his regard, in his hand the heavy sword cuts, dazzling black flame can definitely burst out instantaneously, erupts the formidable energy fluctuation, black flame and horseman heavy sword dissolves as one, cuts to fall again outrageously.

Le Zhengyu back pair of wings opens, whole body white Battle Armor takes possession, the light of body falls unceasingly, is coordinating Trial of Light, initiates assault time and time again. But a that darkness horseman attack and defense body, a troops body, steadily like mountain. time no one how anyone. But from the Soul Power vigorous degree, obviously is darkness horseman wants on high to plan.

Xu Lizhi on the other hand is in the people idlest one, this time he, the body has also covered Battle Armor. His Battle Armor is white, but is different from Le Zhengyu white. Without Sacred aura, but seems actually very weighty, he is tall, after putting on Battle Armor, could not see obese, instead had a majestic feeling.

He stands side Xu Xiaoyan, looks like the Xu Xiaoyan faithful protector.

Both sides entered have entangled to fight the condition, but black-clothed person of distant place started to continue in the compartment to slaughter.

Tang Wulin and match dogfight, while is paying attention to audience Transformation. He looked at several, kept abreast of the distant place companion situation.

Cannot delay, delays again, on entire Soul Guidance Train several hundred Life completely will kill in the Evil Soul Master hand.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin face upwards to cry loud and long suddenly, „All-Out act !”

With this drinks greatly at the same time, his Battle Armor golden light (Jin Guang) puts greatly, the imposing manner of Tang Wulin whole person had Transformation instantaneously. His both feet falls to the ground, the whole person is common just like the palatial mountain.

In his torso part, brown-yellow ray of light bursts out. This ray of light outward release at the same time, that is maintaining has been telling to start attack Seven Rings Soul Saint Evil Soul Master to him to feel suddenly the body sinks, fell on the ground directly. But his pair of Sharp Claws grasps once more, when Tang Wulin front, actually felt terrifying instead shakes the strength to erupt, unexpectedly his hand claw of fluctuation raises directly backward.

This is...

The Tang Wulin right foot stamps, Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth!

Eight golden-colored little dragon(s) drill suddenly, the formidable impact just will be pulled to meet ground the whole body paralysis of Seven Rings Soul Saint Evil Soul Master fluctuation.

He also heard Tang Wulin that to drink greatly, in addition at this time sudden Transformation, his without hesitation once more stimulated own fifth Soul Skill, at the same time, Seventh Soul Ring also has shone.

In this flash, Tang Wulin knows finally this Evil Soul Master Martial Soul was anything.

A whole body is covering armor piece huge bat appear(ance) in front of Tang Wulin, Bloodsucking Bat! Is this Evil Soul Master Martial Soul, no wonder his speed such rapidness, can blood of Control human body. Originally his Martial Soul is related with blood.

However, even if has released seventh Soul Skill Bloodsucking Bat avatar, the huge suction that in the ground transmits enables it in first time to work loose.

Tang Wulin attack has actually launched. The Bloodsucking Bat whole body of Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth fluctuation is lacking in vigilance, but relies on the Martial Soul avatar formidable defense strength, he was only sluggish the moment must struggle is running out outward.

The brown-yellow ring of light suction that but, the Tang Wulin body releases was really too strong, his speed was limited in the certain extent.

In the Tang Wulin hand Golden Dragon Spear treats as whip to use, to drop from the clouds directly, pounds to fall downward. Meanwhile, in his mouth exudes one to roar, Golden Dragon Roars!

In eyes the purple electro-optic shoots, Purple Demon Eyes.

In an instant, Tang Wulin has all released Control kind of Soul Skill that own all can use.

Bloodsucking Bat does not have the means that can only make own change into one group of mist instantaneously, uses is separated from battlefield way (of life) that he has most excelled, wants to escape.

But spiritual frightening of Purple Demon Eyes makes his movement be half beat behind, is these half racket, has decided fight outcome.

golden figure together suddenly is quietly leaps since ground, Bind on him. Entrains his downward. Meanwhile, in he did not have to change into the instance before mist completely, Golden Dragon Spear pulls out finally strikes above his body.

Seven Rings Evil Soul Master called out pitifully, his Two Word Battle Armor exuded a series of to shatter sounds, stiffly was struck by pulling out in the ground.

The right foot of Tang Wulin lifts, but his body actually suddenly skyrockets, rises into airborne. Substituted for him formerly the position, changed into an incomparably huge body. second Soul Spirit, Tyrannosaurus!

Tyrannosaurus giant right foot without hesitation steps on outrageously falls, stepping on maliciously on that Seven Rings Soul Saint.

Must know that the Tyrannosaurus height has 60 meters, his body weight, even if a Tang Wulin 100,000 jin (0.5 kg) strength is impossible to shake.

Above most terrifying slaughtering as the earth, the might of Tyrannosaurus this foot, made the earth shiver directly, the distant place fell in ground Soul Guidance Train by fluctuation about rocked.

The Tang Wulin right hand toward compartment direction one finger, „golden speech (Jin Yu), goes!”

Formerly Bind changed into Evil Soul Master golden speech (Jin Yu) benefits the arrow together, black-clothed person overran toward these Three Rings cultivated.

Faint trace mist disperses to surroundings from the Tyrannosaurus under foot, is rapid toward the distant place escapes.

The nostril of Tyrannosaurus spouts steam, he has opened the mouth suddenly, scarlet-red flame has sprayed from his mouth.

Bloodsucking Bat Evil Soul Master this incarnation mist Soul Skill, what most is good at dodging is physical attack, but in the fog condition, the energy attack function will actually double in his effect.

In the pitiful yell sound, he had been spurted by that terrifying flame directly.

But also at this moment, flies to project innumerable small bat from that mist, toward flies in all directions. The Evil Soul Master maintaining life method emerges one after another incessantly.

------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#794: Great Angel's Anger

Tang Wulin cold snort, stands in the Tyrannosaurus top of the head, the right hand beats the own chest, immediately, formerly appear(ance) brown-yellow ring of light appear(ance), the huge gravity drops from the clouds once more, these small bat of suppression fall to the ground in abundance. Then, Blue Silver Emperor rise straight from the ground, changes into Blue Silver Thrusting Wave. Is ordinary just like the string candied fruit, the body penetration of that only bat.

Eliminate evil thoroughly! This point Tang Wulin can do unusual is good.

Tyrannosaurus turns around the personal appearance, directly soars another side battlefield to flush away. His that terrifying personal appearance, the giant sole, every step steps forward, is having the unequalled impact.

Since Tang Wulin has completed the burying bone in Dragon Valley, his Tyrannosaurus Soul Spirit does not know when can become the entity.

Said accurately that should when burying the bone process, Tang Wulin buries behind one already grows Wings Tyrannosaurus, his Tyrannosaurus Soul Spirit Devour that skeleton. Then falls into has been one year of deep sleep.

Once more appear(ance) time, Tang Wulin can summon to fight it directly.

But this is not does not need to pay the price, the price must consume Tang Wulin Soul Power. Moreover, consumption speed incredibly fast is incomparable. At the Tang Wulin present Soul Power intensity, Tyrannosaurus can only fight for a half minute for him.

However, in such battlefield, a half minute of time can decide the lots. Even is outcome in battlefield.

Seven Rings Soul Saint, in the Tyrannosaurus suddenly appear(ance) short several seconds, completely was solved by Tang Wulin.

While Tang Wulin shouted All-Out fight, his companion also erupted!

Yuan En Yehui face upwards to roar, body Fourth Soul Ring shines suddenly, her body contracts several points, but the a pair of arm actually becomes even more sturdy, in the hand Giant Hammer(s) rumbles, pounding stiffly flew front Skeleton Evil Soul Master.

Gigantic Demon Titan!

Yuan En Yehui jumps, a pair of Giant Hammer(s) launches, initiated madness attack to that Skeleton Evil Soul Master.

Another side, in the Ye Xinglan hand Star Divine Sword changes into the sword star rain, the innumerable sword tip(s) gables to that giant wolf Evil Soul Master, at the same time, on her Fifth Soul Ring shine.

Ye Xinglan eyes becomes radiant such as the stars generally is suddenly bright, in the hand Star Divine Sword to airborne one finger, her whole person vanished is in-situ.

In Sky suddenly became illusory the flash, a handle great sword as if cut Zhangkong to drop from the clouds generally. Crashes instantaneously! Points to that giant wolf Evil Soul Master.

giant wolf Evil Soul Master felt huge Life to be critical, Sixth Soul Ring shone, the body inflated once more, the upper body raises, raises head the long and loud cry. Shines one group behind him just like the bright moonlight corona, but this bright moonlight is actually blood-red.

Sixth Soul Skill, Blood Wolf Howls at the Moon!

Blood Wolf Howls at the Moon Soul Skill, can frighten by huge spiritual to the match simultaneously, stimulates own bloodline, erupts over three times of attack and defense ability.

What a pity, what he faces is Ye Xinglan, Peak Yu Jian Ye Xinglan.

In the Body and Sword Unity condition, Blood Wolf Howls at the Moon spiritual frightens unable to Ye Xinglan to have any influence.

Great sword of dropping from the clouds, chops to fly a that giant wolf Evil Soul Master sword directly. Formerly has protected One Word Battle Armor of his body to split a giant slit, was dug from the center, but also has left behind a huge scar of deep obvious bone on him.

This is under the protection of Blood Wolf Howls at the Moon Soul Skill, otherwise, the body of this giant wolf Evil Soul Master will be dug to become enlightened two halves directly.

Le Zhengyu god Holy Light glow restrains suddenly, but his whole person actually completely turned into golden-colored, back pair of wings also changes into golden-colored. In the hand Holy Sword is burning Sacred Flame. His whole person instant is becoming dedicated.

Fifth Soul Ring ray of light blooms, his white opens golden-colored trace halo circulations, that appear(ance) on Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting golden-colored Little Angel appear(ance) behind him. Suddenly integrates in his body quietly.

The Le Zhengyu body shakes, the back left a pair of wing, but this to the wing is actually illusory. Sacred aura that but on him erupts actually by geometrical multiple promotion.

Sky has shone in this flash suddenly, looked like has Sun to drill nighttime sky, the golden-colored light beam dropped from the clouds together, falls on Le Zhengyu. Long has Angel Light and Shadow of six wings also along with it appear(ance) in the upper air.

In the Le Zhengyu hand Holy Sword looks like a mirror of refraction, has approached that darkness horseman the huge golden-colored light beam refraction that drops from the clouds.

The nightmare warhorse under darkness horseman body sends out silent roars, black flame ascends, body complete coverage of darkness horseman. darkness horseman Sixth Soul Ring blooms. Both hands grip the great sword, the sudden horizontal sword, cut the head of own. The head fell, falls his waist, but his darkness aura actually instantaneously erupted the unequalled terrifying fluctuation.

The great sword wields horizontally, collides with Le Zhengyu fifth Soul Skill together.

Le Zhengyu fifth Soul Skill, Great Angel's Anger! Inspiring most pure light Sacred Power, sweeps clear all Evil.

But that darkness horseman sixth Soul Skill is actually terrifying horseman changes the body. Can geometrical multiple fighting strength of promotion own.

Both sides fought from formerly entangling almost change into Life and Death to spell instantaneously.

„Bang -” golden light (Jin Guang) suddenly to launch, blooms in the air just like the fireworks generally, Le Zhengyu received weakening of clown Evil Soul Master eventually. In that purple-black sword tip(s), his divided flying upside down.

But that darkness horseman does not feel better, cross under nightmare warhorse to shatter, changes into bones, is burning golden-colored flame. He, conducted Great Angel's Anger Holy Light to the own saddle horse with no other choice, on his own similarly was also contaminated by Holy Light, has to madness stimulation of movement Soul Power, with that Holy Light resistance.

Mutually wounded!

The eruption is not their Three Great Assault System Battle Soul Master that the human most shocks, but is Xu Xiaoyan.

Star Staff lifts up high above the top of the head, in the Xu Xiaoyan mouth muttered was talking over anything. Third Soul Ring Great Release of Rays of Light, in an instant, Starlight Radiance!

Stellar lines are centered on her body jumps to shoot, almost while Ye Xinglan, Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui erupt, that stellar lines accurate looking have surrounded their each Evil Soul Master.

Xu Xiaoyan formerly had not used community Power Control Soul Skill, is waiting for this opportunity. The Control match, is very unexpectedly important, first time was unexpectedly more important.

starlight looked like the eye was steadily ordinary, fell on neighbor each Evil Soul Master instantaneously. The Shrek Seven Monsters people coordinate the what kind tacit understanding! starlight glittering on Xu Xiaoyan, that radiant stellar lines just started appear(ance) the time, Le Zhengyu, Yuan En Yehui and the Ye Xinglan three people front line are first time make reaction, fends rapidly one side, made way attack passageway to starlight.

Xu Xiaoyan One Word Battle Armor is dark blue, above has point starlight to sparkle, looks like the nighttime sky and star. Her One Word Battle Armor name is the star!

Shrek Seven Monsters advocates Control Soul Master fighting strength to show in this moment completely. When that starlight accurate incomparable falling on Evil Soul Master, they looked like instantaneous freeze generally, all decided in same place motionless.

Like this good opportunity people able to let off?

Xie Xie four do several things at the same time also to flash through, in an instant, four cultivated for low Evil Soul Master is cut open the throat.

Yuan En Yehui jumps, dual hammers such as at top speed one after the other, pounding maliciously in Skeleton Evil Soul Master chest place. In clear break sound, Skeleton Evil Soul Master throws accordingly flies.

Le Zhengyu clenches the teeth, is suppressing own ill, in the hand the Holy Sword direction, together Trial of Light is almost the close engagement after the stellar lines, fell on incarnation terrifying horseman darkness horseman, his whole body that divided was been densely covered by the golden-colored electric light.

Ye Xinglan formerly just had used own fifth Soul Skill Stars Sword, at this time in the hand a Star Divine Sword finger, whole body Battle Armor starlight jumps shoots, incarnation one group of starlight suddenly to dodge, passed over gently and swiftly from giant wolf Evil Soul Master instantaneously, Sword Divine Star! Although is only first Soul Skill, but speed is quickest, under Battle Armor and Star Divine Sword amplification, the might is similarly out of the ordinary.

time, numerous Evil Soul Master almost simultaneously suffered the heavy losses.

Also with the aid of this opportunity, in Xu Lizhi hand Restoring Stuffed Meatbun accurate falling before people, making them only need to open mouth to bite. But Tang Wulin also draws support from this opportunity, rode Tyrannosaurus to clash.

Majestic Tyrannosaurus batters, Innate Body has not arrived, opens mouth, huge flame has emitted.

This Tyrannosaurus Soul Spirit and Tang Wulin regard is interlinked, flame spouts, just before one side, threatens Xie Xie their several Evil Soul Master to cover completely.

flame that Tyrannosaurus emits is really genuine Dragon Flame! As king of the most formidable land dragon, Tyrannosaurus individual fighting strength is not in fact worse than True Dragon, is even more fearful in the fields. When once the Tyrannosaurus transformation, grows Wings the time. Then, he was close Nine Great Dragon Kings that stage existence.

#795: Conquering the enemy

Blazing Dragon Flame has swept, stays behind has ashes. Dragon Clan Dragon Flame is not Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces fire element of inspiring outside, but is pregnant in own special flame, high of temperature, but must by far above Gu Yue initial blue flame Fireball(s).

Why bother, at the Tyrannosaurus Life intensity, flame that he emits one time in the magnitude is also extremely formidable!

Starlight Radiance can irreversible letting person stagnate for one second, is this second of time, has decided Life of countless person. The situation almost reverses instantaneously.

Xu Xiaoyan Control had not finished. golden-colored ring of light is almost in an instant on appear(ance), in that had been pounded under the Skeleton Evil Soul Master body that flies. He just restored from Starlight Radiance, feels the severe pain of body. The body by Star Wheel Ice Chain Bind, same place could not be being been moving.

Time that Yuan En Yehui beforehand dual hammers pounds, happen to pounds to fly in Tang Wulin here direction him. Because she saw at that time that Tang Wulin has solved the own match, is catching up toward here. Although their not too clear Tang Wulin this Tyrannosaurus is any ghost. But they have the absolute confidence to the Tang Wulin strength.

Therefore, when body of that Skeleton Evil Soul Master once more by anchorage, he helplessly saw that a colossus arrived in front of own.

The tail of Tyrannosaurus goes up, before a pair of , the claw draws in the front, an extremely sturdy both legs pad step, then jumped.

At its huge body, this jumps, seems unexpectedly a little gruff feeling, seemed not so ominously is severe the look.

But in the Skeleton Evil Soul Master eye reveals, is actually desperate!

Over 60 meters in height, the body majestic drops from the clouds just like the colossus of mountain.

The Skeleton Evil Soul Master height ten meters, were very huge. But ten meters high and 60 meters high, but compares from the volume, differed that is not six times, 60 times continued.

The Tyrannosaurus most terrifying place is his formidable incomparable body, finally can be imagined.

„!” In a series of skeleton break sound, Skeleton Evil Soul Master turned into one pile of fragment(s).

Yuan En Yehui dual hammers brandishes, looked for the Le Zhengyu opposite directly by darkness horseman that Trial of Light covered. Without doubt, the balance of victory inclined.

That hides on the following clown Evil Soul Master face reveals color of the shock, when Tyrannosaurus steps on has broken to pieces the Skeleton Evil Soul Master body, his slow curse falls on Tyrannosaurus.

Tyrannosaurus roars, the body shines dark-gold ray of light, slow invalid!

This is Tyrannosaurus talent ability, called: Overlord. All Control kind of Soul Skill fall on it, the effect of can playing by weakening of enormous degree. Although clown Evil Soul Master is Six Rings, but Life stage and Tyrannosaurus differed are too big. Therefore, his slow curse cannot play the least bit effect.

clown Evil Soul Master the release cursed, while turned around runs. Very obviously, he also saw that this situation is not wonderful. Lifts the hand, one group of yellow ray of light shoot up to the sky. Immediately, in Sky, fierce yellow Skeleton Light and Shadow blooms.

Tyrannosaurus Dragon Flame spouted, has covered the huge range. Blocked the clown Evil Soul Master way, in Sky golden light (Jin Guang) dodged. During next flickers, is panic-stricken clown Evil Soul Master, was pierced by that golden light (Jin Guang) directly, sews in the ground. Golden Dragon Spear that Tang Wulin ejects.

Tyrannosaurus summon time also arrived at this time, changes into Light and Shadow to integrate Tang Wulin within the body to vanish does not see. Tang Wulin wrist glittering in nine color chain bracelet ray of light slight(ly), above that Crystallized Body halo circulation, has appeared specially beautiful during the night.

Tang Wulin vertical leaps to forward, directly soars the Golden Dragon Spear direction to fall, when his hand grasps Golden Dragon Spear that flash, the clown body that then ran throughout by dragon spear trembles, the body of whole person withers rapidly, changed into a dry corpse. Tang Wulin only thinks from Golden Dragon Spear transmits pure Life to inject into within the body. Too is not strong, at least and clown Evil Soul Master Six Rings cultivates for some are not proportional.

He gawked to understand slightly that this Evil Soul Master Life can not strong and its Evil ability has certainly the close relation. Evil Soul Master Life energy will be quite perhaps weak. However, Golden Dragon Spear the place of ruling by force can also be inferred.

Looks up the yellow Skeleton fireworks that airborne had not diverged as before, the Tang Wulin brow slightly wrinkle. Actually this is the retreating signal, is the requesting reinforcements signal?

If the latter, perhaps also has the trouble.

Train goes off track, nearby city obtained certainly the news, but when does not know the rescue groups of Federation government to be able.

Skeleton Evil Soul Master and clown Evil Soul Master Fallen, about the strength of people, other these Evil Soul Master Elite also fast was solved successively. Has Xu Xiaoyan Power Control, these Evil Soul Master want to run cannot be inescapable.

The distant place, golden speech (Jin Yu) fled rapidly, these massacred black-clothed person of passenger to be killed by it.

golden speech (Jin Yu) now seemed a little likely is not a snake, the height has exceeded seven meters, Can golden-colored, the forehead two bulge places were all over the body obvious, the hypogastric gives birth to a pair of former claw, sharp Sharp Claws grasped in the ground, can let it quicker migration. The a pair of shining eye pupil when looks at Tang Wulin to send out gentle ray of light, but looks at to other things time, always indifferent appearance.

It is Tang Wulin first Soul Spirit, the Bind skill and Blue Silver Thrusting Wave is it entrusts with Tang Wulin, therefore, these two Soul Skill its own can also use. The body intensity obtains moistening of Golden Dragon King bloodline, had to melt the flavor of dragon more and more.

Soul Spirit will have possibility of growth, but generally speaking, the growth of Soul Spirit is mainly depends upon in Spirit Raising Platform absorb Spiritual Power. But golden speech (Jin Yu) absorb not only obviously Spiritual Power, what are more is came from Tang Wulin the strength of Qi and Blood.

Golden Dragon King Seal each unties, it will follow is evolving together, Tang Wulin in the Dragon Valley three years, absorb these dragon spirit(s) also similarly has the huge advantage. dragon bone(s) that although obtains with Tyrannosaurus also missed, but its evolution actually continued. Gets down according to this speed, one day it can incarnation True Dragon.

„Walks, we quickly save others. Does not know that Evil Soul Master sends out requesting reinforcements signal. We hope that the Federation aspect can select and assign the human to come quickly.”

„First saved others says again.” Ye Xinglan frown said.

Regardless of Evil Soul Master does have the reinforcements, they now are impossible such to leave. In Train had been killed did not know many passengers, but also has more passengers to need to save the sick and wounded.

The people are not good at treating, but Xu Lizhi Restoring Stuffed Meatbun actually at least can help the injured person enhance the treated and cured opportunity.

Tang Wulin said to Xu Lizhi: „Reason, your third, fourth and fifth Soul Skill Steamed Stuffed Bun gives us respectively one. In order to avoid there is Evil Soul Master reinforcements appear(ance) without enough time.”

„Good!” Xu Lizhi complies with one, starts to recite the incantation.

Steamed Stuffed Bun distinguished appear(ance), the people hurries to receive. The amplifications of some Battle Armor to Soul Power, the Xu Lizhi overall Soul Power vigorous degree, is in all people strongest one.

manufacture Steamed Stuffed Bun, people while fires into the compartment fast.

In the life-saving, Tang Wulin appeared his exceptional superiority, Blue Silver Emperor Martial Soul has displayed, one with just liked with huge Vine the python emerges in the compartment generally. They can be the hoisting jacks, opens compressed spatial, can be the stretcher, careful leads wounded. Under Tang Wulin Spirit Abyss Realm Spiritual Strength Control, life-saving speed is quickest.

Other people follow simply side him, by Blue Silver Emperor the wounded who leads from the compartment, they carry on some urgent treatments, Xu Lizhi give borderland Restoring Stuffed Meatbun again. Is stabilizing the condition of wounded.

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#796: Powerful enemies

The front several compartments did not have the opportunity of treatment, was killed by Evil Soul Master. But they have routed Evil Soul Master luckily, in behind more compartments, although the casualty rate is very as before big, but also over one-third people live, the severely injured are many, some injury light people after are living in the mood stably, starts to help noble spirit of saving the sick and wounded. All in develop finally toward a good direction.

One seems the middle-aged person of doctor runs up to side Tang Wulin, „hello, Thank You (xiexie) you have saved everybody. Has the news, when will have the rescue groups to rush, many stretcher patients cannot delay, stretcher patient who particularly internal organ(s) damages, delaying a while, the probability of rescue will be always lower.”

Tang Wulin frown said: „I have not had communications device, has no way to contact nearby city, where I do not even know now us.”

Middle-aged person slightly somewhat disappointed [say / way]: „That did not have the means that can only wait. But all Soul Guidance Train have the Localization system, will have an accident is certainly known by first time. This place happen to two cities, the rescue troops should need certain time to catch up. Now can only be completely the human affairs, listens to the destiny. I saved others first. Makes some simple treatment in one's power. If you discover to have the first-aid packet on vehicle and so on, helping me bring, will have very big help.”

„Good, was laborious you.” Tang Wulin nodded.

Xu Xiaoyan squats on the ground, a careful gang wounded dresses the wound on good arm, supple sound track: „All right, you are all right, but the arm bone broke, I helped you do fixedly, do not move, such peaceful was lying down, a while rescue groups arrived, sent you to the hospital.”

What was treated and cured by her is an old man, although old man because of ache, but some complexion pale white, but actually appears very tranquil, „Thank You (xiexie) your young miss, you simply like Angel. Thank You (xiexie) you have defeated these cruel scoundrels. Can tell me you to come from where?”

Xu Xiaoyan shows a faint smile, „we are the Shrek Academy students.”

The old men have gawked staring, „Shrek Academy? No wonder.”

Xu Xiaoyan comforts him saying: „Has been all right, you are lying down here, I help other people.” At the same time was saying, she smiles to old man, stands up to run to another wounded.

Sees her form, old man brow slightly pressed, sighed one lightly, „was really a good miss. Shrek, worthily is Continent first Academy. Besides the strength, made one feel moral behavior that was hard to hope to attain.”

In this time, suddenly, old man pupil fierce enlargement, sad and shrill yelled: „Miss, be careful!”

The purple-black shadow, together when does not know, being quietly to Xu Xiaoyan behind. Like lightning punctures to her back of the body place.

This gets down was really too sudden, suddenly arrived at all people unable reaction to come.

But of old man drinks severely, obviously played the role.

Xu Xiaoyan combat experience is rich, is hearing the sounds/voices flash of old man, the whole person forward falls down. Moreover, her Battle Armor has been dressing, has not taken back. Is feared that also has the possibility appear(ance) enemy anytime.

purple-black ray of light almost pasted her back to pass over gently and swiftly, Xu Xiaoyan stuffy snort, the whole person is flown, hit directly in a not far away Train compartment that ray of light led rebounds to return again.

On dark blue Battle Armor point starlight blooms, as far as possible melts that is striking. But attack of enemy was too strong, the position of her Battle Armor back was ripped open a big opening, but luckily was Battle Armor has also blocked overwhelming majority assault, Xu Xiaoyan thought that body one cold, hurried to stimulate to movement Soul Power, simultaneously heart with amazement.

Here suddenly appear(ance) Transformation, other Shrek Seven Monsters people immediately on reaction.

„Xiaoyan!” Le Zhengyu roared, back pair of wings All-Out flapped, the Second Soul Ring sparkle, Holy Sword released, almost moved sideways to keep off in front of Xu Xiaoyan.

purple-black ray of light freeze, the form also reappears together from darkness along with it.

That is a complexion extremely pale white middle-aged person, his eyes is dark-purple, looks at Le Zhengyu, [say / way] that lets somebody cool off or calm down: Person who „was you have killed my? You must die!”

This person does not have Battle Armor, but actually gives people extremely gloomy aura.

Le Zhengyu no matter front is, when he looks helplessly Xu Xiaoyan by this person instant, his flickers only thought that the heart of own strikes to fly must jump from the chest cavity.

eyes golden light (Jin Guang) jumps shoots, back pair of wings launches, Fourth Soul Ring lightens instantaneously, whole person aura selects for promotion by the geometrical multiple, Angel Descends!

Void one step steps forward, Holy Sword cuts like lightning to that middle-aged person.

purple-black halo ripples from the middle-aged person, entire Eight Soul Rings, does not have the omen reappears from him.

Three purple five black! Eight Soul Rings is complementing his body. Facing Le Zhengyu Holy Sword, he does not dodge unexpectedly does not evade. Whatever Holy Sword cuts.

When Holy Sword brings blazing Holy Light flame to cut into that purple-black halo instant, Le Zhengyu only thought that own sword light as if cut into muddy Marsh, is unable to penetrate the half minute again. Those who make him shock, Holy Sword cuts into purple-black ray of light that part to be polluted by that purple-black unexpectedly instantaneously, Holy Light by Devour, was being melted rapidly.

This is...

Le Zhengyu is surprised.

[Say / Way] that the middle-aged people let somebody cool off or calm down: „Most repugnant Sacred aura.” At the same time was saying, he waves to Le Zhengyu, purple-black ray of light flings together, directly soars his draw off.

At this time, Shrek Seven Monsters experience has appeared. Facing attack of middle-aged person, Le Zhengyu not startled, treadons the Ghost Shadow Perplexing Track step, retreat, the body just like illusory Light and Shadow, in the hand Holy Sword lets loose like lightning instantaneously, not having the least bit not to abandon. Meanwhile Sacred Light puts greatly, Holy Light shines on own together directly.

Fast reaction made him avoid that purple-black ray of light frontage, but was brought a point, Holy Light and protection light of Battle Armor release covered has blocked that purple-black ray of light reluctantly, but Le Zhengyu felt that purple-black was spreading to the body of own. Can pollute including Soul Power?

Along with it transmitting, his body was led revolving to fly vigorously horizontally.

But also at this moment, big hand appear(ance) behind him, baseless, pulled down him. Meanwhile, a pair of Giant Hammer(s) behind flies high to fall from that middle-aged person. Directly soars his overhead to pound.

The middle-aged person corners of the mouth place reveals one to disdain, suddenly, both hands hold the day, in the eye the purple light jumps shoots, Third Soul Ring sparkle.

One group of intense purple light erupt suddenly. From inside to outside, looks like bomb that explodes, radiates to all around.

Tang Wulin just lagged behind Le Zhengyu, immediately shouted one not to be good darkly.

Yuan En Yehui dual hammers pounds to fall, receives that purple light assault, was flown by the instantaneous ball by her strength unexpectedly. Personal appearance of Xie Xie concealment also has to instantaneous High-speed retreat.

Ye Xinglan sword tip(s) flashes through together, similarly was shot to fly, what is more fearful, so long as is that purple light contacts, will be contaminated by purple rapidly, even if their All-Out stimulates to movement Soul Power, is unable to throw away that purple.

That purple ray of light has filled ice-cold with Evil aura, but also has the terrifying corrosiveness. Yuan En Yehui that is so huge to Giant Hammer(s), pounds the part on purple light to start to melt unexpectedly. Stimulates to movement the Soul Power resistance, can only be makes the ablation speed reduce.

Le Zhengyu turns round, rushed to side Xu Xiaoyan, hugs her, flaps pair of wings, flies away like lightning.

Tang Wulin has not drawn back, at this time, as team Nucleus, as the Shrek Seven Monsters Soul character, he must strive for time to companion, let alone, in ground also some that many wounded.

A spirited dragon roar sound resounds from him, Tang Wulin grasps Golden Dragon Spear, whole body Battle Armor golden light (Jin Guang) blooms. Directly soars the purple light cover that expands to puncture.

Before appear(ance) brown-yellow halo bloomed from his chest place once more, making the earth sink, in the meantime, Blue Silver Emperor swarmed, Bind was occupied by that famous wounded in abundance, flung to fly in a direction them.

At this time could not attend to many, maintained life is most important.

The distant place, Xu Lizhi both hands, with Tang Sect secret arts Controlling Crane Capturing Dragon, catches the wounded who Tang Wulin flings.

Golden Dragon Spear pricks the purple light, Tang Wulin first also felt that has been similar to the Marsh common mud feeling. That purple light without a single exception follows Golden Dragon Spear to spread, wants to pollute the corrosion it.

At this moment, Golden Dragon Spear pricks the purple light to cover the part to reappear suddenly diamond-shaped golden-colored dragon scales light pattern, golden light (Jin Guang) puts greatly, in the dragon roar sound, works loose that purple light outrageously. Golden-colored Dragon Head reappears in the lance point place, is Golden Dragon Shocks the Heavens , directly soars that middle-aged person, when the chest hits.

Moreover, Tang Wulin drinks greatly, Golden Dragon Roars!

-------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#797: Ten Thousand Years Deep Turtle

The formidable voice is mixing Spiritual Strength as well as the Golden Dragon King dragon power eruption.

The middle-aged person stares slightly, the purple light that releases covers immediately one slow.

Reappears at the same time the purple only shield in his front, that only shield presents is the carapace appearance, impressively is a purple-black turtle, has blocked Golden Dragon Shocks the Heavens assault with the shell.

Does Soul Spirit protect the body?

In Tang Wulin heart one startled, he felt that transmits vigorously, hits to the body of own.

Tang Wulin strength is astonishing, although cultivates to be by far inferior in the match, but his body intensity is also the superelevation. The Golden Dragon Tyrant Body release, whole body scales and Battle Armor all changed into the mirror surface shape, Golden Dragon Spear can resist the pollution that purple light covered to make his confidence increase. Is relying on own strength and Battle Armor and Soul Skill, must shoulder opposite party assault hardly.

As a result of his resisting, has given own Blue Silver Emperor enough time finally, has flung nearby wounded, makes companion have time retreat.

But the next quarter, the absolute strength disparity has appeared.

Tang Wulin only thought that chest one stuffy, own hit flew, the strength of strong Golden Dragon King Qi and Blood weakens rapidly, he discovered with amazement, although the purple light of opposite party cannot pollute own, but actually needs own the strength of Qi and Blood to carry on the counter-balance, can not be corroded. Just contacted this flash, Tang Wulin felt that own the strength of Qi and Blood received not small assault.

The middle-aged people let somebody cool off or calm down looks to Tang Wulin, „a little meaning.” The right hand extends, that only purple turtle falls in his palm. The turtle is not big, diameter about one foot, purple-black, has the eye of a pair of white all over the body, in the eye pupil that white and shines has filled cold and gloomy aura.

„Deep Turtle!” Xie Xie loses one's voice startled.

Deep Turtle, very rare Soul Beast, only lives in the gloomiest cold and gloomy place, absorb Negative Energy is to live. The growth of Deep Turtle is slow, just when the birth Deep Turtle height be was only less than one inch, each Thousand Years can length one inch, in other words, Deep Turtle on this middle-aged manpower, have Ten-thousand Years to cultivate fully is.

The Deep Turtle most formidable place, is it can the air/Qi of refining Extreme Yin, if meets Soul Master that Martial Soul agrees with, big of its amplification function, even can let the Martial Soul directed evolution.

Let alone Ten-thousand Years, even if Thousand Years cultivates for Deep Turtle is extremely difficult homing existence. This Evil Soul Master can have Ten-thousand Years Deep Turtle to take Soul Spirit, the great strength of its strength, it can be imagined.

Eight Rings Soul Douluo rank Elite, has not dressed Battle Armor to make Tang Wulin they somewhat be hard to resist. Although only then a person, but formerly all Evil Soul Master added that was inferior that his threat is big.

Le Zhengyu is holding Xu Xiaoyan, looks to her Battle Armor ripped open place. Luckily, Battle Armor has blocked overwhelming majority attack, but after Xu Xiaoyan carries on the back, piece of purple-black is spreading slowly, Xu Xiaoyan eyes shuts tightly, All-Out stimulates to movement Soul Power, can limit this piece of purple-black in certain range.

„Negative Energy enters the body, must relieve immediately. Once otherwise entered main meridians to be big on trouble.” Xie Xie to Le Zhengyu rapid saying.

Tang Wulin moves sideways to arrive at side your Xu Xiaoyan, right hand Golden Dragon Claw empty according to above her sores, the strong Golden Dragon King bloodline beginning to accrue interest surge release, fills firm bloodline aura to drill into under the Xu Xiaoyan skin, melts that purple-black rapidly.

Golden Dragon King bloodline, to positive just, to pure to positive! Deep Turtle is strong, cannot compare with Golden Dragon King bloodline stage. That Evil Soul Master cultivate to profound, practices extremely pure air/Qi of Jihai day of the tenth lunar month, this makes Tang Wulin be hard to resist. If both sides cultivate for in the same level line, Tang Wulin naturally must compared with him.

Xu Xiaoyan opens eyes, hit to tremble smartly spirit, „quite cold!”

Le Zhengyu hurries to enclasp her, „how is it? Many?”

„Was all right!” Xu Xiaoyan shakes the head to him.

At this time, the Shrek Seven Monsters seven people besides Xu Lizhi, all gathered here.

Tang Wulin lifted the hand to squeeze in the own mouth to eat two Steamed Stuffed Bun, Xu Lizhi third Soul Skill, Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun, the fourth Soul Skill Puncture fork gets a swelled head!

Not only he, Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan respectively has also eaten up these two Steamed Stuffed Bun. Three people stand in the front line, looks out the match.

Yuan En Yehui a pair of Great Hammer was corroded 1/10, that Negative Energy diverges. Obviously its might.

That black-clothed person as if interesting visits them, „no wonder can kill my person. You somewhat are truly different from ordinary Soul Master. Interesting, but, you believe that depends on you to prevent me?”

His words spoke of here, suddenly, the eyebrow selected, mutters the tunnel: „Comes is very quick, such being the case, can only fight a battle to force a quick decision.”

At the same time was saying, his pair of purple eye pupil ray of light greatly is suddenly bright, the back purple light ascension, changes into the giant ghost. aura suddenly to increase who sends out from him. purple-black armor reappear from him.

purple-black armor piece filled was gloomy and cold and gloomy, what stranger was, his breastplate front had the oval scoop channel, the middle-aged person backhands presses, that Deep Turtle according to entering in scoop channel. Immediately, the color of Deep Turtle whole body became profounder, unexpectedly with his Battle Armor unified whole.

Back, the a pair of giant wing opens, this is the Two Word Battle Armor characteristics. But is very obvious, what this middle-aged person puts on is not Two Word Battle Armor.

demon mark reappear from Battle Armor, the under foot also along with it appear(ance) diameter three meters purple-black ring of light, the ring of light addendum circle presented the thorn shape, the interior is the complex demon mark constitutions, most central is a ghosts and demons shape.

Martial Soul projection, Domain Aura, Three Word Battle Armor!

Is representing Two Word Battle Armor like Wings, Domain Aura is representing Three Word Battle Armor!

Three Word Battle Armor brings Domain special effect, moreover absolutely is Domain that and Soul Master itself agrees with extremely. In this Domain, Soul Master fighting strength at least can promote one time.

Eight Rings cultivates is, Three Word Battle Armor! This can shake hardly does not put on the Battle Armor Super Rank Douluo stage strength!

The look on Shrek Seven Monsters people face becomes ugly!

Domain mighty energy that the terrifying pressure that Three Word Battle Armor brings, that momentarily possibly blooms particularly, the Tang Wulin six people of oppression have the feeling of not gasping for breath. Even if Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun started to play role, but stage of both sides differed is really too far.

Tang Wulin bites the tip of tongue, steps forward forward one step. On the face the look sinks to congeal, „Yuan En, Fallen Angel! Xiaoyan, Star-time Chains!”

In has in front of Super Rank Douluo stage Elite, wants to run away radically is impossible. But can listen from just thinking aloud of that Evil Soul Master, the reinforcements should not be far. This is their only vitalities, so long as insists that may live.

In a Tang Wulin horizontal hand Golden Dragon Spear, four golden-colored ring of light ray of light bloom. He was unable to summon Tyrannosaurus at this time again, otherwise, can certainly insist longer time. But is Captain, he must keep off in the dead ahead. Protects own companion.

Xu Xiaoyan was relieved the air/Qi of Extreme Yin by Tang Wulin, although the consumption is not small, but displays Soul Skill is without question. Also eats up Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun rapidly, simultaneously has lightened own fourth Soul Skill.

illusory as if the chains series that becomes by stars condense on everyone, dissolves them as one.

Star-time Chains, Shared Life! attack that they withstand, will all share on everyone. On Xu Lizhi of distant place, has connected Star-time Chains.

They each other can feel heartbeat, can feel each other condition, the regard is interlinked.

Le Zhengyu grabbed the hand of Xu Xiaoyan subconsciously, Xu Xiaoyan has struggled gently, but Le Zhengyu actually grasped was very tight, said that anything is not willing to let loose.

In just, him thinks that own must lose Xu Xiaoyan, luckily, Xu Xiaoyan has shouldered. He is not willing to let loose her.

„Kills you, does not have what difference with being run over and dying ant!” Saying that Evil Soul Master lets somebody cool off or calm down. Back pair of wings flaps, the right hand in airborne empty grasps, immediately, a huge purple-black big hand, directly soars the dead ahead the Tang Wulin overhead to grasp. Meanwhile, spreads in his Battle Armor Domain Aura instantaneously, one completely covers Shrek Seven Monsters.

In the Tang Wulin heart the secret passage is not good, this Evil Soul Master has not despised them because of the strength disparity of both sides, inspires Domain Aura, must strike to kill them in shortest time.

Did not have the means! Cannot his Domain to cover all. Otherwise, in his Domain, own and companion can only be whatever butchers.

Tang Wulin fourth golden-colored ring of light Great Release of Rays of Light, a golden-colored aperture along with it appear(ance) in his, the outward diffusion to the diameter five meters, covers in which Shrek Seven Monsters suddenly completely. At this time, Xu Lizhi receives lead of Star-time Chains, converged rapidly.

-----------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued..)

#798: Extreme Yin

In the golden-colored aperture, Mighty Dragon coils around faintly, the people only thought that strength of the strong Qi and Blood drills into own within the body instantaneously. The spirited dragon roar sound reverberates in the ear.

The body of Tang Wulin rises suddenly against the wind, raises to about three meters directly, Qi and Blood fluctuation also in instantaneously suddenly to increase, but, his a pair of eye pupil no longer is golden-colored, but turned into scarlet golden-colored. aura by the promotion of geometrical multiple madness.

fourth bloodline Soul Ring technique, Golden Dragon Frantic Domain.

Golden Dragon King Seal broke through the fourth level, Tang Wulin had this ability. But he never has also used beside dragon bone(s).

Golden Dragon Frantic Domain, can let his own Golden Dragon King bloodline rioting, enters the crazy condition instantaneously. Meanwhile, in the Domain range all allied forces will obtain the Golden Dragon King bloodline addition, attack and defense enjoy his own one-third promotion. In Tang Wulin in Golden Dragon Frantic, strength, defense and attack, can suddenly to increase one time.

Raises with the body to three meters, Tang Wulin scales becomes weighty, was affected, the dragon scales design that on One Word Battle Armor reappeared turned into weighty dragon scales to cover completely, had to plant his own dragon scales counter- volume unexpectedly Battle Armor gable feeling.

His own aura also along with the it rapid elevation, Tang Wulin at this time looks like consciousness Ferocious Beast to the feeling of person, Golden Dragon Spear obtains his bloodthirsty and intense bloodline energy support after Frantic dual amplification, [gold/metal] puts greatly, moreover mysterious raises to increase with his personal appearance.

„Raising” third ring of light shines, the spirited dragon roar sound erupts, front Evil Soul Master Battle Armor ring of light Domain arrival of formidable Qi and Blood fluctuation assault slow a racket. Next flickers, the Tang Wulin whole person changed into golden light (Jin Guang) to hit together.

Golden Dragon Soars!

Takes Golden Dragon Spear as sharply , to promote by Golden Dragon Soars, his without hesitation goes to the opposite party Domain hit directly.

At this time cannot have retreat of least bit, once fell into the opposite party Battle Armor Domain Aura Control range completely, that completely was the world of opposite party.

Cold and gloomy aura heads on, that is Extreme Yin the cold air/Qi, although Tang Wulin has not known that Martial Soul of match is anything, but can Negative Energy refining so pure, even if in the Evil Soul Master world, it is estimated that at present this is also the character of non- common component.

But this time he, seems like burning Sun, combustion is not flame, but is Qi and Blood. That strong Golden Dragon King Qi and Blood front Negative Energy will dispel actually, Golden Dragon Spear goes just like the golden-colored direct impact opposite party front together like lightning.

On the Evil Soul Master face reveals one to be astonished, how he will unable to see that Tang Wulin is only Five Rings Soul King stage cultivates is! Five Rings One Word Battle Armor Master, can actually dispel own the air/Qi of Extreme Yin, moreover made own feel the threat, this was the unprecedented situation.

But Evil Soul Master will therefore not be obviously startled, saw that Tang Wulin breaks in the own that only purple-black big hand, on the face cannot help but reveals one to sneer.

But next quarter his sneering on condense, because his surprised seeing, center that purple-black big hand that in own releases, appear(ance) a golden-colored eyelet of vortex shape, that golden-colored vortex has increased rapidly, twisted to break to pieces that only purple-black big hand of own unexpectedly actually. golden light (Jin Guang) dodges to pass, arrived at his front directly.

Evil Soul Master reaction is quick, the right hand wields like lightning, strikes side Golden Dragon Spear. When his palm and flash of Golden Dragon Spear contact, suddenly, his whole body trembled.

This and cultivates for irrelevant, completely is the suppression on bloodline. Tang Wulin Soul Power promotes stage every time, his own Golden Dragon King bloodline aura will also strengthen, can better and own Qi and Blood fuses, making Golden Dragon King aura stronger.

Can become Shrek Seven Monsters Captain, what Tang Wulin relies on is the absolute strength. Moreover, his Golden Dragon King bloodline also follows the itself intensity to increase, making his fight way (of life) also more and more develop in the powerful suppression direction.

Golden Dragon King bloodline to Yang Zhigang the restraint of aura enormous degree the air/Qi of that Extreme Yin, held in the Golden Dragon Frantic Domain in addition, although other Shrek Seven Monsters people felt as before the whole body is cold and gloomy, but is also insufficient to come up to be corroded.

If this traded has repaired to weakly also not have the situation of Golden Dragon Frantic amplification, once entered this Three Word Battle Armor Evil Soul Master Battle Armor Domain Aura, by the Negative Energy corrosion, quick will be changed into the bloody water.

golden-colored Star Wheel Ice Chain are quietly raises from the Evil Soul Master under foot, the Xu Xiaoyan Control Soul Skill most formidable absolute establishment nature burst out most formidable mighty energy instantaneously. Right hand instantaneous stagnation that Evil Soul Master wields in midair. Is grasping opportunity, Xu Xiaoyan deserves absolutely.

In the Tang Wulin hand Golden Dragon Spear almost passes through from that Evil Soul Master fingertip, Qi and Blood shocks with Star Wheel Ice Chain establishes absolutely is almost simultaneously appear(ance). Next quarter, Golden Dragon Spear on thorn maliciously in his chest place, body of that only Deep Turtle.

purple-black Three Word Battle Armor instantaneous Great Release of Rays of Light, the Guard Screen stress lives, this is Battle Armor most normal stress reaction. But sends out from Three Word Battle Armor, mighty energy, but is not One Word Battle Armor can compare.

To cold air/Qi instantaneously flying upside down of Tang Wulin hit, appear(ance) that but, a hole as before is actually quietly has carried on the back in Deep Turtle, glittering light golden-colored.

Tang Wulin feels obviously that transmits cool air current from Golden Dragon Spear. The Life strength, that is the Deep Turtle Life strength.

Golden Dragon Spear brings properties to destroy the hardest defenses played effect at crucial moments, the eruption of Guard Screen cannot shake Golden Dragon Spear directly flies, made him leave a trace on that Deep Turtle eventually. Although that is only Soul Spirit, but this stage Soul Spirit already is Soul Master part.

Tang Wulin is very clear, takes cultivation of own as, the Golden Dragon Spear might is impossible to display completely, destroys the hardest defenses special effect is also so. Therefore he has not chosen other Evil Soul Master critical positions, because that has the Three Word Battle Armor protection, he does not think that own attack can break through Three Word Battle Armor. But that Deep Turtle is in itself more like Evil Soul Master Soul Power Nucleus, defense should be inferior to Battle Armor itself, therefore he has chosen in this direction attack.

„You dare!” Evil Soul Master angry sounds/voices along with it resounding, Tang Wulin has not seen clearly to have anything, felt that the body of own was selected by cloudy and cold energy together directly, the body of flying upside down accelerates suddenly, hits directly to companion.

But at this time, Star-time Chains special effect has appeared, Shrek Seven Monsters seven people of Battle Armor are ray of light glittering, withstands assault that this has struck together.

Seven people simultaneously exude one stuffily, but melts strength that this has struck eventually. Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu simultaneously caught the body of Tang Wulin in behind, melted his assault strength.

„Extreme Yin Domain!” Evil Soul Master cold and gloomy sounds/voices resounds through the audience.

Tang Wulin and his companion only thought that surroundings all become viscous, his Golden Dragon Frantic Domain is similar to the air/Qi of turbulent mighty waves general terrifying Extreme Yin oppresses instantaneously. purple-black ray of light raises from the ground together suddenly, covers Xu Xiaoyan.

That is richer than Evil Soul Master Battle Armor Domain Aura the air/Qi of ten times of fearful Extreme Yin. Moreover, when its appear(ance) instance, has shut off Star-time Chains that extends from Xu Xiaoyan unexpectedly directly.

This situation people or first time meet, although Star-time Chains is also starlike image class Soul Skill, but its absolute establishment nature manifests, once displays can with companion link, and very firm. But this firm is not cannot be broken.

----------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( ~^~)

#799: Reinforcements, Sacrifice

Very obviously, Evil Soul Master has felt, in Shrek Seven Monsters, to he threatens in a big way cannot frontage assault Tang Wulin, but from establishes the natural in Xu Xiaoyan that absolutely Control. If no that Control, just Tang Wulin possibly did injure has resulted in his Deep Turtle?

Therefore, he used own sixth Soul Skill, the goal must solve Xu Xiaoyan first.

That Extreme Yin Domain just likes a coffin is ordinary, covers the body of Xu Xiaoyan completely. Golden Dragon King aura that Golden Dragon Frantic Domain produces is consuming rapidly. Almost is only during several breath, Xu Xiaoyan defense will be broken. At that time, in Extreme Yin Domain, she is her Battle Armor, will be melted directly.

„Xiaoyan!” Le Zhengyu said one, a back pair of wings fierce racket. Almost does not have the half minute to hesitate, outrageously broke in that Extreme Yin Domain.

Extreme Yin Domain individual attack strength strong, moreover is in itself also strong Control kind of Soul Skill. Otherwise will not be elected to be own sixth Soul Skill by Evil Soul Master, its only issue, is the attack range is small, can only a attack person. But is actually he strongest single body Soul Skill, he is first time saw, daring that some people like a moth to the flame breaks in own Extreme Yin Domain directly.

Bunch of pure white Sacred Flame almost same time lights from Le Zhengyu. Is burning that Sacred Flame, impressively is his back a pair of wing.

That pure white flame seems gentle and warm, to feeling that the human one type warm-hearted comforts. Le Zhengyu breaks in Extreme Yin Domain, the back burns the wing of flame to close up inward, protects Xu Xiaoyan completely during the bosom of own.

Mysterious appear(ance), by the Extreme Yin Domain that formidable attack strength, unexpectedly was unable to pollute that flame, kept off outside actually.

„Sacrifice! Holy Angel Family!” Evil Soul Master cold snort, but many carries over the flavor that several points dreaded in sounds/voices.

Sacrifice? Other Shrek Seven Monsters several people heard this name to stare.

Also at this time, the distant place, severe roar came, that Evil Soul Master complexion slightly changed, revealed one to dread, let somebody cool off or calm down looked at Tang Wulin their eyes, the personal appearance has been hidden suddenly.

In Tang Wulin their All-Out defense, protects Xu Xiaoyan and Le Zhengyu, prepares greets severely attacks time. Disappearance that Evil Soul Master actually disappears from the scene.

„Well, Sacrifice?” Airborne suddenly resounds surprised sounds/voices. The air as if baseless had been ripped open, the silvery-white form falls together baseless.

silvery-white pair of wings launches, leads his body to descend slowly, the under foot, silver ring of light ray of light blooms.

Three Word Battle Armor Master! Also is Three Word Battle Armor Master. But without a doubt, light aura that releases from him can feel that this definitely is not Evil Soul Master.

The head has helmet, on the face has mask, cannot see the look. This person of silver light dodges, a handle silver little hammer departs, flies sky over Extreme Yin Domain. Radiant silver light bloom, take shape a series of mirror surface general shapes. „Whiz”, Extreme Yin Domain vanished under the reflection of that mirror surface.

This is......

Is burning white flame restraining, Le Zhengyu actually as before tight is hugging Xu Xiaoyan.

„Sorry, Xiaoyan.” Le Zhengyu said in the Xu Xiaoyan ear in a soft voice such, then slowly fell in him softly.

The Tang Wulin body contraction, has taken back Golden Dragon Frantic Domain. To that silver armor Three Word Battle Armor Master respectful [say / way]: „Thank You (xiexie) your rescue, are you?”

On that Three Word Battle Armor Master silver light glittering, each Battle Armor likely turned into the mirror surface, under strange shine, drilled into his body to vanish quietly does not see, has revealed him the true self.

He is a handsome middle-aged person, seems the 30-year-old appearance, a blue short hair appears very spiritual. eyes is fiery, what stranger is, his eye pupil unexpectedly is silver.

„I am Federation War God Temple Preparatory War God Luo Shaofeng, you are very good. Actually can block Zun Fang to be so long.” Luo Shaofeng somewhat surprised looks on front these to dress the One Word Battle Armor young people.

Tang Wulin somewhat anxious [say / way]: „older generation(s), whether to help us have a look at my companion first, he......” was saying at the same time, his been careful receives Le Zhengyu from the Xu Xiaoyan hand.

Luo Shaofeng beckons with the hand, said: „He is all right. So long as Holy Angel Family Sacrifice is Sacrifice flame has not extinguished, oneself will not be injured.”

Xu Xiaoyan at this time appears some delay, she was unable to restore from formerly feeling.

When Extreme Yin Domain falls on her, and has shut off all Star-time Chains time, her first reaction ended. At that time, she only thought that extremely cloudy and cold aura from welled up in all directions, own is unable the move half minute, in Soul Power on joined bodies unable to transfer. Only can be felt that the air/Qi of that Extreme Yin fast is corroding the Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Frantic Domain amplification to give own bloodline aura.

But at this moment, the white form has been full of her line of sight suddenly, then she was supported into during a warm bosom. His hug that powerful, in that flickers, she heard his intense heartbeat. His that just like twittering general „sorry”. He uses the wing of own her gable, has blocked that cold and gloomy corrosion for her.

In that flash, Xu Xiaoyan sudden innermost feelings stabbing pain maliciously. She wants to break free of his arms, she does not want to make him withstand that for own obviously is the fatal injury.

But, his bosom was really too powerful, powerfully to letting her is unable to work loose. He entered Extreme Yin Domain, similarly is unable to move, two people were stranded, in momentarily will have carried off in their Life world.

When Le Zhengyu falls in her softly that flickers, she saw his smiling face, gratified smiling face, smiling face of feeling relaxed. That sorry no longer proud, but has filled the light warmth and sincerity.

Tears, not by Control flows following the cheek of Xu Xiaoyan, her sounds/voices somewhat is shivering, „older generation(s) , he won't he have the matter? Why that did ability call Sacrifice?”

The Luo Shaofeng eyebrow has selected selecting, „aren't you friends? Hasn't he told you Holy Angel Family Sacrifice talent? Reason that Holy Angel Family is Soul Master most Top Rank Family, the Sacrifice talent has lasting achievements now. When they in facing match irresistibly, can the combustion own Life strength release Sacrifice flame as the price, Sacrifice flame has to resist all negative effects, to ability of own Sacred Power three times of amplifications. Can let have pure bloodline Holy Angel Family member to have over time fighting strength instantaneously temporarily. of course, has to obtain certainly will pay, after lighting Life Flame, uses the Sacrifice talent to carry off they ten years of Life strength each time.”

Ten years of Life strength? Simply speaking, that is ten years of life!

Yuan En Yehui that because originally continuously the Xu Xiaoyan matter is not feeling well to Le Zhengyu very much, looks that the Le Zhengyu look changed. Other people all so. Xu Xiaoyan has had tears streaming down the face.

Luo Shaofeng is also contains the [say / way] of appreciation: „Protects other people by own Sacrifice, this is a Holy Angel Family [lineage/vein] proudest place. This boy has not given his Family to lose face, Holy Angel is arrogant, is protecting the belief of their own eventually.”

Tang Wulin only thought that in the throat as if choked up anything, the look nearly stagnated, facing genuine Elite, they as before that small and weak. Can they be joined to Shrek Seven Monsters these characters really? If were not Le Zhengyu has used Sacrifice, perhaps Xu Xiaoyan died. But is Captain own, Duty-bound Responsibility.

Yuan En Yehui walks to go forward, hugs into Xu Xiaoyan the character bosom. The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, „Xiaoyan is accompanying Zhengyu here, we continue to save the sick and wounded.”

At this time, the distant place, light shone piece by piece, Mecha dropped from the clouds. Not only these Mecha have the fight type, there are special rescues type. After falling to the ground, the incarnation for small rescue Platform, the massive medical care personnel gushes out in abundance, saves the sick and wounded.

That said that is War God Temple Preparatory War God Three Word Battle Armor Master Luo Shaofeng has not participated directly during the treatment, but is float in the midair, around the bird's eye view, is having the possibility appear(ance) enemy anytime.

Some matter people of life-saving have taken over, the Tang Wulin half step arrives under the Luo Shaofeng body, gains ground to look up at him, asked: „Is Zun Fang that older generation(s), you said a moment ago who?”

Luo Shaofeng looked at his one eyes, „, if I have not guessed wrong, you should come from Shrek Academy? Inner Court disciple?”

Tang Wulin has gawked, immediately nodded.

-------------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. Thank You (xiexie) everybody.( ~^~)

#800: War God Temple

Luo Shaofeng shows a faint smile, the expression became was intimate with several points obviously, „that was Junior Brother and Junior Sister. I also come from Shrek. Also once was Inner Court disciple. That fellow who you just ran into, has Zun Fang of name of deep cloudy ghost livestock. This fellow is the Holy Spirit Cult high level, air/Qi of Extreme Yin is troublesome. I pursued him to be very long, feels his aura with great difficulty, catches up in first time.”

„Holy Spirit Cult?” [Say / Way] of Tang Wulin doubts.

Luo Shaofeng sinking sound track: „This was one existence does not know the mysterious religious sect that many years, said accurately, should be has filled evil Sect. His all member are Evil Soul Master, takes training Evil Soul Master as own duty. They like slaughtering, destruction and Ruin, from seeks to promote self- special energy. Holy Spirit Cult nearly takes to a Humanity catastrophe before Ten-thousand Years, afterward Ice Spirit Douluo led then one generation of Elite to rout, finally goes into hiding. But in later Ten-thousand Years, they will occasionally have appear(ance), does not have a tenth macroclimate luckily.”

„Recently for these years, Holy Spirit Cult often had terrifying to move appear(ance), so long as there are them, is the loss of life aspect. Today has you luckily, perhaps otherwise, this car(riage) person cannot live, will link Soul to be walked to be used for cultivate by Evil Soul Master refining their cult tactic.”

Tang Wulin surprised looks at Luo Shaofeng, Evil Soul Master Sect? This he is first time has heard. But is actually not first time meets. Without a doubt, initially he and Mo Lan on Train bitter experience in Evil Soul Master that arrived, should also be receives this Holy Spirit Cult to pull strings?

Luo Shaofeng looks at Tang Wulin to be silent, sinking sound track: „Holy Spirit Cult stops at nothing, and is sly. After having the lesson of beforehand Fallen, their motions are surreptitious. Later meets Evil Soul Master easily act , being far away as far as possible. Now Federation is also working hard to seek for their trails, has hit several, Evil Soul Master was more peaceful recently, has not thought that has created this kind of disaster, is really hateful!”

Tang Wulin said: „Really couldn't find them? This Holy Spirit Cult actually strong?”

Luo Shaofeng shakes the head, sinking sound track: „Does not know. Nobody knows Holy Spirit Cult strongly. But you are clear, his match at least has the three parties, Federation War God Temple, Spirit Transferring Pagoda and Shrek Academy.”

The Tang Wulin heart shakes.

Luo Shaofeng then said: „These Evil Soul Master all are Madman, their anything matter can do. If not was unable frontage and we contends, they already came out.”

Tang Wulin said: „What is War God Temple? I am first time heard.”

Perhaps because of the common origin reason, Luo Shaofeng has not borne because of the inquiry of Tang Wulin, „War God Temple is the high-end strength that Federation trains specially. Your simple such understanding on line. All War God Temple member will obtain the resources incline of Federation, thus promotes own continually. But when Federation bitter experience crisis, War God Temple member must await to dispatch. of course, our degree of freedom is very high . Moreover, we are the military, has the military rank. The words said that you are One Word Battle Armor Master, in the future becomes Two Word Battle Armor Master can graduate from Inner Court, is interested in coming the War God Temple words, we will welcome very much.”

Tang Wulin curious asking: „older generation(s), does War God Temple have our Academy person?”

Luo Shaofeng shows a faint smile, „specific I cannot say, but I can tell you am, Academy can have Federation that many respect and support, with the Academy neutrality, standing aloof from the world has much to do with. But the person who Academy comes out, must have the destination, particularly our Inner Court disciple. War God Temple is a good choice, you can consider.”

„Good, Thank You (xiexie) Senior. However, Senior, we have joined Tang Sect, but can also join War God Temple?”

Luo Shaofeng has gawked, „joined Tang Sect? If you are not the Battle Soul Hall people, that should not affect. But if you have joined Tang Sect Battle Soul Hall, that stays there. The Battle Soul Hall treatment is not bad. Tang Sect working low key, but is powerful, relates with Academy is closer. Also is the good choice. Right, heard that Academy did select new generation Shrek Seven Monsters?”

Tang Wulin flexure scratching the head, somewhat embarrassed nod.

Just is been so miserable, some of his really embarrassed acknowledgments that Evil Soul Master hit.

The Luo Shaofeng what kind eyesight, „you will not tell me, is your several?”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Lost face to Academy.”

„Not, not!” Luo Shaofeng beckons with the hand again and again, even the whole person from airborne descended, high and low sizes up Tang Wulin saying that „looked like you are is impossible to join War God Temple.”

Tang Wulin stares.

Luo Shaofeng then said: „Shrek Seven Monsters is the Academy future, is impossible to be controlled by Federation. Has not thought really! Such quickly can see you. Do not think that just gave the student to lose face, the polarity, you can ask these wounded, you are the heroes, knows? If not you, at least here several hundred Life did not have. You are the heroes, you have not given Academy to lose face. I just looked, the Evil Soul Master quantity of dying in battle were many, let alone you have bumped into Zun Fang. Luckily, he should not know that you are this generation of Shrek Seven Monsters, otherwise, he will not perhaps hesitate the price strikes to kill you. Junior Brother, has remembered, before your strength is not very formidable, do not tell others you are this generation of Shrek Seven Monsters. Academy friend are many, the enemy similarly are also many. But dares to oppose with our Academy, not ill Top Rank Elite.”

„Why is your this must go? I turn head to deliver you a regulation, ensures your securities.”

Looks at the Luo Shaofeng serious appearance, in the Tang Wulin heart one warm, really worthily is Senior!

„We are participate in military training, the specific situation is not clear.”

„military training?” Heard these two characters, Luo Shaofeng hits to tremble smartly spirit, looks that the Tang Wulin look also became strange, said that was one type has several points to pity the flavor the look.

„I cannot deliver you to go, military training must depend upon own. Junior Brother......” Luo Shaofeng wants to say anything, has not said eventually, but lifted the hand to pat the racket on the Tang Wulin shoulder, „you, strove for carefully fortunately.”

The Tang Wulin brow wrinkles, as if this Senior has also participated in military training, moreover military training has made very profound impression on him. Poor impression!

The work of noble spirit of saving the sick and wounded reaches the last act quickly, the severely injured needs to ship to nearby city, breakage Train, the destroyed track needs to repair. These are not Tang Wulin they need to be worried.

With the help of Luo Shaofeng, Tang Wulin they hid the identity, by the official investigation, had not been ridden one flying Mecha that is used to transport to arrive in the recent city.

This evening, can describe with soul-stirring absolutely. Nearly perishes is not anything is good to experience.

„Later did not sit Soul Guidance Train!” Tang Wulin some saying of making a determined effort. „Everybody quickly rests. Zhengyu......”

Le Zhengyu also lethargic sleep, complexion pale white.

„I take care of him.” Xu Xiaoyan saying without hesitation.

In the Tang Wulin heart relaxed secretly, „good. Everybody rests earlier, waits to confirm after Zhengyu body unobstructive, we hurry along again.”

„Good!”

The people went to the room to go respectively, Tang Wulin delivered to the room to leave Le Zhengyu.

Xu Xiaoyan is Le Zhengyu takes off the coat, twisted the towel to clean the body to him, the cover quilt. own pulled a chair to sit in the bedside visits him.

Le Zhengyu of peaceful time is as before handsome, although some complexion morbid states pale white also still so.

-----------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( ~^~)

#801: Listens to my confession

Unknowingly, Xu Xiaoyan at present became blurred, tears „and” downward fell.

„Always said you to be proud, always said that you keep aloof. In fact, am I innermost feelings am also proud? Right that you said that I a little feel inferior actually. My family background and you compare difference are too many. You are so outstanding, was too easy to attract liking of many female student. I feared really that later time grew, you to my affection not that many.”

„The day, on Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, when you arrived in front of me to say to me competitive these words, I had to plant by you am regarded the feeling of accessories. But I do not want such, I am I.”

„A half year, entire a half year you do not have to manage me. Do you know? On that day after Blind Date General Meeting went back, I regretted. Although I did not regret that own rejects you, but I actually do not deserve that many people to make you unable to get out. But now, I regretted, I should not reject your, is I do not have the confidence to you.”

„Sorry, Zhengyu. Was I is too narrow-minded. Are you a bit faster good? Later, I am not willful.”

At the same time was saying, Xu Xiaoyan gently is stroking the Le Zhengyu forehead.

„It is not good, I like your willful, you are any appearance, you who I like any appearance.” Temperate sounds/voices resounds, Le Zhengyu has opened eyes slowly.

Xu Xiaoyan had a scare, must take back the hand of own, was held the wrist by Le Zhengyu.

„Do not walk and do not leave me. In the half year, I was sufficed.”

Xu Xiaoyan was grabbed the wrist by him, pretty face slightly red, „when do you and you awake?”

Le Zhengyu shows a faint smile, „started to confess that time that in you.”

„You......” Xu Xiaoyan pretty face is red, wants to escape really immediately, but was actually grasped by Le Zhengyu is very tight.

„Now, this you listen to my confession?” Le Zhengyu supple sound track.

Xu Xiaoyan stares slightly, looks up to him.

Le Zhengyu looks at her eye, „sorry, Xiaoyan. Is I am not good. You said right, I was too arrogant, was too proud. This is the bad problem that I foster since childhood, in fact, our family, all people have this problem. Everyone has. But I have not actually noted your feeling. On that day, I was too anxious, on Sea God Fated Blind Date General Meeting, I am thinking can make you justifiablily my girlfriend, has actually neglected you at that time the feeling. But I do not have the giving charity feeling, does not have the least bit to look down upon your family background.”

„Sorry, my sincere apologized to you, and I promised you that I will change, later I will try hard to change own. I will respect you, to cherish you, defends side you. Please forgive me?”

Xu Xiaoyan visits him dull, enough after long time, she muttered the tunnel: „Fool.”

Le Zhengyu sits sets out, after he wakes, is a little weak besides the body beside, anything has not obstructed greatly.

„Yes, I am silly. Even I also loses temper with you today, but also Control does not live in own that laughable pride as before. But, do you know? When I saw that you were occupied by with formidable Soul Skill Control by that Evil Soul Master, saw that flash that you will soon die, I suddenly thought that own simply is the world silliest person. If you died, perhaps I did not go on living., Believes me, if you died, I will certainly go all out after you revenge, following you to go.”

Xu Xiaoyan lowered the head, „can I not believe you? You for me, have used Sacrifice. For me, has burnt the own Life strength.”

Le Zhengyu has gawked, „did you know?”

Xu Xiaoyan nods, „may you not tell me, you really have such ability.”

Le Zhengyu shows a faint smile, „you, when the pride of our Family does come from where? Our noble not from bloodline, but came from Sacrifice spiritual. In order to protect own companion, we momentarily can Sacrifice. Therefore, the Holy Angel Family person, will never tell friend own to have this ability, we only when companion need, protects them with this ability, died until own.”

Xu Xiaoyan gains ground fiercely, suddenly is choked with tears, grasps Le Zhengyu, „ten years, ten years of Life strength! You......”

Le Zhengyu is hugging her, said with a smile: „With can protect compared with you, ten years of Life strength, what was also considered as? So long as you can return to side me, little lives for ten years, I am also joyful. Without your day, the world is darkness, now, you came back. Won't walk again?”

[Say / Way] that Xu Xiaoyan muttered: „In you use since Sacrifice that moment for me, I was your person, regardless of, you were what kind to me, regardless of you were whether proud, regardless of my own had feels inferior, I will not leave you. You for my Sacrifice, I and you share the future.”

The young biggest advantage is to restore quickly, a late recuperation, the second day very early in the morning, Shrek Seven Monsters besides some Le Zhengyu complexion also pale white, other people are the god ends the air/Qi foot.

„Boss, do we walk? By the way, saw that you such eat meal, is really very happy.” Xie Xie said with a smile.

In Inner Court, everybody is separates cultivate, life also not in the same place. cultivate life that especially Tang Wulin that nearly closes up, already very long not with companion Joint Training.

Tang Wulin said: „Does not ride the Soul Guidance High-speed Train words, we do not have other choice, can only be Soul Guide Steam Vehicle.”

Le Zhengyu said: „If there is Mecha to be good.”

Yuan En Yehui said: „Do not tease, Mecha? You have Mecha to have no way in Federation airborne flying. Only if you can attain the entire Federation charter of concession. That is impossible. Federation each region has the special pass, only if some extraordinary parts or is the military, has the qualifications to drive Mecha to move in any place.”

Xu Xiaoyan said: „Zhengyu this in other words did not say. Then was good on the automobile.”

The people look askance instantaneously, vision all centralized on Xu Xiaoyan.

Xu Xiaoyan some not comfortable [say / way]: „Why do you think so me?”

A Xie Xie face curious [say / way]: „Did you become reconciled?”

Le Zhengyu stared his one eyes, „when don't we feel better? But before , a little slightly misunderstands.”

„Is!” Xu Xiaoyan echoes to say immediately.

Xie Xie curled the lip, „you won.”

Xu Xiaoyan holds in the arms the arm of Le Zhengyu, a happiness of face. „Heard that our Tang Sect has prolonging the life Heaven and Earth Treasure, turned head this military training to finish, I looked for such task to do with Zhengyu.”

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „It is not you, should be everybody is together right. We are a whole.”

Ye Xinglan that quite a while has not spoken said: „Captain, what do you have to plan? What I refer to is regarding us.”

Tang Wulin said: „Yesterday from the War God Temple older generation(s) mouth, we obtained many useful things actually. For example we knew War God Temple existence, knew is the unspoken rule on Continent. War God Temple should be the Federation high-end strength, is the Elite centralized place. Spirit Transferring Pagoda should have similar organization, our Tang Sect has Battle Soul Hall and Worship Hall. Academy has Inner Court, to have Sea God Pavilion. These are on Continent most Top Rank strength existence. But as new generation Shrek Seven Monsters, we almost will be tacitly approved into the Academy representative. In other words, we first cannot join Spirit Transferring Pagoda and War God Temple. But at the same time we are the Tang Sect person, Tang Sect and Academy relate closely. Therefore, from the future, we, regardless of makes anything, should not go beyond this category. At least before cultivation to be certain extent is not good.”

„We after this military training finished, if like Old Cai says, can continue for two years to complete military training, our strengths should be increased to the new degree, should some people break through 60th Rank, became Soul Emperor. Then, the following two years, we must complete the Battle Armor promotion as soon as possible. Only then after becoming Two Word Battle Armor Master, we had genuine self-preservation ability. Two Word Battle Armor had Wings, even if no Mecha, to us will not have any affects. The Federation radar can limit Mecha, but actually could not limit our own Wings.”

Here, Tang Wulin has stopped, then lowered the head slightly, „apologied to everybody in this me. Because left for more than three years, after coming back, continuously earnestly own cultivate, I and everybody's Joint Training were too few. I some have not been familiar with everybody's operational way (of life), cannot better and everybody coordinates. Otherwise, yesterday the situation will not be perhaps awful.”

-----------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. The following plot must get on soundings. We hope that everybody likes.( ~^~)

#802: Golden Road or Death Road?

The people look at each other in blank diamay, Xu Lizhi sighed one lightly, „in fact, this cannot blame you. Because is we, Joint Training was also short. After entering Inner Court, we are studying with different Teacher(s), promote own, the Joint Training opportunity were much less than before. The tacit understanding truly does not have what promotion, particularly after everybody becomes One Word Battle Armor Master. We truly should strengthen this aspect.”

Tang Wulin nodded, „right, our present tacit understanding, was training in the past together. The four years ago degrees, even might as well at that time. But in fact, we are not familiar with each other new skill, this is not good. We are Shrek Seven Monsters, we are a whole. The whole must promote to be good in the together strength. Moreover should be the geometrical multiple. Therefore, during military training, we must increase Joint Training, increases the degree of adaptability.”

The Ye Xinglan nod said: „I agreed.”

The people nod the head in abundance.

Tang Wulin said: „Good, set off. We must look for a car(riage) to be good as soon as possible. Old Cai emphasized time, our time certainly will not be then abundant. Let alone also has come across yesterday's such thunderbolt.”

Mu Chen to the Tang Wulin money is quite abundant, buys the car(riage) not to suffice, but Car Rental. Rents in the current city, to the destination city, has returned in Car Rental Company local minute of Company.

Everyone will drive, this is not the major problem. Seven passenger cars, happen to meet their needs. It is not luxurious, is considered as reluctantly comfortably.

Xie Xie is responsible for driving, Tang Wulin looks at map, other people in behind.

The day before Xu Xiaoyan also opposed nonchalantly with Le Zhengyu, today turned into being inseparable. She had not had a good sleep yesterday evening, the car dealership was steady, is quick she to fall asleep in the Le Zhengyu bosom.

„According to our current speed, if every day over ten hours on road, but also needs four days of time to reach the destination. Soul Guidance Train speed is quick!” Tang Wulin looks at the map, slightly some frown.

„Ok, has an accident? time cannot such calculate. Boss, you have not sat the Soul Guidance Train life.” Xie Xie said with a smile.

The following traveling schedule was quite finally steady. At least again has not encountered the Evil Soul Master this rarely seen situation.

Four days later, they arrived at Continent northeastern part coastal city North Sea City. Comes to the northeast, after these many days traveling schedules, the temperature changed lowers obviously. Although to their such cultivation is, Transformation of temperature affects to the body is not big, but long time is a little cold.

„Finally.” Drove North Sea City, first car(riage). On people face somewhat exhausted look.

Every day drives several hours of car(riage), to the body is not the load, but actually very much boils spiritual.

Tang Wulin said: „We cannot stop, I some premonitions, behind will be very always troublesome. I inquired first, how to go to sea, goes to our destinations.”

According to instruction that Old Cai gives, their military training place, is going to sea from North Sea City, island about 30 kms away. But wants here to arrive in the island from them now, certainly must have the ship to be good.

„The Car Rental line is also transportation trade, perhaps they know where can rent the ship?” Xie Xie refers to the Car Rental line that they just walked.

Tang Wulin said: „Has the possibility.”

Xie Xie said: „I asked.”

A moment later, when Xie Xie walks from the Car Rental line, complexion becomes somewhat is ugly.

„Boss, your judgment is correct, wants to arrive in that nameless island is really not that easy. You know how Car Rental line of people of did say?” A speechless appearance of Xie Xie face.

Tang Wulin said: „What situation?”

Xie Xie said: „Car Rental line of people of heard that we must go to sea, immediately is one fantasy the appearance, said that we do want to bring death? Moreover, according to them, North Sea City does not even have including the wharf, the simplest wharf does not have. Because, North Sea City here sea area, not only has the giant storm, but also has massive Sea Soul Beast active existence. In their words is, Life forbidden area!”

„I know.” Speechless of Tang Wulin face.

„Isn't large oceangoing vessel good?” Le Zhengyu asked.

Xie Xie said: „Large oceangoing vessel? You want to be too many. Wharf that the large oceangoing vessel can anchor, in Continent northeastern part sea area, only then Celestial Sea City and Eastsea City have. Here distance two cities far? How long back and forth does one want? Moreover, can we transfer a large oceangoing vessel to come the Sea Soul Beast crowded sea area?”

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, said: „It seems like, this should be we must first face troubled. Also is Test before military training.”

Yuan En Yehui said: „First has a look to the seashore, does not rely on hearsay to seeing is believing, first has a look at the Sea Soul Beast intensity to achieve any situation. The matter is not we can resist.”

„Walks!” Tang Wulin waves, the people got up one Car Rental, directly soars the North Sea City east side seashore direction to go.

When they arrived about five kilometers place to be blocked from the seashore.

Looks at the distant place reaches as high as hundred meters, when above is densely covered the dike of various heavy Soul Guidance weapon or is being a city wall. The people somewhat are dumbfounded.

Although has not seen sea, but can see from these defense Sea Soul Beast city walls that outside that was the sea world is how fearful.

„Anyone of you knew that what above Soul Guidance Device is?” Asking that Tang Wulin muttered. Regarding Soul Guidance Device, he truly does not have any too many research, only understands some foundation knowledge.

The Xie Xie forced smile said: „Soul Guidance Device I do not understand, but you look at that side city wall below, that should be ultra can the Soul Guiding Power Battery array. The function of this Little Thing did not need me to say.”

Yeah, looks following the Xie Xie finger direction, under the city wall, at least on three has the extremely dangerous marking house. Can distinguish from the shape and above marking of house.

Ultra can the Soul Guiding Power Battery array, be a structure is complex, takes Soul Guidance Method Array to be able as Nucleus ultra the battery. Can provide huge energy. Generally speaking, is only for some formidable Soul Guidance Device uses. For example large-scale Soul Guide Screen, this is military, is different from Academy that type. Moreover some ultra can the Soul Guidance cannon, must take it as foundation.

Now let alone was to cross the sea, even if were wants to go out of town becomes very difficultly and is very difficult.

„This where is any Golden Road, simply is Death Road!” The Xu Lizhi forced smile said.

Tang Wulin after short being startled immediately restored calmly, „walks, we go back first.”

Is Captain, his of course cannot bring companion to move rashly, returns to the city, Tang Wulin looked for a small hotel first, opened a room, then on the table spread out just the map that bought from North Sea City.

„Everybody looks, the red region should be the city wall protection area, this is a 50 kms in length coastline, including part is the giant reef, does not have the reef impediment place, all was covered by the city wall. All places have the defense facility. Very obviously, monitoring the radar can be most advanced. Wanted possibly to sneak across in the past almost not. Cannot hit.”

On the map showed that outside sea area is a Skeleton sign, it can be imagined that means anything, but Old Cai gives on their map to be possible not to have these marking, has an island, with one from the North Sea City set off straight distance.

Behavior Golden Road, should from of North Sea City to that island.

„Cannot break through the past, only then means that that detours. We must have a look to the seashore first. Moreover, we do not even have including the Coordinate. Knows that from the North Sea City straight line direction 30 kilometers, has such island.”

---------------------------------------------

I think that you definitely could not guess correctly what they must face is anything. Asked the recommendation ticket!( ~^~)

#803: North Sea Corps

Yuan En Yehui said: „Detouring words must be very far, North Sea City here has North Sea Corps, is stationed in the seashore, it seems like, should be defense this piece of sea area Sea Soul Beast. We detour do not know where must circle. Moreover here seashore all by the military radar control, we cannot circle, can only go to that island from the sea directly. Without the Coordinate, seeks for islands in sea, fishes the needle not to have anything to distinguish with sea.”

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, „ground previous was impossible in the past, under the ground similarly is not good. We only then ascended the sky.”

„Heaven?” The people stare.

Tang Wulin said: „Soul Guidance aircraft these year of High-speed develop, although forbids civil, but the army actually absolutely is the massive equipment. We have no way to pass the ground, even was sea in the past. But if we can do to Soul Guidance aircraft, perhaps that we can from airborne in the past. 30 kilometers distance, was very near regarding airborne. Even if were the glide in the past, soon.”

Xie Xie loses the sound track: „Boss, you may be able to think. That is Soul Guidance aircraft! The military controls strictly. Did not open civil. You know where can rent aircraft to be inadequate?”

Tang Wulin said: „Rents is definitely impossible, can only be ‚borrowing’.”

Xie Xie and Yuan En Yehui look at each other one, [say / way] with one voice: „North Sea Corps?”

Right, North Sea Corps big regiment that is second to none as the northeastern areas, certainly will provide Soul Guidance aircraft. In the actual combat, Soul Guidance aircraft does not conflict in the airborne function and Mecha, the same rank manufacture Mecha material and resources, manufacture ten Soul Guidance aircraft, aircraft flying speed was been sufficiently quicker by Mecha. Moreover can carry many people, carries Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell.

Soul Guidance aircraft development before hundred years starts, after the High-speed development, now is Federation indispensable arming strength. The big regiment has the special flying brigade, coordinates Mecha Brigade. It is said that now most advanced Soul Guidance aircraft can through airborne fly Star Luo Continent directly or is Heaven Dou Continent. In the science and technology, Douluo Continent must lead another two pieces of Continent by far. Just, Federation do not start the meaning of war.

‚Taking advantage of’ aircraft, without doubt is quickest way (of life). But the issue came, they will not open!

„We can infiltrating go, how to open aircraft? And before arriving at the island, hadn't been discovered or shot down by the military?” Le Zhengyu said.

Tang Wulin said: „This need strict plan is good. Although I study not many to Soul Guidance Device. But Soul Guidance aircraft or is many that also Soul Guidance flying I understand. Opens us is not good, but we, since must borrow, pilot together borrows. But regarding strength of regiment, their long-distance attacks ability to cover 300 kms away sufficiently. We ‚taking advantage of’ pilot and aircraft, then, they must first confirm. After all can be cautious about harming evildoers lest the innocent be hurt. So long as in their firing distance Control range, they did not fear that we can run away the act heart. Is right?”

The people nod in abundance.

Tang Wulin continues saying: „However we do not need to escape from 300 kilometers, so long as 30 kilometers were enough. Regarding a fighter aircraft, 30 kilometers are the distances that among the moment can be. When the time comes, we only need to complete one time to land, comes also goes back ‚taking advantage of’ aircraft and pilot that naturally will not be attacked by North Sea Corps, we can also arrive in the destination.”

Tang Wulin spoke of here, suddenly discovered side own specially peaceful.

The people all some glassy-eyed visit him.

Xu Lizhi muttered the tunnel: „Boss, what ghost is landing?”

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, „is drops from the clouds! We have Zhengyu and Martial Soul of Yuan En two people can flying. To the goal place, we landed from the upper air, by their flying ability and ensure we can slide to the island on the line. Really is not good, can reduce our crash speed. At our One Word Battle Armor defense strength and own defense intensity. So long as does not fall in the ground, does not need to fear. Falls , the issue is not big.”

Xie Xie has swallowed saliva, „Boss, you may be able to think. My first time knows, originally your idea can unexpectedly so like a heavenly steed, soaring across the skies. Is this method really a little dangerous?”

Tang Wulin said: „Really, definitely has risk, first, our whether infiltrating north regiment, and seeks for the pilot and aircraft makes it take off. second, in 30 kilometers, before arriving in the island, cannot be shot down. Third, after falling into sea, must be able to defeat Sea Soul Beast, rushes to the island. If first we cannot achieve, risky relative is not big, by our fighting strength, the whole body draws back very big opportunity, even if draws back does not have to draw back, the surrender does not have the issue. Without the Life danger. second words, I think 30 kilometers, North Sea Corps start attack several not to be sincerely big to us, even if initiated attack, we can also give up aircraft, landed to sea. At that time the risk came from Sea Soul Beast mainly. Therefore, the distance that aircraft departs is farther, is close island, our risks are also smaller.”

„Finally, copes with Sea Soul Beast. My bloodline aura has certain pressure function regarding all Soul Beast. I think, only if we are specially bad luck, has met Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast, otherwise, in certain distance, to should. Zhengyu and Yuan En, your flying ability whether to be leading our other five people, even if were the glide in the past?”

Le Zhengyu said: „Should almost, take our present cultivation as, the words that All-Out to go, are bringing everybody flying in airborne short time. But considers the upper current reason, there is an uncertainty.”

Tang Wulin looks to Xu Lizhi, „can your agile little dragon(s) package, how many components reduce our?”

Xu Lizhi [say / way] without hesitation: „30% definitely do not have the issue.”

Yuan En Yehui said: „Thinks so really has certain feasibility. Lands you to plan highly is how many?”

Tang Wulin said: „Theoretically, of course the lower the better. Like this landing time will reduce, because we must consider after we are separated from aircraft, the North Sea Corps base gives our long-distance attack, landing time is shorter, receives the possibility of attack to be smaller.”

Ye Xinglan said: „Good, sounds as if, but biggest problem or first. How we can infiltrating North Sea Corps, and ‚taking advantage of’ walks aircraft?”

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, „this seems most difficult, but also and has the shortcut. This difficulty generally speaking, how the most important point goes . After entering the North Sea Corps base, must be easier relatively. Because of any military installation, the foreign defense strength is strongest, interior naturally easy to do.”

„How does that go in?” Xu Lizhi curious asking.

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „through yesterday's matter, I understood a matter suddenly. That is, has difficulties, looks for Senior! War God Temple has our Senior, North Sea Corps, I believe that certainly also has.”

Xu Xiaoyan has smiled, „Captain, did I have saying that I liked your this confident appearance.”

A Le Zhengyu face vigilant [say / way]: „Do you like him?”

Xu Xiaoyan helpless [say / way]: „Appreciation, is of appreciation likes.”

Le Zhengyu has smiled immediately, „that I also like. Captain, present you, a little restored the four years ago appearances. No matter what, we listen your, how you said come, how we come.”

Tang Wulin has smiled, „bold supposition, careful proof. We go to North Sea Corps to look for Senior, this always does not have any issue. Perhaps, can we borrow aircraft really?”

Ye Xinglan said: „We with what showed that we are the Shrek people? We may anything not have the belt to come out, Academy basically is makes us leave home with only their clothes on their backs.”

Tang Wulin said: „This is not difficult, Academy can make 1 st, why can't we make 15? Why you forgot me are? Inner Court disciple badge, I make several. Are our strengths, in addition insufficient?”

„You won.” Ye Xinglan rare has shown the smiling face.

Entire plan in fact Tang Wulin also temporarily wants to come out, but in the process of discussion, along with the question that everybody raised, this plan continually was also being improved.

At the beginning, Tang Wulin truly has thought that or strove to excel ‚borrowing’, but he just suddenly got a sudden inspiration, has remembered yesterday's War God Temple Senior.

Shrek Academy it can be said that has pupils everywhere absolutely, this is the Academy strongest place. It seems neutral Academy, has the huge influence to entire Federation. Student, Shrek Inner Court walks particularly from Shrek, which is not a God's favored one, moreover they have the greatly strengthened sense of belonging to Academy inevitably.( ~^~)

#804: North Sea Corps base

North Sea Corps has certainly person who Shrek Academy comes out, but Shrek takes to the graduating cadet first point, is the high starting point.

If a graduate enlistment of Shrek Academy, is always impossible only to be a big end of soldier. At least impossible is the big end of soldier. Otherwise, he did not have qualifications to graduate from Shrek Academy.

So long as there is a human, that was easy to do. As for the excuse, among the Tang Wulin intention phonographs has thought.

...

North Sea Corps, built before 1600 Hundred Year, is a Douluo Continent Federation time-honored organization system. North Sea Corps itself has strong naval battle and air fight ability. The regiment manages three divisions, separately is the North Sea aviation fight master, the North Sea Marine divisions as well as the North Sea Fleet.

And, what largest is the North Sea Fleet, they have ships more than 30, is stationed in the North Sea Corps free harbor. This resists the Sea Soul Beast main force. Because Sea Soul Beast of North Sea sea area is almost the Douluo Continent peripheral sea area is strongest, therefore the equipment of North Sea Fleet, in all navies is also strongest. Do not look at North Sea City not to have the harbor wharf, but must discuss fighting strength, the North Sea Fleet must certainly strong in the Eastsea fleet. Some ultra specification weapons, here has the equipment.

The North Sea Fleet altogether has the combatants more than 12,000 people, various auxiliary work personnel reach more than 30,000 people.

But the North Sea aviation fight master has various aircraft more than 70, besides aircraft, special High-speed reaction army, is the Mecha army. Federation air force strength is by Mecha and fighter aircraft coordination with each other, is divided into many branch of the services.

The North Sea Marine divisions mainly in view of the ground operation, particularly battle to the sea, the primary equipment massive heavy weapons, like the seashore defense system of North Sea City, are all completed by the North Sea Marine divisions. Well-equipped, is good at to Sea Soul Beast defense.

Is primarily combatants with the army regiment generally, a regiment is probably different in three and 40,000 people. Because North Sea Corps needs massive auxiliary staff, entire regiment adds, has 80,000 people fully. Is big regiment that deserves. The military rank of North Sea Corps military officer, compared with regiment high Half Rank with on stage also because of so.

When Tang Wulin and companion have gotten down Car Rental, was shocked by all of distant place.

Has Car Rental to place to be away from the North Sea Corps base them about one kilometer place, because forwards again, was the military control area.

North Sea Corps gives their first impression does not look at the boundary.

Looks to North Sea Corps from their location place that the regiment surrounding does not have the wall, is the big wire netting, has dozens meters high fully. Said accurately that is an electrical network. Any life form contacts, can by the high-voltage baptism.

Can see that the large-scale military vehicle passes and out from the entrance, looks into a farther place, in the base, can see anchoring some aircraft, then also has many them unable to name the character the military installation.

„It seems good. I suddenly thought that Boss said that he must become a soldier in the future is a very good choice!” Xie Xie somewhat excitedly said.

Man Inborn has to yearn to the military, since Soul Guidance Technology development, has made the weapon very formidable. Even if most Top Rank Soul Master, when facing that type can the to destroy the heavens and exterminate the land Soul Guidance weapon, does not dare the frontage to touch hardly.

Formidable military strength is all safeguards, Federation such has also done.

Entire Douluo Federation has the standing army 2 million, six greater military areas, North Sea Corps subordinates in Northeast Military District, is in the Northeast Military District three regiments the strongest sea and air regiment.

„Walks, we pass. Nature that everybody displays on line.” Tang Wulin walks in the forefront, on the face is having the smile, other people follow behind him. On the people besides simple Soul Guidance Storing Device, has not carried anything.

Yuan En that also receives to some Great Hammer of breakage in Soul Guidance Storing Device.

Has not waited for them to approach the North Sea Corps base main entrance, had been blocked by one team of patrol soldiers.

„Halts, the restricted area, is far away.” The patrol soldier is drives, obviously was in the base already discovered them.

Tang Wulin goes forward two, said: „Hello, we are the Shrek Academy students, is carrying on to gain experience task. The task goal of Academy arrangement is carries on one time to teach to the expensive regiment especially. Whether to trouble you to notify for us.”

„Shrek Academy? We have not received any notice.” The patrol soldier is not obviously good to coax.

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, resigned-looking [say / way]: „If has the notification, that this was not Test. In fact, Academy requests us to come to carry on teaches especially, has not actually given us any help, how to enter expensive military training to practice, this wants our own to try to find the solution. But you also saw, what means can we have? Only can such come, walks the proper way to inquire directly, whether can arrange us to teach especially.”

The patrol soldier eyebrow has selected selecting, „are really you Shrek Academy? How to show?”

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „proof? This is actually easy.” At the same time was saying, he has given a hand signal to companion, next one flickers, seven people simultaneously released their Martial Soul.

Seven people simultaneously release Martial Soul, and in the situation that the Soul Ring quantity is the certain extent shocks. Especially in one crowd is only in front of the soldier of average person.

When the soldiers on patrol car see in Soul Ring that in front of own blooms, particularly in the Soul Ring stage quite not low situation, they stare in a big way the eye.

Five, all are Five Rings!

Tang Wulin and his companion are maintaining a complete triangle battlefield. Tang Wulin in the forefront, he behind is three people of one row, the both sides separately are Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan, the middle is Xu Xiaoyan. Behind them is also three people of one row, the both sides are Le Zhengyu and Xie Xie, central Xu Lizhi.

Although has not been at the battle condition, but they are maintaining the lineup of fight, this is the became a habit nature issue. Especially in the former once facing Evil Soul Master in that passive the situation, their this drove North Sea City, on the road does not have little discusses everybody's coordinate question.

Tang Wulin stands in the front line, body Five Soul Rings three purple, one black, one green. Said accurately is green-gold.

Even if the soldiers are not Soul Master, when they see Tang Wulin green Soul Ring, as before surprised dumbfoundedness. But on Shrek Seven Monsters, they have not seen purple following stage Soul Ring. This means any without a doubt.

Five Rings, seven Five Rings Soul King. Moreover these young people seem on about 20 -year-old appearances! But the soldiers on patrol car, the age and they are almost the same.

Envies and envies all sorts of mood is almost instantaneously on appear(ance) in these soldiers hearts. Is everybody person of same age, the disparity so is big?

The responsible soldier on patrol car has swallowed saliva, is returning to normal the mood, then takes up own military Soul Guide Communication Device, puts through the communication.

The military Soul Guide Communication Device most major characteristics are civil completely separated, above does not have the function of digit dialing, each button is representing a specific telephone conversation object, therefore this soldier has pressed, immediately puts through.

„Report, discovered that seven suspicious personnel, they said that from the Shrek Academy student, wants to enter the base to participate in the training. The complete seven people are Five Rings Soul King stage Soul Master, the age probably are at about 20 years old. Please instruct.”

Listens attentively to the order that Soul Guide Communication Device has transmitted slightly, the soldier said immediately: „Yes!”

Hangs up the communication, his vision somewhat strange looks at the Tang Wulin seven people, said: „Invited to wait a bit, will immediately have the car(riage) to meet you.” -

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#805: Trap

On Tang Wulin seven faces as if by prior agreement revealed the smiling face, had the car(riage) to meet, has the gate. It seems like what they judge is correct, person who in the northern regiment base, has certainly Shrek Academy. Moreover, Shrek Academy has the pivotal status on Continent. Where the Inner Court student to is popular.

time is not long, was a military vehicle opened, on this vehicle has not gone on patrol the soldier, the Tang Wulin seven people boarded, the beforehand that car(riage) in front, joined their car(riage)s, went toward the northern regiment base travel.

„Waits a minute to act according to circumstances, our most important goals must remain. Then strives to relate puissant Senior in regiment, so long as can complete with peace way (of life), we did not need ‚borrowing’.” Tang Wulin said in a low voice.

Ye Xinglan nodded, „first we cannot be separated, was not separated will not have the issue.”

„Um.” Tang Wulin has selected under.

The base of northern regiment was really too big, looked from outside, but felt its broad scale, but entered, in a big way can actually realize it.

Even if drives, opened for nearly 20 minutes, stops. Stops before seems and common, but actually very big construction.

Arrives at the construction front, the soldier stands in the hand signal that the entrance makes invitation.

Tang Wulin and companion as before are maintaining the lineup, walked.

Passing through the gate, Tang Wulin slightly frown, because this seems a little likely is a warehouse place, inside is various types of metal(s) equipment, almost they did not know.

Led the military officer of second lieutenant military rank to welcome, „were you Shrek Academy people? Has the identification?”

Tang Wulin hurried to take badge that own made, has handed over.

The military officers looked, many confirmations have not given back to them, „comes with me.” Saying, him was walking toward inside.

Tang Wulin and companion could be said as the boldness becauses of one's skill, did not feel timid, the stride followed on the heels, curious looks at surroundings.

Various facilities in warehouse seem very advanced, was quick they to see some shape huge Soul Guide Cannon. The silvery-white barrel is gigantic, although does not have energy to pour into, but actually as before can feel withering aura from their there.

Walked about hundred meters, in a quite spacious place, another military officer waited there, the military uniform of north regiment is dark blue, the straight military uniform serves as contrast the military officer handsome face , the epaulet on shoulder is having two rings, central silver star, a Two Rings star, this was the major military rank.

This major seems the 30-year-old appearance, is tall, on the face is having the genial smile.

„The Shrek Academy God's favored ones, welcome you to arrive at the northern regiment.”

In the Tang Wulin heart moves, hurries to go forward several steps, „hello the officer, takes the liberty to come, put to trouble to you.”

The major said with a smile: „Has not related, said your purposes in coming.”

Tang Wulin preparing the good excuse said that i.e. they hope can probably comes the northern regiment to carry on time special teach, thus completes Academy to give their to gain experience task and so on.

„......, After we have pondered carefully, thought that is direct, hopes that can give shelter by our north regiment.” The Tang Wulin smiling face has affinity very much, he handsome, after restraining Golden Dragon King bloodline aura, is makes people very easy to have the closeness.

The major nodded, said with a smile: „I understood. However, the little brother, does not know that you have thought an issue does not have. Since Shrek Academy lets your to gain experience place comes our north regiment, then, where this to gain experience difficulty is?”

Tang Wulin stares, this to gain experience is he compiled, because without guaranteeing the opposite party will help their, cannot say the real situation easily.

„Is your meaning?” Tang Wulin doubts looks at the major.

The major said with a smile: „The Shrek Academy teaching, will not always be aimless. In fact, you are not the first batch come here. Before you, almost every several years, will have your Academy person to come. Directly just, visits like you are not many. Generally is looks for the opportunity, sneak crossing goes to sea! Even wants to seep the larceny our flying tool! Such will be more. Your this types splendid come , after I come to here, in any case first time meets. Has saying that you must have the courage compared with your older generation(s), is more self-confident.”

The feeling of Tang Wulin was not very good, listened to the words of this major, he suddenly discovered that own has made a fatal mistake. They are not the first batch come the military training person, then, comes military training before them, is Senior that Shrek Academy Inner Court comes out, but this military training historical actually how long they do not know, can only affirm is, at least Old Cai that generation has participated. The topic is the same, then, in the northern regiment is protecting in the coastal territory situation, how Senior go to that island? Must in stipulating time enters, walks this Golden Road.

Walks into a trap to have?

The Ye Xinglan eyebrow selects slightly, Tang Wulin actually subconsciously stretches out the arms, blocks companion.

„Officer, are you what kind of?” Tang Wulin asked. At this time impulsed unable to solve the problem, others can such tranquil standing speak with confidence before them, moreover knows that their seven people were in the Soul King situations, impossible not to have prepared.

Tang Wulin in an instant, has made many judgments in heart, only the opposite party does not know should be they are Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters, this is also the secret that they can keep only.

The major said: „Um, is very good, can be calm in your this age is not easy. Said honestly that I have to speak the wind discouraging talk, reason that you fall to this situation, is your Academy causes completely. We already received the notice, recently seven Shrek Academy students will come, then your goals, go to sea inside Devil Island, but is very obvious, wanted from our defense lines in the past, that was impossible. We have the responsibility, protects the Federation people safety, does not permit anybody close seashore. Gives our time according to Shrek Academy, you must in arrive in Devil Island from the 15 day after Academy set off, otherwise task failure . Moreover the consequence is very serious. Therefore, we not to you how, so long as you close for ten days in the prison in base, sufficiently collects 15 days later complete, will put you to leave.”

On the Tang Wulin forehead pulled down three heavy lines, the Academy this also Taikeng, has informed the northern regiment including their motion time. This simply is......

Also can resist with others regiment depending on their such how many people?

[Say / Way] that the major smiles: „You can calmly face, truly is very intelligent. Otherwise, if you to my attack, that mean that you initiate attack to the Federation military, at that time, even if I ordered to kill you, conformed to the military discipline. But now, only needs to imprison your time. Good, please be without a fight.”

„Is without a fight, snort!” Le Zhengyu cold snort.

The major said: „To revolt? You can try greatly. You do not have a look at all around.”

Tang Wulin had not looked, but he also felt that around the warehouse, the metal(s) gun tubes drill slowly, aims at them completely. Although does not know that the specific effects of these gun tubes are anything, but from the length and gun tube itself size of gun tube, can see, this is extremely the terrifying weapon.

Tang Wulin said: „Everybody do not move.”

The major said with a smile: „Comes the human, takes to them seals the soul handcuff.”

One team of soldiers ran from behind, in each individual hand has one approximately width one foot, the height half foot square shape metal(s) box. The half step arrives in front of the Tang Wulin seven people.

The major said: „If you want to revolt, now also with enough time.”

Tang Wulin sighed, dejected [say / way]: „Has not thought that can be this unexpectedly, Academy was too sinister. However, this to us, received a profound lesson, finally is trip has not been made in vain. Lost lost, but we certainly will not make next time the same mistake. According to doing that he said that no one must revolt. Fell to others hands, let our hoodlum point.”

At the same time was saying, he lifts both hands on own initiative.

A soldier hangs the metal(s) box above Tang Wulin both hands, that metal(s) box splits rapidly, gathers to below, wraps in which the Tang Wulin both hands wrist.

Immediately, Tang Wulin only thought that the intense feeling lacking in vigilance transmits from the wrist place, whole body trembles, own Soul Power was prohibited immediately. It is not able to communicate the slightest.

Other people listened to Tang Wulin eventually, put on this type of sealing soul handcuff.( ~^~)

#806: Accepts fate?

On the Xu Xiaoyan face reveals a desperate expression, „good quite to be uncomfortably and sad! Captain, what to do should we?” Her sounds/voices even somewhat sobbed, timid.

„Do not fear that will not have the matter. At the worst this to gain experience task. Goes back to accept the penalty. Relax, our anything has not done, the north regiment can detain us, will not be what kind of us, after all Academy knows us here, we have not made any attack or steal the behavior.”

The major said with a smile: „Therefore , your choices are correct. Takes away them, detains. Was right, by the way. I graduate from Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy. Or the high level of northern regiment basically came from Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy. Therefore, our continuously very repugnant Shrek. Has not thought that is situated in the northeast regiment, the high level actually came from in western Bright Capital City Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy. The relations of related two Academy, do you know?”

Knows? Can not know? Initially Tang Wulin also led companion to go to Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy to smash the gathering place.

Tang Wulin does not lower the head cheerfully, has accepted fate appearance, this quite therefore entered the nest of thieves!

The major continues saying: „Do not install, although I am very repugnant your Shrek, but looks at your appearances, certainly is the Inner Court students . Moreover, Five Rings cultivates is, definitely was One Word Battle Armor Master. Relax, I will not give you any opportunity. How you install again, I will not show mercy. Come, gives them to take spiritual to prohibit helmet again. This was basically absolutely safe. Cannot move the thought that everybody well rests here for ten days. I guaranteed, ten days later certainly puts you to walk, perhaps, you will be quite by that time hungry, but definitely cannot die.”

Saw that these soldiers put out helmet to walk, Tang Wulin fierce gaining ground, the whole face was the startled color, „you and you cannot such do. You......!”

The helmet cover falls, intense magnetic field instantaneous assault comes, Tang Wulin body one crooked, softly falls to the ground.

Soul Power of other people were prohibited, wants to revolt is impossible, can only be taken helmet, faints separately.

The major shrugs the arm, „originally this. Shrek student, sly serious. Cannot give them the least bit opportunity. This type specifically aims at spiritual of felon to prohibit helmet to seal up their spiritual sea. Obedient sleeping you. Does not know Shrek Academy to be able because of their this time bitter experiences, later to them good. Also or, dismisses them directly? Do not blame me, strange blamed your Academy being too ruthless. Takes away them, delivers to the guard chamber that side. Ten days later puts them to come out again.”

The soldiers run over, every two person, build the Tang Wulin seven people to go fast.

The major right hand feels the chin of own, on the face is revealing color looking pensive, the sinking sound track: „Lets special action team searching base surrounding, the radar sounding, having a look at them to have concealment same party members outside. Whether especially must reconnoiter Mecha.”

„Yes, Major.”

Major both eyes narrow the eyes, he conduct meticulously is always famous, will not let off any detail.

The darkness guard chamber, regarding army is always the place that the servicemen most fear.

Confinement indoor anything does not have, the entire guard chamber be only two feet high, happen to lets the altitude that the human is unable to sit, inside does not have any ray. One small mouth, can deliver the food to come.

The guard chamber most fearful place was its anything does not have. The average people were closed here, can insist that seven days, that is quite formidable existence. In darkness airtight spatial, spiritual will collapse for a long time.

Tang Wulin they are bringing the handcuff and helmet, static lying down in guard chamber.

Has not known long time, in that darkness spatial, a pair of lifted slowly, gently holds by own helmet, then breaks off slowly it.

Right, is breaks off. Does not have the key and electronic password, helmet cannot open. But actually his stiffly broke off with both hands.

In the hand has the handcuff, is not quite convenient, that both hands fierce makes, metal(s) handcuff instantaneous to shatter, the next quarter, he has also raised own head helmet.

Has rubbed the rubbing the hands wrist, feels within the body Soul Power gradually to restore, in the eye pupil sends out the light purple light.

This breaks free of the handcuff, to take off helmet, is not just Tang Wulin?

He looked at surroundings, companion. He also along with it relaxing.

Has distinguished probably, he first broke off the Xie Xie handcuff and helmet. Then a hand covers the mouth of Xie Xie.

After long time, the body of Xie Xie shakes gently, Tang Wulin said immediately in a low voice: „Let alone words. Maintains silent.”

Xie Xie understands immediately that with the restoration of spiritual, starts rapidly to restore own Soul Power.

Tang Wulin follows a set pattern, unties the companion handcuff and helmet.

Why hadn't he been sealed up spiritual sea by that helmet? Said that does not have what special place. Seals the soul handcuff to seal up Soul Power, this point is without a doubt, even if cultivates for again strong Soul Master, was sealed on the soul handcuff handcuffs, the situation is also same.

But don't forget, Tang Wulin also had the strength of formidable Qi and Blood. When helmet buckles above him, he stimulates to movement the strength of Qi and Blood to pour into the forehead immediately, forcefully a take shape protection. If the major can see at that time helmet inside Tang Wulin, does not think that he can prohibit him, at that time, on the face of Tang Wulin reappeared golden-colored dragon pattern(s).

Has the impediment of strength of Qi and Blood, the helmet seal Spiritual Strength effect was very naturally difficult to realize. The following all were simple. After outside is peaceful enough, Tang Wulin has relieved own and companion prohibiting immediately.

„Academy Taikeng.” Xie Xie cannot bear said in a low voice. The breath of people slightly somewhat is loud.

Yeah, Academy chooses North Sea City is not aimless, here North Sea Corps specially is keeping the pit they! No wonder each knows the person who military training situation, looks their vision are bringing pitying. This did not have on the island, they have faced so the condition.

„Was good, spits the trough to be useless. The situation has not calculated finally badly. At least we now are also in the base, always compares outside is better. Xie Xie, you release to do several things at the same time to reconnoiter.” At the same time was saying, a Tang Wulin tumbling, arrived at the entrance of guard chamber. That is a door, very weighty, locked.

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, concentrate spiritual, feels outside situation. Outside has not guarded. Perhaps is because to sealing soul handcuff and sealing god helmet the effect is too confident, outside guards continually does not have.

However Tang Wulin does not have the general idea, turns around to withstand Xie Xie saying: „Does several things at the same time to be certainly careful, where you only needed to reconnoiter to have Soul Guidance aircraft to be OK. In this base will certainly have many security measures, the thermal imagery type scanner is unable to discover your, but energy analysis meter actually. If were discovered that you immediately let do several things at the same time to dissipate, they will not suspect in any case is us. All careful, brings back to some useful things as far as possible.”

„Good, relax, gives me.” Xie Xie nodded to Tang Wulin.

The Tang Wulin right hand finds out, has not found the way to open the door directly, but comes to side the guard chamber, „here is the vent, I open the entrance, through the Spiritual Strength feeling, this vent is very small, normal Humanity cannot exit, but should your doing several things at the same time?”

The Xie Xie nod said: „Does not have the issue, I can compress doing several things at the same time of energy shape, so long as there is an arm thick crevice, can drill.”( ~^~)

#807: The idea decides

„Good. Come.” A Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Claw stroke, broke the vent gently, Xie Xie Soul Ring ray of light dodged, Shadow Dragon Doppelganger split together, the hand grasped Shadow Dragon Dagger, the drilling into vent of being quietly.

Under Xie Xie Control, does several things at the same time to contract, relies on the creeping motion of body to drill outward, quick arrived at outside.

Outside is a corridor, the surroundings two rows both are the guard chamber. Xie Xie observed around, does not have what sound.

He is extending wall vanguard cautiously, walks, while is observing all around.

Because does several things at the same time, moreover is stealth does several things at the same time, he in fact does not fear is discovered that but actually cannot be discovered the guard chamber, because this will make the person of northern regiment associate to is they ran away.

Luckily, here does not have the energy analysis meter. The guard chamber is not the important restricted area, but is used for the soldier who detains the breach of discipline.

Here does not even have the entrance guard of prison that division region, he very smooth arrived at outside.

At this time, outside weather was completely black, but the northern regiment base is actually brilliantly illuminated, often has the soldier jogging process.

Xie Xie hides in the gloomy corner static the observation, his doing several things at the same time cannot be away from Innate Body to be too far. Takes now cultivation of Soul King as, most can only be separated by one kilometer, exceeds this distance also to maintain the relation and Control, Soul Power and Spiritual Strength consumption can the geometrical multiple increase.

Here was really too big, actually Xie Xie is unable to distinguish him now in any position. But fortunately, he saw aircraft quickly.

Guard chamber not far away, warehouse large door opens slowly, just aircraft that dropped from the distant place slowly opened, stopped into the warehouse.

Those who make Xie Xie pleasantly surprised is, this anchors the aircraft warehouse, in side of their guard chamber location place, but has separated two walls.

The Xie Xie breaking in warehouse fast, just saw that puts up screen on aircraft to open slowly, under four pilot are setting out aircraft.

Xie Xie several jumped over on aircraft, the probe head looked.

This is a fighter aircraft, interior has four positions to sit the human, is not spacious. Internal types of instrumentation equipment seem somewhat are really complex, now the above light is going out gradually. Four pilot are merry has gotten down aircraft. screen that aircraft lifts closes slowly.

In this warehouse, such aircraft also has another. The style is also same.

Xie Xie both eyes narrow the eyes, has gotten down aircraft quietly, returned to the guard chamber fast.

Tang Wulin hear of Xie Xie narrated specific situation, thinks carefully after long time, „this truly is an opportunity. However, perhaps if according to the convention, we do not have that easily to be able aircraft to open. Must break through the warehouse, best is other aircraft carried out task the time, naturally takes off. But this means that we cannot come up to kidnap pilot, such did is too discovered easily. But, aircraft is too small, radically not to spatial that we hide.”

Xie Xie said: „After these pilot leave, the special attendants go, inspect the aircraft condition. It is estimated that before next time will take off, must conduct the inspection.”

Le Zhengyu said: „The superiority of fighter aircraft is speed is quick, once All-Out accelerates, 30 kilometers distance is in a flash already. But the fighter aircraft also has its issue, that is in Placement sets too few, we also need pilot of specialty to operate. The interior is unable simultaneously to accommodate our these many people. Moreover, the probability that two aircraft simultaneously take off was also too small. If the transport aircraft, or is helicopter, the internal capacity is actually enough, but they are too slow in launching phase speed, perhaps we cannot leave the northern regiment base to be grasped.”

Tang Wulin said: „Xie Xie, if in did not consider that in pilot situation, all of us push in a fighter aircraft, you think this has the possibility?”

Xie Xie expression somewhat strange [say / way]: „Is very difficult. Four positions, we have seven people. Perhaps a Lizhi person position not necessarily suffices. That aircraft was too small.”

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, „is only the words of four people, if our some people can drive aircraft, is not good. But the premise must be, our own drives aircraft to be good.”

„own driving?”

Tang Wulin said: „The control of aircraft certainly be more complex than Soul Guide Steam Vehicle, but not necessarily is more complex than Mecha many. Even also wants to be simpler. To leave through Control pilot, uncertainty was too big, completely not in our controllable scopes. Opportunity only then one time, what to do if we do meet being unafraid of death pilot? Therefore, I have an idea......”

„Our does own open aircraft to exit? But, who opens?” [Say / Way] of Ye Xinglan doubts.

Tang Wulin looks to Xie Xie, „we also nine days of time, in nine days, I believe that aircraft in that warehouse also meets the second sortie. You give me to go to the careful observation, how observes them to control aircraft in the launching time, writes down, society. Looks several times. My request is not high, so long as you can open aircraft, and takes off smoothly, acceleration, makes an effort the Power Control system direction, was OK. We only need to fly 30 kilometers.”

Xie Xie stared in a big way the eye to look at Tang Wulin, „Boss, didn't you fear the catastrophic crash? Do you such believe me?”

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, said: „The aircraft crash has the possibility, but there is Zhengyu and Yuan En, catastrophic crash to being insufficient. However, if was defeated, perhaps we really cannot military training. Therefore, all depended on you.”

Xie Xie has swallowed saliva, „do that I try?”

Tang Wulin said: „time also has, we must let plan strictness as far as possible, Xie Xie, for serveral days wanted to be laborious you. Reconnoiters and studies aircraft driving. Pays attention to each detail.”

Following several days, will have the person of northern regiment to examine the confinement indoor situation every day. helmet destructs the internal system, puts on. The handcuff is also same, simple camouflage.

After all, guard chamber is so short, the soldier who is responsible for examining is also only looks at one, saw them not to have any sound also to leave.

Finally time to seventh day.

Xie Xie quietly returns.

„How is it?” Tang Wulin asked in a low voice.

Xie Xie said: „Can confirm, two aircraft in this warehouse, in early and late will carry out flying to reconnoiter task every day separately. When they took off the process I basically to remember. Opens the comprehensive acceleration should the issue aircraft not to be big. When do we move?”

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, „all adapting way (of life) we have planned, is in front of the goal a foot on difference this. This time situation is truly dangerous, but we are Shrek Seven Monsters, in any event cannot such dingy going back. Tomorrow early morning begins. In the morning should be easier than the evening, the person of this time duty is most exhausted.”

second day, in the morning.

Rouff as the flying teams and groups team leader, he is first arrives at the warehouse. With just examined the aircraft attendants to greet, he stands under aircraft, looks at own aircraft, on the face is revealing the satisfied expression.

He liked aircraft since childhood, he likes hovering the feeling in Sky. He is only an average person, in order to into qualified pilot, he has carried on very assiduous exercise. Under the ceaseless efforts, finally started flying five years ago.

From initial practice pilot to the present flying teams and groups team leader, he has made the innumerable efforts, he deeply loves flying.

Before him, is the Federation new-type warplane, Sky Flyer 17, is the 17 th generation of fighter aircraft. Is equipped with the Soul Guidance turbine wheel spraying equipment, adds speed to break through the sonic barrier instantaneously in 26 seconds. Four extinguish the soul aerial cannon, carries on attacks continually, simultaneously may hang eight Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, carries out the upper air long-distance attack. Is the new generation attack machine, may simultaneously ground-to-air, launch the attack to the place. Federation after six years ago replace this generation of fighter aircraft has served, by stable performance and superelevation attacks fast is famous. Most suits coordinates Mecha to carry out long-enduring attack, or as the firepower support use of Mecha regiment.

The Sky Flyer 17 fighter aircraft, 36 meters in length, the wingspan 29 meters, provide a turbine wheel injection engine, needs to slide 900 meters to takeoff to take off.

All these data deeply brand mark in Rouff heart of hearts, he deeply was already loving the own fighter aircraft, is familiar with its each detail extremely.

Sky Flyer 17 complete flying teams and groups comprised of four people, the unit team leaders are also the aircraft commanders, deputy aircraft commander, aerial cannon archer and missile archer.

The aircraft commander is mainly responsible for controlling Sky Flyer 17, deputy aircraft commander is responsible for the direction guidance, the contact control tower and control radar.

Aerial cannon archer and missile archer as the name suggests, the missile archer is responsible for fire control system locking. This is also why Sky Flyer 17 must provide four pilot reasons.

-----------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( ~^~)

#808: Boarding

But the modern fighter with the High-speed development, toward the direction progress of less personnel, along with the Soul Guidance intelligence development, it is said the next generation fighter aircraft was only needing two people able to complete now four people's complete controls.

Rouff has inspected the own flying clothing, as the average person, must withstand assault of fighter aircraft High-speed flying to body, he needs the comprehensive protection of flying clothing and helmet, cannot have any careless mistake. He is always a rigorous person, this is also he can become the trump card pilot important reason.

„Aircraft commander!” Three put on the same aircraft crew to walk from outside with him, was his another three companions. On Rouff face reveals a smile, greets to them.

Suddenly, he is wielding hand stiff in midair, because his surprised seeing, the form drops from the clouds together, is almost only the personal appearance dodges, his three companions already slowly falls to the ground softly.

„Enemy raids!” Rouff comes on reaction instantaneously, but just opened mouth in him, wants great shout. Suddenly, at present one black, fell down slowly softly.

„Reconnaissance!” Low and deep sounds/voices resounds. Several forms stick out suddenly from surroundings, is inspecting surroundings rapidly, they hide in the darkness corner, does not make own expose.

Because must carry out flying task immediately, large door of warehouse was opening, can see inside from outside.

The bodies of four aircraft crew were towed to entrain to the corner in rapidly.

The distant place, several people separately toward sending out sounds/voices that person compared the thumb.

„Boarding, Xie Xie!” Tang Wulin wielded to Xie Xie started.

Xie Xie traces on Rouff, attains one to have Control of round button, simultaneously takes off his helmet, wore on own.

Toward the Sky Flyer 17 button of fighter aircraft according to beginning, immediately, the aircraft top access panel opens slowly.

Yes, has attacked this aircraft crew, is Shrek Seven Monsters. Their of course not under killer, but knocked down the Rouff four people.

At this time, on Shrek Seven Monsters each face is revealing the tense and excited look. This is ‚borrowing’ aircraft! Moreover, they have not taken the fighter aircraft. This does not make is playing.

Starting from this moment, they have handled the illegal matter. of course, so long as can clash, believes that behind had Academy to solve for them, after all, this was the order of Academy, in their hearts did not have what restless place.

Xie Xie first leapt up aircraft, sat in the main driving position. Ye Xinglan also fled, sits in his nearby copilot position. This each position beforehand reaches an agreement. Tang Wulin jumped up aircraft Wings, Blue Silver Emperor flings, Bind lives in the body of Xu Lizhi, to previous, by his strength, has flung the body of Xu Lizhi directly, exactly right falling in engine room, Xu Xiaoyan also almost in same time had been delivered the engine room by Le Zhengyu.

Xie Xie both hands are controlling front aircraft control stage rapidly, „Boss, needs the fingerprint and pupil recognition.”

Tang Wulin waves the arms about, Blue Silver Emperor departs, lives in Rouff Bind below corner, the wrist shakes, Blue Silver Emperor has flung Rouff, looks like the flying trapeze is simply ordinary.

Also is Blue Silver Grass springs, lives in his body in airborne Bind, crosswise, the next quarter, he falls during Tang Wulin grasps. Tang Wulin is raising Rouff, vertical leapt the slender nose position, has given Xie Xie Rouff.

Xie Xie is taking Rouff's finger, is pulling then his head, carries on the fingerprint and pupil recognition appraisal.

„Drop, drop and drop!” Resounds with three sonic-electronics consonants, the measuring appliance light in aircraft cockpit shines in abundance, various types of indicating lamps start to demonstrate the current aircraft condition.

Xie Xie cheers one, „became.”

The Tang Wulin wrist flings, straight that Blue Silver Emperor stretches, returned to the ground Rouff.

„Quickly debugs and starts. According to sets sail officially time, we have one minute of opportunity. After one minute, should confirms time.” After these days observation, all already during their controls. Entire plan also as precise as second.

Xie Xie both hands fast moves buttons, simultaneously compares one not to have the hand signal of issue to Tang Wulin.

The Tang Wulin body, falls on the engine room, in the tail wing front position, „Zhengyu and Yuan En, takes place.”

Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui at this time on both sides wings. aircraft can only accommodate four people, is impossible to push more, can only come flying with special way (of life).

Blue Silver Emperor proliferate from Tang Wulin, has extended the both sides wings following the fuselage, in the meantime, the machine access panel falls slowly, in four people will cover fall.

Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu crawl respectively on the both sides wing, then to Blue Silver Grass own and wing Bind in the same place, Tang Wulin own is also so, just his position in the machine access panel rear point place, it can be said that assumes the center, somewhat rides the feeling of aircraft greatly.

Blue Silver Grass three people of body fixing firmly on aircraft, Tang Wulin lifted the hand to rap on aircraft gently three.

The machine access panel closure, sounds/voices cannot pass on, only then determined through the engine room rap as well as the hand signal. Sits specifically is responsible for observing the order of Tang Wulin in engine room back row Xu Xiaoyan.

Xie Xie laughs, „waiters, we must prepare to take off! The first flight-test and first flight-test, I am quite excited.”

„You, your family Yuan En may carefully also on the wing!” The reminder that Ye Xinglan lets somebody cool off or calm down he said.

„Relax, knew.”

Tang Wulin, Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui three people clearly have outside tasteful, the Tang Wulin body intensity is best, moreover is Captain, the dangerous place must he assume personal command personally. Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu itself has Wings, can flying, the critical moment, be separated with aircraft in the upper air, their survival ability also sufficiently make them live.

Therefore they naturally outside engine room was best to choose.

Xie Xie mold type Control aircraft, „ignition!” His own gave a loud shout, has pressed a red button.

Immediately, Sky Flyer 17 fierce shakes, ear-piercing buzz the whining noise also along with it resounding, the rear turbine wheel injection orifice starts High-speed to revolve, the interior has the intense air current to spout slowly, promoting aircraft to slide slowly forward.

„Day nine, the day nine, why the advanced ignition, please reply.” In this time, in the Xie Xie earphone is hearing the rapid inquiry sound.

He has pulled down sounds/voices immediately desirably, replied: „appear(ance) some small applauses, the servicemen have made me try the firing test.”

„Why the appear(ance) breakdown does not notify first, your flow appear(ance) mistake.” In the earphone transmits serious sounds/voices.

„Sorry, is my flow is wrong.” Xie Xie said.

„Now orders you to extinguish engine immediately, waits to process.”

„Yes!” On the Xie Xie mouth is complying, but Sky Flyer 17 left the engine off warehouse under his Control slowly.

Driving of Xie Xie without a doubt is not familiar, but the aircraft itself weight is enormous, Xie Xie continuously observed Rouff to operate these many days, the control of most foundation will not be wrong. After sliding the warehouse, he needs Control aircraft forward about 300 meters, then turns right, can on the aircraft runway carry on to take off.

„Day nine, days nine, are you doing, why left the engine room.” Angry sounds/voices transmits from the earphone once again.

Xie Xie raised sounds/voices suddenly, panic-stricken saying: „The Control System series malfunctions, the Control System series to malfunction, request assistance and request assistance.” Lifelike of his sounds/voices study, making Ye Xinglan somewhat look askance, because sounded at this time, this completely was not Xie Xie usual sounds/voices.

---------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( ~^~)

#809: The mantle soars

„Do not be flustered, All-Out strives for Control. The service vehicle quickly to your there, as far as possible Control do not have the collision.” That side the control tower instead likely was calm.

Control? of course wanted Control, but was Control quickly is actually taking off.

Xie Xie promotes the pushing ram, aircraft rapid corner, because speed is somewhat too quick, in the process of corner, aircraft crooked, two sides flutter of airplane wings, but is much quicker than normal speed, directly soared the runway glide in the past.

„Day nine, days nine, issue the warning to you. Who you are, dares to kidnap aircraft. This is the capital crime, redundant, this is the capital crime, immediately stops, otherwise, the base has the right to destroy you.” sounds/voices of control tower suddenly becomes ice-cold.

Xie Xie stares, this was discovered that how to be possible? He thinks own study looks like very much!

Sits presses firmly between the fingers a thing to pull down from the engine room in back row Xu Lizhi suddenly, „I think that was this has exposed us.”

That is a small camera, without a doubt, it can transmit the situation in engine room to the control tower, so long as the control tower assigns out the video, immediately can see their here situations.

Ye Xinglan rapid [say / way]: „Quick!”

„I know!” Xie Xie draws the pushing ram, on without enough time runway, because the ear-piercing alarm sound has resounded, can see indistinctly that on the distant place runway is used to be responsible for sealing up the back plate of runway to raise slowly, even if they wait a minute to be able on the runway, was impossible to take off.

In the Xie Xie eye cold brightness glittering, right hand holds on the propeller Control pole, fierce entrains backward.

In an instant, a terrifying thrust force instantaneously in four people engine room maliciously according to chair, but the three people outside engine room only thought transmits vigorously at the same time, extremely intense air current instantaneous assault on them.

Tang Wulin bellows, „Battle Armor!”

Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu simultaneously released own Battle Armor, his own was no exception, was relying on the mask of helmet and mask, this felt better.

aircraft suddenly accelerates, moreover is not the smooth acceleration, the Sky Flyer 17 front noses were lift to beat first, then entire put up aircraft suddenly to leap up.

They now on the glide runway, are not the genuine runways, has more than 300 meters from the front runway, but another side of runway is a lawn, or is Lu Huadai, smooth is smooth, but that is not the flinty ground.

Sky Flyer 17 end injection orifices erupt dazzling orange yellow ray of light, the short 300 meters distance is almost in a flash already. Almost is the flash, they broke in the lawn.

Xie Xie roars, both hands All-Out drawing joystick, the lawn width also has 400 meters, again front was the big piece barracks. If cannot fly, they will directly hit.

At the same time is drawing the control feeling, in engine room four people of Battle Armor as if by prior agreement have also released, no one wants dead, the situation not like they estimate, cannot take off on the genuine runway, can only put together these.

„!” In the Xu Xiaoyan mouth sends out ear-piercing to scream that Sky Flyer fierce fluctuation of 17 in lawn, saw, a 400 meters distance in lawn will arrive at the end, the weighty concrete wall in the front.

At this moment, aircraft fierce shakes, the Sky Flyer 17 powerful engines fully erupt, the nose-high is the same, all vibrations stopped suddenly, the front concrete wall as if to sinking has gotten down, the aircraft base hears a ear-piercing to shatter sound, but under flickers, they broke in the upper air.

„Oh! Flew!” Xie Xie stimulated shouts one.

„Had the collision, quickly inspection is any situation!” Ye Xinglan gets angry to him exclaims.

Xie Xie looked at a measuring appliance, then shrugs the arm, said: „Sorry, I cannot understand. You think that I looked at that fellow's several days control, can real Control put in order to put up aircraft? But judging from the present situation, we at least flew, flew in airborne, this called to hover. Ha Ha! Acceleration and acceleration!”

At the same time was saying, he draws the control feeling fiercely, aircraft increases rapidly.

In the earphone transmits control tower angry sounds/voices, „rapid return, otherwise, starts surface-to-air attack immediately. This is not the warning, this is the order.”

At this moment, in the ground, Soul Guidance rays from airborne have delimited, entrains the dazzling brilliance.

Without a doubt, these Soul Guidance rays are used to warn their.

„Has the skill you to hit father. The truth told you, we were this generation of Shrek Seven Monsters. If we died, you wait to come from the Shrek Academy anger.” Xie Xie roared, then has closed communications device rapidly.

North Sea Corps base, control tower!

In the control tower this time is a confusion, the supervisory system demonstrated that Sky Flyer 17 unexpectedly in the attached runway adds under the lawn condition, used 700 meters distance to complete merely took off forcefully.

Although had been discovered promptly, but all these come is too sudden, all people cannot come in first time reaction.

This situation is it can be said that unprecedented. In communications device transmits Shrek Seven Monsters these characters, some staff ignorant of audience.

That special action team major military officer said right, North Sea Corps is the Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy back garden. But because of so, here people clearer Shrek Academy is also meaning anything, is representing anything.

Reason that North Sea Corps does not have the student who Shrek Academy graduates, existence many political significances, if no support of Federation, this is impossible to achieve. Who does not know that on Continent most outstanding Soul Master came from Shrek!

However, even if they repel Shrek again , not clear Shrek Seven Monsters these significances of characters will not be anything. This simple five characters, are the symbols of entire Shrek!

If Shrek Seven Monsters died here, then, absolutely becomes the stir entire Federation important matter.

Control tower commander-in-chief Colonel Liu Ming the face was green at this time! What situation? When Shrek did Seven Monsters arrive at the North Sea Corps base? The news that he obtains said that base has grasped several high-pitched and fine, may be from Shrek Academy, only needs to detain their several days, bled off on the line again.

The situation that but, that major reported was, these Shrek students should put on sealed the soul handcuff and seal god helmet. Why can they actually drive aircraft to take off?

„Colonel, what to do?” The staff of control tower are looking at Liu Ming.

Liu Ming's breath is somewhat rapid, „immediately puts through the communication of general to me.”

The North Sea Corps armed forces regimental commander, Shen Yue Lieutenant General, is the military new generation dazzling star, 38 years old, became Lieutenant General. Is promoted as an exceptional case by Federation.

„General, the situation is this, please instruct!” Colonel Liu Ming has completed the report of own with quickest speed.

Another side of communication silent, „day character flying regiment take-off, North Sea first Mecha regiment take-off. Ensures their securities. Launches the air cover. If, forcing them to return to landing. How if they insist on, must ensure their securities.”

„Yes, understood.”

Shrek Seven Monsters, the impacts of these characters were too strong, even if Lieutenant General, moreover is at with Shrek Academy disagreement condition Lieutenant General, does not dare to make them die in the own domain.

Shen Yue of military garb stands in the office, her height one meter about seven, the military uniform is straight, the years have not left too many traces on her face, seem are about 30 -year-old appearances. Moreover she is very beautiful, in the past, in Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy, she was also existence of school flower rank.

„Makes the icy peak major see me.” Shen Yue has pressed button on a table, issues the order.

„Shrek Seven Monsters?” The Shen Yue brow is tight, they truly obtain the news, has the Shrek Academy Inner Court student to come to carry out to gain experience. But that Shrek tradition she is knows that she even sent for attempting to go to that islands, is Commander North Sea Corps, is Northeast Military District Vice Commander, she in the military, has the right to speak of considerable degree in the own regiment particularly.

But is very obvious, initially her procedure received the severe criticism of higher authority in short time. Therefore, for her, that islands is a riddle.

Shrek came the human, moreover said that was Shrek Seven Monsters. If is really, that may really somewhat trouble.

Shrek Academy always hides shortcomings, if Shrek Seven Monsters has had an accident own here, the reason how regardless of she explained perhaps, is unable to smooth the Shrek Academy anger.

Shrek Seven Monsters is not the casual choice, after must be previous generation Shrek Seven Monsters retires after meritorious service, again crosses an outside not to know that is how long time, can choose. Moreover in line with too little better than toomuch principle, if no enough good candidate, rather the vacancy cannot appear(ance).

#810: Airborne capture

All previous Shrek Seven Monsters is not ill startled certainly colorful Elite, had two in one generation of Shrek Seven Monsters, because extraordinary event Fallen. That time, deep sleep temperate Shrek Academy has revealed the fang of own suddenly. The retaliatory action of that terrifying, until now also makes the human have a vivid memory.

Shen Yue also sees in the material of military strict security, that event, directly caused Federation Member of Parliament to replace 16 Member of Parliament.

The folk is nobody knows obviously had anything, but that time has had the enormous vibration regarding the entire Federation high level. Actually as to have anything, records without any material. Said the consequence is extremely serious. All and that two died the Shrek Seven Monsters concerned person, all has Transformation of varying degrees. That is not Transformation that anybody is willing to accept.

At this time, Xie Xie Control aircraft was rising into airborne, Sky Flyer 17 speed are quick, far ultra ordinary Mecha. Suddenly the sword, sea has been in sight.

Xie Xie does not have any experience regarding the aircraft control obviously, but the simple direction can complete Control. After rising into the upper air, directly soars the sea direction to fly. Now they need, seeks for that islands.

That islands, actually where?

Xie Xie looks out into the distance, 30 kilometers, in airborne is a visible range. However, was quick his look on the delay. Because he discovered impressively that in distant place sea, has islands existence, but is actually not an island, but is one piece, the entire islands, take a broad view to look, at least has one and 200 islands densely covered in the distant place sea area in very big a range.

„What to do?” He saw, Ye Xinglan naturally also saw.

Ye Xinglan showed the whites of the eyes, „what to do do I know? I am not Captain. Now cannot relate, first flew to say again. At the worst we look to the island in again.”

Xie Xie angry [say / way]: „Academy was also too ruthless, gives us 15 days of time, blocked the coastline not saying that was unexpectedly false including the map, radically was not islands.”

„wait a moment, the map shows me.” Sits said in following Xu Xiaoyan suddenly.

The map in Ye Xinglan, she is responsible for the piloting, she has handed over the map.

Xu Xiaoyan said: „Academy again pit father, but at least they give on our map, the islands shape should not be wrong. Xinglan, you look according to the islands shape, looked from Sky that can find the shape to be similar, has similarly, we toward that side in the past.”

Ye Xinglan eye one bright, hit a sound to refer, „was reasonable, Xiaoyan you were too intelligent. Flies toward that side!”

Ye Xinglan is pointing at the direction of archipelago, then in eyes purple light glittering, looks out into the distance, seeks with the map on shape similar islands.

At this time, Tang Wulin shuts tightly in aircraft back both eyes, intense air current assault his body, is having Blue Silver Emperor luckily forcefully fixed, in addition their body enough tenacity, otherwise, already could not withstand.

Under this position, cannot see is any situation, now can only be waited for that Xie Xie they can guarantee found the appropriate place.

At this moment, suddenly, two howl to resound. Tang Wulin looks up reluctantly, saw only two shadows to pass over gently and swiftly from the Sky Flyer 17 both sides instantaneously, impressively was also two fighter aircraft, many that but speed be quicker than them.

Two fought the undershield a circle, kept off in their front, maintained same speed flying with them. Also is two fighter aircraft, appear(ance) in the both sides, again two, appear(ance) behind them. All is maintaining and their same speed.

In Xie Xie earphone, sounds/voices once more appear(ance).

„Orders you to return immediately, otherwise, direct airborne wrecking.”

[Say / Way] that Xie Xie disdains: „Has the skill you to wreck, won't go how is it?” At the same time was saying, his fierce pushes the control handle, aircraft suddenly accelerates, flushed toward slanting under. Let alone was the North Sea Corps fighter aircraft, Ye Xinglan had a scare by him.

The airborne six fighter aircraft hurry to change the flying direction , to continue to surround toward them.

Without doubt, the Xie Xie flying technology is how regardless of cannot compared with them.

Control tower.

Shen Yue Lieutenant General of military garb rushed to here with quickest speed, that caught the Tang Wulin seven people of majors to stand side her, but, the expression of this major was somewhat restless at this time.

„Situation how?” Shen Yue Lieutenant General asked to Colonel Liu Ming.

„They are very strong, is not willing to return. We sealed off reluctantly, reduce them to approach Devil Islands speed, but their battering were very dangerous, might create the catastrophic crash fate anytime. General, carries on the airborne capture?” Colonel Liu Ming sinking sound said.

Shen Yue brow tight wrinkle, „how long North Sea first Mecha regiment also arrives.”

Colonel Liu Ming said: „One minute soon will arrive. The leading troops also 20 seconds arrive.”

Shen Yue relaxed slightly, „after the Mecha regiment arrives, immediately carries on the airborne capture. Leads to me them. Remember, I must live, cannot injure them.”

„Yes.” What the fighter aircraft in airborne excels is attack, if no Mecha regiment to coordinate, wants to complete the capture is the difficulties matter.

Sky Flyer 17.

„These bastards, they use the airplane tail wake effect unexpectedly we. To, what to do?” Xie Xie is quite annoyed at this time. They were away from the archipelago to be very near. But the control of airborne that six aircraft is really good, unceasing is carrying on a series of impediments, is guiding his off-course. If not Xie Xie several bold collision suddenly, they even might be forced to return to the North Sea Corps base.

But this is not the means that Xie Xie after is a crude person, is really limited to the aircraft Control level. Moreover cannot collide . The opposite party two aircraft came an airborne vertical balance a moment ago unexpectedly, with turbine wheel injection orifice air current assault of airplane tail their aircraft. Caused their aircraft to sink to below, deviated originally the direction. Another several aircraft also followed a set pattern, guiding them to fly toward the side.

Without a doubt, others that six, are trump card pilot. Copes with Xie Xie this young new military recruits, the method were too many.

„Asks Captain, what to do? Lands ahead of time.” After Ye Xinglan slightly one hesitates, immediately said to Xu Xiaoyan.

Xu Xiaoyan hurries by engine room screen, gives several simple hand signals to Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin naturally also saw surroundings these aircraft to their a series of influences. In the eye cold brightness glittering, beckoned with the hand to Xu Xiaoyan, then has referred to own.

In this time, in the engine room, Xie Xie is crying suddenly, „Mecha!”

Under, altogether six Mecha howl, speed is not slower than the fighter aircraft, they all have the painting of black, rapid appear(ance) under. But also at this time, regarding completely found out embrasures under their surroundings six aircraft, clathrias in airborne High-speed spraying, instantaneously 17 gave to cover their Sky Flyer.

These clathrias launch unusual was ingenious, has avoided the turbine wheel injection orifice, moreover after the net was occupied by them, immediately stretches straight, six aircraft powers obviously compared with aircraft, directly lead them to want round trip flying.

Airborne capture!

This situation let alone sees, Tang Wulin they listening not to have heard, this time was also broadens the outlook.

At this moment, has crawled in aircraft back Tang Wulin, suddenly sat the body straight.

Then, a colossus suddenly on appear(ance) before his body.

At this time, that carries on the airborne capture to them six aircraft, driving below six Black Rank Mecha that is responsible for protecting, as well as control tower, is all paying attention to them in the airborne situation.

----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#811: The dragon rides the fighter aircraft

Looks what is clearest is control tower, through the large-scale radar, they can catch the airborne brilliant image. In fact, if North Sea Corps wants they from airborne to hit Tang Wulin, that is not any difficulties matter, by the ground-to-air defense system of North Sea Corps, a piece of Soul Guide Cannon ball in the past, absolutely was evaded not to be possible to evade.

However, can they do really? Even if Tang Wulin they ‚taking advantage of’ walked aircraft, but their status is special, the radical measures are unusable, otherwise has the possibility appear(ance) major problem. Therefore, they can only catch them with the quite gentle method.

Although cannot strike to kill Shrek Seven Monsters, but grasps is absolutely . Moreover, compared with serious results that striking to kill, if grasps, attacked regarding Shrek Academy. Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy or was the military even can say that this was Shrek Seven Monsters that you chose? Also is mediocre.

Therefore, Shen Yue Lieutenant General personally will assume personal command, waits to look that good play that they stress.

But, flickers below, she saw has let her dumbfounded one.

In Sky, has completed airborne seizing six aircraft just about to bring Shrek Seven Monsters and that puts up aircraft to return, suddenly, a colossus has broken open that big net.

Can very clear seeing, 36 meters in length Sky Flyer 17 above, be many one altitude over 60 meters, incomparably majestic huge form. Its weight was really too terrifying, appear(ance), instantaneously brought that to put up Sky Flyer 17 and surroundings complete six aircraft simultaneously falls to falling.

Six aircraft compare thing of course to be much stronger, this is the basis of airborne capture. But when, caught the object to be airborne Tyrannosaurus. The situation became completely different.

The area six, fly straight under! Directly soars below sea area to fall.

Below also six Black Rank Mecha, unexpected, they directly were nearly pounded. Hurries to scatter in all directions to separate.

Tang Wulin lifts the hand, Blue Silver Emperor outrageously crushed on the Sky Flyer 17 cockpits coverglasses, the howling rumor spread to the entire cockpit instantaneously. aircraft also turned into the hood version.

„Xie Xie, prepares the All-Out acceleration.” Now their this aircraft situation is very strange, because of riding of Tyrannosaurus, aircraft tail downward, brings other six aircraft to crash directly. Tyrannosaurus somewhat seems to be vacant, does not know that what happened.

Nearby six aircraft have finally made reaction, they gave up the capture network rapidly, from the sky disperses.

Because of the influence of huge gravity, these six aircraft are unable Control to live in the own airborne stance again, is tumbles, good pilot, in this case wants to maintain own aircraft Control, needs time and formidable psychological ability.

„Acceleration!” Tang Wulin explodes drinks one. Tyrannosaurus vanishes instantaneously, he also returned back of aircraft. Blue Silver Emperor find out, four people of waist of Bind in engine room.

Xie Xie promotes the pushing ram, aircraft in airborne fierce shakes, then accelerated in a direction.

This time Xie Xie, only thinks dizzy, but under the aircraft injection orifice accelerates suddenly, had their seven people to clash fiercely.

First from the sky pulls up, then Control System series naturally lets the aircraft sustain level flight condition. Their luck are very good, is in the direction of archipelago.

At this moment, that six aircraft have not been able the Control good own shape, but six Black Rank Mecha plunged them respectively and ensure the allied force security is most important, prepares to rescue at any time.

The bird that Sky Flyer of Shrek Seven Monsters driving 17, look like emerging is common, non-stop flies the archipelago direction.

„Decreases in the altitude!” Tang Wulin drinks to Xie Xie. Did not have impediment of engine room screen, Tang Wulin sounds/voices to pass on.

Xie Xie big mouth has panted for breath several, „too exciting Boss!”

„Everybody is ready, I shouted that one, two and three, unties your safety belts.” These words naturally were in four people to engine room say.

„Prepared.” Xie Xie laughed, has let loose the Control pole.

„One, two and three!” Tang Wulin drinks three greatly, his fierce jumps from aircraft, at the same time, Blue Silver Emperor entrain suddenly. Under his Control, six forms are almost following close on him, simultaneously is separated from aircraft, appear(ance) above Sky, seven people, under Blue Silver Emperor Bind, have composed a strange shape.

Control tower!

„Is this also good?” Icy peak major dumbfounded looks at this.

In six surrounding and capturing of fighter aircraft and under six Black Rank Mecha, can they also run out of the tight encirclement unexpectedly? When Tang Wulin they jump out aircraft, Sky Flyer 17 entered in the range of that islands. Then flew by far.

The Mecha army of behind big piece arrived, but has not actually entered in that islands range.

Strange appear(ance), just broke in that islands range Sky Flyer 17, the sudden whip, drops from the clouds, wormed one's way into toward the islands deep place, as if appear(ance) any illusory halo, then it vanished to disappear. When does not have the appear(ance) crash should have the explosion that.

Tang Wulin may unable to attend to these now, lifts the hand, beforehand squeezes in the mouth Xu Lizhi to the agile little dragon(s) package that they complete, to reduce the own body weight. Other people are also so.

Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui, one white, one black, two pairs of wings also open, with the aid of airborne air current, diligently leads everybody's body to stabilize as far as possible from the both sides.

„Good quite to be crisply and crisp!” Xie Xie excited yelling.

Since birth, today absolutely is most exciting one that he faces. By road sense that his company crude person is not, can actually bring companion to encircle tightly prominently, what ratio this but also there is to let his stimulated matter?

In the Tang Wulin sudden heart moves, the body sends out brown-yellow halo, immediately, seven people thought that body one light, has to plant to the feeling of airborne fluttering.

Mountain Dragon King Torso Bone takes to Tang Wulin Soul Skill gravity Power Control, when fights with Evil Soul Master, Tang Wulin once repeatedly had used. Besides gravity Power Control, another defense class Soul Skill, but Tang Wulin did not have the means to use now, perhaps in his feeling, that defense kind of Soul Skill must wait till his Seven Rings to cultivate for can use. Therefore, Child of Nature is not his first has actually the unuseful skill.

At this time, Tang Wulin through gravity Power Control, carries on reverse Gravity Control, the gravity reduces, Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui is naturally more relaxed.

Control tower!

„General.” Colonel Liu Ming called out in a low voice.

Shen Yue brow tight wrinkle, but she is the high-ranking after all, can maintain tranquil as before, „considers as finished, making them go. Now I believe that they were this generation of Shrek Seven Monsters. Pays close attention to the Devil Islands sound, the 3rd Rank combat readiness. Let them go, definitely does not have good deed.”

„Yes! 3rd Rank combat readiness.”

Shen Yue turns head to look to the icy peak major, „I think that I need an explanation.”

The icy peak major stands at attention and salutes, „is!”

Shen Yue turns around to walk outward, icy peak major hurries to follow in her behind, blindly follows suit.

Gazes after them to leave, Colonel Liu Ming then relaxed, very early in the morning, makes such a matter, is makes in the person heart not be feeling well really!

Below has transmitted the findings, Rouff and his unit unobstructive, sobered.

Without the casualties, but actually lost Sky Flyer 17, regarding the regiment, this is the quite serious attack.

But, regarding them, Devil Islands is actually the forbidden area, the Shrek Academy person enters that range, they were helpless, the fighter aircraft was naturally impossible to look comes back.

From the sky the glide is steady, Tang Wulin has the thoughts to observe below archipelago at this time. What from the sky looks is very clear, the under big piece and big piece islands, have covered very wide scope, but appeared some are tranquil. These islands all are black, jet black like black ink. The terrain is complex, there is a vegetation, but as if is black, seemed like caught ink.

What is more unusual, in these island surroundings, in the sea water from islands 300 meters range unexpectedly also is black, with blue blue sea water take shape of distant place striking contrast.

Without a doubt, this is not an ordinary place. But this is also their military training place.

Tang Wulin does not think they arrived in this islands to cross difficulties in 15 days, without a doubt, genuine difficulties, likely genuine started from this moment.

„That side!” Ye Xinglan said suddenly that simultaneously lifts hand to refer to a direction.

----------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. Thank everybody's support.

#812: Airborne

Ye Xinglan in observing this islands, is seeking for on the map that Academy is giving the similar shape island.

Looks following her finger direction, appearance on that side relatively big islands and map resembles.

Did not need Tang Wulin saying that Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui have adjusted the direction, flew toward that islands.

They are at about the kilometer upper air at this time, slowly drop. Suddenly, seven people simultaneously felt that the body trembles, as if airborne had any invisible thing to hold them one, distortion of surroundings spatial slight(ly). They continued to fall.

In the Tang Wulin seven people of feelings, this is only instantaneous absent-minded, but on the North Sea Corps radar, their seven people actually vanished.

The gravity clearly increases, entrains the Tang Wulin seven people to fall to falling by quicker speed, the Tang Wulin sinking sound shouted to clear the way: „Everybody do not fluster, will not have the matter. Xiaoyan, Star-time Chains!”

Xu Xiaoyan Soul Ring ray of light sparkle, the fourth Soul Skill release, golden light (Jin Guang) shining Star-time Chains rapid the people links.

They jump out aircraft time, from ground about three kilometers, but from three kilometers upper air, if no in the Wings situation to change into the freely falling body, only takes most two minutes, will pound in the ground.

Even if under the assistance of Wings, when they from ground more and more recently, just passed for five minutes.

Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu have eaten up Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun, have whipped their pair of wings that All-Out to go , the attempt can stabilize live in the body of own, after being insufficient to crash, meeting a cruel death that falls.

Tang Wulin as connection of all people, by the person of that huge Vine connections, he is quiet, as if has not become because of the present aspect startled.

Is nearer from the ground, they more can see clearly, in ground piece of black, but is actually not the rock or the land, in the islands of mountain range fluctuating, is growing Plant, but these Plant unexpectedly are also black. Therefore looked from the distant place upper air that here looks like a black monster.

Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui are relying on the Battle Armor amplification, in the situation of although in the gravity increasing, is adjusting the personal appearance as before reluctantly, flies to the direction of their target island. Was getting more and more near from the ground.

„Everybody prepares against assault.” On the side of Tang Wulin is drinking greatly, five Soul Ring ray of light are partly visible, blue-gold Blue Silver Emperor start in his body surroundings many drilling.

Arrived at the ground shortly, Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu whipped own Wings to melt rapidly brunt, but seven people actually as before were similar to at top speed generally fire into the ground.

At this moment, suddenly, on Tang Wulin Second Soul Ring Great Release of Rays of Light, Blue Silver Grass emit just like the python generally, direct to the ground, his Fourth Soul Ring has also shone, that Blue Silver Emperor becomes is similar to the thigh is thick or thin immediately, digs in the instantaneous downward bend of ground, but the formidable elastic enormous degree is actually melting their assault strength, looks like meat pad, making the momentum weaken rapidly.

Together golden light (Jin Guang) excitedly, just like golden-colored little dragon(s) generally fierce a brace in ground, the formidable counter- tension shoots Tang Wulin, his both arms shake, Bind in companion Blue Silver Emperor vibration, all flings immediately into the people airborne, all momentum also therefore melt, the people in airborne have stopped slightly, falls in the ground again slowly.

Blue Silver Emperor takes back, the accurate landing, is shocking but not dangerous.

„This may really be too exciting!” Xie Xie somewhat excited crying.

Truly was too exciting, such situation, all people were first time face, but has saying that the entire process was also in their control scopes.

Although Tang Wulin is not the aircraft driver, but as motion control of sizing up the situation, all grasps unusual is good. Especially when he releases the Tyrannosaurus god to come the pen, making them be able to get rid of the entanglement of fighter aircraft and Mecha successfully, if not that instantaneous High-speed crashes, wants to run out of the tight encirclement not to be definitely easy, North Sea Corps is not good to cope.

„Is everybody how is it?” Tang Wulin asked.

„Does not have the issue!” The people give all normal hand signals to Tang Wulin. They are One Word Battle Armor Master, although some final time assault, but the Battle Armor defense strength melted all sufficiently.

Tang Wulin waves, the people gather side him rapidly, composes the lineup. Tang Wulin, Ye Xinglan, Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui outside, other three people.

At this time the people can all around a better observation. On the other hand, the sea area of Continent Northeast room was cold, therefore, is growing in this islands the trees mostly are the coniferous forests. It seems green and luxuriant. Made people somewhat depressing was only, here all trees and vegetation even were the earth, all was black, jet black like black ink. Made one be awed at the sight, as if had ghost numerous.

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, Spiritual Strength is assigned away from the capital, is feeling surroundings aura.

He discovered that here all, although is black, but rich Dark Element aura, all are very not normal, with the normal forest not anything too big difference.

What's all this about? The Tang Wulin mind moves slightly.

Without doubt, this place, since were called Devil Island, certainly has its special place. But Academy so-called military training here, will not be aimless. They initially encountered not too wonderful experience including Old Cai, it can be imagined. When which becomes Super Rank Douluo Elite is young is not startled certainly colorful!

„Boss, we now what to do?” Xie Xie asked in a low voice.

Tang Wulin said: „The rest, replied the optimum condition to say in turn first again.” Cannot go forward blindly, Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu just took Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun, consumes is not small, the consumptions of other person also some varying degrees. Especially psychological assault of just landing to everybody was quite not actually small, first under stabilized the mind to say again other obviously were very necessary.

Xu Xiaoyan, Xu Lizhi and Xie Xie first sit down to restore Soul Power. Other four people outside, on Tang Wulin Third Soul Ring shine, halo outward diffusions, Blue Silver Golden Light Wave. Has Element Peeling and community Control formidable Control Soul Skill.

„Zhengyu and Yuan En, you also rest, has me and Xinglan protects, should be enough.”

„Good!”

The Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun backlash effect started to appear, Yuan En Yehui and Le Zhengyu they, although cultivates for is not weak, but the consumption is not small. Especially formerly Le Zhengyu had used Sacrifice, the Life strength consumption is not small. To go to after just All-Out, at this time also was really somewhat exhausted.

In Tang Wulin eyes purple light glittering, the Purple Demon Eyes release, careful searching surroundings, he outward quietly is then proliferating own Blue Silver Emperor, is feeling Life aura on this islands.

Since his Spiritual Strength has achieved Spirit Abyss Realm, his sensation was strengthened before were too more. Especially and Blue Silver Emperor unifies mutually, can easily with all Plant communications.

In this time, suddenly, Xie Xie that sat down first has been opening the eye fiercely, said with amazement: „Why does not have Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, my Soul Power is unable to restore.”

His voice falls, other people also separately opened the eye, in the look have revealed color with amazement similarly.

Right, their feeling are exactly the same, in this jet black such as the islands of black ink, they have not felt any Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces existence.

The Tang Wulin heart moves, hurries to feel with rapt attention. Yeah? Sky over this Devil Island turbulent, does not need Blue Silver Golden Light Wave, here itself passed through Element Peeling to be ordinary. All aura are usual, but Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces is actually nothing left.

Without Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces existence, they cannot absorb these energy restore own cultivation are. Soul Power will consume, only if their Soul Power does not use. But, is that also possible?

As Soul Master, cultivated for particularly has achieved Soul King stage Soul Master, they in influencing subtly will have certain Soul Power consumption, stimulated to movement Soul Power to protect the body became their normally life condition, let alone Mysterious Heaven Skill cultivate grew continually, Soul Power has revolved, although the escape consumption was few, but had. If absolutely does not have the Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces place in one, does not need to output Soul Power, their own Soul Power gradually will also vanish.

The Le Zhengyu discoloration said: „Is this legend place of taboo?”

Tang Wulin looks to him, „what situation is the place of taboo?”

Le Zhengyu sinking sound track: „Our Family ancient book has recorded, in ancient era, some places because of the particularity, was punished by God Realm, thus became the place of taboo. Was eliminated all Life existence possibilities. All Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces are unable in this place take shape. But, here clearly has Plant! If the restricted area, Plant should not existence be right.”

#813: Dies out Devil's Island

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Your guess is perhaps correct, I have not felt any Life aura existence from here Plant.”

The place that they fall to the ground is a quite smooth place, not far away is jet black such as the woods in black ink, the Tang Wulin half step walks, when he palm of own according to a big tree, touch hand is icy cold, not having half minute Life aura to transmit did not say that a thick deathly stillness feeling ascended instantaneously. If not Tang Wulin own Life aura is greatly strengthened, the Qi and Blood fluctuation is greatly strengthened, by this dead air/Qi invasion, the body will certainly be received some degree of injury.

„These trees not real. Probably carbonized generally, firmly like the iron stone, but does not have least bit Life aura.” Tang Wulin brow tight wrinkle.

Does not have including Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, cultivate did not have any significance, the people gathered, regarding side Tang Wulin.

Xu Xiaoyan asked: „Captain, does not have Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, besides affecting our Soul Power, can be also influential to the Life strength? Or can affect our strength of Qi and Blood?”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Meeting. Any life form depends upon in Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces survives, this point is without a doubt. The water and sunlight, are Life origin, the imposing manner that they bring is one sublimation of Life energy. In any Life energy place, our own Life aura unceasingly will not have consumed. In short time is all right, but time is long, perhaps we must turn into the dry corpse here, or with these Plant same carbonization.”

Tang Wulin such remarks, people complexion is a big change.

„That what to do?” Xie Xie somewhat anxious [say / way].

Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, „Academy, since makes us come military training to here, certainly does not make us bring death. Moreover, actually our military training also cannot know where at present. From the airborne bird's eye view, this piece of archipelago completely are black, the coastal water is also. But after the sea area exceeds 300 meters, will turn into the normal color. Infers by this, the normal color sea area should be able to feel Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces. In other words, we when the time comes can try the normal sea area to go to absorb Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces to restore oneself.”

Ye Xinglan shows a faint smile, „you can always be so calm. The situation should almost.”

Tang Wulin smiles, „actually I was also worried, but is worried to be useful. Must face. Good, since has no way absorb Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces to restore oneself, we go to the seashore first, in any case we in assigning time arrived. first closed Golden Road to be, we have a look to the seashore now, then Zhengyu and Yuan En flew, had a look at my judgment was right.”

All these are the jet black islands give the inexplicable pressure, actually at least at present they have not been able to search to observe to be clear are any situations. First seeks for the escape route to be without doubt important, therefore Tang Wulin has not launched the reconnaissance to islands eagerly.

The place that they descend, in this islands peripheral zone, after clearly recognizing the direction, has not walked far, they saw sea.

From airborne looked that black sea with looks from the ground, clearly is two feelings, is in shocks. The ocean waves fluctuate, are whipping the shore, that jet black such as sea water of black ink, looks like the terrifying abyss, momentarily can swallow the human.

Tang Wulin releases Blue Silver Emperor, to sea diamond drill bit.

Blue Silver Emperor just contacted the water surface, Tang Wulin felt suddenly the whole body shakes, a terrifying suction transmits from that sea water. Strength of Soul Power and Qi and Blood of Tang Wulin within the body follows this Blue Silver Emperor to swarm immediately.

He hurries to fling Blue Silver Emperor, but is such free time of flash, before this Blue Silver Emperor turned into a grayish white.

„Do not move this sea water, the sea water has strongly swallows the Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces effect. Once contacts, will accelerate Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces to drain.”

Tang Wulin rejoiced very much that just they directly did not fall into this piece of black sea water, otherwise, so long as gets wet, their consumptions meet the geometrical multiple promotion.

Yuan En Yehui said: „I have a look.”

Tang Wulin has selected, „all careful, felt that to immediately does not come back.”

„Um!” Yuan En Yehui has selected, back Fallen Angel pair of wings releases, a racket, flies into gently airborne. Then slowly float to that piece of black sea water above.

She just now arrives in the sea level, body faintly has the black fog to brave, Yuan En Yehui hurries to pat pair of wings, soars to a higher place. Then lets black fog reduction, then flies toward the distant place.

300 meters distance arrived quickly, between islands and islands, except for the black sea area, because the distance is far, is some clear sea area existence. Yuan En Yehui departed that 300 meters range finally, but in that flash, her form suddenly vanished.

„Vanished? Yuan En!” Xie Xie is greatly anxious, running together of two syllables in rapid speech summon.

Tang Wulin holds him, „do not fluster. First had a look to say again.”

Where Xie Xie can not be anxious! He just about to again says anything, Light and Shadow dodges, Yuan En Yehui appear(ance) in the distant place, then fierce flapping pair of wings, flew just like arrow dart again, floating falls to the ground.

Xie Xie then relaxed, goes forward quickly, „Yuan En, you are all right.”

„All right.” Yuan En shakes the head, „similar of situation and Captain judgment, left 300 meters range, after entering the normal sea area, Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces had. However, in the normal sea area, has fierce Sea Soul Beast. I only thought at that time, as if has drilled absent-minded this world, then I noticed that a big mouth opens to me, aura is intense. Then I quickly came back. Strange saying that that Sea Soul Beast is strong, but actually does not dare to contact here Black Sea. However, words that we want, is not easy.”

Tang Wulin brow slightly wrinkle, „do you have a feeling, this place a little likely is Prison Cage, as if imprisons anything to resemble.”

The interior does not have Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, outside is fierce Sea Soul Beast, from their all passes through enters, in addition Yuan En Yehui the turnover, indistinctly can feel this islands as if in a piece ties within.

„Truly, a little looks like.” Le Zhengyu nodded, „instead here me was feeling that is very uncomfortable. It is estimated that you are also same. Here any Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, all have not been full of the deathly stillness, this feeling may really be uncomfortable! Do we have a look to the deep place?”

Tang Wulin shakes the head, „is not anxious. Outside bad risk came from Sea Soul Beast mainly. But Sea Soul Beast generally speaking cannot leave sea. We must find the escape route to be good first. Yuan En, you try again, if flies from the high place, whether not to be attacked by Sea Soul Beast.”

„Good!” Yuan En Yehui complies with one, pair of wings to flap, flies to higher airborne. However, has not waited for her to depart in the Black Sea direction, suddenly, she projects on hundred meters airborne personal appearance to crash suddenly, whipping wing that although she goes all out, has crashed to 50 meters stabilizes lives in the own personal appearance.

„Bans spatially!” Yuan En called out with amazement, „above resembles invisible strength, I fly about hundred meters, seems like patted a palm of the hand, my reaction is luckily quick.”

Prison Cage! These two character once more appear(ance) in the mind of people. This time explanation, only then these two characters were most accurate.

Cannot ascend to heaven, cannot enter the sea. Enters comes and unable to exit. Without Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces. Then, can only wait for death here inadequately?

Tang Wulin takes the bull by the horns, „walks, I the thorough islands have a look.” He always believes that since Academy makes them come here military training, certainly has the Academy goal and significance. Academy you do not have any reason to send in Prison Cage them.

--------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#814: Breaks, another world

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin pushes to the front, walks toward the Devil Island deep place.

In the island does not have the road, only then the jet black woods, are unable to take one's bearings, can only walk toward the deep place.

Enters in the woods, Tang Wulin formerly once felt the deathly stillness of having been to becomes even more obvious. surroundings air somewhat cloudy and cold, majority were walked in forefront Tang Wulin blocks. His that Golden Dragon King bloodline aura, vigorous such as fierce positive, scatters the majority of cloudy and cold deathly stillness, bringing companion to be continually thorough.

Did not need Tang Wulin saying that everybody also as far as possible saved own Soul Power, Control is not making Soul Power past voluntarily. Soul Power must keep critical moment use. If could not find one to connect the Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces place in the islands, they need sooner to find the way to come facing the present predicament.

Tang Wulin walks, while is observing the weather, they were in the morning ‚borrowing’ aircraft set off, the weather was gradually bright. At least outward looks from the island that does not have what different place.

Actually is how huge strength, can make piece of archipelago well turn into this appearance! Very obviously, this should not be artificial, because Federation simply does not have the significance this.

Since is not thinks that then, this piece of Devil Islands appear(ance) should be the natural situation. Then they from where do come?

Has what huge Soul Guidance Method Array on the island, is stripping Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces in air continually? Can if so, then, Black Sea explain? Black Sea has to swallow all energy terrifying ability directly.

Walked for two hours, on the people slightly saw the perspiration, but to save Soul Power, they have not used Soul Power to promote speed. In Soul Guidance Storing Device has certain food, but shut tightly had eaten for serveral days much, had not supplemented with enough time. At this time can only save as far as possible practical.

„Everybody rests same place.” The Tang Wulin sinking sound said.

The influence that the whole, he comes under here is smallest, formidable suddendly Golden Dragon King bloodline aura, in short time will not come under the too tremendous influence. May be this, continued time to be long, was not good. Only if he breaks through own next Golden Dragon King Seal, has the possibility of persistent resistance.

Tang Wulin has climbed up big tree fast, to the high place, looked into the distance to the distant place.

black forest seems to be vast, when he looks to the Devil Island deep place, is indistinct, as if saw piece of purple-black is partly visible.

purple-black? What is that?

Only looked at one, Tang Wulin felt that an intense palpitation arose spontaneously, making him as if have a body to be ripped the fragment(s) general feeling.

Very strong big energy! It is not right, since has energy, energy should also be Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces part. That place, perhaps is a breach!

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin spiritual inspires greatly, after returning the ground, immediately told companion that own sees.

Takes a break, eats something again, their set off, this time, finally had the explicit directivity once more.

Also walked for two hours, they spread that black woods finally, but the earth is as before jet black, spreads to the distant place. This time, even if in the ground, they can see distant place that purple-black.

purple-black ray of light is partly visible, to human a terrifying dying out feeling.

„What is that?” Xu Lizhi shouted one lowly.

Le Zhengyu frown said: „I felt that is very difficult to be thin. As if the whole body must be torn into shreds discomfort.”

„I am also.” Xu Xiaoyan is panting for breath, Le Zhengyu hurries to keep off before her body, she is then more comfortable.

„Returns the woods.” Saw that companion reveal the color of pain, Tang Wulin has issued the order immediately.

He also has the similar feeling, because his own Golden Dragon King bloodline aura is powerful enough, does not have companion to be so painful.

retreat, returns to remove to the woods, there is a mask of woods, was much better.

„That aura is really fearful. But probably does not belong to we have seen any attribute energy. Actually is that what?” Ye Xinglan sinking sound track.

Tang Wulin said: „Must be able to determine to near the examination. You are waiting here, I had a look in the past.”

„Captain.” Xie Xie holds on Tang Wulin, „I go, my speed is quick, I use Battle Armor, even if there is any improper, can hurry back as soon as possible.”

Tang Wulin shakes the head, „your speed truly is quick, but your resistance ability is not good. I have the strength of support bloodline, relax, will not have the matter.”

On the body resistance, truly nobody can compared with resulting in Tang Wulin, Yuan En Yehui is not good.

The takes a deep breath tone, Tang Wulin no longer saves own energy, One Word Battle Armor covers the whole body, golden-colored mask closes up slowly, isolates his Innate Body and outside, strong Qi and Blood fluctuation also along with it filling the air.

Tang Wulin moves sideways, left the woods. Acceleration that suddenly does not stop, directly soars that purple-black ray of light appear(ance) direction to dash about wildly to go.

Really, has the isolation of Battle Armor, all felt that was much better. However, Tang Wulin actually as before can feel, that as if can crushing all energy be getting more and more near and constantly strengthen with own.

Strength of Soul Power and Qi and Blood unifies perfectly, told the revolution according to Mysterious Heaven Skill way (of life), the Tang Wulin right hand wiped on the forehead, Golden Dragon Spear started, the lance point outward, pointed to the front.

golden-colored halo takes Golden Dragon Spear as to assume the umbrella shape advance state-of-art, making that terrifying aura ratio force as far as possible. The pressure reduced, Tang Wulin speeds up speed once more. He can feel that own strength of consumption Soul Power and Qi and Blood is quick.

That not by Devour, but to resist that terrifying aura consumes.

Near, was getting more and more near. After he runs out of the kilometer, he even competently felt that the surroundings air is to shatter. These to shatter air sway on own, looks like a handle handle sharp knife blade is cutting his body unceasingly. Made him have to stimulate to movement many energy to resist.

Under the One Word Battle Armor surface starts to reappear the dragon scales design, Tang Wulin has no recourse, released Golden Dragon Body.

Low and deep dragon roar regarding his body, withstands that formidable to shatter feeling reluctantly. At this moment, suddenly, he only thinks the front, the present all turned into purple-black, his body looked like by any thing Devour has gone. Shakes fiercely! Formerly the terrifying pressure instantaneously vanished, whole body one light, he arrived at another world.

Tang Wulin big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath. In just that flickered, he felt really the body of own must be torn into shreds completely. Battle Armor must unable to withstand. But at this time, all oppression strength all vanish, making his whole person have to plant to want the weak general feeling.

Slightly after doing pants for breath, he discovered that own places in huge valley. In valley no longer is unexpectedly jet black, the surroundings green and luxuriant growth many Plant, the distant place, a huge purple-black light beam is shooting up to the sky, sees it, beforehand palpitation once more appear(ance). But what makes Tang Wulin surprised is, here has Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces existence unexpectedly . Moreover, is quick he to feel, in this place, the Life aura rich degree goes far beyond outside world.

He is Plant System Martial Soul, to the Life aura sensation is clearest, is only the takes a deep breath tone, has the whole body washed clean feeling.

„Good, has not received and instructed can come.” In this time, somewhat hoarse sounds/voices is resounding. In Tang Wulin heart one startled, when turns around to look, discovered that an old man is tilting the head looks at own.

He seemed is really too old, height approximately in one meter about eight, but actually some rickets the body, somewhat disorderly white hair sagging, on the face full was being surroundings, chicken Pi Hefa. In the hand is grasping a walking stick, the eye pupil is very limpid, not pale yellow.

He was too old, therefore Tang Wulin can only force to see from his facial expression that he seems is smiling.

Tang Wulin hurries saying: „Hello. I am Tang Wulin, came from Shrek Academy.”

The old man slight bow, „knows and knows. Shrek Academy. The young fellows, you very handsome.”

Tang Wulin scratches the head, „older generation(s), can you tell me, where is here?”

The old men said: „Here is Devil Island, of course is living the devil(s) place. Ha!” Spoke these words, his own has smiled first.

Is living the devil(s) place? The Tang Wulin heart moves slightly, from front old man, he cannot feel the least bit threat, even cannot feel on this to have the energy fluctuation of least bit. It looks like the ordinary old person of last years of life.

Tang Wulin said: „Academy makes us come Devil Island military training, does not know that what the military training content is?”

The old men shake the head, „I, no matter these. However here some people can manage. Then, your Academy very long has not seen somebody off. Everybody is waiting. Comes with me, I lead you to pass.” At the same time was saying, he has turned around, supports the body of own with the walking stick, is walking toward the valley deep place that the step limps.

#815: Nightmare and Disillusioned

„older generation(s), wait a moment. I have other companion. They what to do? Can I take them to come in?” Tang Wulin asked.

The old men stop the footsteps, „can you take them to come in?”

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: ‚That wants me to exit to be good first. But, I do not know how should exit.’

The old men he he smile, „therefore , you should better first come with me to say again. Here cannot exit.” Then, he continues toward valley walks.

Tang Wulin has not said anything again, hurries with coming up, is supporting by the arm the old man on own initiative.

This old person walked seems is really too difficulties, the step limped. Tang Wulin gently is holding his armpit, reduces the weight of his body.

„older generation(s), or I at the back of you.” Tang Wulin said.

„Good!” The old person is impolite.

The Tang Wulin squatting down body, carried the old man. Old person's body is very light, regarding Tang Wulin this grade of strength, he does not have any component.

„Um, walks toward . The boy of good intention. However, I must remind your am, on Devil Island, the good intention is not useful. Moreover very probably brings to you troublesome.” sounds/voices of old man transmits from the back, Tang Wulin smiles, in direction that the old man refers, fast vanguard.

valley is very big, the ground is not smooth, but various Plant grow is good, many Plant are Tang Wulin hears something never heard of before. Moreover he discovered pleasantly surprised, because of here Life aura extremely rich reason, even if desirably meditation, is not only during the breath, the strength of his Qi and Blood will restore subtly, simultaneously leads Mysterious Heaven Skill to revolve, gradually is resuming the beforehand consumption.

Really, Academy will not find the place that keeps them from surviving to carry on military training.

Quick that Tang Wulin walks, the place that because he must quickly find is good to go to companion also to meet, because he knows, if own does not exit, time will grow everybody to be certainly anxious.

Across a piece of jungle, Tang Wulin oneself cultivate to restore was similar. At this time, the front topography suddenly changed low, the ground also turned into piece of purple-red. Those who make the human shock, Tang Wulin saw that place huge purple-red light beam appear(ance) place.

That is together seems very anomalous giant ore, it inserts in the ground, inserts in valley, only reveals part. That terrifying purple-red light beam, to airborne extends from this ore. Sees that purple-red giant ore, Tang Wulin only thought that a whole body severe pain, the body and Soul of own as if must be torn into shreds, stuffy snort, on on one knee knees down.

The golden dragon scales piece stress, proliferates the whole body rapidly. Battle Armor also flickers to release below. Under their protections, Tang Wulin felt better several points.

„Well!” The Tang Wulin back after behind old man surprised one, the next quarter, Tang Wulin has stood up.

„older generation(s), are you all right?” He cannot see the back old man this time strange look.

„, I am all right. We already became a habit here all.” The old men said: „You are truly good, first time saw the person who the stone of Ruin can block may not be really many. Most people can the stupor, I thought you also to be able.”

Has Tang Wulin gawked, stupor? Since knows that own may stupor, why he has not reminded......

He thinks of here, suddenly, at present one black, anything does not know.

Tang Wulin fell to the ground softly, old man then takes back has cut the hand on his neck, „was really a dumb kid. If this dumb kid places our that little while, where can live! Saw that a stranger so is close, really acts recklessly. Nightmare, comes out and come out! Throws this boy, how making me have a look at him to take to bring in his companions.”

The form as if walks together from the air, arrives in front of the white hair old man.

This similarly is an old man, seemed also compared with the white hair old man young many, but the stature was more grandiose than him.

„Disillusioned, is this boy of this batch of sending? Does own come in?” Nightmare referred to putting on Battle Armor Tang Wulin as before.

„Yes! own comes, as if also good. Throws him, looked that he can own take to bring in the companion.” Is called the Disillusioned old man waved.

„Why is I? How don't you go?” Nightmare very unsatisfied [say / way].

Disillusioned smiles, „not why! Because you cannot hit me. So is simple.”

The Nightmare eye stares, surroundings has black air current appear(ance) faintly, but next quarter he returned to normal, works on the ground Tang Wulin, „being disinclined manages you, came some small toys with great difficulty, I may have no free time to pay attention to your this old ghost.”

Then, he swings the body in a flash, next one flickers, baseless vanished.

Disillusioned has rubbed rubbing hands, in the limpid eye pupil full is excited, „! Had some small toys with great difficulty. This time cannot be so easy to put them to walk. How can make them be at the brink of collapse actually did not collapse? Um, this is a very interesting proposition, has been out of practice, must practice.”

When Tang Wulin sobers, the side encircled completely the kind look, was not just own companion.

„Boss, you awoke.” Looks at Tang Wulin to wake, Xie Xie called immediately excitedly.

Tang Wulin stands up from failure to sit up rapidly, traces the neck of own, the body does not have what ill place.

„How do I come back?”

Le Zhengyu shrugs the arm, „flies, flies from outside. With artillery shell, is Yuan En you following. What's the matter? What has discovered?”

Tang Wulin slightly does to hesitate, before own, all that experiences said.

„Can be the illusion?” Ye Xinglan asked.

Tang Wulin shook the head, „and is not the illusion. Strength of my Soul Power and Qi and Blood truly restored, that place rich Life aura vacation not. The preparation, that place should be our military training genuine must go. We must go.”

„Good!” The people do not have the means to restore Soul Power here, but the Tang Wulin present condition actually restored the peak.

Tang Wulin said to Xu Lizhi: „Everyone two Restoring Stuffed Meatbun, making everybody restore the peak the physical strength, then nobody Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun is ready. Also, your Crystal Bun also gives everyone one, in making these Steamed Stuffed Bun situations, your Soul Power also suffices to support Battle Armor All-Out defense?”

Xu Lizhi said: „Does not have the issue, I consumed before very slightly. Ok.”

Crystal Bun, is Xu Lizhi fifth Soul Skill, after taking, can let edible within one minute, the body surface increases a crystal protective layer, its effect is equal to own All-Out defense ability one time.

But this Hard Crystal Bun also has an issue, that is manufacture time must be quite long. Very difficult manufacture in the combat process to come out, must prepare ahead of time.

Why this was also on that day they, when facing Evil Soul Master, Xu Lizhi gave everybody without enough time the manufacture reason.

Each manufacture takes ten minutes, moreover is big to his own Soul Power consumption. But the advantage is, this Hard Crystal Bun his own ate is also some effects.

Xu Lizhi manufacture Restoring Stuffed Meatbun has eaten to everybody first, recovers the energy. Tang Wulin starts assault that arranges to wait a minute.

After careful ponder, he had the plan.

Cultivates, everybody is Five Rings, but by Soul Power, Yuan En Yehui has achieved 58th Rank, is away from 60th Rank recent one. Ye Xinglan also had 56th Rank. Other people also mostly in 55th Rank about, have Tang Wulin own or 51st Rank.

Therefore, the Soul Power issue is not big. Most important was the body withstands ability.

-------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#816: All charges

Tang Wulin has experience that had formerly charged, strength of assault that Ruin the frontage withstands is most intense. Without a doubt, he must keep off in forefront, but other people must withstand from assault in all directions. At this time, his Golden Dragon Frantic Domain will take an important role, in addition needs eye Star-time Chains. Under numerous in addition holds, should be able to make them go through the difficulty.

After one hour, all person preparations finished.

Tang Wulin said: „Steamed Stuffed Bun takes well, listening to me to order to eat again. Preparation.”

At the same time was saying, he own Golden Dragon Spear horizontally before the body, lance point outward.

All people put on Battle Armor, the Tang Wulin sinking sound shouted to clear the way: „To!” At the same time was saying, he pushed to the front to clash.

Star-time Chains rapid all people link. Tang Wulin has not actually used Golden Dragon Frantic Domain in first time, because the Domain consumption is too big, the earlier period could not have used.

What Yuan En Yehui uses is Fallen Angel changes body, but is not defense strength stronger Great Titan Ape changes the body, reason that so, Tang Wulin has the consideration. If Great Titan Ape changes the body, assault that in the volume too big situation, Yuan En Yehui receives will be also bigger, instead might as well change the body with Fallen Angel, has own to keep off in front, assault that everybody withstands will be smaller.

Had experience, quick that Tang Wulin clashes. He has blocked directly that terrifying energy. But that energy is everywhere, from all directions assault their bodies.

All people promote own Soul Power, in the Le Zhengyu hand Holy Sword wields, besides Yuan En Yehui, several other people were all many Holy Light. Although next quarter Holy Light on to shatter, but can resist the flash to be always good.

In the Ye Xinglan hand Star Divine Sword wields, selects point starlight to wield the powder to all around, that starlight also fast similarly to shatter, can only reduce some pressures slightly.

All person various show its energies, suppress that to own tears into shreds the pain, follows close on behind clashes before Tang Wulin.

Because there is Star-time Chains existence, therefore Tang Wulin can feel everybody's consumption clearly, Ruin energy assault on the body, they are the average consumption. Although Tang Wulin own in front, when charge him consumes to be much bigger.

At this time cannot save. The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, under foot ring of light shines, the Golden Dragon Frantic Domain release, his body instantaneously was also inflating three meters.

Three meters high body compared with formerly wanted majestic many, has blocked overwhelming majority energy assault, speed also along with it speeding up. Other Shrek Seven Monsters six people obtain on Tang Wulin to send out the energy in addition to hold, the pain reduced immediately.

Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Spear shakes, the Golden Dragon Ascends The Heavens opening, the spirited dragon roar sound counter-balances Ruin aura that is flushing directly, his body also starts fiercely is shivering.

Every time goes forward a step pressure to promote, but the present is withstanding of seven people.

Tang Wulin hands over the left hand Golden Dragon Spear, whole body scales Great Release of Rays of Light, right hand Golden Dragon Claw springs, Golden Dragon Fearful Claw wields outrageously, but before what is different, time that his Golden Dragon Fearful Claw wields, Golden Dragon Claw as if illusory glittering, that flash, Golden Dragon Claw in fact has completed consecutively nine times wielding.

This was Golden Dragon in Golden Dragon Nine Styles searches the claw, Tang Wulin searches the claw and own Golden Dragon Fearful Claw Golden Dragon of Ancestral Master instruction unifies, originally creates this type Golden Dragon dead out, the front air was torn into shreds instantaneously, the strength of these Ruin also came in an instant to shatter. The strength of Tang Wulin Qi and Blood fierce feeble.

„Bean Paste Bun and Crystal Bun, eat!” He explodes to drink one, Golden Dragon Spear punctures suddenly, Golden Dragon Soars!

Dies out to break spatial with the aid of Golden Dragon, again before Golden Dragon Soars instantaneous clashes, he quite therefore gave companion to open passageway.

The people full speed follow up at the same time, ate Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun and Hard Crystal Bun.

Outside everyone Battle Armor rapid appear(ance) crystalline lens, have been isolating the strength of outside Ruin.

Hard Crystal Bun Tang Wulin is also first time eats, the effect is much stronger than the imagination, felt that on looked like the whole body were also many armor piece, although that Ruin energy was also decomposing Crystal Body, but actually decompose themselves to protect to be much slower than directly.

In Golden Dragon Frantic Domain and Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun add on under the function of Hard Crystal Bun, the people felt that pressure relief, All-Out initiates the charge.

Food System Soul Master early fighting strength is weakest, the amplification was also well below that these have the amplification directly Soul Master. But with cultivation for the promotion, Food System Soul Master ability gradually will appear. Their amplifications are more direct, side effect is smaller , to continue time longer. Moreover not broken danger.

Food System Soul Master be more difficult than Auxiliary System Soul Master cultivate, they need more vigorous Soul Power to promote , but once Food System Soul Master is the certain extent, his function must certainly above Auxiliary System Soul Master.

„Puff!” The feeling of instantaneously blowing off made Tang Wulin spiritual inspire, this has proven, before he saw that old man was is not having a dream.

Other people are also felt that whole body one light, the next quarter, their appear(ance) in valley that Tang Wulin once had been.

The pressure reduces suddenly, surge Life energy that in addition instantaneously is used, makes everyone in gulps pant for breath. Also revealed the color of feeling relaxed.

Tang Wulin gold helmet gold armor, grasps Golden Dragon Spear to stand in the front line. Because before other people, has not replied Soul Power, at this time appears very exhausted.

In this time, Tang Wulin was seeing a black clothed old man, similarly is the beard and hair is all white, but before does not have , that he sees seems that genial, the look is cloudy, aquiline nose, double hand back after behind, let somebody cool off or calm down visits them.

„older generation(s), hello.” Tang Wulin takes back Golden Dragon Spear, nods to that old man.

The old men have a look at him, is having a look at him behind is panting for breath the people, waves, „comes with me.” His sounds/voices sounds somewhat outwardly submissive but inwardly evil-hearted high-pitched and fine, how to make people think a little irritable.

„Yes!” Tang Wulin beckons, bringing companion to hurry with coming up.

The unhappiness that the black clothed old man walks, route is the same with that former Tang Wulin walks, arrived here again, observes all around, Tang Wulin to distant place that was saying that the feeling of purple-black ray of light was more profound.

Although this place has filled with the thick vitality, but distant place that huge purple-black light beam actually as before gives people the intense sense of fear. That is full of the Ruin aura flavor scared, is completely subconscious, not by own Control fear.

Other Shrek Seven Monsters six people to are also observing, is revealing the curious color. Is this their trip of destinations of? Although has been through repeatedly hard and dangerously, but finally.

Across woods, black clothed old man led them to arrive at a stretch of open area to stop.

„Knows why you come to here are?” The black clothed old man light [say / way].

Tang Wulin said: „Academy makes us come to take military service, is military training.”

The black clothed old man has smiled suddenly, he smiles, the wrinkle on face as if must fold puts together, strangeness that could not say.

„Right, is military training. The military training content is very simple, so long as does not collapse, you can stay here, most two years. In this period, so long as your Mental Breakdown, will have packed off, leaves here. Therefore, the kids, you strove for fortunately. Introduced your own.”

Mental Breakdown? Hears these four characters, the Tang Wulin seven people do not have the reason feels the moral nature one cold.

„I am Captain Tang Wulin, Five Rings Soul King. One Word Battle Armor Master.”

„Ye Xinglan, Five Rings Soul King, One Word Battle Armor Master.”

„Yuan En Yehui, Five Rings Soul King, One Word Battle Armor Master.”

„Xie Xie, Five Rings Soul King, One Word Battle Armor Master.”

„Xu Lizhi, Five Rings Soul King, One Word Battle Armor Master.”

......

-----------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#817: Severe pain

The situation of people are similar, therefore also basically is the registration character.

Listened to their introduction, on the black clothed old man face not to reveal the least bit to be surprised, light [say / way]: „I called Nightmare, believes that you will remember quickly my name. Here is Devil Island, your location place, is Devil Island central zone Devil Valley. But I am here devil(s), you can call me Nightmare Old Devil.”

Nightmare Old Devil? He obviously is a human, why can say devil(s)?

The Tang Wulin heart is surprised, but does not have well to ask.

„older generation(s), what do we now want to make?” Tang Wulin asked. Must make clear them to do anything to be good here!

Nightmare smiles, „does not use anxiously, some are you must do. Later here is the place that you rest. Remember, does not want, because the curiosity attempts to approach that side Ruin's Light, if were contaminated by Ruin's Light, nobody can save you. Yes?”

Ruin's Light? Tang Wulin of course is curious, not only he, other people are also very curious that Ruin's Light what's the matter. The purple light that shoots up to the sky looked that can the palpitation quite a while, actually that is how fearful existence! Moreover they can feel that reason that this Devil Island outside fills dead out, should have the direct relation with this Ruin's Light.

„You just arrived today, tomorrow, your military training will start directly. Food own looks, in forest some are various types of food. Good, arrived here.” Spoke these words, Nightmare Old Devil turns around to walk, his body suddenly became illusory, as if moved sideways, vanished in the field of vision of people.

Nightmare Old Devil walked, Tang Wulin said: „Everybody rested first same place, restored the physical strength and Soul Power said again. Here Life aura is rich, very much has the advantage to us.”

The people somewhat were already impatient, does not save the place that from Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces slightly, arrives at this so Life aura rich place, how they can not grasp time. Regarding Soul Master, what but also there is full a more important matter compared with Soul Power?

companion rest, Tang Wulin also sat cross-legged to sit, with rapt attention meditation, here Life energy rich before surpassing him, has felt in any place, even if on Sea God Island, did not have so rich Life strength. This has the extremely good help function to his cultivate, Blue Silver Emperor in Life aura rich place cultivate, definitely has the twice the result with half the effort effect.

Tang Wulin is just about to enter the meditation condition, suddenly, a crisis transmission, he has opened the eye subconsciously. Then he saw that a shadow is pulling out in the own direction.

It is not good!

His subconscious both hands lift, promotes.

But that shadow comes was really too quick, Tang Wulin stuffy snort, transmitted vigorously, he pulled out strikes flew.

Not only he, other Shrek Seven Monsters people also suffered same attack, time, seven people under the unexpectedness, all pulled out leaning this way and that strikes.

What situation?

They are almost the quick release own Martial Soul, hurrying gather. But also at this moment, the body transmits the intermittent stabbing pain.

When lowers the head looked, sees only place that pulled out strikes, gripped eyelets, had blood to flow out faintly. Pricking next one already after turning into ignition feeling.

A Xie Xie first pitiful yell makes noise, must grasp the punctured place with the hand.

„Do not move!” Tang Wulin grabs his hand. He also felt similarly intense stabbing pain, those who make him be startled, even if by the strength of his bloodline, is unable to weaken that pricking.

„Toxin?” Ye Xinglan tolerates the severe pain, on the face look actually also changed.

„On your this vigilance, is called Shrek Seven Monsters? You believe that here was safe?” Nightmare Old Devil sounds/voices from transmits in all directions.

„Enjoys this nerve poison well. Does not need to attempt to treat or resists with Soul Power, useless. Suffices sorely for two hours, naturally will restore. Um, lets the appearance that I have a look at your pain quickly, did not have the mood to be so joyful for a long time.”

Nerve poison!

In free time of Nightmare Old Devil speech, the Tang Wulin seven people of aching feelings started to intensify rapidly, Assault System several people are better, Xie Xie, Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi are complexion are pale, the sore whole body shivers, if not clench teeth to endure patiently, perhaps already could not withstand.

They somewhat understand finally Nightmare Old Devil that Nightmare Two Word came from where.

But, they then just came! Moreover, but improves their vigilance, was this too a little ruthless?

Tang Wulin situation best one, is not because he is not sore, because his withstands the ability far supernormal person. Passed through suffering of that many Golden Dragon King bloodline, he endures patiently the ache ability strong.

But is in such a case, he is also the forehead sees the perspiration, body slight(ly) is shivering.

„” Xie Xie cannot endure patiently finally , said. His called, looked like has sent out signal, other people were also in abundance stuffy snort make noise, the emanation pain of not being able to endure patiently call.

Hurts for two hours! The Tang Wulin heart twitches, is this also training one way (of life)?

Passed for ten minutes, besides Tang Wulin, Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui, other four people hurt swayed back and forth on the ground.

Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan sit cross-legged to sit on the ground, are shivering, the distance that the body keeps collapses is not far.

Strange saying that this severe pain has been strengthened.

Tang Wulin can also stand reluctantly, but the body also starts to rock.

In this time, the aching feeling was weakening several points suddenly, then starts to weaken slowly.

The potential of human body is infinite, when the pain starts to be weaken, although is as before painful, but at least felt that will be better.

Finally, when ten minutes, the aching feeling already reduced to a supportable range, the people reluctantly sat.

„This was also too ruthless, our anything has not done. Demonstration of authority?” Xie Xie complained.

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Was we are negligent. Including Old Cai and Ancestral Master they dreaded that very much here military training, we should carefully be more right, later wants is the rest, must keep the human to admonish. Two hours that luckily, that older generation(s) said deceive our.”

Yuan En Yehui said suddenly: „, The nerve poison I have not necessarily understood some, this Little Thing is not easy to dissipate, it may be......”

Her voice falls, the people aching feeling of suddenly starts becomes fierce. Really, is not easy to melt!

Hurts for ten minutes, the slow ten minutes, hurt again......

The body of this process to human suffers is part, suffers to spiritual also similarly is extremely fierce! That feeling probably is, just Control you are insufficient the sore stupor, what makes you experience profoundly is ache Peak.

One hour later, people perspiration leaves like the rain, soon collapsed.

Tang Wulin also sat , he Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui also reluctantly support to sit, other four people can maintain sober were very not easy.

Xu Lizhi when is not that sore leaps act to meet some manufacture Restoring Stuffed Meatbun maintains the physical strength to everybody.

Xie Xie looks to Tang Wulin, „Boss, you knock down me, I must unable to bear, was too sore. Hurt in the bone. That convulsion ache really quite hard to endure.”

Yuan En Yehui stares to Xie Xie, „is not good, cannot faint, if the nerve poison in the comatose condition, likely will injure to internal organ(s). When sober can through stimulating Soul Power protects oneself. Boiled to be all right. Xie Xie, insists.” At the same time was saying, Yuan En Yehui thinks that Xie Xie extends act , draws him to own side.

Had Yuan En Yehui as the dependence, the Xie Xie mood has stabilized.

In this time, sounds/voices of applause is resounding, „good, one hour did not have the stupor. Your withstanding ability are quite good. Looked in you display in outstanding share, this first Test, even if were.”

Nightmare Old Devil appear(ance) in the line of sight of people, in his hand is also taking again a small jug, arrives in front of Tang Wulin, he gives Tang Wulin the jug, „experience teaches, does not need me to teach you. This is the antidote, wipes directly in the sores.”

Tang Wulin received the jug, a forced smile of face. Somewhat helpless [say / way]: „Nightmare older generation(s), your this also really comes up to give us a demonstration of authority!”

Nightmare Old Devil light [say / way]: „You, since arrived here, we must be responsible for you. All that you withstand now, is the future may face. The human body has important characteristics, that is two times withstands with the carrying capacity that first withstands has Heaven and Earth Difference, particularly withstanding at heart. Good, this.”

Then, he stands up, once again vanished.

---------------------------

Recently in the family had an accident, affected to me is big, I tried hard maintain the renewal, but Monday three stopped temporarily, normal two. Extremely was sorry. But asked everybody to make me adjust the condition. Thanked politely.

Before I have said that for me, this possibly is in the life most suffering and painful time, hopes that everybody can understand. The normal renewal, I will try hard maintain.

#818: Too cruel

The Nightmare Old Devil words made in the Tang Wulin heart slightly have the comprehension, he held this military training properties indistinctly, but had no way to talk clearly completely.

Tang Wulin gives Ye Xinglan the jug, „you wipe first. I admonish.” At this time, pain is not that intense, Tang Wulin is supporting standing up, this time he does not dare to be negligent, takes out Golden Dragon Spear, is observing all around vigilantly.

Cavern.

Nightmare Old Devil reappears from illusory, in the cavern has a gigantic crystal ball, the diameter has one meter fully. Inside Light and Shadow is glittering, not just Tang Wulin and his companion this time situations?

Disillusioned Old Devil stands in front of the crystal ball, in the mouth „” makes noise, „cruel, you were really too cruel. Did not reach an agreement wanted the light point? How to come up so to be ruthless. What to do if they couldn't withstand to collapse? Haven't we resulted in play?”

Nightmare Old Devil ill-humored [say / way]: „Does a bit less this set, you do not know that excited, haven't I known you? In view of the different situations, of course must adjust the difficulty. These kids can enter valley by own strength, the body carrying capacity is quite good. That made us seek for their limits to be good gradually. However, they also are really pure laughable. Unexpectedly anything believes.”

Disillusioned Old Devil smiles, „obviously is one hour, you must say that is two hours. What medicine did you just give them are?”

Nightmare Old Devil has also smiled, in smiling face has been full of the mean flavor: „Was quick you to know.”

Tang Wulin is last smears the medicinal ointment to wound , after the medicinal ointment smears, clear cool, comfortable of not being able to say. The place that before was damaged because the severe pain was inflamed, but after spreading this medicinal ointment, inflamed vanished unexpectedly rapidly, the cool feeling made the human enjoy.

Xu Lizhi, Xie Xie, Ye Xinglan and Le Zhengyu sat, on the face full is the appearance of feeling relaxed.

In this time, is smearing medicinal ointment Ye Xinglan to sway from side to side the body of own first gently, „is a little itchy. Was the wound is better? This was also too quick.”

Her saying a saying, about the same time smeared the medicinal ointment with her the Xu Lizhi expression also becomes strange, „probably was a little itchy!” His gently in wound surroundings flexure, this flexure was unimportant, the itchy feeling increases instantaneously, his body not by Control sways from side to side.

„Quite itchy!”

Tang Wulin excitedly discoloration, that medicinal ointment?

After several minutes, the wonderful itchy incomparable feeling appear(ance) in his wound place, that itchy, is wishing one could lets the human own has torn into shreds the feeling.

Xu Lizhi cannot bear both hands go to the body of flexure own, the clothes of quick upper body had been ripped open by his own, the body was also left bloodstains by flexure.

Tang Wulin clenches the teeth, relies on the astonishing willpower strength to resist the itchy feeling, the intention is moving, the Blue Silver Emperor release, Bind fast lives in the hands and feet of companion, pulls open their hands and feet, does not make them go to flexure.

„Boss, lets my flexure flexure, lets my flexure flexure, was too itchy, could not bear!” Xu Lizhi yelled.

Pitiful yells resound, compared with formerly ache time also wants fierce several times. The ache endures patiently relatively fortunately, this may not be easy itchy.

The fierce itchy feeling, making the bodies of all people twitch.

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, the body shivers many Blue Silver Emperor to release, not only Bind lives in the hands and feet of companion, but also is squeezing in Blue Silver Emperor their mouth horizontally, has cut by biting the tongue of own in order to avoid them because of the pain in excess.

This where is military training? Simply on suffering of trouble-maker! No wonder they said that own is a devil, they are, they are!

The fierce pain made the convulsion that the body of everyone went all out, the itchy feeling has continued for a half hour. When that itchy feeling removes finally gradually, the people somewhat suffocated. Especially Xu Lizhi and Xu Xiaoyan situation is most awful. Xu Lizhi gave the feeling of person even likely is thin one.

Tang Wulin big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath. At this time he gradually unties in companion Blue Silver Emperor Bind, everybody gathers.

Xu Lizhi and Xu Xiaoyan already complexion pale white fell into half comatose condition, the Xie Xie situation is slightly better than them, by Yuan En Yehui. Le Zhengyu complexion pale white, is hugging Xu Xiaoyan. His situation was insufficient to be so bad, because the Life strength formerly consumed excessively, therefore, the body resistivity naturally also dropped much.

Tang Wulin, Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui three people can also maintain sober, but their bodies similarly often will also twitch, slight(ly) is shivering.

Tang Wulin grasps Golden Dragon Spear, unceasing comes absorb Life energy in air to recover the energy through the deep breath. As Captain, he cannot get down absolutely but actually, he must protect companion.

Has saying that Nightmare Old Devil this demonstration of authority took a profound class to them, that is, when regardless of cannot readily believe others, must momentarily maintain the vigilance.

„Good, compared with imagination. Hungry, eats a thing.” Nightmare Old Devil from the nihility, in the hand has been raising a big gift box once more, arrives in front of them, opens the gift box, inside has eight fully, is all kinds of good food, fruit.

Nightmare Old Devil very natural is placed these food in front of them, then shows a faint smile, the hand signal that makes invitation, turned around to vanish.

Saw food, the Tang Wulin heart shivered, he liked eating, moreover formerly consumed that in a big way, facing so numerous good food, the intense impulsion made him want to overrun.

But, can he overrun really? God knows in these food has to intoxicate. They just had undergone nearly the tribulation between Life and Death. If comes again one time, no one can guarantee that everybody can collapse.

Is unedible, the good good food, cannot touch. Although in the Tang Wulin heart has told him, this time should not suffer again, these food should not have the issue. But if, this time he has believed Nightmare Old Devil, that next time? Who can know when is that behavior Test?

takes a deep breath tone, Tang Wulin sinking sound track: „From now on, regardless of Nightmare Old Devil sends any thing we unable to touch, everybody admonishes carefully, first recovers the energy. You rest, I am defending. If were hungry, first eats dry rations. After Lizhi restores to come, makes Steamed Stuffed Bun to eat to everybody.”

Ye Xinglan nodded, in her hand starlight blooms, selects point Star Grain(s) to fall, cuts these food completely broken.

Tang Wulin and she looks at each other one, he understands that this is she is strengthening the own faith.

„Waste food is ignominious behavior! I use the own prestige to guarantee that just these food did not have an issue. Your this psychology withstand ability, but also is really the weak pity.” Nightmare Old Devil is full of the ridicule sounds/voices to resound.

Tang Wulin remains unmoved, „, when just sent the antidote, your moral behavior has exhausted, from now on, we will not believe your any a few words. Since our military training contents must survive here for two years, then, we, so long as survived diligently on the line. The work you do not take the trouble.”

Cavern.

„Such quickly came on reaction? Moreover seems is very firm.” Disillusioned Old Devil surprised saying.

Nightmare Old Devil shrugs the arm, „is that also what kind of? Then just started. But is a appetizer, behind some are feast is also waiting for them.”

Under persevering of Tang Wulin, the companion physical ability and Soul Power gradually restore. Nightmare Old Devil appear(ance), the rest, in addition has not had Xu Lizhi Restoring Stuffed Meatbun again in turn, the people restores to the optimum condition finally reluctantly.

Brings Food System Soul Master is being this, will never fear that has not eaten.

-------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#819: Na'er?

Ye Xinglan watched the weather, „already a day. What to do should we then?”

Tang Wulin thinks that said: „Anything does not do, keeps here cultivate, our, besides Lizhi, their one group, is responsible for guarding. Other people on meditation cultivate, considered close up here. This place Life aura is so rich, has very big advantage regarding our cultivate.”

The people nod in abundance, they felt. Although beforehand experienced inhuman suffering, but in this place cultivate, truly has the twice the result with half the effort effect. Life energy in air is most pure Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, complements one another with the characteristics that Mysterious Heaven Skill grows continually, when cultivate compared with the effect in Academy is better obviously.

Some Xu Lizhi fear [say / way]: „That Nightmare isn't Old Devil easy to let off us?”

Tang Wulin sinking sound track: „Is ready to cope with anything to resist by whatever means available. Everybody has remembered, we do not eat here thing as far as possible, does not drink here water. The potable water that we bring is saving using. First watches changes quietly, they also will certainly have any movement. If we moved first, was very easy to be swindled in this completely strange place. Therefore we must wait for them first act .”

„Good!”

The people comply with one separately, starts cultivate respectively.

The calm of Tang Wulin has given everybody not the small confidence.

„Well, what is that?” Xie Xie has referred to the front suddenly.

The light yellow mist wells up slowly toward them, not only the frontage, this yellow mist from comes in all directions.

Tang Wulin hurries to shout to clear the way: „Holds the breath. Everybody was careful.”

The new pattern came.

At the same time was saying, Tang Wulin has given a hand signal to Yuan En Yehui.

Yuan En Yehui Soul Ring ray of light glittering, has released immediately own Great Titan Ape Martial Soul. The double fist brandishes, bunch of Air Artillery rumble toward all around, as far as possible scatters these yellow mist.

But at this moment, under their bodies also surges massive yellow mist, completely covers in which their seven people directly.

The flash before stupor, in the Tang Wulin mind the consciousness of appear(ance) is, should not stay in this place, because this place is also Nightmare Old Devil leads them to come!

Seven people fell to the ground slowly softly, quick fell into the comatose condition.

yellow mist diverges, two forms arrive at side them.

Disillusioned Old Devil over the face wears a smile, Nightmare Old Devil as before is a face is also mean.

„One group of kids, but also wants to play the mind with us. Hey! Let you know and know fiercely.” Saying that Nightmare Old Devil lets somebody cool off or calm down.

Disillusioned Old Devil said: „Good, good. You quickly. Let us have a look, in these kids hearts is thinking anything.”

When Tang Wulin sobers, he discovers own as before also in same place, but companion vanished.

Stands up from failure, he jumps rapidly, on the face revealed the dignified color.

He started somewhat to suspect now that this is Academy makes them come to the military training place really? How all are passing strangely . Moreover, that any Nightmare Old Devil does not train in view of the method that they use likely, likely is only suffering them.

Is Devil Island, actually what kind of place?

„” A scream made Tang Wulin hit to tremble smartly spirit. The squeal is very familiar, should be the person of understanding, but is actually not one of the Shrek Seven Monsters.

Is who?

The Tang Wulin quick release own Battle Armor and Golden Dragon Spear, in this strange place, he must hit 12 spiritual to be good.

companion do not seek in the side . Moreover, this place is Nightmare Old Devil leads him to come, should not stay here.

After Tang Wulin slightly does hesitates, fast in the direction that sounds/voices transmits runs.

„” Is a scream transmits, but he has not directed the direction. Tang Wulin shuttles back and forth in the woods. Suddenly, the distant place, a lake presents before him.

The bund, a fair form is pouring in ground retreat, in the hand is also grasping slowly handle silver light glittering long spear. Her body does not have an inch wisp, seemed formerly seemed taking a bath. But before her body, a python is approaching slowly, this python height exceeds hundred meters, thickly like the water jar, the giant head seems like small house, opens the huge mouth, slowly to that young girl oppression in the past.

„Na'er!” Tang Wulin loses one's voice to call out in alarm, then he completely is without hesitation overran.

golden light (Jin Guang) dodges, Golden Dragon Soars. Among personal appearance suddenly to launch, almost kept off before the Na'er body instant.

Right, that grasps silver dragon spear, is Na'er. But before her body, this python, the whole body is sending out extremely terrifying might.

Tang Wulin face upwards to roar, without hesitation has released Golden Dragon Body, Golden Dragon Roars.

Receives Golden Dragon Roars assault, that python body has contracted backward, it opens the big mouth, has nipped toward Tang Wulin.

In the Tang Wulin hand Golden Dragon Spear sweeps away, happy does not fear. Is relying on the Golden Dragon Body amplification, he promoted Peak own strength.

„Bang” in bang sound, the python head pulled out to strike by him one side. That python eats the pain, on the huge body scales stands erect, comes toward his Bind rapidly.

Tang Wulin complexion sinks to congeal, the thought moves, Tyrannosaurus summon. Passes for day, Tyrannosaurus has been able to summon. Copes with this everybody, is Tyrannosaurus is most appropriate.

After Tyrannosaurus appear(ance), the big mouth opens, bit on the neck of that python. Struggling that the python starts to go all out, on huge body Bind Tyrannosaurus body.

The Tyrannosaurus most terrifying place lies in its formidable linking strength, was bitten by Tyrannosaurus, basically has been doomed the result.

Tang Wulin has turned round, actually stayed.

Na'er is a young girl, was not initially that little girl. Her both hands are not enough to protect the body interesting part completely. time, Tang Wulin only thinks steam to rush on.

He hurries to nip the tip of tongue, lets the own sober several points diligently, then takes off the coat rapidly, throws to Na'er, „puts on quickly.”

Na'er received the clothes, looks at Tang Wulin, in the beautiful pupil is the tears is graceful.

„Elder Brother, Elder Brother you are quite cruel-hearted, why aren't you willing to want me? Na'er where is not good, why you are not willing to want me!”

She does not wear the clothes, fierce throws to Tang Wulin in front, jumps into him to cherish closely grasps his body.

Tang Wulin is been stiff by the whole body that he holds, hurries saying: „Na'er, leaves this. We tidied up that python to say first again that you also did come here military training? Why may Pavilion Master say that you do disappear?”

Na'er sobs to say in a low voice: „Teacher(s) does not want to let me and you in the same place, his offended. Is sent to frontier service here to come me. But, I quite think you! Elder Brother. Do not leave me to be good? Later do not leave me good?” At the same time was saying, she hugs Tang Wulin to hug was tighter.

In the Tang Wulin heart sighed darkly, actually does not know that should say anything was good. But can find Younger Sister, for him is a very happy matter.

Gently traces the Na'er long hair, „don't this, Na'er. We solved the python to say first again.”

Na'er said: „Elder brother, you told me first, did you elect me to elect her?”

Tang Wulin looks down to Na'er, what sees is the a pair of stubborn eye pupil.

„Na'er, I told on that day very clearly you. I......” he just spoke of here, actually suddenly discovered that the Na'er look becomes ice-cold, a chest pain, silver light penetrated his body together.

„Na'er, you......”

Tang Wulin dull looks at Na'er, silver dragon spear in Na'er hand pierced his chest.

On the Na'er face full is the mean color, „why? Why don't you elect me? My anything compared with her, you actually does not elect me. Does not elect me, you die!”

At the same time was saying, the agitation that she makes an effort silver dragon spear in hand, the fierce pain was making the Tang Wulin whole body convulsion get up, the Life strength passed rapidly.

„And, You are not Na'er, Na'er not like this to my!” Suddenly, the eye pupil of Tang Wulin has shone, looks at that whole face mean Na'er, „you are not Na'er, in any event, Na'er not to my act . Nightmare, Nightmare Old Devil. You are not Na'er!”

Tang Wulin roars, right hand Golden Dragon Claw wields, Golden Dragon dies out!

„Puff!” Front Na'er comes to naught instantaneously, python is also. surroundings all become twist.

„Such strong spiritual willpower, wants to make you collapse really is not quite easy! Then, good. Then on Peak some.”

At present all become illusory, Tang Wulin at present one black, falls into the stupor once more.

When he wakes once more, discovered that own returned to the distant place. Stands up from failure to sit up, Tang Wulin subconscious traces the chest of own.

Without the wound, of course does not have silver dragon spear. Na'er is illusory, is Nightmare!

--------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. Thank You (xiexie) everybody's blessing, I strong faces all, in the booth the matter does not fear the matter. Also wished everybody Happy New Year ahead of time.

#820: Mating?

Tang Wulin big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath. Has lived through finally, but for him, when Na'er punctures silver dragon spear the thorn pricks his chest, he at that time shocked and pain is simply beyond description.

Luckily, the firm faith and trust Na'er have defeated Nightmare. Was supports finally, may so, Na'er sounds/voices as if weeping and complaining still reverberate in his mind, made in his heart pain as before. Yes! own has disappointed eventually Na'er.

Then, at this time in dream in sober condition? Tang Wulin is not clear. Because Nightmare was really too real, the pain was also real existence.

In this time, Nightmare Old Devil is reappearing slowly before him.

„Very surprisedly?” Nightmare Old Devil teased looks at Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin complexion sinks to congeal, to this, he really does not have the means to have the respect now again.

„My companion? They where?” Everybody can gather, many will be better.

Nightmare Old Devil said: „Do not worry, was quick you to see them. But you need to do something for me, if you cannot achieve, the consequence will be very serious.”

The Tang Wulin eyebrow selects, „what matter?”

Nightmare Old Devil said: „of course is the difficulties matter, is inferior to this, I make you have a look at the consequence first.”

At the same time was saying, his right hand wields gently, a illusory picture takes shape gradually.

„Has saying that your Spiritual Strength is very good, and willpower is firm. Can such quickly work loose from my Nightmare, at least two Hundred Year come, you should be quickest. This is very good, but, I am very unsatisfied. Since the dreamland is unable to make you feel the genuine pain, cannot let your Mental Breakdown. Then, we trade real slighting the law. I manage him to be called, Heart of People Test.”

The picture presents, inside is divided into three parts, each part is a cavern, in the cavern, has two people respectively.

In a first cavern, impressively is Xu Lizhi and Xu Xiaoyan, a second cavern is Ye Xinglan and Xie Xie, in the third cavern is Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui.

Each cavern is not big, seems has several square meters appearance. Above the cavern is hanging pink photosphere, inside has the mist to fill the air faintly.

„Saw? They are very good. of course, is only the present.” The smiling face on Nightmare Old Devil face is very strange, strange hysteria.

Tang Wulin lets somebody cool off or calm down visits him, „are you how is it?”

Nightmare Old Devil said: „You looked at the pink mist in their room. Through the understanding their dreamland, they should be three pairs. Then, I analyze them, places in a room separately. But that pink mist, is most intense that I can find in view of the medicine of men and women, regardless of human and animals, so long as smelled that mist, the matter that can handle has one,”

Here, he hit a sound to refer, [say / way] that then smiled: „Mating!”

Tang Wulin stared in a big way the eye, warm-blooded instantaneous above, „I spelled with you!” His fierce one step goes forward, a fist goes to the Nightmare Old Devil head bang.

Nightmare Old Devil body illusory, the one of the fist of Tang Wulin from him puts on. Next quarter, he already appear(ance) another side of Tang Wulin.

„Kid, do not impulse. Do you want to make me open that three types of mist now?” Nightmare Old Devil wields, the three groups of pink mist in picture start to ripple immediately.

„Does not want!” Tang Wulin both hands closely grip the fist, because is angry, the nail pricked the palm.

This was too fearful, the intense sense of fear arises spontaneously. His of course knows after that mist was released, what happened. That is an absolute disaster.

Three pairs of lovers exchange, was made anything by that dense fog infection, this simply killing them was crueler.

„You very much want certainly to say. Your here is military training, why must such do, is right?” Nightmare Old Devil shrugs the arm, asked to Tang Wulin.

The Tang Wulin breath shortness, both eyes are red, maliciously is looking steadily at him. He had realized that this Devil Island, is not simple.

Nightmare Old Devil sighed, said: „Actually, all imagine complex many compared with you. First I must tell you am, my age, had 1764 years old.”

Tang Wulin one dull, over 1700 years old? What concept is this? Even if most formidable Titled Douluo and Limit Douluo, is very difficult to live 300 years old.

Nightmare Old Devil said: „You think that I do want to become such old? I do not think that but I do not have the means. I want dead am not easy. Said accurately that I am not Humanity. But is a wisp of ghost on Devil Island. This islands, are no longer existence, because of the arrival of devil(s), lets its appear(ance). But at that time, did not have that many Sea Soul Beast in this sea area.”

„devil(s) is that purple-red ray of light that you see, on Devil Island, is biggest fragment(s). We called it Devil Fragment(s), called Ruin Fragment(s). Each islands on Devil Islands have such together fragment(s). At that time, when these fragment(s) fell into sea, I just with several friends here fish. We are just the average people. To keep a family.”

„That terrifying strength has torn into shreds our fishing boat directly, has torn into shreds our bodies. Ignorant, has not known how long, I had suddenly discovered that I lived. Starting from that time, I turned into Nightmare. Became this person of non- person and ghost not ghost appearance. We are here part, but is actually not able to leave here. Then we such lonely life.”

„Outside person, if enters here, is unable to survive. Only if in you at present valley. But this is our places, the bystander is impossible to come. Until one day, your Shrek Academy older generation arrived here. He is very formidable, formidable by that time we are unmatchable. Here, he and we have fought for a long time, finally, caused heavy losses by Ruin Fragment(s) strength. But he before departure, said to us that makes him obtain benefits with our fights a great deal. He hopes that in the future his later generation can also come here to gain experience. Here, we were really too lonely, therefore, we complied with his request.”

„To you, arrived here is to teach especially. But to us is actually not true, you are only our toys. Soon before, we can grasp Ruin Fragment(s) origin strength finally. Did not need to fear your Shrek Academy anything. Therefore , our these Old Devil heads, can let loose have done let our own happy matter. Although cannot leave here, but based on this, is in us to control. Rattles on! The boys, you accept fate, only blames your lives not being good strangely.”

Listens to the Nightmare Old Devil words, the heart of Tang Wulin to sink to the valley gradually. All are more fearful than the imagination.

His fierce bites the tip of tongue, lets the own sober several points with the aid of the stabbing pain that the tip of tongue transmits as far as possible, „Nightmare Old Devil, you want to make me make anything, is willing to let off my companions.”

Nightmare Old Devil smiles, „military training, that of course was the command prompt listens to direct. I have gotten down the Nightmare curse on you, do not want to flee my Control. So long as I think that momentarily can kill you. I know that you possibly do not fear death, do these you but who you see at present fear? After I let they have the relations, certainly will not kill their, I will give Shrek Academy these contents, sends back them. Oh, thinks to feel that quite excited, at that time, you said that what Shrek Academy can be feels? Is very interesting?”

The heart of Tang Wulin somewhat shivered, „you make me be any me to comply, do not let that mist dispersing, otherwise I will make trouble will not let off your.”

#821: I teach you!

Nightmare Old Devil contemptuous [say / way]: ‚We are the ghost, ghost also feared that the ghost is inadequate? The threat does not have any function for me, handles a meaningful matter. Well what let you do? Um, this, you go to a shore North Sea Corps, steals aircraft to open again.’

Steals aircraft? Why does not know, after listening to this order, in the Tang Wulin heart relaxed slightly, the situation that because this must face the companions is much better. At least does not let the matter that the human collapses.

„Ok, but, I will not open aircraft.” The Tang Wulin sinking sound said.

Nightmare Old Devil said: „This simple! I teach you!”

„Do you teach me?” Tang Wulin has gawked staring, will on the island on Thousand Years old devil(s), open aircraft?

Nightmare Old Devil said: „You cannot suspect that my ability, cannot suspect my intelligence quotient. Yeah, can make the matter that we are interested in few. Come, I teach you to open aircraft. Then, you go to steal aircraft to come back to me.”

Tang Wulin does not have chooses. After 20 minutes, he saw aircraft, Sky Flyer 17, that puts up them to open, turned into Sky Flyer of hood 17.

Looks at front Soul Guidance aircraft, Tang Wulin realized suddenly an issue, cannot bear ask: „Nightmare Old Devil, I learned to open aircraft, opened this aircraft to go, had no way a person to drive two aircraft to open!”

Nightmare Old Devil principle of course [say / way]: „Who made you drive two aircraft to open, I will deliver you, then your own opened aircraft to come back on the line. Devil Island how you come, how can the north regiment go.”

„?” Tang Wulin dumbfounded visits him, Devil Island how to come? Airborne! Also lands to return to the northern regiment?

Are the northern regiment various types of radars ornaments? If own goes back, first time will be discovered that that can also have well?

„Do not be surprised, your own tries to find the solution. You can steal aircraft to run from the north regiment, doesn't have second time means? Good, on aircraft.”

At the same time was saying, Nightmare Old Devil has arrived in front of aircraft, sees only his hand to wield, unexpectedly appear(ance) black steps, direct connection the place of cockpit. From him, Tang Wulin has not felt any Soul Power to fluctuate, but all these that take shape naturally.

Nightmare Old Devil stepped onto aircraft, Tang Wulin sits the copilot.

„I simply speaking, then leads you to realize the aircraft pleasure first.” In the Nightmare Old Devil look flashes through one to be full of the Evil happy expression. At that moment, he narrated a Soul Guidance aircraft flying principle to Tang Wulin simply, as well as the primary function of each button.

Tang Wulin will control Mecha, on the other hand, the Mecha control in fact be more complex than Soul Guidance aircraft. When controls Mecha, not only need control various types of buttons, meanwhile must coordinate the motion of Mecha through some own body movements. aircraft does not need obviously such troublesome, so long as controlled various buttons and types of Control poles is OK.

Tang Wulin earnest is studying, quick wrote down.

„Remembered?” Old Devil asked.

Tang Wulin nodded, „remembered basically.”

„Is very good. Then, I lead you to experience now!” Nightmare Old Devil was saying at the same time, waves, in the aircraft front, cyclopian riprap appear(ance) originally Transformation, the quarry stone sank suddenly slowly, jet black such as the band of light of black ink extends to the distant place, changes into the runway.

In the Nightmare Old Devil mouth exudes one to be similar to the cheers of young people, starts Sky Flyer 17 aircraft rapidly, is operating the Control button on aircraft skilled, draws the Control pole, Sky Flyer 17 slides slowly, starts to accelerate gradually.

Tang Wulin very vigilant has fastened the safety belt to own, a not too wonderful feeling in next quarter on appear(ance).

The Sky Flyer 17 rear area turbine wheel injection orifices burst out orange-red flame , to promote aircraft to accelerate instantaneously suddenly, terrifying pushing back feeling Tang Wulin pressure maliciously on chair, next one flickers, Sky Flyer 17 have soared. speed of this launching does not know that be quicker than on many Xie Xie. As if no including reaction time, immediately already take-off.

In the Nightmare Old Devil mouth is sending out ear-piercing smiles strangely, joystick to the end, Sky Flyer 17 skyrocket directly at the same time, deviated path originally gradually, unexpectedly came one to fly high the empty to turn directly.

Tang Wulin only thinks dizzy, where time could not distinguish clearly completely is Sky, where is a ground.

He only thought that Nightmare Old Devil both hands illusory the rhythm on the control stage, then Sky Flyer 17 after the backward somersault, immediately to the flank barrel, the continual tumbling as if must turn over completely in internal organs of Tang Wulin, is having intense assault and dizziness, aircraft from the sky shuttles back and forth.

......

„Saw. If not obedient, that is the consequence. This dense fog puts, finally you can definitely be able to imagine.”

Xie Xie dumbfounded looks at front Nightmare Old Devil, he wishes one could to rip fragment(s) this fellow. Especially what sees in that picture side stupor Yuan En Yehui to lie down is Tang Wulin time. The extreme fear made him cannot help but shiver.

„You and you cannot such do, cannot such do. You are what kind, I promise you......”

On the Nightmare Old Devil face is revealing the color of Evil, „is very simple, helping me steal aircraft to come back. Opens aircraft? I teach you well, visits you to come time that waste appearance, six aircraft gave you airborne caught, simply was the waste cannot again the waste.”

......

„You!” In the Ye Xinglan hand Star Divine Sword ray of light is radiant, but she is not the first time is patted to be in-situ by front Nightmare Old Devil. Looks picture that at present Nightmare Old Devil releases, her double cheek lump of red, the tender body does not shiver on own initiative.

„Your this is only illusion, I do not believe! Moreover, you Wulin and Lizhi put together, can they be what kind of? Even if your is the anesthetics, they cannot......”

Nightmare Old Devil hey said with a smile: „Can't really? You do not know, between the man and man, can actually......”

„Let alone, I promised you......”

......

„Vomits......” Tang Wulin on one knee to kneel on the ground, has spat for dozen minutes. Even if so, the brain as before is dizzy, in the belly is overwhelming.

He never has such uncomfortably, even if breaks through Golden Dragon King Seal the time not so painful. Nightmare Old Devil led him to fly for one hour. But this hour of time, he has shown the Sky Flyer 17 all limit controls to Tang Wulin, so long as is aircraft itself can achieve, Tang Wulin has all experienced.

Even if his body intensity far supernormal person, after this terrifying High-speed assault and tumbling, could not withstand as before.

Nightmare Old Devil stands before his body not far away, „waste. Looks at your prospect, my old person such big age has been all right, what appearance do you have a look at your likely? Quickly gets up, we come again! Your rested was longer. Not being able to get up words, I must put the gas cloud to your companion.”

„You......”

So three times......

strength as if has been far away from Tang Wulin to go, he only thought that own is ignorant, the whole person looked like the powder has put up. The body is soft, strength cannot use. complexion pale white like paper. He has not wanted to spit now, because simply does not have the thing that anything can spit.

Nightmare Old Devil raised him to get down aircraft, threw toward the ground, own has moved the body, smiling thought aloud: „For a long time did not have this carefree dripping feeling. Why looks the appearance that your pain I so am happy? You said that I am a little mental issue!”

----------------------------------

Sorry, reason that today really has having no other choice. Renewal late, two chapters of Lian Geng.

#822: Vomiting ...

Tang Wulin can very clear hears his words, could not speak back and forth on him. He does not know how should respond is good, he only wants in all virulent languages this world to give this.

The next quarter, he fell to the ground softly, the lethargic sleep in the past.

Light and Shadow flashes through together, Disillusioned Old Devil appear(ance) side Nightmare Old Devil.

„Good! Imagines compared with me bans to toss about. Other people two are not good, this Tang Wulin had insisted three just can also scold you in the heart. Really good, is a good seedling. The good seedling to suffer well. Let the storm come is more violent.”

The following day, Tang Wulin fell into the abyss of suffering. So long as wakes, he will be taken aircraft by Nightmare Old Devil, then rises Sky. Upper air high difficulty skill flying repeatedly.

From his second waking time, has not spat, no spitting, can only be disgusting cannot be disgusting. Dizzy cannot be dizzy.

Tang Wulin knows situation that finally why can appear(ance) collapse, because, he thought that the own distance collapses is not far. If beforehand Senior come here experiences such bitter experience, that collapse was too easy.

How long has not known, after Tang Wulin ignorant cannot feel the pain gradually, he discovered that the own state of mind started becomes clear.

He discovered with amazement that own started the adaptation unexpectedly. Yes, regardless of aircraft in airborne how tumbling, anxious acceleration and anxious deceleration, vertical maneuver, flying upside down. The dizziness feeling cannot again appear(ance). He already gradually became a habit, moreover gradually had the sense of direction in the upper air. He can see sea, can see clearly the surroundings fog, how whatever Nightmare Old Devil controls aircraft, that disgusting feeling has been far away gradually. Moreover takes off each time again time, previous time be better.

Gradually, he started somewhat to feel the pleasure of upper air soaring.

„Walks! Nightmare Old Devil. Continue. You were tired, I estimated that you were old, flew motionless?” Tang Wulin wicked [say / way].

Nightmare Old Devil both hands fork waist, two eyebrows one high one low looks at Tang Wulin.

„Brat, you think that the old man didn't have the means to put in order you? Very good, since you were not dizzy. Then, changes you to drive to try.”

„Changes me?” Tang Wulin has gawked, turns into the driver from riding, this feeling is absolutely different.

When Tang Wulin sits to the driving position, looks at front numerous button and control stage time, why does not know, does not have the appear(ance) strange feeling and frightened feeling in his heart, instead extremely familiar feelings.

Yes! Does not have the means not to be familiar, every day looks that Nightmare Old Devil controls these buttons to suffer own, these buttons early already brand mark in his mind. He has been able clear awareness, which buttons when Nightmare Old Devil presses down own will withstand what kind of assault, can clear awareness, when Nightmare Old Devil appear(ance) what kind of expression, he must do.

Somewhat jerky pressing button, prepares to take off slightly. The familiar feeling becomes more and more clear, lags behind the joystick, Sky Flyer 17 accelerates slowly, then soars suddenly.

When aircraft enters spatial that flash, Tang Wulin only thought that own has to plant to hover, but feeling. Not only the familiar feeling is stronger, that fish enters sea carefree is unprecedented. Before all pain changed into this moment smoothly crisp. He moves several buttons subconsciously, entrains joystick to the final position, direct Control aircraft was coming a tumbling backward in the upper air.

slight(ly) of aircraft in the process of nose oven trembles, some are not steady, Tang Wulin hurries to grip tightly the joystick, Control aircraft has been completing the entire movement actually.

The acceleration , to continue the increasing altitude. Under Tang Wulin Control, Sky Flyer 17 start to get up in airborne flying.

He had controlled Mecha after all . Moreover, after these days suffering, various assault and dizziness that feeling aircraft brings said goodbye with him. Soaring in airborne, he has a feeling of having at one's command, as if this Sky Flyer 17 became part of his body. This feeling was really too comfortable.

At the beginning, Tang Wulin somewhat was jerky in the Control process, but gradually, his movement became skilled. Formidable physical quality in the incisiveness that in the aircraft control manifests. First is his hand fast enough quick, next, body anti- assault strength enough, makes him be able to control this Sky Flyer 17 to make some limit as far as possible the movement.

time, aircraft from the sky goes up and down abruptly, up and down, suddenly the tumbling, crashes suddenly rapidly. Flexible looks like a bird.

After Tang Wulin most likes tumbling, anxiously that feeling of acceleration, looks like releasing for flight, simply is comfortable cannot be comfortable.

Light and Shadow flash through in the side, Control when he has not given full expression aircraft is falling returns to the ground. He discovered that Nightmare Old Devil did not have sounds/voices. When turns head to look, he discovered with amazement when does not know, Nightmare Old Devil vanished unexpectedly.

Cavern.

„Vomits......” Nightmare Old Devil to bend the waist, makes the vomitive the condition, his body glittering in reality and illusory.

„How can like this. Originally sits in the copilot so is really uncomfortable! Why my Soul will receive such intense assault. This mixes the boy, how he such quick can control was so good. This is unscientific!”

Some Disillusioned Old Devil being in a daze looks at Nightmare Old Devil, „your body......”

Nightmare Old Devil beckoned with the hand, „nothing. Some do not adapt. Moreover, our here these many years, what even if there is, you have what not to give up?”

Disillusioned Old Devil „quack” smiles, „is also, we two situations always compare that several fellows to be good. Then, they are also about to regain consciousness. I must pay silent tribute for these kids.”

Control the aircraft steady landing, Tang Wulin is jumping down aircraft time, saw Nightmare Old Devil stands there.

„Who makes you get down , to continue to fly. When practiced me to say has been OK, can.” Nightmare Old Devil waved, is the bang fly is likely ordinary, has caught up with aircraft Tang Wulin.

Insufficient, Tang Wulin also became a habit flying, simply continued to drive aircraft to fly.

Then, in the impression of Tang Wulin, he fully has practiced one month, can achieve with Sky Flyer 17 dissolves as one degree completely.

„Good, arrived here. Today, you can steal aircraft to come back.” Nightmare Old Devil made being utterly exhausted Tang Wulin get down aircraft. Lifted the racket of hand in his top of the head, Tang Wulin has fainted.

The time of once more sobering, the Tang Wulin surprised discovery, own is unexpectedly refreshing, the condition restored the peak. Also by aircraft, Nightmare Old Devil also.

Nightmare Old Devil sat driving position, the Tang Wulin nature in the copilot.

Nightmare Old Devil light [say / way]: „Airborne, did not need to be the safety belt, later I directly flung you. Surplus depending entirely on own. I give you three days of time, aircraft do not come back, puts the gas cloud. Understood what is heard?”

„Understood.” Tang Wulin as if suffered has submitted, lowers the head to comply.

This Nightmare Old Devil drives is very steady, quick, Sky Flyer that aircraft flies 17 has achieved most High-speed. Increases to ten thousand meters upper air.

Does not have the engine room lid, Sky Flyer that the terrifying strong winds sway 17 to shiver fiercely, the ultra-low temperature fast is consuming the Tang Wulin physical ability.

communications device in aircraft suddenly resounds, „here is North Sea Corps, orders your air landing low clearance. Otherwise, will shoot down.”

Nightmare Old Devil smiles, suddenly, he is controlling the Sky Flyer 81 lateral tumblings, on fierce has gripped toward below one. On Tang Wulin does not have the safety belt, sudden Transformation makes him almost be fallen, hurries to hold the arm rest.

„Lets go, I deliver you to get down!” Sky Flyer 17 in airborne fierce shakes, then the crosswise tumbling flings, Tang Wulin did not have reaction to come, suddenly thought that holds the hand of own vigorously, then own seems like lost trash, throwing.

In upper air, dizzy. Tang Wulin first realizes is, on own probably not any parachute and so on thing. Moreover cannot flying companion assist.

Such throws?

His body High-speed drops, ground huge gravity is entraining his body, just likes artillery shell is ordinary, flies to the earth.

These days aircraft driving, making Tang Wulin adapt to the airborne dizziness feeling, where at least was insufficient unable to distinguish clearly is the ground, where is Sky.

First has adjusted the body, he calms down immediately. Blue Silver Emperor rapid from within the body release, each other Bind above his top of the head in the same place, establishes a big net mutually, then the big net tightens slowly, changes into the man-made parachute.

#823: Airborne hijack

speed that air current assault, Tang Wulin drops starts to reduce. Wipes the light smile also along with it appear(ance) on his face. Thinks really I don't have the means? Already thought.

The Blue Silver Grass wondrous use, showed at this time without doubt. If is really the grass, of course is impossible to withstand such strong assault strength, but this is Blue Silver Emperor, in addition has the Blue Silver Overlord Transformation amplification, is only load bearing his weight, that was the relaxed matter.

However, the Tang Wulin smiling face just reappeared, quick stiffened on the face.

Because he saw impressively that two Sky Flyer 17 one plunder from the own side.

North Sea Corps reaction was also too quick!

Two Sky Flyer 17 in airborne have captured, their once more appear(ance) in front of Tang Wulin, speed markedly reduced, then Tang Wulin saw that a big net heads on, covered the body of own directly.

Airborne capture?

This is his second time facing airborne caught, previous facing time, he used Tyrannosaurus to break the capture of North Sea Corps aircraft. These time cannot do obviously again.

Here is nearby North Sea Corps sky sea area, even if crashes, own is also the dead pigeon.

However, was held by the airborne capture network, Tang Wulin is actually not startled counter- happy, the body was brought to fly by aircraft High-speed horizontally. For serveral days suffering of Nightmare Old Devil played very good role. At least Tang Wulin not after that formidable assault strength arrives suddenly on faint in the past.

The airborne capture network transmits intense electric current, Tang Wulin whole body tingles with numbness immediately. Battle Armor protects the body, appear(ance), covers the whole body voluntarily. Tang Wulin cold snort, both hands fling, two Blue Silver Emperor Bind on, increase following the capture network upwardly, Bind on the aircraft tail wing, at the same time, he has drawn is entraining Blue Silver Grass, making own approach aircraft itself more and more.

North Sea Corps pilot had not realized obviously this issue, the airborne capture network caught airborne troops that is the easiest matter, so long as generally the airborne capture caught, the assault strength that had instantaneously will directly make the opposite party lose the resistance, even if the opposite party physical quality were extremely good, that also in the following high-voltage by electronics corona.

So long as is not Two Word Battle Armor Master above existence, the airborne capture almost goes smoothly everywhere. What a pity, this time faces, is Tang Wulin this body intensity is not inferior in Two Word Battle Armor Master existence.

Relies on Blue Silver Grass to entrain, Tang Wulin climbed up the following wing quickly. At this time, this Sky Flyer 17 started to return. Tang Wulin is relying on Blue Silver Grass Bind, drew close to the position of cockpit slowly.

The pilots were driving steadily, suddenly thought that the ray was gloomier, in he is perplexed, near the ear suddenly hears the knocking.

Subconscious, he looks up upwardly, just saw lies Tang Wulin on cockpit waved to him. That meaning, seems makes him exit.

pilot startles greatly, but his reaction is actually very rapid, Control aircraft, has been completing instantaneously a lateral tumbling.

But also at this moment, the to shatter sound gets up, a pair of shining Sharp Claws has grasped into the high-strength glass of cockpit. The next quarter, the cockpit was patted directly broken. Tang Wulin stands up from failure, infiltrated. Fell on the following position.

„Bye!” Tang Wulin pats the ejection button, aircraft also in the High-speed tumbling process, that pilot by ejection. After the ejection exits, will have the parachute naturally. Is relying on sharp Golden Dragon Claw, Tang Wulin in High-speed tumbling aircraft, own steady fixing. Then Blue Silver Emperor drill rapidly, Bind on aircraft, is relying on the mask of Blue Silver Grass, seals up the cockpit temporarily.

Tang Wulin holds own Blue Silver Emperor, crawled the driving position, was skilled and rapid Control buttons.

At this time, Sky Flyer 17 in completely is the ear-piercing alarm sound, Tang Wulin has shut off and communication of control tower first, then holds on the joystick, under a series of disturbance control familiar Control, enabled this aircraft to grasp balanced.

„Whiz!” Sky Flyer 17 rapid passed over gently and swiftly from his side. Obviously was just another aircraft. In front of his flying fast. The airborne capture network releases once more, this aiming at is actually entire puts up aircraft that Tang Wulin drives.

Where Tang Wulin can make its such Control live in own! Pushes the joystick, Sky Flyer 17 under presses suddenly, relaxed the facing set from the airborne capture network in the past, then rear turbine wheel injection orifice Great Release of Rays of Light, promoting aircraft to increase speed instantaneously, one has surpassed another aircraft, flies in the Devil Island direction.

Another aircraft does not want to give up obviously, because Tang Wulin has shut off the communication, behind, a series of aerial cannon sounds get up, the big piece light rain sprinkles.

Tang Wulin is unhurriedly, both hands illusory has swept on front Control board, the Sky Flyer 17 crosswise tumblings, have rapidly made a series of circumvention movements.

Skill named Bat Maneuvers that the matter that he does not know, own displays at this time.

bat relies on the ultrasonic wave to make various keenest circumventions regarding the ascertainment of object, its circumvention movement is most is also unpredictable. The rear aerial cannon fails completely, Tang Wulin turns around aircraft, the sudden nose oven, aircraft from the sky draws together the perfect ring-like arc backward, once more when appear(ance), already in another aircraft rear area.

Tang Wulin hesitant, finally has not launched the aerial cannon, a fierce acceleration, flushes away below sea level direction.

Front aircraft was circled suddenly by the match behind, this of course is the most dangerous situation, because own will directly become a target, will hurry to make a series of circumvention movements. But when he saw on the radar aircraft of Tang Wulin driving is far away, to pursued again already without enough time.

30 kilometers distance is written in water regarding High-speed flying aircraft. ray of light flashes through, aircraft of Tang Wulin control submerged the Devil Island range to vanish without the trace.

„Oh!” Tang Wulin sits in hood aircraft exudes one to cheer, effort has brandished the arm of own, aircraft under his control, falls in the ground steadily. But shortly after Nightmare Old Devil also just just came back.

Looks that cheers Tang Wulin that jumps down from aircraft, on the Nightmare Old Devil face flashes through different color.

„You very happily?” Nightmare Old Devil light looks at Tang Wulin.

The Tang Wulin restraining smiling face, somewhat vigilantly visits him, but said: „You made me who I was achieve. I opened aircraft. Now can let off my companion?”

Nightmare Old Devil has smiled, „lets off them? When I said that must let off them. Come, making me have a look at their present situations.”

At the same time was saying, his right hand in airborne wields, that once picture once again appear(ance).

However, when Tang Wulin sees that picture again, sees impressively is, the bunch of pink mist dispersed in the cavern, have covered six people in three cavern.

„You......” Tang Wulin have a big shock, just because of recapturing aircraft produced excited nothing left.

On the Nightmare Old Devil face reveals the dark smiling face, „embarrassed, incautiously does not have Control to be good, made the gas cloud reveal unexpectedly. This may not be easy to do!”

Tang Wulin one step overruns, right hand Golden Dragon Claw Great Release of Rays of Light, has divided toward Nightmare Old Devil directly. Received these many days to offend, has completed the request of Nightmare Old Devil finally, but he actually......, This time Tang Wulin, already some nearly madness.

If makes companion really......

How they also live!

illusory Light and Shadow dodges, Tang Wulin attack falls on the vacancy.

The Nightmare Old Devil right hand wields, suddenly, the pink mist in that three cavern as if are received Control to be common, was attracted to absorb, restored spherical appearance originally.

#824: Tour in the past?

Tang Wulin has stagnated stagnation, finally does not have second time to begin again. He gets angry exclaims: „Do you want to do?”

Nightmare Old Devil shrugs the arm, „doesn't do, but does not like looking at your happy appearance. Remember, I am devil(s), devil(s) only likes looking at others' pain and sadness, makes me see your joyful appearance again, I make you know that anything is called to forsee the concomitant tragedy.”

The breath of Tang Wulin somewhat is obviously rapid, looks at front Nightmare Old Devil, he never has such to hate a person, may at this moment, in his heart actually wish one could to rip fragment(s) front this fellow.

Not only he suffers his body, but also suffers his heart.

„Actually you how are willing to put my companion to come out.” Tang Wulin exclaimed lowly.

[Say / Way] that Nightmare Old Devil disdains: „That must think your performance, but steals aircraft, you think that I can let off them? Actually, I very much have wanted to have a look, after Mating under their this interlocking, what mood can they be? I have been suppressing the hope of own innermost feelings for you, you should thank me to be right. You have a look, you now this is any expression, quick, smiles one to show me, otherwise, I make the gas cloud disperse.”

„You......” Tang Wulin have nearly bitten a steel tooth, Control that he tries hard the own mood, on the face was revealing a smiling face reluctantly.

Nightmare Old Devil arrives in front of him, has patted his shoulder, „, this is right. Good, you will start next segment. I think that what next segment is? Since could not stump you from the airborne past, then, then, swam in the past, when you swam the past, stole aircraft to come back to the opposite shore, I let off your companion.”

Tour in the past? A Tang Wulin pupil contraction.

What meaning was the tour in the past? Must from that black the middle reaches of sea area in the past, fill from that to all energy Devour several hundred meters sea area tours in the past. Even if so, 30 kilometers sea must cross, in that sea does not know that has many Sea Soul Beast existence.

Can make Federation send a regiment to protect here, but also has established that formidable defense fortification, the Sea Soul Beast strength in this sea can be imagined. Can own swim really in the past?

Nightmare Old Devil lifts the hand, black crystal has flown in front of Tang Wulin together.

„This is my Nightmare Crystal, when you felt own cannot support, pours into which Soul Power, naturally will return to here. Good, then looks at your own. However, if time is too long, perhaps which day, my being able help made them bring to me joyfully, quack!”

In a series of strange laughter, Nightmare Old Devil vanished baseless.

Tang Wulin has gotten hold of Nightmare Crystal in hand, the breath obviously becomes rapid.

He does not fear difficultly, does not fear challenge. However, saw that Nightmare Old Devil likely is not the person who keeps the commitment.

However, what means does he have? Facing the threat of Nightmare Old Devil, he can only do according to his words. Nightmare Old Devil held in his innermost feelings the frailest place, for companion, for everybody, he does not have other means.

Swimming Tang Wulin meeting, but, passes through sea facing that many Sea Soul Beast, this was really extremely difficult. Let alone, in sea another side, is the North Sea Corps defense fortification, he does not doubt, that moment when own comes ashore, will face the North Sea Corps Soul Guide Cannon crazy bang to explode randomly.

......

Xu Lizhi big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath, his clothes were soaked by the sweat once again. In his mind full is frightened, body even not by the Control convulsion.

„Waste, you simply is a waste. You said that you are useful. If did not look that you make the this place like plumply and fair-complected very much, I already made you cut the sliced meat to rinse thinly am eating.”

„Also can see from the appearance of your this waste, in the past, you hide certainly in others behind. Some dangerous always others keep off for you, you said that what you are competent? Cannot exit including 300 meters Ruin sea area, when can you go to the opposite shore? aircraft driving, you used three months of time reluctantly to withstand, unexpectedly also not thin. Waste and waste! Simply is the waste is not good. Your this, can you steal aircraft? Ok, the old man looks for some pleasure from other place.”

Xu Lizhi loud is panting for breath, then he sees, front appear(ance) a picture, in picture, only then two people, one group of strong red fog has lifteds open, covers in that two people.

Ye Xinglan and Xie Xie.

„” Did not see that the body of Ye Xinglan starts to sway from side to side, as if regained consciousness from the stupor, another side Xie Xie body starts to shiver, clothes gradually to shatter. In the Xu Lizhi mouth erupts not roaring of sounds of people immediately.

He rending general was roaring, „did not want and to ask you not want. I go all out, I to try hard. I can certainly swim to the opposite shore go. Certainly. Asked you, stopped quickly, stopped quickly!”

He „puff passes” one to kneel down in front of Nightmare Old Devil, the whole body keeps shivering. His heart must collapse, if because of the hopes, he has not wanted to live really in this world.

„!” The iron fence dropped from the clouds together, blocks plunged Ye Xinglan Xie Xie.

„Goes to sea!” Nightmare Old Devil lets somebody cool off or calm down said to Xu Lizhi.

„” Xu Lizhi roars, both eyes red flushes away to that jet black such as the devil(s) sea of black ink. His madness is waving the arm, while within the body energy by rapid absorb, going all out swims away toward sea.

The wave ripples, he that obese body actually erupted the extremely astonishing potential in this moment, the sea water dispelled to the both sides, was getting more and more weak, but his spiritual was extremely stimulated, if in cannot run out of Sea of Ruin, Sister Xinglan wanted......

The formidable thought is supporting him, within the body Soul Power comprehensive eruption, his nearly madness is swimming.

Nightmare Old Devil stands in the shore, the corners of the mouth place is revealing the Evil smiling face. That presents Ye Xinglan and Xie Xie picture comes to naught to vanish without the trace, saw that Xu Lizhi was ran out of that jet black sea area unexpectedly, finally has drilled into luxuriant blue sea.

But quick, only Sea Soul Beast on appear(ance) before him.

Xu Lizhi madness is waving the arm, Controlling Crane Capturing Dragon and Mysterious Jade Hands, under various Tang Sect secret arts in his All-Out erupts, made in sea appear(ance) vortex. Sea Soul Beast was only torn into shreds by him, his All-Out to go to overruns to the deep place. Until, the bunch of blood fog in body appear(ance), wounds burst open on the body.

......

Lies on the beach, Tang Wulin moves does not want to move, his whole person as if has disrupted came. He also clear remembering, in just that flickered, he has even felt the advantage tooth of that only giant devil(s) fish to prick the feeling of own skin.

Even if the golden dragon scales piece cannot block that terrifying Devour, Demon crystal led him in the final moment, but he is actually exhausted.

Is relying on own cultivation for with the ingenious application of Blue Silver Emperor, he can run out of Sea of Ruin. But, outside sea area, although has rich Life aura, is actually fearful.

In that piece of sea, absolutely does not have Hundred Year one cultivates for Sea Soul Beast, because Hundred Year one cultivates for Sea Soul Beast perhaps already became these formidable Sea Soul Beast desserts.

Each Sea Soul Beast is such terrifying, they form groups. Can frighten many colleagues on the land Golden Dragon King bloodline aura, is very limited in the role that in sea can play. Tang Wulin has put together completely All-Out. But, can only go forward 500 meters in sea, finally the strength uses up, cannot resist Sea Soul Beast attack.

Sea Soul Beast is limitless, making him unable to see the hope. He has gone all out to slaughter reckless, but always has and more formidable Sea Soul Beast appear(ance).

It is not good, I am incorrect! Even if I can become Titled Douluo, perhaps cannot run out of this sea area. In the heart of Tang Wulin started somewhat dejected. But whenever, at this time, he will think about own companion. If own is unable to overrun, companion can......

Thinks of here, his heart clutches suddenly tightly, subconscious stands up from failure to sit up.

A person came from the distance, arrived in front of Tang Wulin to sit.

Sees him, Tang Wulin has gawked, because comes is not Nightmare Old Devil, but is not his companion. Arrived here to be so long, he was second time sees this.

„older generation(s)!”

On the beard and hair white Disillusioned Old Devil face throughout is all having the genial smile, „your matter I knew. Nightmare simply was too despicable.” At the same time was saying, on his face revealed the hating bitterly expression.

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket, recommended the ticket, tomorrow can go home. Really recently had come across specially specially the difficulties matter, hopes that the new year will be good. Also blessed everybody health.

#825: Absorbs Ruin aura

Looks at his appearance, in the Tang Wulin heart has ignited a hope, „older generation(s), you help me, please help us. This way, I could not bear.”

Disillusioned Old Devil sighed, „sorry, I did not have the means. Nightmare Old Devil was too formidable, I am not his match. I can only while time that he rests, comes to see you quietly. What he makes you make, are you so painful?”

Tang Wulin hurried to say the experience of own simply, after listening to his narration, the Disillusioned Old Devil forced smile said: „He has really given you one not task that is possible to complete. Let alone you were only One Word Battle Armor Master, even if you were Three Word Battle Armor Master, wanted such to break through this sea area is also impossible. In this sea area, but there is Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast existence!”

The Tang Wulin delay said: „What to do should I?”

Disillusioned Old Devil said: „Nightmare this fellow never anything patience, moreover his is not very calm, drags again. Your friends were dangerous. I do not have the means to help you rescue them, but I currently have means that can make you break through this sea area.......”

„Any means that asking you to teach me.” Tang Wulin looked like held straw to grasp, hurried to ask.

Disillusioned Old Devil sighed, said: „This means are very dangerous, will be big to your body load. Do you want to study really? It is not good, will make you have the danger of being frightened out of one's wits!”

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, „I can look, Nightmare Old Devil wants to suffer us, had not planned that makes us leave here. Is dies in any case, at least I want to spell, I cannot look helplessly my companion were suffered by him. Asked you to teach me.”

Disillusioned Old Devil nodded, „that good. Looked that your this child and I am predestined friends, I show a bright way to you. You saw Devil Island central that Ruin Fragment(s). In that Ruin Fragment(s), is having extremely terrifying the strength of Ruin. But what unusual artificial brick is, when its crash world, but also follows with Ruin completely opposite Life energy. Therefore can suppress this Ruin Fragment(s) strength to be insufficient outward diffusion many of too.”

„Because of these Ruin Fragment(s), was having this piece of archipelago. But surroundings Sea Soul Beast, in fact is attracted by Life energy that Ruin Fragment(s) associated comes. Simply speaking, these Sea Soul Beast like that rich Life energy extremely, you can also be able to feel this Life strength the advantage. But similarly, their very frightened that Ruin energy to own corrosion. Therefore, wants safely broke through this sea area, only then means that that is, let on you in the contamination Ruin Fragment(s) aura. After feeling that Ruin aura, Sea Soul Beast will naturally hide you by far. But by your body ability, wanting tour over 30 kilometers of course not to have the issue.”

......

„But, how can I be able to infect Ruin Fragment(s) energy?” A Xie Xie face hopes for looks at front Disillusioned Old Devil.

The Disillusioned Old Devil forced smile said: „That will be painful, and is dangerous. If your willpower is not very firm, Ruin aura can Devour your Soul, then Devour your body. You believe that your spiritual is firm enough?”

Xie Xie [say / way] without hesitation: „I can, I be able. For Yuan En, for everybody, my anything. Asked you, older generation(s) taught me.”

Disillusioned Old Devil sighed, „that good. You must be mentally prepared. That process will be painful.”

......

Yes, is painful. When Tang Wulin approaches Ruin Fragment(s) slowly, but approaches to its kilometer range in time, he feels that pain that Disillusioned Old Devil said.

In his hand is grasping together purple crystal, in crystal is sending out strange energy fluctuations, can attenuate reluctantly or filters some Ruin energy terrifying aura.

May so, these Ruin energy after the filtration becomes more exquisite wells up to his body.

That painful feeling is not the dependence endures patiently to withstand, looks like the body is ripped fragment(s), then combines. Unceasing is duplicating the process of this Ruin and fusion. Suppose, when own saw the when body of own was decomposed, what feeling that can be!

All sensations are that clear, the feeling deep brand mark that even each cell to shatter reorganizes continually again in his Soul deep place, this suffering cannot describe in the spoken language. Even if by the firmness of Tang Wulin willpower, will send out pitiful yells unceasingly.

In process that whenever his body to shatter reorganizes gradually again, the body will contaminate vague purple-black. Tang Wulin knows that should be Ruin aura that Disillusioned Old Devil said.

Cavern.

Nightmare Old Devil curls the lip, „you suffer them more ruthless than me obviously, actually also works as the good person. Really is not a good thing.”

Disillusioned Old Devil hey said with a smile: „This is I and your difference. You were doomed only to make devil(s), perhaps, I can also make Saint.”

„farting and farting! You are Saint of nonsense. If they know that you give their Disillusioned Crystal to enhance their body and spiritual sensitivity, can count with ten times of feeling own painful existence, will also be grateful you?”

Disillusioned Old Devil principle of course [say / way]: „My this is good for them. Only the such keen sensation to own body Transformation, where can a clearer limit, if the pain is not very intense, is rashly thorough, what to do couldn't the body withstand collapsed directly? I am the big good man.”

„Nonsense and nonsense. You are want to visit them to withstand many suffering that's all. Should one month almost suffice Ruin aura, lets your such lane, not sufficing of three months of impossible absorb.”

Disillusioned Old Devil, „you are also not look with great interest!”

Really effective!

When Tang Wulin steps into that jet black such as Sea of Ruin of black ink once more, immediately feels Transformation on own body, own energy was markedly reduced by Devour speed. Moreover makes him have to plant and feeling of surroundings Sea of Ruin fusion. As if the own body is part.

of course, this is only very short feeling, energy in within the body is passing as before still, but does not have originally that intense that's all.

Left Sea of Ruin once more, enters fully that is in Sea Soul Beast sea. The feeling is also same. Tang Wulin discovered that some quite small and weak Sea Soul Beast has not dared to approach him again, only then above Thousand Years cultivates for Sea Soul Beast will also initiate attack to him.

Because formerly when Sea of Ruin saved Soul Power obviously, he naturally can also insist for a long time. This time, he swims one kilometer unable to insist.

Relies on Nightmare Crystal to return, as before is intense weak. But at least he had found the opportunity. Found can in the sea middle reaches a farther opportunity.

Although he how , regardless of being not willing to return to nearby Ruin Fragment(s) again, but, he actually has to go back.

Can swim this piece of sea, means that in the future he has the possibility is bringing companion genuine leaves this just like the Nightmare general place. To save companion, first wants own to become formidable.

Under such mood, Tang Wulin took Disillusioned Crystal to arrive around Ruin Fragment(s) once again. One and one step, careful approaches to Ruin Fragment(s). Again is feeling the feeling of body to shatter and reorganization.

Golden Dragon King bloodline is fluctuating in this process fiercely, Tang Wulin felt that Qi and Blood turns wells up, not many Transformation. In his purple-black, actually follows times to approach to Ruin Fragment(s), but becomes is getting more and more rich.

......

--------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket, recommended the ticket, today eve of the Lunar New Year, if I have not remembered incorrectly. Um, blessed everybody Happy New Year, wishes coming true.

#826: Rigid of Xu Lizhi

„” Le Zhengyu called out pitifully. on one knee knees down, this does not know that was his many time cannot withstand Ruin aura assault.

Sacred Power that he has the greatly strengthened repel to Ruin aura naturally, therefore, when withstands Ruin aura assault, his pain is also fiercest.

Stands, I must stand. Xiaoyan, cannot let Xiaoyan lose chastity.

Le Zhengyu clenches the teeth, support bit by bit the body of own is standing up, his big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath. Although the pain of body makes him call out pitifully to make noise once again, is, his look actually as before firm. Made one shock firmly.

......

Tang Wulin falls in the place, absorb slowly Ruin aura in air, has not been knowing many days, in the extremely painful process, could not attend to the sunrise sunset. He in advance diligently.

Devil Island rich Life aura is to the body best supplement, here does not need to eat meal, so long as absorb that rich Life strength, can live every day.

ray of light on Ruin Fragment(s) is partly visible, has rich Ruin aura to reappear in Tang Wulin body surroundings unceasingly. After these days thorough, he discovered gradually that in own all ability, as if contaminated on Ruin aura. All Soul Skill also as if had the formidable destructive power.

In his Golden Dragon King bloodline, as if also contaminated on some purple-black. Regarding this, Golden Dragon King bloodline not only has not repelled, instead in influencing subtly absorb.

Tang Wulin already had ability assault ninth Golden Dragon King Seal, but he this. Because Old Tang had already reminded him, following nine Seal are most painful. Once he has broken through ninth Seal, quick must face following nine. When the time comes can be any situation his own does not know.

But, in absorb in the processes of strength of these Ruin, Tang Wulin can feel every day obviously own ninth Seal started the appear(ance) to shatter fissure, that fissure unceasing spreads, he more and more Control did not live in Seal strength. Therefore, he has to make the own progress slow down. Letting own can a better adjustment, stable Seal.

He most fears is, Seal of own in the absorb Ruin aura process breaks through, he does not know in completely such situation what happened.

......

absorb, absorb and absorb!

Xu Lizhi, one step is going forward to the Ruin Fragment(s) direction. His step is extremely firm, like his look.

The body gradually becomes illusory, reorganizes just like molecular general to shatter again. In that terrifying pain, he has not roared to make noise extremely unexpectedly.

He will not fight, he will only make Steamed Stuffed Bun.

He will only shout that Steamed Stuffed Bun has the meat not on the pleat.

Whenever facing powerful enemy time, always companion keep off before the own body. Always the Sister Xinglan horizontal sword is protecting him. Whenever looks that starlight sword tip(s) blooms radiantly, he so is always satisfied.

But, Nightmare Old Devil was reminding him time and time again, he was a waste.

Yes! Isn't he a waste? As a man, must hide behind the own beloved woman. Looks that the beloved woman faces powerful enemy time and time again, but own only will actually make Steamed Stuffed Bun behind her. This is a sad matter.

He thinks that own can keep off in front of Ye Xinglan, keeps out wind and rain for her, resists that formidable enemy for her.

But, he cannot achieve, he was always not since good.

He is very small and weak, his actual combat ability is very bad. Only then in the close-range situation, can fight by some Tang Sect secret arts.

He does not hope such, does not hope.

When his absorb some Ruin aura, broke in sea, with bringing Ruin aura Soul Power is patting broken Sea Soul Beast time, Xu Lizhi only thought that own had finally found the opportunity. That Ruin aura looks like a weapon, although when absorb it is that painful, the destructive power that but it has made him have stronger fighting strength finally.

He has been pursuing such fighting strength!

I want to become strong, I must protect my Sister Xinglan. I am not willing to become the disabled person in companion eye. I must be a useful person.

Whatever pain, cannot make my footsteps stop!

Xu Lizhi step by step, firm powerful forwarding. Strong Ruin aura time and time again assault his body. Made his plump and fair-complected body almost turn into purple-black.

For better absorb Ruin aura, he has not even resisted with Soul Power, but lets loose the body of own, even goes to initiative absorb the strength of these Ruin.

This without doubt enormous degree intensifies the to shatter degree of his body. But Xu Lizhi does not care, what he cares is own whether becomes in this process formidable. Whether better protector own Lover after promotion.

Finally, he is unable to forward again, body to shatter and reorganization speed arrived at Peak. As if next quarter own Soul to shatter, the Life brand mark will not stay behind completely.

At this time, Xu Lizhi stopped footsteps, in the mouth read the soul incantation.

Incantations resound in his mouth, Soul Ring increase from the under foot.

„Steamed Stuffed Bun has the meat not on pleat, I have Crystal Bun!”

Glittering and translucent carving Crystal Bun appear(ance) in his hands, his without hesitation squeezes in the own mouth it.

Crystalline lens reappear just like armor piece generally, gable his body. However, actually as before can see, in that matter crystal, his obese body is duplicating to shatter and reorganization as before.

Next flickers, strength of hit a Ruin comes, Xu Lizhi took advantage of somebody's authority instead runs, ran out of the Ruin aura range. Then he sits cross-legged to sit on the ground immediately, close eyes meditation.

He eats up Crystal Bun, to not draw support from Crystal Bun the strength of firm comes defense, but to draw support from Isolation Power of that crystal armor, will inhale absorb of Ruin aura completely Imprison in within the body in the own body.

Because, before him, in cultivate process, so long as left the Ruin aura category, Ruin aura fast will also diverge, can only have very small part to remain, invades his body.

However, after using Crystal Bun is different, overwhelming majority Ruin aura will be remained.

of course, this takes to Xu Lizhi, wants the intense non- several fold compared with others the pain, continuous pain. But, his willpower strength is firmer than all people. Because, he needs this strength, ability that needs the strength of this Ruin to bring.

......

„Has not thought!” Nightmare Old Devil frown said.

„Has not thought!” Disillusioned Old Devil is also surprised of face.

„Other did not say, these kids the firmness of willpower, but also really has surpassed our judgment. Especially that Little Fatty. His Food System Soul Master, willpower can actually strengthen to this degree, is really somewhat unthinkable. I could not have thought that three months he must collapse. It looks like, I underestimated him. Moreover, he unexpectedly is in all people most thorough one, is really surprising!”

Disillusioned Old Devil smiles, „isn't this? Appearance that looks at their pain, is really joyful.”

„Has this good deed, why does not awaken me!” Low and deep sounds/voices suddenly resounds.

Nightmare Old Devil and Disillusioned Old Devil also turn head, what sees is a big incomparable form.

„Devour!” Their calling out with one voice.

That is also an old man, but his hair is actually not white, but is yellow, seems just likes the subtilis is ordinary, in top of the head bare.

Some big body rickets, look is old and ugly, what is more fearful, his mouth is specially big, when he starts talking, after his big mouth even can split to the root of the ear.

„You monopolize unexpectedly this pleasure, simply is not the human!” Devour Old Devil face upwards to heave a deep sigh, „I, no matter, then, they are my. I must make them feel well, Devour pleasure!”

Nightmare Old Devil and Disillusioned Old Devil frowned, „was good, gives you to play. However, must wait for them to swim was good in the past.”

......

„!” A Tang Wulin hand strikes in sea water, under the light sea water, in the sand beach has left behind a deep grasping mark.

He almost with moving, rubs the ground from sea own. Lies there, he moved really does not want to move.

purple-black aura winds around, both eyes shut tightly, complexion piece of pale white.

Came, finally came. After does not know absorb many Ruin aura, he can make these Sea Soul Beast no longer start to him by Ruin aura finally, finally swam.

However, in this process, he has met specially formidable Sea Soul Beast, received attack. Even he already by that only Sea Soul Beast Devour to belly. Because his Ruin aura makes the opposite party loathe, has spat. Was spurted.

#827: Enters

This process, cannot describe in the spoken language completely. However, he arrived at shore finally, finally came.

Lies there, whatever the sea water is washing out the body of own, wipes the light smile to reappear on the Tang Wulin face.

Ate these many, to receive these many crimes painstakingly, finally succeeded?

He lies there is motionless, hides own Soul Power completely originally. He is common just like the sea turtle, the dispelling sand quietly, buries own. Control the temperature of own body.

Only by doing so, can as far as possible not by the radar discovery of North Sea Corps. He needs to rest, at least now he moves does not move.

The breath is gradually even, is adjusting the Qi and Blood fluctuation of own.

Since arriving at Devil Island, like the peaceful time also is really very rare. Tang Wulin completely understands now initially the Old Cai expression so will be why strange. This Devil Island, but also was controlled by devil(s) really! Moreover, said according to Nightmare Old Devil that the present situation was different, can they even live are going back not to say.

If from just came to here, although Tang Wulin does not know explicit time, but should also in the past have about three months. Then three months, he suffered Life and Death cannot. Even if military training is normal, that other more than one year time this did pass? What thing will behind have to wait for them?

Sighed one darkly, Tang Wulin relaxes the body, was restoring the physical ability slowly. Three months, his food has not even eaten. Even if this time can steal aircraft to go back, Nightmare Old Devil will let off own and companion, obviously is not easy.

Ok, does not manage, whatever, can guarantee that the companion safe moment, has the First-tier vitality. At least now own can cross the sea by integration of Ruin aura. This coming , he not only to steal aircraft, what is more important, he wants the circuit that found one to go back. Once there is an opportunity to rescue companion, he can lead everybody, returns to Federation.

Tang Wulin once has also thought must return to Academy to request reinforcements, is, he is very clear, this is not realistic. If with Soul Guide Communicator, what reaction Academy aspect did not say first that by Nightmare Old Devil that strange ability, he can know? Tang Wulin does not dare to bet, once because lost was beyond redemption! He does not hope to see companion self- Ruin in the pain.

Rested a double-hour, the Tang Wulin body condition gradually has adjusted. But here after is not Devil Island, does not have that rich Life strength. Therefore, his physical ability restores almost, first feels is the intense sense of hunger.

Early knows that grasped Sea Soul Beast a moment ago, even if eats raw fish fillet, can supplement some physical abilities!

Gains ground slightly, quietly looks toward the defense belt of distant place. On the weighty tall wall, searchlight light often flashes through, at this time just in the evening, taking advantage of the light can on the clear seeing protective belt that steel and iron forest piece by piece.

Tang Wulin does not doubt, this degree of defense, even if Hundred-thousand Years Soul Beast dares to initiate assault, will be ripped fragment(s) in short time. Humanity Soul Guidance Technology, already was not Soul Beast can resist.

Also because of the High-speed development of Soul Guidance Technology, status of Soul Master on Continent was inferior that now beforehand is so lofty.

It is not good, cannot rush hardly, own does not have an opportunity. Does not ascend the sky good, does that enter?

Tang Wulin before coming to have the plan, he has a pair of formidable Golden Dragon Claw, supplements shredding and crushing special effect separately, digs a hole this matter should not to calculate too difficulties. By him understanding to Humanity Soul Guidance Technology, even if underground, perhaps also same has defense or surveys equipment. It is not good, below was discovered will be more troublesome.

But must try, walks from below always compares directly faces the terrifying Soul Guide Cannon hot storm to be much stronger from above.

Thinks of here, Tang Wulin both hands release Golden Dragon Claw slowly, starts to the under fluctuation silt, making the body of own sink gradually.

Has saying that Mountain Dragon King Torso Bone to his help is very big, this does not know that is any grade Soul Bone, not only made him have control of gravity ability, the enormous degree strengthened his defense, made him have high compatible to Earth Element.

The body of Tang Wulin sinks slowly, soil becomes under the aura influence of Mountain Dragon King Torso Bone soft, is relying on a pair of sharp Golden Dragon Claw, he penetrated quickly underground.

Underground somewhat will be unavoidably worried, but the Tang Wulin physical quality made him definitely to neglect these. Golden Dragon King bloodline nature circulation, provides to his huge energy, in addition his strong strength. Quick, he went down to the bottom deep place.

Ten minutes of time, he has passed through the sandy soil level, entered the lithosphere. Facing the rock, the Tang Wulin movement was instead quicker, the possibility that because the rock at least has not caved , cannot like in facing the sandy soil level, but must depend upon Mountain Dragon King Torso Bone strength to go to the stable surroundings broken place.

This passageway Tang Wulin may, not only prepares with one time, in the future he will also plan to rely on this passageway to lead companion to escape. Therefore in the process of excavation, he is careful. Has not developed in the North Sea Corps direction eagerly, but downward deep cutting as far as possible.

Without a doubt, the tunnel is deeper, discovered possibly is smaller.

One hour passes by, relies on the formidable physical quality, Tang Wulin was penetrating the underground hundred meters. He also had faced in this period many difficult problems, for example ground water.

Ground water appear(ance), making him have to crosswise change passageway first, seeks not to have the ground water place to continue again downward. This process without doubt is difficult and tortuous. But luckily, he succeeded.

The underground hundred meters, the thick lithosphere is all best mask, will not always be discovered.

Tang Wulin keeps off in road that own digs out, slightly somewhat rapid is panting for breath. Here air is thin, can take to bring in the air that to be few from outside. Also average person, already already suffocation. But he now as far as possible in makes own transfer breathes, this can support.

Judged own probably the location position, Tang Wulin started the crosswise excavation at this time, the rock in front of Golden Dragon Claw crushing and shredding two big special effect, did not have much difference with the bean curd. The Tang Wulin powerful both arms are absolutely easier-to-use than any excavator, the body rapid traverse, drills in the North Sea Corps direction.

Generally speaking, military's below searching regarding ground observes way (of life) to have several types, most important is Seismometer. Right, is Seismometer.

Because under the ground has any Transformation, will produce exceptionally vibrates, these vibrations meet the take shape ripple, once were investigated by Seismometer, can the first time take shape data. When fluctuates is strong, the data that the survey obtains can also along with it to become strong.

Seismometer even can survey underground dozens kilometers Transformation. But it also has an issue, that can only survey relatively the big fluctuation.

Next is Soul Power Detector. Through under searching of Soul Power fluctuation to the ground observes to seek for suspicious existence. The Soul Power Detector searching range does not have Seismometer to be so big obviously, can only have the function in the underground 500 meters. But its survey be slighter than Seismometer, so long as is slightly intense a point the Soul Power fluctuation to feed back.

These two types of Detector complement one another, constituted to the effective monitoring of underground world.

Like Tang Wulin, in does not use any Soul Guidance machinery, does not use Soul Power, pure relies on the body intensity to the situation of underground excavation is being very rare. Even if Titled Douluo stage Elite, only if Innate Body Sect that body cultivates, is very difficult to achieve this point. But in fact, even if the science and technology is advanced, impossible to prevent accidents before they occur all.

#828: Sneaks the warehouse

Therefore, Tang Wulin when underground goes forward slowly, not by various Detector discoveries of North Sea Corps. On Seismometer, what demonstration is only the normal fluctuation under ground. A activity of person, is not enough to make Seismometer sound the warning by far.

Then, Tang Wulin tired on rest a while, restores to continue to unearth. His own does not know how long has dug.

In this period, when he returned the ground has rested twice, really hungrily, returns to sea, hunted and killed Sea Soul Beast, slivered raw fish fillet to treat as food by Golden Dragon Claw Sea Soul Beast. After recovering some energy, returns his underground world to continue to unearth.

„Biting” resounding appear(ance), the Tang Wulin movement stops suddenly immediately. The whole body fine body hair stands erect, the whole person restrains to begin to accrue interest rapidly.

What situation?

Does not dare to release Blue Silver Grass to bring ray of light, Tang Wulin can only release own Qi and Blood Soul Ring, under shining of golden-colored ring of light, his surprised seeing, in the passageway end of own excavation, the metal(s) board has blocked the way together.

metal(s) board? Is this North Sea Corps? Is the underground engineering or isolates the outside?

Tang Wulin gently the palm fitting on that metal(s) board, is feeling silently.

He is close Saint Craftsman stage Blacksmith, regarding the metal(s) familiar far supernormal person. Through touching and Spiritual Strength sensation, can determine metal(s) properties basically.

He such does now, is quick he to distinguish, what in front of own is one type especially near, does not calculate specially rare. But actually very firm. Is Titanium Alloy one.

And does not have any energy fluctuation existence, in other words, this is not large-scale Soul Guidance Device, is only pure alloy.

This made Tang Wulin feel relieved, if were Soul Guidance Device, he had to trouble, if at least wants the means to continue downward, bypassed this metal(s) wall to be good. But if only the pure metal(s) wall, that means that he bigger possibly enters the North Sea Corps underground engineering outer layer. So long as breaks through this metal(s) wall, can enter North Sea Corps.

The heartbeat accelerates slightly, after Tang Wulin ponders moment, stretches out finger slowly, the dark-gold light blade edge drills from the fingertip place slowly, in prick front rare metal(s) that is quietly.

tenacity can rare metal(s) again compared with his Dark Gold Fearful Claw? After the sharp knife blade pricks, revolves under Tang Wulin Control slowly, quick drills a hole.

The Dark Gold Fearful Claw front is releasing light ray of light quietly, extends to a farther place. A moment later, Tang Wulin felt that fingertip one light, he knows that bored through.

Takes back finger quietly, he also for it with amazement.

The thickness of this metal(s) wall, has about two feet. This grade of weighty alloy wall, defense strength absolutely strong, the construction cost is extremely also high. North Sea Corps is really also willing under the initial capital!

One bunch of weak ray of light transmit through eyelet. Why does not know, sees this ray of light time, Tang Wulin has the feeling of having tears streaming down the face. Finally saw to belong to Humanity ray of light! Since mounting Devil Island, he has been living the inhuman life. Can see some human spirits finally.

Do not look is only an eyelet, had this eyelet, Tang Wulin that Spirit Abyss Realm Spiritual Strength has been able to extend the eyelet to enter slowly, sensation silently internal situation.

Just as such that he judges, here is really the North Sea Corps underground engineering, moreover what made his pleasantly surprised was, this was a giant warehouse. In warehouse dazzling is placing various types of Soul Guidance weaponry, are most, impressively Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. Without a doubt, Tang Wulin entered the North Sea Corps most important storage center accidentally. No wonder outer wall alloy can that weighty.

The warehouse biggest advantage is nobody, the biggest fault is, this and other important warehouses, outside defense certainly strong.

Should be what to do good?

In any event, said advanced again. Really is not good can also the old route return. Being able to advance or retreat. First has a look in this warehouse to have the opportunity to exit.

Thinks of here, after Tang Wulin slightly makes ponder, has been located in north in the to speak a shelf dark corner, approaches the position of ground. This position is discovered easily.

Is relying on cutting of Dark Gold Fearful Claw, time is not long, square shape metal(s) was cut slowly, for low key as far as possible, he cut small to speak of one foot square, at his stature, drilled also really somewhat to use energy.

The fresh air made the Tang Wulin feelings open greatly, the comfortable groan nearly made noise. Drills cave entrance quietly, covers to seal up metal(s), so long as is not carefully looked specially that is impossible to discover.

Suddenly, a sense of fear raises from the bottom of the heart, Tang Wulin whole body one stiff, hurries by not to dare to move on the wall.

But is quick he to know that this sense of fear came from where, the sense of fear that has the rack of Skeleton mark from him. On the rack, is placing Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell.

Has the knowledge about Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, Tang Wulin also studies in Academy too much, this is Humanity Ten-thousand Years comes most terrifying weapon after all. It is said that most formidable Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, even if Limit Douluo does not dare to touch hardly. Obviously its mighty energy.

Front these Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell from volume and marking, mainly in 4th Rank to 6th Rank. This is might biggest Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell that the normal fighter aircraft can carry. More formidable artillery shell, needs Super Rank Mecha to carry, to guarantee security.

Tang Wulin has not moved, but releases Spiritual Strength quietly, the situation of feels this warehouse.

Feeds back through Spiritual Strength, he judges quickly, this is one approximately about 3000 square meters warehouses, inside deposits over 50% are Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. If these many artillery shell explode, perhaps the entire North Sea Corps base can be raised flies.

In addition, some Mecha stockpile, is service pattern Yellow Rank Mecha.

Accurate, this warehouse storage is quite the formidable strategic resources, but is not most Top Rank that type, at least does not have 7th Rank above Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell and higher stage Mecha appear(ance).

In the warehouse has the monitoring camera, but has in the most essential position. As the matter stands, means that Tang Wulin was is not discovered easily, so long as he were more careful.

Has the opportunity!

Spiritual Strength is unable to leave the warehouse, the surroundings metal(s) jade was too thick, therefore outside is any situation Tang Wulin does not know.

After having remembered the positions of all cameras carefully, Tang Wulin starts to move quietly, he must first leave own that entrance to be good. In this case, even if he were discovered that at least the entrance easily had not been discovered that later also has the opportunity of withdrawing.

Only is worth rejoicing is, the warehouse that this type stores up Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell is impossible to have the attack system, otherwise, once the attack system initiates attack, detonated Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell that to be the devastating disaster.

Looked following the wall near probably. This warehouse airtight very good, air, humidity and temperature Control based on this. To be what to do good? Cannot exit from here! Outside has certainly very strong defense strength. Does not have internal pass, own to run out of large door, will be discovered immediately. But here North Sea Corps, Tang Wulin, although is One Word Battle Armor Master, but he does not think that can such hardly rush by the own strength.

Is pondering over own to dig the tunnel in him, moreover looks for an to speak time.

Suddenly, gets up with a series of electronic sounds, warehouse weighty large door opens slowly.

Did some people come?

Tang Wulin hurried to hide in the corner.

Sure enough, after the gate opens, several people walked from outside.

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket, recommended the ticket.

#829: Staff Officer Shen

Walks in the forefront, is one puts on the young girl of major military uniform. Her stature is extremely good, the military uniform is unable to cover up that has to concave-convex the tender body. On pretty face full is cold frost, flavor that somewhat the stranger do not enter greatly.

The leather boots tread in the metal(s) ground, exudes the clear collision sound.

„Did inventorying quantity have the result? Previous few two 5th Rank do Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell find out the feature?” Asking that the young girl military officer lets somebody cool off or calm down.

Follows in her side similarly is a major, this male military officer seems had three, 40-year-old appearances, the whole face compensates the [say / way] that smiles: „Staff Officer Shen, we were investigating, but currently did not have the result. Inventorying has also been completed, is consistent with the previous quantity.”

Staff Officer Shen stops the footsteps, lets somebody cool off or calm down looks to him, said: „Your meaning i.e., that two 5th Rank did Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell lose really? Do you know that what this does mean?”

That male major complexion changes, the forehead sweats, „knows and knows that I as soon as possible put certainly out the findings. We investigated all monitoring video recording, really not any discovery. We plan again to install the probe head in the warehouse immediately, must not guarantee any dead angle. Staff Officer Shen, but must trouble you to give me before the general fine talk several. You also know that my Lao Chen is always timid, how possibly to make the matter that embezzles?”

Staff Officer Shen sneers, „has to embezzle your own to be clear. No matter these I, I want result. That two 5th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell could not find, even if the general cannot protect you. Gives you again three days of time, I want the result, does not want to listen to your mental journey.”

„Yes, yes, in three days, I put certainly out a result to come.” Major Chen wiped the cold sweat on forehead, in the heart complained of hardship secretly.

„Leads me to have a look in the warehouse.” Staff Officer Shen ice-cold complexion slightly has relaxed several points at this time , to continue to inspect the warehouse under the leadership of Major Chen.

Opportunity!

Without a doubt, this is a golden good opportunity, not fault-tolerant good opportunity.

Almost does not have hesitant any, Tang Wulin fled.

Two majors behind, are only with four soldiers, Tang Wulin almost moves sideways, four soldiers softly have fallen to the ground.

Staff Officer Shen and Major Chen first time comes on reaction. Ten tree root Blue Silver Emperor have caressed the face to go to them.

Major Chen calls out in alarm one, wants to brace oneself the Soul Guidance pistol, actually directly by Blue Silver Emperor Bind solidity. It seems the 20-year-old Staff Officer Shen reflection is rapid, after she first is one leaps, two yellow two purple four Soul Ring rapid raise from the under foot.

Unexpectedly is Four Rings Soul Ancestor?

Staff Officer Shen aura suddenly changes cold, the temperature in air also with it reduction, the cold and gloomy air current blooms with the innumerable snowflakes, directly soars Tang Wulin to cover.

Tang Wulin knows that at this time own under the monitor, was unable to delay time, four golden-colored ring of light raise at the same time, third ring of light has shone.

„Raising” spirited Golden Dragon Roars made the entire warehouse get up along with it fluctuation.

Four Soul Rings that the Staff Officer Shen whole body megascism, just released was shaken unexpectedly directly has dispersed, the intense dizziness feeling made her one stagger.

Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Roars facing cultivation to be higher than the own matches can have an effect, let alone at present this cultivation to also be inferior to him.

Moves sideways, Tang Wulin arrived at behind Staff Officer Shen, the racket of left hand on her lower abdomen, the right hand seized her neck.

Staff Officer Shen Soul Power had been sealed up by Tang Wulin directly, Tang Wulin cold voice said: „Do not move, otherwise has killed you.”

Staff Officer Shen did not have fully to restore at this time from Golden Dragon Roars, only thought that intense man aura wells up, making her dizziness feeling as if more intense.

Tang Wulin pats the hand of her Dantian to hug directly on her slender waist, her body is chilly, is especially sensitive to the temperature. She only thought that behind man whole body has filled the blazing male character, made her whole body some worns out and aching.

The enemies raid!

Staff Officer Shen had realized immediately has anything. But she has not definitely been able to revolt at this time.

„You and you cannot be inescapable.” Shen Xing is to shame the anger at this time occurred simultaneously. She had not been contacted by man so close-range. She has not even seen clearly Tang Wulin to be long any appearance. Felt that on the back man transmits intermittent strong firm aura, should be young.

„That is uncertain.” Tang Wulin chuckle, clamped Shen Xing to run out of warehouse large door rapidly.

At this time, the ear-piercing alarm sound has remembered instantaneously. But Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell warehouse heavy, here was hit by the attack suddenly, absolutely is the important matter of shock entire base.

Tang Wulin keeps off Shen Xing in the slanting flank of own body, another hand has taken off Identification Card on her neck.

Without a doubt, this beautiful woman major's status in the North Sea Armed forces is quite good, is relying on Identification Card, he ran out of three electronic entrance guards continuously.

Tang Wulin knows that now they should in the underground deep place of North Sea Corps base, he now first to do, is arrives at the ground to come up.

„How goes to the ground to walk?” Tang Wulin asked to Shen Xing.

„I will not tell you. You want not to think! Had the skill you to kill me.” Saying that Shen Xing lets somebody cool off or calm down.

Tang Wulin light [say / way]: „Has killed you? Why I must kill you. I believe that you do not fear death, but, as a woman, the death was not the most fearful matter.”

At the same time was saying, the Tang Wulin right hand wields, Shen Xing only thinks on the own right arm one cool, the military uniform sleeves fluttered, changes into fragment(s).

„” In her mouth sends out a scream of ear-piercing, the intense fear spreads over the whole body instantaneously.

Tang Wulin fills Evil sounds/voices to reverberate in her ear, „knows that what I do want to make? I believe that perhaps under these many gazes of monitoring, the North Sea Corps army is visiting us. Your such big beautiful woman, if completely exposes in their eyes, you said that these soldiers can make the profound impression?”

„Your bastard!” Tears not by flowing copiously of Control.

Tang Wulin right hand Golden Dragon Claw lifts once more, „said? Did not say that next time is the entire item coat.”

Will he do really? Answer of course negative, threat, must look for the effect. Since had been trained after by Nightmare Old Devil, Tang Wulin discovered that the heart of own wanted compared with before hardly . Moreover, seemed also easier to seek for others' weakness.

Regarding the girl, particularly the girl of aloof like Shen Xing, the most effective threat method certainly is not Life and Death. Her such miss, regards reputation Life be more important.

of course, if Shen Xing resists stubbornly, in fact Tang Wulin also takes her not to have the means that he cannot tear to pieces others clothes.

But is very obvious, the Shen Xing psychological quality her surface is not good, „right!” She screamed one, tender body in rustle has trembled.

She definitely is unable to imagine, if the body of own exposes the consequences under all monitors. own will certainly go crazy, that really compared with dying more painful matter. At that time, perhaps not only own, entire Family must be shamed because of own!

Tang Wulin satisfied [say / way]: „This was right. However, next time I will ask your anything again, if your reply is not that happy, I will not give the opportunity that you ponder again. Not only in any case, you have the coat, doesn't this have the pants?”

„Your bastard!” Shen Xing only wishes one could behind this fellow to cramp to skin at this time.

Tang Wulin he he smiles, „are more than person of my bastard.”

Really, the passageway right end, there is an elevator. Tang Wulin brushes Identification Card, the elevator door opens accordingly. Tang Wulin brought Shen Xing to enter the elevator directly.

He did not worry that own will catch a turtle in a jar, in the hand has the hostage, in the heart is unhurried. The status of this major is not very obviously ordinary. Four Rings major, but is rarely seen. Should be right of some status.

Moreover, his speed is quick, leaves North Sea Corps reaction time not to be many.

Facts showed that the judgment of Tang Wulin is correct, in the elevator upward process, has not met any obstruction. That flash that but when the elevator door opens, outside, dozens handle Soul Guide Ray Gun have aimed at the elevator to speak.

„Cannot move, lets loose Staff Officer Shen.” Low and deep sounds/voices resounds, the one who stands in all soldier front line is a stature majestic male military officer. Lieutenant Colonel military rank.

Tang Wulin left hand Golden Dragon Claw covers the neck of Shen Xing, said with a smile indifferently: „Makes way. Otherwise, I did not mind that throws a corpse to you.”

That Lieutenant Colonel cold snort one, „aren't you Shrek student? Can Shrek Academy allow you to slaughter innocents? I do not believe that you dare to begin. Immediately is without a fight, otherwise, do not blame us not being impolite.”

Without a doubt, the Tang Wulin status had been recognized.

--------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket, recommended the ticket.

#830: Holding under duress

Tang Wulin has smiled suddenly, „real? You think really I don't dare to begin?” The intense murderous intention bursts out from his within the body, in an instant, his eyes turned into blood-red suddenly. Left hand Golden Dragon Claw must close up inward.

Shen Xing only thought that at this time blood of own whole body wanted freeze, terrifying aura that the Tang Wulin body burst out made her suffocation, her first time felt that the own distance death was such near.

She has thought own does not fear death, can offer own Life for Federation. May arrive at Life and Death life or death moment , the sense of fear arises spontaneously.

The male military officer is also the complexion big change, „stopped, has killed her, you were Federation sinner, we will execute summarily you similarly.”

Tang Wulin laughs suddenly, in his laughter has been full of the hysteria, „Devil Island that crowd of Demon suffer me daily, I already do not want to live, some people are buried along with the dead, is a good matter. Come, that makes us perish together, dies with a beautiful woman, is not the painful matter.” At the same time was saying, he held the right hand of personal appearance to raise from the ground her directly, Shen Xing pretty face instantaneously became piece of pale white.

„Stop! retreat.” The male military officer has nearly bitten a steel tooth, by his rigid character, but also others, perhaps the person of his rather Sacrifice one's own side, must take the enemy. But, Shen Xing is different! Not only Shen Xing in his dream sweetheart, what is more important, she is the North Sea Corps armed forces regimental commander, Northeast Military District Vice Commander Shen Yue own Younger Sister.

If Shen Xing had an accident, how making him confess with Shen Yue?

The soldiers carry Soul Guide Ray Gun retreat, Tang Wulin are placing in the ground Shen Xing slowly again, clamps her body stride to walk outward, looks like strolls general in own.

Nobody dares to begin, Tang Wulin had already shown his strength, let alone front this Lieutenant Colonel strength not necessarily certainly can defeat him, even if Titled Douluo here, facing One Word Battle Armor Master time, will not have confidence before the homicide person kills him.

Shen Xing big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath. Just at that moment, she felt really own as if arrived by Grim Reaper. The unprecedented sense of fear lets her pretty face pale white like the paper.

Extends passageway to walk outward, does not need others to tell, relied on to the feeling of air current, Tang Wulin had been finding the to speak quickly, in numerous soldiers „crowding around”, walked.

Outside air is really happy! Tang Wulin deep inspiration, then looks to all around.

„Looks for aircraft to come to me. Wants Sky Flyer 17, do not use trick. So long as you have met my request, I can assure her security. I know, in North Sea Corps has certainly Elite to guard. However, I have enough self-confidence, before your Elite extinguish me kills, I can draw a pad back.”

Saying that Tang Wulin lets somebody cool off or calm down, „gives you ten minutes.”

At the same time was saying, Tang Wulin is drawing the personal appearance, looked for an angle to sit down, his own leaned on the corner, such following two directions did not fear some people of attack. Lets Shen Xing again by in the own bosom, covers the body of own with her body.

Shen Xing basically sits on the Tang Wulin thigh, her buttocks very curl upwards specially, because fears, body slight(ly) is shivering.

In the Tang Wulin heart raises fiery, but at this time, what is more important is all around the observation. In order to avoid appear(ance) any Transformation.

aircraft has not come, the human were getting more and more. The massive Jun soldiers have encircled watertight surroundings. Soul Guide Steam Vehicle unceasing opens.

„Five minutes!” Saying that Tang Wulin lets somebody cool off or calm down.

At this moment, a military vehicle arrives at the nearby rapidly, „” stopping. Opens the vehicle door, Shen Yue of military garb jumped down from the vehicle.

Gets out, she sees own Younger Sister, in Tang Wulin during grasps.

This time Shen Xing, the appearance is really somewhat distressed, sleeves did not have, on the face completely is the tear stains, the body by Tang Wulin, but also slight(ly) is shivering.

Intense anger „whiz whiz” upward goes against, the Shen Yue stride walks toward Tang Wulin. This time she, soon exploded with rage simply the lung.

Recently recently she had sufficed annoyedly, had been made Sky Flyer by Shrek Seven Monsters 17, later unexpectedly in airborne directly had been stolen one by Tang Wulin. This simply is the North Sea Corps great shame.

But what she has not thought that in soon, Tang Wulin unexpectedly came, moreover this time has also kidnapped own Younger Sister.

„Lets loose her!” Saying that Shen Yue lets somebody cool off or calm down.

Tang Wulin looked at an epaulet of her shoulder, in the heart is also one tight. Lieutenant General! This absolutely was he has seen the highest military appointment.

„General Your Excellency, hello. My aircraft? My patience is limited.” Tang Wulin light saying.

Shen Yue looks at Tang Wulin, suddenly sinking sound shouted to clear the way: „I said that lets loose her.” Her roars, with intense spiritual fluctuation.

Tang Wulin only thought that at present one black, an invisible dignity oppresses to him, is almost subconscious, he wants to obey the order of Shen Yue.

But absent-minded is only the flash, Tang Wulin next one flickers in Shen Yue, sudden seizes the neck of Shen Xing comes on the strategic place, simultaneously the right hand wields, in the Shen Xing ear-piercing squeal, drew her another side sleeves.

Shen Yue flushed, when sees the Tang Wulin movement, she has to Control the body of own make own stop.

„To die, that together dies!” The Tang Wulin anger exclaimed.

The Shen Yue double fist grips tightly, „lets loose her, I am your hostage.”

Tang Wulin sneers, „general Your Excellency, you, when I am a three -year-old child? Your this year discipline can become Lieutenant General, you that formidable Spiritual Strength, it can be imagined, your strength certainly was much more formidable than a moment ago me. Works as the hostage with you? Am I dislike the own life to be long?”

Shen Yue did not have the means, she was not really clear, why own spiritual frightened to be unexpectedly useless to this boy. Must know that her Spiritual Strength has achieved Spirit Abyss Realm! How to be useless?

„Three minutes, aircraft has not come, I do not kill her, each one minute, I have torn up her clothes. Come, you can bet me to dare.” At the same time was saying, Tang Wulin has untied the first knot of Shen Xing collar place.

The Shen Xing mood collapsed finally, she yelled: „Elder sister, saves me.”

Ended! Her called, Shen Yue knows that was finished. The aspect lost the control thoroughly.

Really, Tang Wulin eye one bright, drew Shen Xing to stand, wiped the light smiling face along with it reappearing on his face, „has not thought really that my luck so was unexpectedly good. General Your Excellency Younger Sister! General Your Excellency please feel relieved, so long as you meet my request, I let off her. Two minutes.”

„aircraft opens!” Shen Yue exclaimed lowly.

Her of course knows that issues this order to be disadvantageous to her. As the armed forces regimental commander, facing the enemy threatens chooses the compromise unexpectedly, moreover for own Younger Sister. So long as this matter passes on, has the indelible influence to her future future.

But, can she do? Her such Younger Sister. She cannot look helplessly Younger Sister was shamed, even loses the life!

In her opinion, Tang Wulin was insane. His actions have gone beyond the category that the Shrek Academy student has been able to make completely. However, she is very clear, in the record of North Sea Corps, the Shrek student who any went to Devil Island, time will become very not normal.

Therefore, Shen Yue does not dare to bet similarly, she cannot use own Younger Sister not round trip gambling.

Quick, Sky Flyer 17 advanced in the Tang Wulin field of vision range.

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, draws Shen Xing to stand up.

Shen Yue sinking sound track: „aircraft came, you can let loose her now, I guaranteed by the reputation that making you drive aircraft to leave.”

#831: There can never be too much deception in war

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „General Your Excellency, you think that I am silly? Said that I look likely mental handicap. At this time did you say the prestige to me? The reality, places on aircraft with the chute bag, asking Staff Officer Shen to deliver me a regulation, after I felt the security, will let her parachuting. I believe that you have ability to take her to come back. Other was needless saying that now you can only choose to believe me, or looks that I and she perished together.”

Shen Xing the whole body shivers at this time, is sobbing, her both legs already completely weak, leans on Tang Wulin strength to be able the standing body.

The Shen Yue double fist grips tightly, lets somebody cool off or calm down looks at Tang Wulin, „you are best to pray in the future do not fall in my hands.”

Tang Wulin said easely: „The future matter will say in the future again how now to say?”

Shen Yue drinks one severely, „makes way, lets on them aircraft.”

Tang Wulin is bringing Shen Xing, such under being a focus of public attention, has mounted Sky Flyer 17. Has not closed the cockpit access panel eagerly, his light [say / way]: „Perhaps, we can use another way (of life). Waits a minute me to ask Staff Officer Shen to return to Devil Island me. Then makes her drive aircraft to come back. Like this you do not have anything to lose. I heart that Sky Flyer 17 can install the long-distance control system, does not know that on this has. I do not think that time aircraft own flew. If any, I suggested that your best dismantle to fall. Otherwise, you understand.”

Shen Yue only thought that front this youth simply looks like a slippery customer, considers all matters unusual is close.

„No, has not installed external guidance system.” Her cold voice said.

„Is very good, hopes that you have not deceived me. If you show loving concern own Younger Sister.” aircraft was starting, access panel slowly closed, has isolated outside all.

Tang Wulin with Blue Silver Grass Bind Shen Xing, making her sit in the copilot, controls buttons skilled, Sky Flyer 17 is accelerating on the runway suddenly, rises into already jet black such as Sky of black ink.

Shen Xing panic-stricken looks that Tang Wulin incomparably is controlling aircraft skilled, when aircraft leaves the North Sea Corps base at that moment, her tears cannot help but once more flowed.

Leaves the North Sea Corps base, means that the own destiny completely was controlled by present youth.

At this time, she genuine sees clearly the Tang Wulin look. From one side can see his long eyelash, handsome face, that pair of clear eye pupil.

If looked from the semblance, how regardless of she is unable to imagine this unexpectedly is a bold scoundrel.

Has saying that this is one looks at the world of face, after Shen Xing sees clearly the Tang Wulin look, she discovered that trembling in own heart and angry is not instead fierce.

„Will you and you kill me?” Shen Xing asked.

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „aren't you do not fear death?”

In the Shen Xing eye the anger erupts, „had the skill you now to kill me. You could not live.”

Tang Wulin said: „So long as your Elder Sister does not make piffle, why I must kill you, I also do not have what bitter hatred with you. Good, sits honestly.”

Under the control of Tang Wulin, Sky Flyer 17 speed were promoted Peak, 30 kilometers in a flash already. aircraft drops slowly, must enter the Devil Island range shortly.

Shen Yue really has scruples the Younger Sister security, any attack or has not been Control appear(ance).

Tang Wulin draws the control handle, aircraft increases into spatially, from the sky draws an elegant arc, flies again in the North Sea Corps direction.

„Do you do? You did not say that makes my own open aircraft to go back?” Shen Xing surprised visits him.

Tang Wulin said: „There can never be too much deception in war do you understand? Thanks to you are the operational staff.”

The free time of speech, aircraft passed over gently and swiftly 30 kilometers range. Tang Wulin has taken back own Blue Silver Emperor, „is the good safety belt.”

So-called wants the chute bag, is Tang Wulin confuses Shen Yue intentionally, is makes Shen Yue think that he is not familiar with aircraft.

Shen Xing has realized anything, hurries the safety belt is.

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „mountain does not change, the green water long class. We have another chance to meet.” At the same time was saying, he lifts the hand, has patted on the Shen Xing lower abdomen. Shen Xing only thought that a heat flow surges, own was returned to by close Soul Power. The next quarter, Tang Wulin flapped the button, the copilot seat instantaneously the ejection from aircraft.

„Bastard! I will not let off your.” Shen Xing was screaming take-off.

Listens to her instantaneous remote threat sound, Tang Wulin to smile, Control the Sky Flyer 17 instantaneous acceleration, are directly soaring Devil Island to go.

aircraft drills into Devil Island, slowly landing. Third. This is third aircraft that Tang Wulin makes. However this time finally is not a hood, finally is complete aircraft.

When aircraft steady falling in ground, Tang Wulin surprised seeing, besides Nightmare Old Devil and Disillusioned Old Devil, were unexpectedly many a tall old man.

When facing Shen Yue as well as the North Sea Corps officers, Tang Wulin can control the aspect throughout, when he from aircraft, sees three Old Devil looks, in his heart actually cannot help but one suddenly, in the subconscious, not the wonderful feeling arises spontaneously.

„, And!” Disillusioned Old Devil applauds, „is good and good. Was finally successful.”

Tang Wulin looks to Nightmare Old Devil, „I have achieved, should put my companion.”

Nightmare Old Devil shrugs the arm, „does not have the issue, the old man always means what he says. From now on, I have put your companion.”

Tang Wulin has gawked, he has not thought really that Nightmare Old Devil so is unexpectedly good to speak. Hurries anxious asking: „They where?”

Nightmare Old Devil smiles, „I gave to issue to Devour them. Gives you to introduce, this is Devour Old Devil. You looked that I suffered you to be so long, he already could not repress. Then, your companion were him.”

„You!” Tang Wulin looks angrily at Nightmare Old Devil, on the face full is the anger.

Devour Old Devil said with his hoarse sounds/voices: „Relax, I do not have him not to have the human nature. With the method of anesthetics low, I also disdain. My request is not high, so long as you can achieve, I have put them.”

Tang Wulin calms down immediately after the short anger, the human has to lower the head under the eaves, he already guessed correctly that these Old Devil are not easy to let off own and companion.

He lets somebody cool off or calm down looks at Devour Old Devil, „what do that you want to make us make?”

In the Devour Old Devil eye reveals the frantic color suddenly, „does not make anything, my this whole life, only then a hobby, that eats. Therefore they called me Devour Old Devil. So long as you provide me to your food eat, I let off you.”

Eats? The Tang Wulin expression instantaneously became strange. Such simple matter? Must say what he most excels is anything, Tang Wulin first thinks will not be forging, but will eat.

forging he, although the talent different reported that but after all is also only 6th Rank Blacksmith, 7th Rank above Blacksmith compared with him. But must say eats, Tang Wulin has not thought really on Douluo Continent can have many people stronger than own.

„Good, what eats?” Tang Wulin looks at Devour Old Devil.

Devour Old Devil one step stepped forward arrived at side him, then held the shoulder of Tang Wulin, the personal appearance dodged, led him to vanish same place.

Devour Old Devil and Tang Wulin walked, Disillusioned Old Devil looks to Nightmare Old Devil, „Nightmare, this boy broke the record probably! Three months 6 days, cross sea to be successful, infiltrating North Sea Corps, succeeds to drive aircraft to return.”

Nightmare Old Devil nodded, has broken off the finger head, „probably broke the record. 1500 Hundred Year come the first person. That Little Fatty also crossed the sea to pass, but just passed is killed by the second. Also must make me give him to arrange. But such is normal. This Tang Wulin, worthily is Captain.”

Disillusioned Old Devil breaks off finger saying: „We must quickly want to select the means that suffers him well. He such good condition, carrying capacity also be much stronger than normal Soul Master. Good and good, most liked this abnormal level small Monster. Well where we must look for his weakness.”

Nightmare Old Devil cold snort one, „is not a human was you.”

Disillusioned Old Devil, „with you are person.”

„Disillusioned, you said that he in Devour there, how long needs to shoulder?” Nightmare Old Devil asked.

Disillusioned Old Devil hit to tremble suddenly smartly spirit, „Devour that fellow......, Really was too disgusting, not to mention was his matter good.”

When the scenery transformation, Tang Wulin once more is at present clear at present, has placed in forest. of course, in valley, vitality abundant forest.

-----------------------------------------

Blessed everybody Happy New Year again. Everybody looked slowly that the Dragon King following plot I basic have combed, will be definitely getting more and more attractive. Was right, now finally can in online smooth looked at the Dragon King legend, Peerless Tang Sect as well as God Realm Legends and cartoon of god seal throne, even also had our newest publication the cartoon of big carapace. Everybody uses cell phone searching day Tang animation, downloads this! The trend between cartoon and animation inundates.

#832: Devour Old Devil

Passes through here time each time, feeling that some Tang Wulin types returned to Shrek Academy, is really good to fondly remember the day when Academy! Although their cultivate was also very assiduous at that time, but at least does not have suffering that this body and mind simultaneously withstand.

Boiled with great difficulty front, following and joined. This Devour Old Devil he is first time saw that actually he does want to do?

What Tang Wulin most is worried is the companion situation, already and everybody separated was so long, did not have anything completely clearly. He does not even know that own companion are living whether.

Is Captain, he leads everybody to come here to participate in military training, if had problems, his Duty-bound Responsibility.

Devour Old Devil loosens grabs the hand of Tang Wulin, his sounds/voices is low and deep and vigorous, is even bringing slight(ly) echo in this forest.

„Does not need to be worried about your companion, so long as you worried that your own was good. You could rest assured that without my order, Nightmare that fellow will not take them to be what kind. They like suffering the human, but I actually do not like, that low rank interest also only then their these not mature devil will use. You with me, the day can feel better. You know why my title is called Devour?”

Does the day feel better?

On the Tang Wulin face the expression is invariable, in heart actually in the secret unstated criticism, believes you to be strange.

At the beginning, he actually somewhat believes that Disillusioned Old Devil, may along with him when the crime of absorb Ruin aura receiving, all sorts that in addition afterward had, which his can also not understand that Disillusioned Old Devil and Nightmare Old Devil radically were one group.

At present since this fellow is also one of the Old Devil, but can also compared with their how many? But trades the method to suffer own that's all.

Since does not know that the opposite party must do, he does not talk too much simply. He absolutely does not have other means now, can only be times supports from suffering of these Old Devil. In the Tang Wulin heart , the hopes, he is always hoping, these that own faces, eventually is only Academy Test, these Old Devil just in Test his that's all. Has this to hope existence, how painful process regardless of he has encountered, he can also insist reluctantly.

Devour Old Devil eye including profound meaning looked at Tang Wulin one, reason that „I called Devour, was because I liked eating. Before I liked, afterward after having become the devil, liked. Therefore, I am different from them, their spiritual has the issue, because is really idles here bored. Only then I, always have pleasure existence on Devil Island, that eats. So long as there is a thing of eating, I will not feel bored, eats to take to me the joyful and sense of joy.”

Eats? Heard this character, Tang Wulin has swallowed saliva subconsciously, since has arrived here, infers according to time, should have over three months, he has not eaten anything, completely depends upon here rich Life energy to support the body of own. Although this does not affect his physical condition, but regarding one became a habit with food had supplemented that own energy person, cannot eat the thing absolutely is the huge pain.

Now front had Old Devil to say to him likes eating, Tang Wulin thought immediately an intense sense of hunger broke in spiritual sea instantaneously. That is not reaction in physiology, completely is psychological stage.

Devour Old Devil looks at Tang Wulin to swallow the saliva the appearance, immediately said with a smile: „It looks like, you also like eating, is right?” Here, he hit a sound to refer, „that such looked like, we had the common language. From now on, so long as I eat anything, you eat anything. I guarantee you to be able very easy going through a strategic pass.”

Tang Wulin [say / way] without hesitation: „What does that eat?”

Devour Old Devil smiles, „felt relieved that I will not look for some specially disgusting thing. Since eats, of course must eat these to have the rich nutrition, and thing that can eat is good. Come, boy.”

At the same time was saying, he started toward forest walks. Tang Wulin hurries to follow.

Devour Old Devil walked few step to stop, then his squatting down body, has dug digging under a deep green bamboo, a finger hook, cancelled a length from the soil approximately three cuns (2.5cm), thick such as finger bluish-green big insect.

This insect is all over the body deep green, the body of green-blue seems somewhat insightful, after being held, is wriggling fiercely, seems panic-stricken wish struggles from the Devour Old Devil hand.

The Devour Old Devil right hand dug in earth two, quick has picked up insect.

One unlucky premonition floods in the Tang Wulin mind instantaneously, cannot......

In this time, he was seeing, Devour Old Devil insect will directly throw the own mouth, tucks away . Moreover the appearance that on face also enjoyment, the yellow juice flows following his corners of the mouth by under.( Writes about here, authors were straight disgusting, real regret should not write this after finish breakfast.)

„Vomits......” Tang Wulin is almost subconscious reaction, has turned around to retch toward the one side.

Too disgusting this is really. He again likes eating, does not like eating insect absolutely! The Devour Old Devil appearance, made the human not dare to look straight ahead simply.

At this moment, bluish-green form appear(ance) before him. Looks that is wriggling fiercely body, the close-range observation can also see on it that yellow down, the Tang Wulin complexion drastic change, is almost like lightning toward one side glittering.

For him eats matter that most has enjoyed, may at this moment, see that incomparably disgusting insect is placed in front of own, in addition these many days have not eaten the thing, Tang Wulin is unable to restrain reaction of own body. He is almost turns around runs, at this moment, his anything could not attend, only wants to be far away from that Devour Old Devil rapidly.

But, making his surprised one occur. Regardless of his speed quick, regardless of he uses the Tang Sect secret arts Ghost Shadow Perplexing Track step, is relying on Golden Dragon Soars sprint ability suddenly assault. That bluish-green insect actually rocks before him, absolutely does not have the least bit cast off sign.

Tang Wulin runs, retching that while keeps.

Suddenly, he only thinks in the own brain to transmit a dizziness feeling, he stiffly pressed in the ground, has not waited for his reaction to come, Tang Wulin only thought that a whole body hemp, strength in within the body Soul Power and Qi and Blood lived by Imprison. A big hand has pressed then firmly between the fingers his nose.

As a normal person, the nose was pressed firmly between the fingers, Tang Wulin subconscious opening mouth breath, then he helplessly looks that bluish-green, is wriggling insect has squeezed in his mouth directly.

A Devour Old Devil hand in a Tang Wulin chin place request, the mouth of Tang Wulin naturally closes.

insect in a feeling of person mouth fierce creeping motion......

The scalp sends to explode, at present becomes dark, fierce disgusting physiological reaction. But his anything could not do, even including moving finger could not achieve.

Devour Old Devil hoarse sounds/voices resounds in his ear, „said that but eats the thing. Why must run. Person who I most repugnant do not treat food well. Since you are not willing to eat it, that makes this only Bamboo Jointed Insect gradually be decomposed in your saliva. You will feel it from creeping motion, to cannot wriggle, the change juice gradually, flows following your throat, becomes your body part of feelings. Um, is very wonderful? This process, probably takes entire one day. You cannot move, cannot do any matter, but I can actually notice that your look Transformation also has Transformation of face muscle. Visits you to enjoy this delicacy expression. Oh, was really too wonderful. I must start to think, what will we eat tomorrow?”

------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#833: Vomiting ...

Tang Wulin rather goes to study aircraft, Tang Wulin rather goes to absorb Ruin energy. He even rather faces entire North Sea Corps artillery barrage, is not willing in this state of mind in the sober situation, to bear the so fierce pain throughout.

All that the words exaggeration of Devour Old Devil, he has not said are this time Tang Wulin feel. This is to at heart and suffering of physiological two aspect.

Whenever Tang Wulin suffered consciousness gradually fuzzy time, he will feel that spiritual sea was stimulated, the human instantaneously becomes sober, but at that time, was just he can a clearer feeling in all that in the own mouth had.

This feeling is really hard to describe in the spoken language. He wants dead now, only wants dead.

Finally, 24 hours passed by, racket of Devour Old Devil in the Tang Wulin top of the head, let his successful stupor in the past.

Looks to lie down in ground Tang Wulin, side Devour Old Devil, two forms reappear, is Nightmare Old Devil and Disillusioned Old Devil.

„You said that I was too cruel? I added a material to him. Before this way (of life) me, has imagined, has not realized. Can not be normal his exciting spiritual?” Asking of some Devour Old Devil as if worry.

„Does a bit less this set. You to he eats insect time how without hesitation.” Saying that Nightmare disdains.

A Disillusioned Old Devil face angry [say / way]: „You were really too mean, shameless. Before this method you, how not to have told us. Can you like this? Can you in suffering the method of person exceed us? Appearance that looks at his pain, in his heart, clearly you be stronger than our two. I am very discontented, do you know? My unusual is unsatisfied.”

„Ha Ha Ha Ha! Getting what one deserves. You like being satisfied, the old man is very in any case happy. Very happy. Oh, I must quickly give that several kids also to try. Has a look at them is any reaction. spiritual is not normal is also all right, doesn't have Loathing that fellow? He most can help the human restore spiritual.”

......

„Little Fatty, that such looks like, we had the common language. From now on, so long as I eat anything, you eat anything. I guarantee you to be able very easy going through a strategic pass.” Devour Old Devil smiles said to Xu Lizhi.

Xu Lizhi big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath. He puts together completely All-Out absorb Ruin energy, finally can mount the opposite shore, but, regardless of he uses any means that is actually not able to enter North Sea Corps. In his cognition, when artillery barrage approaches, he does not know that what's the matter, directly returned to Devil Island.

Then Nightmare Old Devil told him, he was defeated, immediately must release the toxic smoke. At this moment, Devour Old Devil just like Savior general appear(ance), Devour Old Devil told him, so long as he listened to own, can preserve companion not to be suffered by the toxic smoke.

Then, Xu Lizhi was brought in forest by Devour Old Devil.

Looks at that emerald-green big insect, Xu Lizhi blinked first, then saw that Devour Old Devil threw into the mouth to make an effort to chew insect.

Xu Lizhi stared in a big way the eye immediately.

Devour Old Devil smilingly visits him, then hears Xu Lizhi to ask surprised: „Can this thing eat? Delicious not?”

This time was one's turn Devour Old Devil to stare, then he saw that Xu Lizhi lifted the hand, has pinched another insect in his hand, has thrown into the mouth of own directly, mastication that also made an effort.

This......

After 32 mastications, Xu Lizhi eye one bright, then sees only his Adam's apple to move, obviously that insect swallowing.

„Oh, I also think very disgustingly. Who knows that the flavor is good! Although slightly has the bitterness, but in acid belt pain, after painstakingly, has to return to Gansu. What is more important, the whole is bringing the quiet fragrance of bamboo. After eating, in belly nice and warm, but also is very comfortable. Delicious! Has not thought that on Devil Island also has the so unique local product. Also, digs one to me again.”

Looks at a Xu Lizhi in high spirit appearance, Devour Old Devil enough slow the long time, muttered the tunnel: „Little Fatty, you are eating this aspect, is really the somewhat original talent.”

He was adding, actually saw that Xu Lizhi arrived at the tree to squat, both hands turn in the soil are looking......

The same thing, some people suffered desires live to want, serious that some people actually enjoy. of course, appear(ance) of this situation really not on Devil Island.

Devour Old Devil is always not a person of conceding, said accurately that everything Old Devil on this island, does not have one to concede. Therefore, he does everything possible to look for various types „superior” food asked Xu Lizhi to taste.

But where he actually knows that Xu Lizhi unexpectedly all comes are welcome, just started also slightly has the hesitation, may along with the passage of time, he actually be eats is getting more and more happy, is getting more and more excited. To finally, is over the face red light that eats, does not need Devour Old Devil to lead, he can also , in Devil Island this piece filled in Life aura valley to seek for various types „food”. Is a self-made person simply.

Devour Old Devil has to be repulsed, he can only choose to suffer other people. He has to acknowledge that the Xu Lizhi talent different reported that the spiritual big strip.

Without a doubt, Xu Lizhi broke the record......

Tang Wulin does not know how completely these two months of own come. Every day passed in the murkiness, to suffering of body also in next, on suffering to spiritual was really too intense.

The person who his likes eating, is noticed anything that Devour Old Devil suffers wants to spit. However, his body adapts to ability to have an effect formidable gradually.

Tang Wulin discovered quickly, body of own not, because the pain suffers to weaken, polarity, along with unceasing eats these strange things, any insect, cockroach, snake, mouse and ant and so on. Qi and Blood became even more is instead exuberant. Especially own Life aura, is strong serious.

......

„Devour Old Devil, Thank You (xiexie) you! But, that did insect have? How long it can live. Can I ask your matter, I stress several again, you ate to Le Zhengyu. This insect Life strength is so rich, is very certainly good to his body. He saved me with the Sacrifice talent before, lost too many Life energies, if can eat several insect, will certainly have good help function to him.”

Devour Old Devil dumbfounded looks a Xu Xiaoyan face take pity on is holding appreciatively in the hand bluish-green big insect, seems like manipulating any treasure the appearance.

Was this world? Food System Soul Master can eat insect, this young miss......

Xu Xiaoyan first time eats insect time, the painful degree and Tang Wulin are similar, but she discovered quickly that in this insect has filled rich Life aura. Therefore, when a Devour Old Devil second plan she eats insect, she had the present performance.

This adapts to ability......

Other is not good, adaptation ability of this miss simply is, certainly!

of course, is specially miserable.

For example......

„Vomited, vomits and vomits, has killed me!” Xie Xie was calling out pitifully. His spiritual must definitely collapse.

„Vomits, I must kill you, vomits, do not give me the opportunity, I must kill you!” Ye Xinglan pretty face became wax yellow.

„Vomits, vomits and vomits. I spelled with you!” The body of Yuan En Yehui is twitching unceasingly.

„Good, has had tears streaming down the face! Devour Mr. Old Devil, excuse me, how these insect should preserve. Can I bring to walk in departure. If can preserve, so rich Life energy support, our Holy Angel Family can more optional use Sacrifice talent. You looked that our Family has enough financial resource, we jointly develop the Life energy insect in Devil Island this valley. Perhaps we can become the raw materials for medicine their refining, in that case, you may be have made the remarkable contribution to the entire day under.” Le Zhengyu is also disgusting, but has him of Sacrifice talent, is all people are most intense regarding the Life energy sensation. Disgusting after having eaten insect, he has discovered mystery.

Thereupon, four people headed by Tang Wulin, had been suffered the entire three months by Devour Old Devil. But Le Zhengyu, Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi, recommended for admission to school to be promoted.

„You know that what in this world I am most repugnant is what?” Has the aquiline nose, the complexion gloomy old man stands in front of Le Zhengyu, asking that lets somebody cool off or calm down.

In his look, has been full of the color of Loathing, as if in his front Le Zhengyu is in this world most repugnant existence.

„I do not know.” Le Zhengyu honest saying.

With Devour Old Devil in together that several days, after is Le Zhengyu arrives at this Devil Island, the most satisfied day of passing. He uses Sacrifice for Xu Xiaoyan the Life strength of consumption, after eating many insect, restored was similar. This calculates absolutely on is the happiness of accident, this also made him decrease regarding this Devil Island loathing mood. Now the only expectation, can rescue own companion.

#834: Loathing Old Devil

„I am most repugnant, is this world. I called Loathing, remembered my name, Loathing Old Devil. I will take to you pain, ten times and hundred times and thousand times and ten thousand times of pain.”

The next quarter, Le Zhengyu was hung. Then, leather whip of getting wet on maliciously pulled out on his body.

Le Zhengyu has believed since that withstanding ability of own to ache is quite good. But in front of Loathing Old Devil, he discovered that own made a mistake. Because he does not know completely that can take to people in this world the pain the method unexpectedly so many and varied, moreover is such „stimulation”.

„” Pitiful yell sound, that moment of starting from being hung, again has not stopped.

The fierce pain continuously is stimulating the body and mind, struggling that Le Zhengyu goes all out, wants to work loose, but he actually can only look at own to be bruised and lacerated helplessly. Helplessly looks that the nail of own was raised flies, looks at own body gradual irrelevant to shatter, gradual suffocation.

......

Both eyes of Tang Wulin somewhat lost the focal distance, three months of suffering , the Life strength of his within the body is quite exuberant, but spiritual obviously somewhat was actually stimulated. Saw any is wriggling thing unconscious will tremble somewhat.

Although felt to afterward him Life energy that these „food” contains. May for him, in Life the so happy matter become so painful, how making him be able to accept?

But he hardly has shouldered, for companion, he has no alternative but to shoulder. In his present heart only then a thought that what kind of suffering, own must pass, must rescue companion.

Is relying on the tenacity will, he has supported the entire three months, supported Devour Old Devil to let off him finally.

Big mouth and big mouth is eating front various „food”, the Tang Wulin whole person was somewhat numb, only then in his eyeground deep place, has this such miraculous glow.

The corners of the mouth of Devour Old Devil also somewhat twitch.

In the object of his first suffering as Shrek Seven Monsters, he to Tang Wulin reaction is very satisfied, moreover practical from suffering the Tang Wulin process felt the intense pleasant sensation.

But, actually had discovered an issue to afterward him. That is, this fellow too can eat simply.

When his spiritual was numb, after own orders eats these seems very „disgusting” food, he started to show his capacity for food.

Most fearful one time, his own person, has eaten a length approximately seven meters, thick such as the python of thigh.

After that python eats, the Tang Wulin own body drew out reaction, scales not by Control under bloodline aura surges to reappear intensely. But he can also eat, and capacity for food increases steadily.

Devour Old Devil suffers Tang Wulin to be very satisfied regarding own, but he also very much loves dearly now. The capacity for food of this fellow is more fearful than that Little Fatty. Although Little Fatty also eats a lot, but Little Fatty, because had not been suffered, early was thrown by him to Loathing Old Devil. But this fellow, clearly is lived at present to want by the desire that own suffers, but this capacity for food also was really too fearful.

Eats that many and that many......

Devour Old Devil wicked thought that must suffer him to retaliate him time and time again to eat that many maliciously, may arrive afterward, she actually discovered that first this way, cannot bear is not Tang Wulin, but is his own. That many superior food! Even if here Life energy is abundant, cannot stand him so to consume! Therefore, he has to let off Tang Wulin, threw him to Loathing Old Devil.

„You know that what I most dislikes in this world?” Loathing Old Devil lets somebody cool off or calm down looks at Tang Wulin.

Do Tang Wulin some vision also delay, „also eat?”

„What eats to eat? Visits your waste the appearance, Devour that trick suffers this you, but also wants this Old Devil dependence pain to help you retrieve spiritual. Really repugnant, was too repugnant, I dislike this world, dislikes all!”

Tang Wulin was hung, leather whip brushing maliciously on him.

„!” The leather whip shoots, Tang Wulin clothes to shatter, skin surface, has left behind a spoken parts mark.

Bai Hen? How isn't the bloodstain? Loathing Old Devil has gawked. Does not believe in evil doctrines and has pulled out a whip, moreover increased several points of strength desirably.

Also is a spoken parts mark, no, said accurately that is only spoken parts mark. That that the first whip pulls out together, vanished......

This......

Loathing Old Devil of course does not believe that this was the normal situation, therefore, his whip was similar to the squally shower generally pulls out strikes on Tang Wulin.

Whip-marks spread across, Tang Wulin clothes ripped crushing. However, when the Loathing Old Devil plan changes a torture instrument, he actually discovered that Tang Wulin whip-mark vanished, has not stayed behind including a trace.

This......

What situation is this?

The pupil of Tang Wulin starts some focuses, he has not thought to hurt, but thought that within the body rich Life strength pulls out to strike outside whip, starts the gradual revolution, starts each other to fuse with the strength of his Qi and Blood. In process that each other blends, a comfortable transmission beyond description spreads the whole body.

Since spiritual sea has obtained is painful assault, finally some comfortable feeling, the spiritual world obtained certain affability finally.

These three months were forced to eat these disgusting things, in some sense, Tang Wulin already the heart seal of own. Can numb eating. His of course does not have time revolution own Soul Power and Qi and Blood intercoordination.

But at this time, in the outside brings under the stimulation of pain, strength of Mysterious Heaven Skill and bloodline will protect the body voluntarily, on revolution naturally, thus stimulates his mind gradually to restore.

The incisive stabbing pain transmits at this moment.

Loathing Old Devil does not know where looked for a long steel nail, punctured the thorn on Tang Wulin, the steel sews under his strength function, finally punctured the skin of Tang Wulin. Has bloodstain appear(ance) faintly.

The stabbing pain brushed formerly the whip obviously is more intense, under this more intense stimulation, Tang Wulin strength of Golden Dragon King bloodline and Mysterious Heaven Skill naturally also on smoother several points of revolution. His spiritual world also finally slowly opens.

Loathing Old Devil saw the eyelet rapid closing that was actually punctured, absolutely does not have the process of scab, restored normally.

When he uses the nail to puncture the body of Tang Wulin, he discovers under the Tang Wulin skin to be similar golden-colored halo, skin itself extremely tenacity, when he uses the steel nail to puncture, will also feel Tang Wulin by the stabbing skin place rapidly to be stiffened, as if also has scales to reappear to resemble.

He lifted the hand to seal up Tang Wulin Soul Power, has sealed up his bloodline revolution. But, he is actually not able to seal up the instinct of Tang Wulin body.

Various types of torture instruments took unceasingly by him, uses on Tang Wulin.

The consciousness of Tang Wulin sobered finally completely, looks at busy Loathing Old Devil, looks on own appear(ance) scars, then looks at their rapid closing. Tang Wulin sneers.

Pain?

When this pain when own six years old starts to study forging already became a habit. He is not does not fear to hurt, but regarding sore withstood ability to go far beyond the average person. Even if powerful Soul Master, impossible and he compares the carrying capacity. Let alone he also has the strong resistance to hit ability.

Golden Dragon King bloodline the strength of self-recovery was too strong, physical attack or energy attack, Tang Wulin oneself has the strong resistance.

Thereupon, Loathing Old Devil used the skills on Tang Wulin, traded was actually only sneering of others corners of the mouth place.

Hurts again, can after assault Golden Dragon King Seal compared with the rending ache of bringing? That is from inside to outside.

------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#835: The gas cloud is near finally

Therefore, Loathing Old Devil had almost been wild with rage by Tang Wulin, under to started the cruel methods finally. May be the bone breaks off, Tang Wulin is also without turning a hair, moreover his body also rapid to heal and recover completely.

As for the strategic point of Tang Wulin torso part, has the Mountain Dragon King Torso Bone protection, only if Loathing Old Devil strikes crushes the Tang Wulin whole body, otherwise is unable to suffer the method of person to use his these in the Tang Wulin body.

„Mixes the boy, you are turtle?” Loathing Old Devil angry incomparable the wolf's tooth club in own hand still on Tang Wulin, turned around to walk. He needs to vent, this is not good, that trades one!

Tang Wulin was put finally, works as Disillusioned Old Devil of good person.

„Loathing this fellow, was really too virulent. Tang Wulin, are you all right?” A Disillusioned Old Devil face kind looks at Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin lets somebody cool off or calm down visits him, „also has any method, you use. When you exhaust the bag of clumsy tricks, should put my companion.”

Disillusioned Old Devil sighed, „this may have nothing to do with me, was Nightmare Old Devil does. I can help you achieve, as far as possible limits him, making him do not release really that gas cloud.”

Tang Wulin did not speak, he more and more somewhat guessed regarding these Old Devil behaviors now.

In any event, at least he now is also living, moreover live is very good.

Under Loathing Old Devil hits randomly, before he, eats Life energy all absorb in these disgusting things to complete with Devour Old Devil together. The present he more and more Control did not live in the strength of own that exuberant incomparable Qi and Blood to go to assault Ninth Layer Seal.

Moreover Tang Wulin even can also feel, so long as own wants, breaks through Ninth Layer Seal to be the successful matter, will not have too many pain.

He must divert attention with very big energy now comes Control bloodline energy of own within the body, is insufficient to break through Seal voluntarily.

If suffers them purely, they should weakly be more and more right, possibly to be how getting stronger and stronger?

Moreover, process that entire suffers although pain, but without a doubt, Tang Wulin has the harvest. He can feel promotion of own in fields. Not only on ability, is in mentality.

Looks at the Tang Wulin ice-cold look, Disillusioned Old Devil complexion sinks suddenly, „didn't boy, you appreciate kindness rendered? Is you thinks I with them am also one group?”

Tang Wulin light [say / way]: „You aren't one group?”

Disillusioned Old Devil gets angry: „of course not. Good, since you think. Good, I did not manage you. How casual Nightmare copes with you.”

Then, he turns head to walk. Personal appearance in a flash, on disappearing trail.

Tang Wulin disdains the appearance that snort, Disillusioned Old Devil has installed where he can unable to see, this clearly is outwardly fierce but inwardly faint-hearted. However, he also believes that these model workers have not let off own easily. What then do they want to make?

In the Tang Wulin doubts time, near ear has transmitted Nightmare Old Devil sounds/voices suddenly.

„Is very good, now nobody was protecting you. That, enjoyment heartily.”

surroundings all suddenly become dizzy. When the dizziness feeling vanishes, the Tang Wulin surprised discovery, he arrived in a cavern.

The ray in cavern is somewhat dim, can only see clearly inside all reluctantly.

Groans along with it resounding, Tang Wulin saw him immediately already separately long time companion.

Xie Xie, Le Zhengyu and Xu Lizhi, Yuan En Yehui, Xu Xiaoyan and Ye Xinglan. They sober in abundance from the stupor. Expressions have the difference respectively.

But, they were on spiritual received certain stimulation without a single exception obviously.

„Is everybody how is it? You fortunately?” Tang Wulin sees companion, the mood surges, hurries to ask. But this opens the mouth to discover that own sounds/voices is unexpectedly hoarse.

People's this time consciousness restores reluctantly, some vision actually as before delay.

At this moment, in the cavern hears rumble suddenly, has not waited for their reaction to come, several iron bars have dropped from the clouds. Isolates seven people.

Tang Wulin is Xu Xiaoyan is separated in the same place, in nearby iron bar, is Xu Lizhi and Yuan En Yehui, another side is Ye Xinglan, Le Zhengyu and Xie Xie three people.

Shrek Seven Monsters was isolated three.

This is......

Suddenly, unlucky premonition appear(ance) in the Tang Wulin heart, at this moment, bunch of thick fog erupts suddenly from their top of the head. They had seen that pink mist.

„It is not good, stop breathing!” Yelling of Tang Wulin almost shouting oneself hoarse.

All people have experienced these pink mist, all tries stop breathing in first time.

But they discovered immediately, own Soul Power by completely Seal . Moreover the whole body is the worn out and aching is incapable. In this case, impossible stop breathing too to be long.

The pink mist floods in the cavern, more fearful matter appear(ance). That mist such as the silk such as the wisp, starts to permeate their skins.

The mouth and nose can temporarily stop breathing, but skin does not have the means.

Helplessly looks at mist permeating within the body, simultaneously the body started to have the dry and hot feeling, seven people were all scared.

Very obviously, Nightmare Old Devil is deliberate way (of life) that they isolate. Absolutely does not have a pair of lover to be isolated together.

Tang Wulin shouted angrily, „male student hit to faint own. Quick!”

His willpower strength is always very formidable, although felt that the dryness and heat in own body made his some Placement be ready to make trouble, but he has made the correct choice in first time. Without hesitation hits toward the sidewall of cavern.

„Puff!”

The hit on cavern stone cliff(wall), actually soft is full of the elastic feeling of transmitting. The body of Tang Wulin was shot directly, sits falls down.

Le Zhengyu, Xu Lizhi and Xie Xie naturally also heard the Tang Wulin words, and has carried out in first time, but their situations actually and Tang Wulin is exactly the same. The body was shot to come back directly, sits on the ground. Although some dizziness, but was remote from stupor in the past.

What to do?

Seven people of all with amazement discolorations.

They most frightened situation, finally appear(ance). The pink mist is getting more and more rich. Because formerly greatly drank to make noise, Tang Wulin has inhaled two inevitably.

The property of this pink mist is quite overbearing, but this time, Tang Wulin Golden Dragon King bloodline cannot play finally protects his function.

The Dragon Clan natural disposition is obscene, is Dragon King, in Golden Dragon King bloodline apparently does not have any resistance in this aspect. Regarding Dragon Clan, they always keep aloof, visits the inferior race is to the dissemination of own bloodline, is a gracious gift, will otherwise not have that many Sub-Dragon appear(ance).

May, this absolutely be at this moment fatal to Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin only thought that the body of own is generally scalding hot just like the charcoal, whole body likely by heat generally. His both hands hold the iron bar, effort knocks to the iron bar the head of own. But actually as before cannot have reduces this time body stronger and stronger impulsion slightly.

He is unable to summon own strength of help Martial Soul and bloodline. Even if wants to commit suicide cannot achieve. Formidable body instinct protects him not to receive any injury sufficiently.

The situations of other people are less than Tang Wulin, in the Xu Xiaoyan mouth has transmitted hum gently, she also grabs the iron bar, the body unceasingly is shivering. Relies on own willpower strength to suppress the natural disposition of own body completely.

Xu Lizhi a little could not bear, his obese body rolls up in the corner. Another side, the Yuan En Yehui willpower strength wants to be stronger, although she breath shortness, but can also be able to bear temporarily.

Xie Xie, Le Zhengyu and Ye Xinglan here situation is subtle, Ye Xinglan hides in the distant place, sits cross-legged to sit in the ground, the forehead sees the perspiration, is restraining the effect of gas cloud reluctantly.

Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu to fear to affront her, they draw back is very far, moreover in distance near place.

In their this time hearts panic-stricken at the same time, intense * also in unceasing eruption.

„Zhengyu, you have killed me.” Xie Xie smiles bitterly was saying to Le Zhengyu.

Le Zhengyu gets angry suddenly exclaims: „You especially touches my thigh to do? I must be able to kill you, you think that I will show mercy? Had the skill you to kill me.”

„I have not traced your thigh, is you hugs my waist to be good. Let me die, making me die!”

They more make noise, the pink mist of inspiration are also more, the body more and more could not withstand the corrosion of this gas cloud.

„Nightmare Old Devil. How you want to make us do, I promise you, stops these gas clouds!” The Tang Wulin fierce anger exclaimed.

Sees the picture is a matter, genuine facing is a different matter.

---------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#836: Gu Yue?

When Tang Wulin could not restrain own shortly, when starts toward Xu Xiaoyan that him approaches slowly, he flustered finally. Regardless of the innermost feelings are firm, in this case, he also has to compromise.

„Fears anything, first enjoys life, that is how wonderful! You looked that a such attractive young miss will soon arrive your reluctantly. Why must restrain own *? The release, released heartily your * is good.”

sounds/voices does not belong to Nightmare Old Devil, instead is a female voice, very delightful interesting to listen to female voice, in sounds/voices is bringing light attracting, although not strong, was similar to at this time the blasting fuse is but ordinary.

The Tang Wulin eye sees with a blur a while ago, that approached his Xu Xiaoyan gradually as if changed, turned into the Na'er appearance, turned into the Gu Yue appearance.

Tang Wulin exhausts All-Out telling own, gradually that approaches is not Gu Yue, will not be Na'er. But, the property of that pink mist was really too strong, formidable, not only corroded his body to stimulate his instinct, was links his spiritual world also to start to corrode to enter.

Intermittent illusion unceasingly appear(ance) in mind, once and Gu Yue in together lovely time unceasing flashes in his mind.

The Tang Wulin double fist grips tightly, the unceasing effort attempts to struggle from this illusion, but he actually discovered that own actually can only unceasing perishing in the illusion.

Finally, a hot and damp palm held his shoulder, Tang Wulin felt immediately the body of own seems similar to the volcanic eruption generally soon will burst open.

He is almost subconscious turning round, his eyes became red.

But also at this moment, all pink mist suddenly are similar to heavy drinker absorbing water generally vanish from the hole top do not see, just likes the waterfall common ice water drops from the clouds, in seven people of squeals, was soaked through the heart to be cool them.

All * was irrigated clean that extinguishes in an instant, the people dizzy brain in an instant is also sobering.

Tang Wulin hit to tremble smartly spirit, his clear seeing, Xu Xiaoyan was near at hand, a hand was grabbing the shoulder of own, but the hand of own lifted, if were not that ice water falls, must fall on him.

Moreover the two sides situations are also similar.

A Yuan En Yehui foot steps on Xu Lizhi carries on the back, Xu Lizhi lies on the ground in gulps is panting for breath.

Ye Xinglan willpower strength, but also no longer is sits cross-legged to sit there, but is both hands support in the ground, makes movement that will soon throw to strike.

What most is awkward is Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu. At this time they have hugged in the same place, after the ice water waters, simultaneously sober two been dumbfounded looks at the opposite party.

„Vomits......” they also to tilt the head, makes the vomitive the movement, then the lightning distributes.

„What you and do you have to me make?” They almost with one voice is roaring.

Luckily, their clothes are complete, obviously has not been in the next step degree.

The intense sense of fear along with it flooding in seven people of mind, they are unable to imagine, if just that pink mist again continued, actually to have what kind of Transformation.

This will let their pain absolutely lifelong, will make them abandon the huge attack of Life.

In suffering to mind, unequalled.

„Now, you should be obedient some.” Nightmare Old Devil brings several points of strange sounds/voices to resound. A series of strange laughter also along with it flooding in the entire pain.

That giant voice fluctuation echo, the Tang Wulin seven people quick fell into the stupor under sound wave intense assault.

Since arriving here, they have met Disillusioned, Nightmare, Devour and Loathing four Old Devil successively. Each Old Devil suffers the method of person is to emerge one after another incessantly, each Old Devil is such terrifying. But they did not resist.

These Old Devil fully held the weakness in their human nature, they who since a half year of time, has suffered regardless of the body and mind, suffered enormous devastation.

When Tang Wulin sobers from the deep sleep, he discovers own also in the cavern. In cavern besides him, another form. That person by stone cliff(wall), the body wears a purple cape, cannot see the appearance.

The takes a deep breath tone, Tang Wulin discovered that own strength of Soul Power and Qi and Blood can again Control. Subconscious stands up from failure to sit up, besides the also a little dizziness, all returned to normal.

Calmed down, Tang Wulin careful arrived at that person of side probe head to examine in the past.

This looked that made him stare in a big way the eye surprisedly.

Under purple hood, is tender face that plays musical instruments to break, her skin is fair and exquisite, the look is not outstandingly beautiful, but has the unequalled important position in the Tang Wulin heart.

Sees her, Tang Wulin first reaction is this is impossible. But, he also has the feeling of body and mind megascism.

He has pinched the thigh of own subconsciously, makes an effort very much. Very sore!

Is is not having a dream, the present all are real. His subconscious and searched the hand in the past, has pinched on her face.

„Um!” Young girls light snort, the long eyelash moves, has opened eyes slowly.

Four items of relative, the Tang Wulin look instantaneously becomes excited, but that person of look, actually appear(ance) absent-minded and confusedness of moment.

„Where I and is my this?” Young girl dull saying.

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „Here is Devil Island. Are you, really you?”

The young girls sit the straight body fiercely, as if at this time returns to the soul, loses the sound track: „How you and you can here. You......”

Yes, this young girl is not others, is missing long time Gu Yue.

Tang Wulin visits her dull, looks at being startled of her face, „Gu Yue, you make me look well painstakingly!”

The breath of Gu Yue is obviously rapid, she stood up fast, looked at all around, muttered the tunnel: „You and you how here, I just obviously also in Spirit Transferring Pagoda, you......”

Tang Wulin shakes the head, „I said that I do not know, you do believe?”

A Gu Yue hand according to above the own milk-white bosom, she has turned around suddenly, the back to Tang Wulin, is looking like is not willing to resemble facing him, breath shortness.

„Why must walk! What matter has is we cannot go facing, to solve together? Yes, present I am not very formidable. Perhaps was unable completely to protect you, but I will certainly try hard, certainly will try hard becomes stronger. Future I, can certainly protect you. Gu Yue, do not leave me again?”

Tang Wulin arrives at her behind, both hands somewhat shiver are holding her arm, pulls slowly her body.

„You do not understand, you did not understand that is not that simple.” Gu Yue sounds/voices somewhat shivers, „, if, how I give up to leave you! However, I actually cannot keep side you, for your security, for your future.”

Tang Wulin makes an effort to pull her, making her face own, „you worried that I am unable to withstand, but actually can you tell me are what matter? You believe that in this world, besides you, I can also like others?”

Gu Yue light [say / way]: „Some that many outstanding girls like you, you can choose them greatly.”

„Are you sincerity?” Tang Wulin sinking sound track.

Gu Yue do not go excessively, has not spoken.

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, „told me, any matter, you must make me know the first truth of matter, we way that came to find to solve are also together good! Perhaps, I did not have ability to protect you now, I also agreed that for our future can separate temporarily. But you at least must make me know the reason, at least must make me see the future hope. You are like my, among us sentiment real, this was enough. I believe own, in the future will certainly have ability to protect you, protects side you. Actually is any matter, told me.”

#837: The bustling place builds up the heart, the desire is boundless

Gu Yue lowered the head, she has not spoken. Suddenly, her fierce throwing to the Tang Wulin bosom, gains ground, kiss to him.

Tang Wulin becomes by her the mood of surging had a scare suddenly, but is feeling that familiar aura, feels lip that she is warming up, he almost fell to the enemy instantaneously.

Her movement is very jerky, when like their first time is kissing each other, but in that jerky, has the Tang Wulin innumerable attachments.

Their breath start become rapid, the temperature in cavern as if starts to elevate gradually. In the Tang Wulin heart fiery is ascending unceasingly.

Their nearly madness is tearing each other clothes, as if all constrains in the heart of hearts * bursts out in this moment.

At this moment, suddenly, Tang Wulin felt that a own front pain, a grieved feeling of difficult word spreads over the whole body slightly instantaneously, makes his ascended unusual intense * fierce trembles.

The front stabbing pain changes into scalding hot, seemed relating anything. Tender body before his body as in All-Out is demanding, but the Tang Wulin look actually gradually becomes Pure Brightness.

He hugs her right hand, golden-colored is sparkling suddenly, changes into Sharp Claws, grasping maliciously on her head. The Tang Wulin anger exclaimed: „You are not she!”

During dazzling golden light (Jin Guang) sparkles, the Gu Yue form instantaneously became illusory, came to naught, vanished before his body without the trace, on Golden Dragon Claw [gold/metal] turnover, the Tang Wulin big mouth and big mouth was panting for breath.

But until this time, is sticking to that silver scales of his chest throughout, ray of light gradually is dim.

Yes, is the reminder of that scales, makes Tang Wulin be able to come soberly, before making him be able to recognize the family background , the status of person.

Surprised and interesting to listen to sounds/voices along with it resounding, „my illusion unearths from your heart of hearts, you can actually from sobers, this is really surprising. However, that as if not belong to your strength. The bustling place builds up the heart, * boundless. Hello, I am *@ Old Devil.”

In the gloomy corner, a female walked gracefully, she says Old Devil, is not old, seems is the 20-year-old appearance, dressing up of ten points exposition, the milk-white bosom half dew, the slender thigh is perfectly round, the frown and smile, direct the person daydream all.

Her look made Tang Wulin somewhat not see clearly, but felt that actually very much looked like Gu Yue. But in fact, trades anybody saw her time, will feel that she looks like own Lover.

In the Tang Wulin eye the cold brightness jumps shoots, „why you and do you want to suffer me with such way (of life)? You......”

*@ Old Devil shows a faint smile, very confident is facing the question of Tang Wulin, „not why, only to have a look, your loves are thorough any degree. I only then *, have not loved, therefore, what that is willing to peep at * is specially others' love brings. This is my joy.”

The Tang Wulin look changes cold, just about to says anything, actually listens to *@ Old Devil saying: „I already guessed correctly actually, in your several people, is most difficult to do should be you, because you are not quite easy to deceive, you do not have Lover to follow come here. What a pity, you fell to the enemy, but can see, you love is very profound. Therefore can so. Do you want to take a look, what are reaction of other people?”

Tang Wulin has gawked, has not waited for him to reply, the *@ Old Devil right hand in airborne wields, piece of Light and Shadow flashes through, six light screens on appear(ance) in him at present.

Six light screens, of course is representing Shrek Seven Monsters other six people.

Light screen similarly in cavern, moreover seems is Tang Wulin location cavern exactly the same place. In a first cavern, impressively Xie Xie, personal appearance transparent Yuan En Yehui, without doubt, that was the illusion.

This time Xie Xie, has been holding Yuan En Yehui, what is extraordinary, he actually less further movement.

Xie Xie gently is panting for breath, as if in restraining anything, both hands of Yuan En Yehui is walking randomly behind him, the tender body as if must insert his body.

The breath of Xie Xie somewhat is obviously rapid, but his movement actually appears somewhat stiff.

„You and you did not say, after we want and other marriage, is willing to be intimate with me?” Xie Xie pants for breath was saying.

The [say / way] of false Yuan En Yehui sounds/voices fluttering flags: „In this Devil Island, we are in a precarious state radically. I quite feared that is good to fear the beforehand situation occurred. I must time give you own first, at least, no longer has regrettable. Xie Xie, loves me.”

The Xie Xie body shakes, subconscious, a hand grasps to the buttocks of Yuan En Yehui.

However, saw his hand must fall before the Yuan En Yehui buttocks flickers, the hand of Xie Xie stopped suddenly. He roars, „you die especially.” The wrist turns, Light Dragon Dagger appear(ance) was grasping, pricked the body of false Yuan En Yehui from the sides of the small of the back place.

Sees this, Tang Wulin is dumbfounded.

When, did the Xie Xie willpower strength become so formidable? In his impression, Xie Xie always does not have what restraint ability person! Moreover, on him is impossible to have like own Silver Dragon scales can awaken own goods existence. His resisted the attack of illusion with the own willpower strength completely.

Not only he, similarly is also shocked in his *@ Old Devil, dumbfounded looks at this. What situation is this?

The body of false Yuan En Yehui came to naught to vanish similarly, then Tang Wulin saw, Xie Xie had tears streaming down the face muttered: „I think that this is real! But, Yuan En that temperament, how possible, because falls into the hopeless situation to devote to me! Person who she has the principle, I to the present, have not drawn several times including the hand! This good deed I also think, but this is how possible! If really good, if really good!”

Tang Wulin speechless, is not this fellow willpower strength strong, but is the Yuan En Yehui character issue, in addition he understanding Yuan En Yehui, even also some hides fearing in heart of hearts. After all, he sees Yuan En to take a bath twice accidentally, later was played by the pain, has cast certain shadow.

Almost is subconscious, Tang Wulin looked to six pieces of Light and Shadow, was Yuan En Yehui that piece.

„!” A Yuan En Yehui big mouth, pulled out to fly false Xie Xie. False Xie Xie to words that she spoke, to similar that beforehand false Yuan En Yehui said.

But Yuan En Yehui is such aggressive......, pretty face blushes, but was still a palm of the hand pulled out flew false Xie Xie.

„You and you how under such heavy hand, you quite hit me to be sore.” False Xie Xie crawls from the ground, the whole face is sad.

Yuan En Yehui sneers, „hurts? Sorer. You radically are not he, he does not have this courage to dare with me to request this. You radically are an adulteration.”

Sees here, in the Tang Wulin heart the secret unstated criticism, Xie Xie this wife managed the strict degree to arrive at what kind of realm to let Yuan En Yehui such having confidence! Usually really has not looked that now looks like, perhaps Xie Xie by the Yuan En control, but heavy!

Is looks at *@ Old Devil in suffering own companion obviously, but why does not know, after looking at Yuan En Yehui and Xie Xie this two sides, Tang Wulin has the impulsion that plants to smile.

What his next looks to approach is the Xu Lizhi location cavern.

„I do not dare, Sister Xinglan, I do not dare. You in my heart are such Sacred, I, I a little have not been ready. Sister Xinglan, you leave this, my a little not became a habit. You in my heart are not such! Do not trace me! I, I and I......”

Little Bai pig that Xu Lizhi looks like trembling, rolls up in the corner, false Ye Xinglan squats side him, feeling that some are unable to start unexpectedly.

Tang Wulin sees here, the corners of the mouth twitched, is really because the Xu Lizhi appearance is not quite elegant, his chubby body rolled up there did not say, but also both hands covered own important Placement, lowered the head, does not dare to look at the coquettish look such as silk false Ye Xinglan.

„Lizhi, are you do do? The beforehand situation you also saw, I feared really that feared here will have the mishap, while us in the same place, I must give you most precious thing. I know that these years you very much have liked me, what do you fear now?”

Xu Lizhi big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath, his body actually as before rolls up in the same place, „Sister Xinglan, I not. I cannot take advantage of somebody. Sister Xinglan, do not force me to be good, I have not been ready. Do you know? The dream in my heart, had been vainly hoping for one day, I can be properly married you, if our marriage room certainly the red arrangement, you wear the wedding dress to sit on the bed, I can justifiable with you in the same place. I am really good to like you, therefore I cannot blaspheme you, the matter of men and women is Sacred, I must complete this life important matter under the etiquette of Sacred with you.”

------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#838: rarely seen companion

Tang Wulin dumbfounded looks at Little Fatty in picture, has not thought really that he is an idealist.

False Ye Xinglan cold snort, „can we live are leaving cannot reach an agreement, you also think that many do do? Isn't your aspect good?”

Xu Lizhi fierce gaining ground, the vision suddenly becomes sharp, „you are not Sister Xinglan, Sister Xinglan has been protecting from infancy to maturity me, words that will not always say this injuring my self-respect. You are not she!”

At the same time was saying, he body, he actually had not then moved in first time, looks that front has removed completely the light false Ye Xinglan, stayed, said: „Sister Xinglan , if not wear the clothes, is such?” Then he has swallowed saliva. Then a palm of the hand claps.

Tang Wulin shot a look at one to stand in own *@ Old Devil, the *@ Old Devil expression was somewhat ugly at this time.

Tang Wulin subconscious looks to another side, looks to the Ye Xinglan location picture.

Really with is the same, Ye Xinglan willpower strength that he thinks absolutely strong . Moreover, she also similarly very much understands Xu Lizhi.

A sword pierces the chest of false Xu Lizhi, the [say / way] that Ye Xinglan lets somebody cool off or calm down: „The Lizhi courage is so small, how possibly dares to do this matter to me. Let alone, his innermost feelings are pure, will not produce unable to live is leaving first has the relational with me the thought.”

Five, five people have been separated from own Control unexpectedly. *@ Old Devil is the willow eyebrows but is actually at this time vertical, both hands fork waist, a resentfulness of face.

Tang Wulin subconscious looks to the Xu Xiaoyan location picture.

Xu Xiaoyan as if has been unable to restrain oneself at this time, is bending down in the false Le Zhengyu bosom.

False Le Zhengyu supple sound track: „Xiaoyan, I love you. Although I do not know that can lead you to live is leaving here, but I am willing to give you all my. I am not the dandy, are you willing to become my first woman?”

The Xu Xiaoyan tender body trembles lightly, „I want, but, I a little feared that I have not prepared. Can Zhengyu, give me to select time again?”

False Le Zhengyu said in a soft voice: „What do you also need time to ponder? I am willing for your Sacrifice all, to use my talent Sacrifice for you, is also not enough to prove me to your love? Even if dies for you, I am also willing. Xiaoyan, I love you.”

At the same time was saying, false Le Zhengyu lowered the head to the Xu Xiaoyan lip kisses.

Suddenly, Xu Xiaoyan look one cold, body starlight dodges, false Le Zhengyu could not move.

„You radically are not Zhengyu, Zhengyu will not bestow favor to coerce. Who are you?” The Xu Xiaoyan anger sound said.

False Le Zhengyu just about to opens the mouth, Xu Xiaoyan a palm of the hand has pulled out. Then his body came to naught to vanish.

Tang Wulin look somewhat strange looks to *@ Old Devil, „you were defeated, because you also insufficiently understand us.”

The breath of *@ Old Devil somewhat is obviously rapid, „and is not I insufficiently understands you, but is my own was mentally confused. Comes under the influences of your front several people, behind was somewhat irritable. Damn, really damn. How can make you affect my mood. Luckily, is successful!”

Speaking of the last few words time, she has smiled suddenly, her smiling face was very beautiful, but Tang Wulin actually moral nature one cold.

Last picture, Le Zhengyu has fallen down false Xu Xiaoyan.

The picture starts becomes fuzzy, Tang Wulin cannot see clearly process, but can actually hear sounds/voices indistinctly.

Zhengyu he......

Seven people, six people in * have not fallen to the enemy, this without doubt is very pleasantly surprised result. However, so long as there is a person to fall to the enemy, Tang Wulin as before felt that was not wonderful.

*@ Old Devil somewhat self-satisfied looks to Tang Wulin, „wants to know very much that what the consequence of falling to the enemy is?”

Tang Wulin heart one tight, gets angry: „Do you want to do?”

*@ Old Devil smiles, „you waited to look know.”

Long time, Le Zhengyu satisfied sends out comfortable sounds/voices, „Xiaoyan, I love you. You could rest assured that I will certainly be responsible for you, regardless of space underground, you where, I where.”

„Are you willing to be responsible for me really?”

The picture becomes clear, Le Zhengyu and Xu Xiaoyan have worn the clothes, when Xu Xiaoyan said these words, her sounds/voices started Transformation, from originally delightful started interestingly to listen to becomes rough hoarse, coarse such as the crow sounded.

Le Zhengyu saw in consternation that front Xu Xiaoyan starts becomes illusory, gradually, turned into an old woman appearance of last years of life.

In the old woman mouth sends out „quack” smiles strangely, „the body of young people, but also is really good. The bustling place builds up the heart, * boundless, hello, I am *@ Old Devil. Do you also love me?”

Le Zhengyu dumbfounded looks at front old woman, a complexion azure, red, suddenly, he „”, spouts fresh blood, raises head but actually.

„!” Tang Wulin *@ Old Devil hit a sound to refer, „then right, this was the effect that I wanted.”

Tang Wulin angry [say / way]: „You......”

*@ Old Devil has turned around, smiling visits him, „* boundless, has * is not the misdemeanor. The time understood restrains own *, when * the release must maintain a sobriety, the human could not control own, was selected the crime is also not anything. Your luck is good, otherwise, you are the same with him.”

Then, pink Light and Shadow dodges, Tang Wulin front *@ Old Devil and that six Light and Shadow all vanished without the trace.

*@ Old Devil, this is fifth Old Devil.

Zhengyu he......

Thinks of the Le Zhengyu bitter experience, in the Tang Wulin heart intermittent icy aura. Le Zhengyu does not know with him what has relations are only a illusion, but will regard the old woman shape *@ Old Devil. This for him, the attack was really too big. Has traded own, perhaps will not compare him to be good many.

It can be said that Le Zhengyu willpower isn't firm? Tang Wulin thinks cannot. Because his own does not have Control to live. Only can say stopping at nothing that Le Zhengyu loves. But Ye Xinglan, Xu Lizhi, Yuan En Yehui and Xie Xie they can avoid this issue, because mainly their these two pairs of relations are quite relatively special.

But Xu Xiaoyan is the luck is good, is just because *@ Old Devil was sad at that time, has not controlled good false Le Zhengyu and her dialog, this made her hold the flaw.

But Le Zhengyu was miserable, this attack is not really small. Does not know after him, how to face. Has traded Tang Wulin own in any case, he thought that perhaps is faces very much difficultly. The bustling place builds up the heart, is the bustling place builds up the heart really! Zhengyu, you may probably shoulder!

Without a doubt, *@ Old Devil is impossible to make him see Le Zhengyu, naturally is unable to tell the truth of Le Zhengyu matter. He was just the psychosexuality Xu Xiaoyan, not in fact made anything. But on the sense organ, just all was really too real. Tang Wulin still clearly remembers, own pinches the own thigh time is very sore.

Light and Shadow Transformation, surroundings all become twist. Tang Wulin returned just to enter the valley place.

Has a look at surroundings, does not have other people, here only then his own.

Tang Wulin of course does not think that these Old Devil like this will let off him, what then can be?

In this time, „thump” sounds/voices resounds, as if has any behemoth to walk in his direction.

„Young people, you passed.” Vigorous sounds/voices paces back and forth in the Tang Wulin ear. In the woods, goes out of a personal appearance huge old man.

Truly must with be able to describe him huge, this old man height exceeds three meters, the body is quite plump. Because although is old, skin already appear(ance) big piece fold, but his appearance looked like appears compared with formerly that several Old Devil young. of course, young woman edition *@ Old Devil not.

Went through a strategic pass?

------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#839: Their stories

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, „calculates according to time, I come here should six months. Before coming to here, Academy told me, this should be two years of military training, do I pass now? If you want to deceive me, perhaps you want to be too many.”

The obese old man arrives in front of him, „why do I want to deceive you? Two years? That is to the average person. You believe that can cross sea to make aircraft to come back, can this matter everyone three months like you complete? In fact, your several friends did not have one to complete. You are only one complete at present. But cannot complete that inspection, is impossible to go through a strategic pass.”

„In fact, believes that you also some guessed. Does Shrek Academy possibly really make you come to bring death? All these are the Academy arrangements. In fact, can you know our origins?” Saying that the obese old man smiles.

Origin?

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, does not have the least bit to believe his meaning as before.

The obese old man he he smiles, „does not believe has not related, when I said that it is estimated that you will also believe some. First makes me come to you to speak the Devil Island take shape reason.”

At the same time was saying, he arrived in front of Tang Wulin to sit without consulting anybody, even if sits, he also be higher than Tang Wulin.

The right hand wields, a front appear(ance) table, then does not know where he from pulls out, various types of food have chocked up one table.

The Tang Wulin retreat two steps, thick smell sharp aroma, making his index finger greatly move. But had Devour Old Devil Test, his of course will not act rashly.

The obese old man waved, „*, comes out.”

The form dodges, young version *@ Old Devil appear(ance), arrived at the table to be implicated baseless.

The obese old man said: „After I he said that you start to teach his knowledge.”

*@ Old Devil nodded, „good. By his talent, one month of time should be similar.”

Tang Wulin has not relaxed vigilantly, freely the present all look like more and more likely real.

The obese old man shows a faint smile, „was good, making us from the beginning mention. This piece of Devil Islands, is more than 1000 years ago suddenly appear(ance). Its appear(ance) has the inevitability, there is a fortuitousness. Said accurately, even if to the present, actually we were not clear to have anything. Our of course is not the genuine devil, said accurately that we once were also Humanity.”

„Devil Island take shape, falls from space falling innumerable fragment(s) after the sea appear(ance). In this piece of Devil Islands, appear(ance) two clearly opposite energy, have believed that you have felt. One type, is incomparably rich Life strength, but another type, is actually as if can Ruin all Ruin energy. Also is you sees that Ruin Fragment(s) to bring.”

„Disillusioned Old Devil does not have lie, here, on each islands has Ruin Fragment(s) together, but the size is different, but by each Ruin Fragment(s), definitely will have rich Life energy. Because balance between their two, causes these Ruin energy to be insufficient to leak, brings the devastating disaster to Douluo Continent.”

„Observes and judges according to we many years of searching, had certain discovery. Estimated according to us that this rich Life and Ruin energy, does not come from Continent itself. Even does not come from our planet.”

Listens to him to speak of here, Tang Wulin could not bear open the mouth finally, „didn't come from our planet? Comes from outside world?” Along with the progress of science, Humanity had already discovered that Douluo Continent that at present they survive is also good, Star Luo Continent and Heaven Dou Continent, these on huge planet.

planet is named as Douluo Star, but through can discover to the observation of outside, in vast universe, some innumerable stars existence. More things, the scientific and technological standard was unable to investigate to be too many at present. But in technical most advanced Douluo Continent as three pieces of Continent, has been developing in the direction of exploration outer space.

The obese old man said: „Right, should come from outside world. Moreover, according to our judgments, they are likely related with us. You should know that had many and many years, Humanity world nobody again became Gods. Like Tang Sect ancestor Tang San, Spirit Transferring Pagoda founder Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao.”

Tang Wulin said: „Has Gods existence really?”

The obese old man [say / way] of without hesitation: „Has . The Tang San ancestor Becomes a God matter, has the detailed record in Continent many ancient books, at that time, Becomes a God also continues he, Shrek Seven Monsters another six people of also completely Becomes a God that he leads, inherited different Gods, flew upwards successively God Realm. Even the Tang San ancestor also once spread some related God Realm situations.”

„Knows according to us, God Realm also has rule existence. So-called God Realm, in fact is Life stage achieves the world that Elite in another standard lived. That world is governing our like this low stage world. But in God Realm, there is social class existence, most Top Rank Gods, was called Godking. God Realm committee that God Realm comprised of five Godking governs, is governing our these Lesser World destinies. But probably receives the rule to limit, they cannot intervene our these low stage potential surfaces to be too many.”

This view Tang Wulin or first time hear, although in his heart vigilant also, but also cannot help but is attracted by all that this obese old man narrated.

The obese old man continues saying: „After Tang San ancestor Becomes a God, obtained once of favors five big Godking, finally becomes the Godking successor. Inherited besides Sea God, Asura God Gods position, thus becomes one of the five big Godking. Five big Godking another four, should separately be God of Good, God of Evil, God of Life and God of Ruin.”

„Their five are governing God Realm, naturally is governing our Douluo Star rule. But, before counting Thousand Years, since Ice Spirit Douluo flies upwards, we again did not have Elite to feel God Realm existence. But in fact, along with Battle Armor appear(ance), the Humanity overall strength was initially more formidable. Present Limit Douluo adds on the Four Word Battle Armor words, was absolutely possible to inherit the Gods position, rises into God Realm. But God Realm does not have any to induce appear(ance) again. This makes us have to suspect that God Realm had problems.”

„This point you do not need to question that this is all previous Shrek Academy, Tang Sect and Spirit Transferring Pagoda high levels spreads. After Top Rank Elite of this Three Great organization achieves certain stage, will attempt to feel God Realm existence, but, actually again also nobody can induce to that world. Besides God Realm itself had problems, I cannot find out other answers.”

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, „that said that God Realm no longer existence?”

The obese old man shakes the head, „specific situation nobody is clear, nobody knows that God Realm had anything. However, we believe that God Realm had certainly problems.”

Tang Wulin said: „What relations that this and does Devil Island have?”

The obese old man said: „You should listen to me to say a moment ago, in God Realm five big Godking, two separately are God of Life and God of Ruin. Then, are you some mental association?”

In Tang Wulin heart one startled, „you said that Devil Island existence is related with two big Godking?”

The obese old man shows a faint smile, nearby *@ Old Devil said: „Really is this judgment. About before two Thousand Years, Life and Ruin energy drops from the clouds suddenly, Ruin energy was that fragment(s), take shape Devil Islands, but these Life energy actually throughout follow Ruin energy, but existence, was restraining it.”

„The Ruin antonym is Creation, but the Creation ultimate goal is Creation Life. This two are opposite, actually complements one another. After these two energy appear(ance), has had very tremendous influence to this sea area. Sea Soul Beast of potential prestige suddenly had the enormous development. Has posed not the small threat to the Continent coastal territory, starting from that time, had the North Sea Corps arrangement here. Also had afterward us to come here searching to observe.”

The obese old man shows a faint smile, „Nightmare that fellow of course is frightening your, in fact, do we possibly have to you any disadvantageously? Although here we truly are very lonely, but in the final analysis, we are common origin.”

„common origin?”

In the Tang Wulin heart moves.

The obese old man said: „Because, we were in the past that generation of Shrek Seven Monsters. Searches to observe Life and Ruin mystery, our Duty-bound Responsibility. Therefore, we arrived here. Here, we had a pitiful fortuitous encounter.”

---------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. Welcome everybody to use the hand and machine, gets down and carries, the day Tang animation, watches our own cartoon! Dragon King and Peerless Tang Sect, God Realm Legends and big carapace master, has it all.

#840: Once Shrek Seven Monsters

Listens he said Shrek Seven Monsters these five characters time, Tang Wulin only thought that the heart shook greatly, the situation of all formerly not being able to explain finally, can say was clear. Moreover, his in the heart has a feeling in this moment, this obese old man does not have lie, all that he said are real.

Here, the obese old man and *@ Old Devil were silent. Very obviously, recalls the matter that initially had, for them is a very painful experience.

*@ Old Devil sighed, „just arrived around this Devil Island time, we were extremely shocked. Here sea area had earth-shaking Transformation. We with the help of Federation, complete the debarkation through some hi-tech means. But at that time, Sea Soul Beast of this coastal water were many, moreover was quite formidable.”

„Federation before four Thousand Years on the promulgation law, must protect Soul Beast, as far as possible does not hunt and kill at will. Sea Soul Beast currently on Continent only has the Soul Beast system of complete existence. Therefore, we cannot slaughter at that time. After landing on the island, we start a series of reconnaissances. Thinks that you also felt at first, here simply did not have any Life aura existence, only then some specially fearful Ruin flavor. All vitalities as if were eliminated. We can also feel, long that too here, we cannot survive.”

„But reconnoiters must continue, we are searching for all on islands earnestly, is looking for the Life bodies and clues of all possible existence. Finally, we had found Ruin Fragment(s).”

„That time we, the strength was not quite weak, at least now this stage stronger compared with you on many. We had found valley, finally felt Life energy existence. At that time our first reaction was, we came across the fortuitous encounter. Thereupon, our seven people keep in valley, carries on the further reconnaissance.”

„But at that time, what is different from the present is. When we arrive in Devil Island, Devil Island Ruin aura outside, Life aura embodiment in valley. But that time Ruin Fragment(s), itself did not have the comprehensive eruption. Therefore, when we see Ruin Fragment(s), it is only gigantic crystalline lens, whether there is the interior as if performs the energy crystalline lens. Can you think at that time our feeling? We thought that has discovered the buried treasure. Moreover is very extraordinary thing.”

„We belong to Shrek, our of course hope returns to Shrek to study this buried treasure belt. Therefore, we attempt to take that Ruin Fragment(s). Therefore, the tragedy happened.”

On the face of obese old man has filled sadly, took up a chicken leg from the table, the worry of effort has been eating one.

The *@ Old Devil forced smile said: „We have initiated Ruin Fragment(s). Almost does not have any reaction time, our seven people, were all ripped fragment(s) by above terrifying Ruin energy, the skeleton have not saved.”

„?” Tang Wulin shouted one lowly.

The obese old man sighed: „At that time, we have not felt any pain, but thought that all become ignorant, surroundings all are suddenly fuzzy and are suddenly clear, suddenly light, suddenly darkness! All seems far away, actually likely is rapid nearness.”

The *@ Old Devil connection said: „Has not known long time, we finally gradually sobers. However, we eventually permanent lost was the body of own. We by the condition of spirit body, existence above islands. But here Life and Ruin energy , the part can be controlled by us.”

„Afterward, we carefully studied to discuss. We thought that this situation appear(ance), very possible was Life energy has saved us. Strength of Ruin Ruin our bodies, Life energy actually prompt protection our Soul. Therefore will have afterward our these Old Devil, by so strange shape existence. Was Life energy has continued our Life, making us be able to live on Thousand Years.”

„We have also been protecting here. The person who does not let the curiosity searches to observe. But this piece of Devil Islands, starting from that moment, belonged to Shrek. After all, this was we pays the Life price to obtain. We have not been able to leave here, once because leaves here Life energy, we will die. Soul will dissipate. Therefore we can only here, wait for Shrek Academy sends the most outstanding talented person, helping Academy carry on training to a certain extent.”

Such that just like the obese old man said that after he narrated complete process, Tang Wulin has believed him. All that because he said are completely reasonable, is flawless.

*@ Old Devil moved sitting there, „we lived was glorious than much years the average person, but, we again are actually not able to return to Shrek, is unable to see Sea God Island unfold on a magnificent scale again. It is not able to feel the Humanity world again point point Di Di. Only can stay here, makes Old Devil.”

The obese old man said: „Trains you truly is some wicked interests, will take to you not the small pain. But you recalled carefully will discover, actually this way (of life) can make you grow rapidly. Not only exercises your ability, exercises your mentalities. Only then after encountering intense setback, can know that Life is how precious, can more discrete going facing this world. You understand meaning that I said?”

Tang Wulin nodded slowly, Nightmare Old Devil in such method as the threat, Tang Wulin learned to open aircraft, absorb Ruin energy with own fusion, making in his aura have was Ruin that can in this sea area round trip free.

Devour Old Devil lets thing that he eats up, although is very disgusting, but without a doubt, has taken to his rich Life energy, neutralize Ruin energy the destruction that might bring. Make him feel Creation and Ruin process fully. Let his oneself be sublimated.

Loathing Old Devil exercises their firm and resolute with the pain, lets them the heart of stable own in the severe pain.

But *@ Old Devil takes to them, is the bustling place builds up the heart, making them realize profoundly * in must maintain sober.

Without a doubt, this all, because of the brutality of use method, can make them have the qualitative leap in short time. From the youth to youth, transits to can the degree of better adaptation society excessively.

Recalls that all these all sorts, to them are the rare exercises, outside world, is impossible to obtain in Academy.

The obese old man shows a faint smile, „you complete quickest one, therefore, then you can gentle with * studied something. After you learned, you stayed in the island, waited for your companion. When they all passed Test, during or is, had any person to give up, you were departing together. According to regulation(s), person who comes together, must walk together.”

Tang Wulin nodded.

Although he currently also has the vigilance, lets words that he is unable to say anything to respect, but in his heart, has believed all these.

The obese old man stands up, nodded to *@ Old Devil, turns around to walk in the direction of woods, his obese form disappears to disappear gradually.

„How should I call him?” Tang Wulin asked to *@ Old Devil.

*@ Old Devil shook the head, „how you did not need to call him, before departure, you should not see him again. Good, making us start. I can give your thing to be many, although the lots do not have what actual combat ability, but will actually have the enormous help to your actual combat, for example, cosmetics technique and Camouflage Technique.”

--------------------------------------

Today Company also began, has made many future plans, for example shoots our Tang Sect investment the network big movie, makes the Dragon King peripheral product, draws the Dragon King hypothesis collection wait / etc.. This year we will have 2-3 soap opera big movies starting. All are prosperous. Blessed everybody in the new year of work smooth, healthy.

#841: Study

*@ Old Devil starts to teach the Tang Wulin knowledge, just as such that obese old man said that all suffering as if passed. Normal guidance.

Tang Wulin is always not a stupid person, quick that he studies, moreover quick had found the pleasure. Just as such that *@ Old Devil said that she teaches to his thing, although does not have any fighting strength, but, has the enormous promotion to his survival. In the genuine significance creates the integrity talented people him.

Taught his, not only *@ Old Devil, quick, Loathing Old Devil, Disillusioned Old Devil, Nightmare Old Devil and Devour Old Devil also successively appear(ance) in front of Tang Wulin. Gives him complex knowledge guidances.

Tang Wulin heard a view from their mouth, before Ten-thousand Years, Shrek Academy has the plan, must train the versatile soldiers. Can adapt to various battlefields, has all -around ability versatile soldiers.

When earliest carries on this plan, has a successful case, that is the Spirit Transferring Pagoda founder, one generation of legends, Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao.

But now, Shrek Academy has not dropped this plan as before, but this plan has not been conducted in Academy, but here.

The person who only then can complete all subject inspections in one year, has the qualifications to study the curriculum of versatile soldiers. Without doubt, Tang Wulin is one of them, moreover he is near Thousand Years comes display best one.

During the front all inspections, built up some heart of course is very difficult, wants to maintain does not collapse is difficult. But more importantly, is most difficult, steals aircraft twice.

Especially the second time, must cross the Devil Island sea area to enter North Sea Corps to steal aircraft, the person who this can succeed was really too few. Came in two Hundred Year recently, only then three people are successful, but these three people, afterward became Sea God Pavilion Pavilion Master. And includes Present Generation Pavilion Master, Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming.

The studies of various rich knowledge, making Tang Wulin always enjoy. He starts to achieve mastery through a comprehensive study these knowledge. It looks like the thing that too has usually not paid attention, will study actually to discover really broadly and profoundly.

For example, Devour Old Devil to Tang Wulin careful narrated that mysterious location of various types of food, how food interior energy completely absorb, this and how the cooking have very important relations. How to distinguish the food, including Plant, animal, sea life form wait / etc.. Every day Tang Wulin was instilled into the massive knowledge.

Entire three months of time, Tang Wulin almost during study of watching. Also does not know how these five Old Devil achieve, can always put out the corresponding thing to provide to him carries on the study and cultivate.

„Was good, we should give you to give you, then, is the process that your own achieves mastery through a comprehensive study. When you return to Continent, but also need more things realize from experience. Only then in the society, you can better achieves mastery through a comprehensive study all these.”

„Thank You (xiexie) older generation(s).” These three months later, Tang Wulin sweeps away regarding five Old Devil malice finally.

Moreover, he now also accurate is grasping the companion situation, but also is good, arrived at Devil Islands to have ten months, although progress he of other people so is not quick, but at least so far, did not have a collapse.

They do not have the legal science entire all things, at least can also obtain here exercises enormously.

*@ Old Devil said: „Surplus time you stay in the island, should relax. Here has best food, a comfortable place lives to you. After your companion ended the inspection, you can leave.”

When Tang Wulin was brought to the local time of housing, his whole person was shocked. If with the comfort described the place that this living, Tang Wulin will think completely insufficiently.

This is a tree room, Tang Wulin does not know how the tree room is manufacture, but here Life energy be richer than valley. Sets up in the room various facilities to have it all, even also some things of modernization. A comfortable bed, but sits to have a drowsiness, wants to relax the feeling well.

Was suffered for six months, has studied for three months, Tang Wulin was really too exhausted. After delivering him to arrive *@ Old Devil that leaves, he almost goes right to sleep. This rests, is three days three nights.

Wakes from the sleep, Devour Old Devil has sent various types superior food that fills Life energy.

Is eating these things, Tang Wulin simply is affected must shed tears. Finally is after the bitter comes the sweet, lived through!

The scenery on Devil Island is not beautiful, but the tree room of Tang Wulin housing is actually a high spot, from here, can see outside, can see sea. The scenery is very beautiful.

Such comfortable feeling Tang Wulin for a long time has not experienced very much, after he eats to the full, falls on the bed once more, quick fell into the satisfactory sleep.

What ratio this happier matter also has? Has the excellent delicacy, has the comfortable environment, nobody forces cultivate again. Has the freedom. Only needs to wait for that companion came out to leave, all pressures were completely nothing left.

Tang Wulin leans in the sofa before tree front door, is looking into sea of distant place, the whole body is warm, relaxation and comfort that could not say. Insect warbler called is that interesting to listen.

„Not!” Stretched oneself, is stranded intent unconscious appear(ance). This is he arrives here the third day. Every day eats the thing to have a look at, satisfactory sleeping, what ratio this more comfortable matter but also there is?

Wipes the light smile also along with it appear(ance) on the Tang Wulin face, stands up, stretching oneself of effort, he turned around to return to the room.

Is headed by the obese old man, *@ Old Devil and Disillusioned Old Devil, Devour Old Devil, Nightmare Old Devil and Loathing Old Devil, six big Old Devil gather, sits in a cavern.

A picture before them, presented was just stretching oneself returns to Tang Wulin of room.

„Hey, this boy, crosses also is really easy and comfortable.” Obese old man somewhat self-satisfied saying.

*@ Old Devil curled the lip, „this has anything to be quite self-satisfied, together is we helps hello.”

„That is also my skill. However, this kid is really not good to deceive. Three months of study that many things, he is actually similar to the sponge generally can all digest absorb, this studies ability is really out of the ordinary. What a pity, regardless of his essence ghost, do not drink the water for foot-washing of old man?”

„Wait / Etc., should not be favorite first.” Disillusioned Old Devil suddenly surprised [say / way]: „This boy has not slept.”

The picture changes, arrived at the indoor, returns to indoor Tang Wulin, on the face is having several points of lazy smile, but he has not actually lain down on the bed, but sat on the bed, sits cross-legged to sit, both hands palm places on the knee of own upwardly, five hearts face upwards, started meditation unexpectedly, standard Mysterious Heaven Skill cultivate posture.

This......

Six Old Devil are all dumbfounded.

„Such comfortable life, eats that many to fill Life energy food every day, can this boy also think meditation unexpectedly? This is impossible. How comfortable day!” Being startled of obese old man face with puzzled.

*@ Old Devil laughs, „makes you favorite, gets what one deserves!”

Yes, Tang Wulin started meditation.

He is feeling in the air silently the rich Life strength, with the revolution of Mysterious Heaven Skill, enters the body of own these pure and abundant Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces absorb slowly.

The Mysterious Heaven Skill revolution has not sped up desirably, but is stimulating to movement naturally, making his own bloodline aura also follow Mysterious Heaven Skill to revolve slowly.

Tang Wulin is not irritable, silently is combing strength of Soul Power and bloodline of own within the body. Reason that so careful, was worried that did not pay attention, has broken through Golden Dragon King Ninth Layer Seal.

So long as cannot or be Control does not live completely, he will not go to assault Seal easily. Is absorb Golden Dragon King Essence, more is the strength promotes, in Tang Wulin heart vigilant is also intense.

Golden Dragon King Essence takes to him formidable strength at the same time, has taken to his other things, these somewhat said that does not scavenge unclear energy, influencing subtly is affecting him.

For example, earlier Tang Wulin, fight way (of life) is changeable, moreover every so often relies on the Wisdom win. But with the great strength of Golden Dragon King bloodline, he actually more and more likes that type coming now toward, suppression of pure strength. Moreover the emotional aspect similarly was also affected, became compares will be firmer before.

Arrived at Devil Island already almost one year of time, in this year, he received various inhuman suffering or is Test, in entire process, what actually the promotion was biggest was the mentality, was the effect on his spiritual level. This also lets him to feel the issue on own body clearly.

--------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket, recommended the ticket.

#842: Soul Power vortex

The formidable strength back, often follows the unpredictable crisis. Tang Wulin more and more started to realize now that Golden Dragon King bloodline might take to the reaction of own. It is no doubt formidable, but formidable strength must during the control of own, be best. Cannot make him lose control.

Therefore, Tang Wulin in the cultivate process, is in itself also unceasingly unifies through Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power and own bloodline now, is relying on Mysterious Heaven Skill pure grows continually to filter own bloodline energy, unceasing its purification.

The surface seems, does this to his cultivation is not big for the promotion, but in fact, is actually continuously is reducing him to have the possibility appear(ance) hidden danger. Moreover, in this process, Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power has further also been compressed. Do not visit him, only then Five Rings cultivates is, but in fact, in the situation of same rank, by the Soul Power compression degree and pure degree, Tang Wulin is second to none absolutely.

Like this time meditation, what he is more is must own learns in this year achieve mastery through a comprehensive study the thing and self- promotion that but does not promote Soul Power eagerly.

Initially, Mu Chen when taught that his forging, first taught him, establishes foundation, with steady steps promotion. Only then foundation is reliable, in the future can walk is farther.

Therefore, Tang Wulin meditation does not worry now, he promotes strength of Soul Power and bloodline slowly, while is feeling own body each slightest Transformation.

The human body has the infinite mystery, Martial Soul similarly so. Is feeling each Transformation on own body silently, making his feeling more and more clear. That insightful flavor, making him gradually enter a marvelous meditation condition.

„Ten minutes, but ten minutes did he enter depth meditation? This boy......” speechless of Nightmare Old Devil face, other five Old Devil are also dumbfounded.

„What to do?”

„What to do can also, we also be able to awaken inadequately from depth meditation him?”

„Should not like this, not should like this!” Obese old man breathless saying.

„Gets what one deserves!”

The spatial bright feeling does not know how long has continued, Tang Wulin Soul Power is revolving naturally, rhythm, when he restores to realize gradually, he discovered with amazement that in the own sensation, the body of own as if became transparent.

All in within the body present are light golden-colored, the circle melt pleasant, in Dantian, golden-colored and Soul Power of white perfect integration leads the strength of bloodline to circle the reciprocation, unexpectedly was take shape vortex.

This seems in not big vortex, Soul Power is rich, changes into the liquid completely, strength of perfect integration gentle Soul Power vortex and bloodline, that quiet revolving.

Tang Wulin felt own Soul Power obviously becomes formidable, what was more important, all energy of own within the body as if had a feeling of order. Under Life aura unceasing moistening, he feels the skeleton and internal organ(s) of own under premise that in tenacity originally increases steadily, unexpectedly were many a transparent sense of reality, insightful, just likes crystal is ordinary.

This is......

Although Tang Wulin does not understand that this is any realm, but he knows that the body of own enters certainly another stage.

In Soul Power vortex about Dantian, is actually clearer by his knowledge. Soul Power vortex should be Six Rings later appear(ance)!

Because, when Soul Master cultivate to Seven Rings, is an enormous bottleneck. In this bottleneck the most important point is the Soul Power qualitative change.

condense Soul Nucleus is the matter that Seven Rings Soul Saint must achieve, only then condense Soul Nucleus has been able cultivation to promote 70th Rank, then Soul Ring direct fusion with Soul Spirit or the Soul Beast is promoted, has seventh Soul Skill Martial Soul avatar, thus enters to brand-new Domain.

Only then above Seven Rings has repaired is, can be called High Rank Soul Master.

Without a doubt, Tang Wulin present range Seven Rings also falls far short, but, before Soul Power vortex is actually condense Soul Nucleus, matter that must handle.

Soul Power vortex can also be said as Soul Nucleus foundation. Relies on vortex appear(ance), Soul Master can absorb to many Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, through revolving of vortex, compresses own Soul Power unceasingly continually, till take shape solid state Soul Nucleus.

Tang Wulin Soul Power now at best is about 53rd Rank, has ten multistage disparities from Seven Rings. But normal, Soul Master starts to try take shape Soul Power vortex in 69th Rank, then waits for Soul Power vortex nature condense Soul Nucleus, completes qualitative to leap. When this process compared with other rank cultivate wants slow many. Why this also surpasses above Seven Rings to cultivate is Soul Master that few reasons.

Once Soul Nucleus take shape, Soul Master regarding the Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces sensation, the guidance, will have the huge leap. Thus makes own incomparably formidable. To that time, too has not needed to be worried that Soul Power will consume completely, Soul Nucleus oneself can tow the Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces prompt supplement. So long as is not fight of oversized consumption, generally speaking, Soul Saint Soul Power grows continually.

Tang Wulin 53rd Rank, Soul Power vortex already take shape, this, not only means that his Soul Power compression degree far supernormal person, what is more important is regarding the understanding of own Soul Power is also so.

Soul Power vortex take shape biggest advantage Tang Wulin felt immediately, was relying on the vortex force of traction, he can better Control live in own within the body the strength of bloodline, was insufficient by them not by Control broke through Ninth Layer Seal.

This is really the accident happy! Tang Wulin can feel obviously own Soul Power has promoted 1st Rank, from 52nd Rank to 53rd Rank. Although one year of time promoted two-level Soul Power to be not many, but this promotion was actually extremely stable. Let alone, he also has learned that many things in this year.

meditation can finish, has not known long time.

While Tang Wulin prepared to finish own meditation time, suddenly, his body trembled slightly, a marvelous feeling arose spontaneously.

That feeling looked like in his body were many a seed, but seed germination, finally started to bloom the feeling of its Life aura.

This feeling was really too marvelous, Tang Wulin only thought that own was surrounded by unequalled Life energy instantaneously, surroundings Life energy rich to instantaneously his body completely Devour.

This is......

„Buzz”

Heads lift unceasingly, look to some direction. On the Old Devil face revealed the shock inexplicable color.

„What situation?”

They noticed that is the bluish-green light beam shoots up to the sky in the islands together suddenly, in the islands enough strong Life aura, increased suddenly by the geometrical multiple violent.

This situation for them is also extremely rare, time, numerous position Old Devil are startled.

„Life Tide? Previous Life Tide is not 20 years ago just appear(ance)? How to come?”

Life Tide, each Hundred Year on Devil Island meets appear(ance) one time. Whenever Life Tide appear(ance) time, is on Devil Island the strength of suppressed weakest time Ruin, is the Life energy richest time. Whenever at this time, near Devil Islands, will gather huge quantity of Sea Soul Beast, makes own evolve through absorb these Life energy.

Therefore, reason that some that many formidable Sea Soul Beast near Devil Islands, have isolated here, to rather is protecting here.

This Life Tide must be bigger than Humanity regarding the Soul Beast advantage, it can guide the benign qualitative change on Soul Beast appear(ance) bloodline directly, said accurately can Sea Soul Beast bloodline purification.

But, with previous time is separated by for 20 years, unexpectedly appear(ance) Life Tide, this completely is not the normal situation.

Light and Shadow flash through, numerous position Old Devil gathered at one quickly.

---------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#843: Life Tide

Besides six originally, but also were many Old Devil. This appearance seems somewhat funny, the small eye and big nose, the big mouth branch, the chin is particularly long, some body rickets. But when his appear(ance), other six Old Devil actually very natural standing in his below first place.

„Life Tide how suddenly appear(ance), Boss?” Disillusioned Old Devil asked to new appear(ance) the old man anxiously.

The old man shook the head, brow tight wrinkle, „I do not know that is any situation, I in suppression Ruin energy, Ruin energy had weakened suddenly, then Life Tide along with it appear(ance). Was different from the past feeling. Normally, Life Tide will have the feeling in the appear(ance) beforehand ten years, it will promote gradually, until blowouts finally. But this time Life Tide does not have any sign. Goes to put that several kids, making them receive the Life Tide baptism, their luck are really good. Can catch up with Life Tide, this is the big chance.”

„I go!” Nightmare Old Devil hurries to say.

„Wait / Etc., Life Tide direction.” The obese old man said suddenly.

„Is his there?” Disillusioned Old Devil also immediately realizes.

„What situation?” Is the first old man sinking sound asks.

*@ Old Devil said: „Is that Tang Wulin, after he since enters depth meditation, had three months. Life Tide energy not likely from the Ruin Fragment(s) surroundings eruption, but starts from his meditation place, is quite strange.”

„Isn't Life Tide that his depth meditation initiates? How is this possible?” A Loathing Old Devil face does not dare to believe.

Numerous position Old Devil look at each other in blank diamay, mind big quake.

Since they come here, had Thousand Years time, they also self-examined have basically found out all sorts of situations and rules on entire Devil Island. But each time when situation that appear(ance) does not conform to the rule, means that they the understanding Devil Island will be more profound.

Although they by energy shape existence, but as here protector, can understand that here all of course are most important.

„In the past had a look!” Is the first old man big hand wields, on seven Old Devil simultaneously ray of light dodges, the next quarter, all vanished.

Tang Wulin does not know that the outside had anything, he felt that own body surroundings Life energy is getting more and more rich, looks like a big cocoon equally his gable.

That feeling is marvelous, was unable to breathe obviously, but he thinks the body unprecedented comfort.

What his own cannot see, in his body surface, ring of light has shone slowly. It is not Blue Silver Emperor Soul Ring, is not golden-colored ring of light that Golden Dragon King bloodline brings, but is that green-gold ring of light.

green-gold ring of light is sparkling strange halo, initially when he just had this green-gold ring of light, regardless of he will pour into many Soul Power by clean of Devour, will be with the help of Sky Raising Douluo, once inspiring of short time.

To Soul Skill that this ring of light brings, Tang Wulin gives the name that it gives to be called: Child of Nature.

At this moment, this Fifth Soul Ring halo was more radiant than any time in the past, the rich Life strength and surroundings that Life Tide energy its oneself sent out complemented one another, complements each other fresh splendor.

Devil Island in the Life Tide process starts slight(ly) is trembling, the distant place, in sea, various Sea Soul Beast come in swarms, subconscious is circling the reciprocation regarding Devil Island. More and more Sea Soul Beast catch up, joins to this team, feels the rich Life strength to take to the own advantage.

The consciousness of Tang Wulin immerses in Life aura gradually, he discovered with amazement, illusory picture appear(ance) in his mind deep place.

He saw nine color variegated photospheres, that photosphere glittering the marvelous brilliance, halo is and out, each ray of light glittering, gives the feeling that the human a mind sublimates.

Then, that photosphere increases suddenly gradually, becomes more and more greatly, was bigger than before the several fold. Indistinct , the photosphere became transparent, has thinned like its semblance.

Tang Wulin can see that in photosphere that increases, really has the fog to be faintly recognizable, has Mountains and Rivers Rivers Flow. Extremely strange.

But also at this moment, powerful ash-gray air current came from the distant place, that air current is extremely huge, blots out the sky, covers in which all within his field of vision range completely, naturally also includes that photosphere.

ray of light on photosphere starts rapidly glittering, each glittering, photosphere's energy fierce shivering, slight cracks will start appear(ance), as if under sweeping across of that air current, the photosphere wanted to shatter.

But also at this time, photosphere surface suddenly appear(ance) marvelous Transformation, two groups of Light and Shadow appear(ance). One group is green, one group is purple. Two groups of Light and Shadow fuse in together, take shape piece of marvelous halo, halo is white, it the entire nine color photosphere all gables, the fissure will have closed, nine color photospheres reduce, internal all gradually do not look clearly, but it does not have to shatter eventually.

But terrifying the huge ash-gray air current sweeps across, leads unceasing trembling of that nine color photospheres in shivering, then integrates in that ash-gray air current to be curled the launching to be far.

Why does not know, sees here, sadness inexplicable raises in the Tang Wulin moral nature deep place, at this moment, he only wants to cry out loud that holds that photosphere.

But also at this moment, three ray of light suddenly enlarge in his field of vision, two ray of light separately are purple and green, but with formerly protected the photosphere compared with that purple and green, these two ray of light want weak many. They in the line of sight of Tang Wulin gradually become in each other collision clear.

That unexpectedly is two forms, but they seem are such illusory, can see indistinctly, the purple form seems a man, but the green form is a female, they always attempt to hold each other, actually cannot achieve.

Finally, during another collision, the purple form broke up, changes into innumerable purple fragment(s) in broken bits to scatter in all directions to flutter about, but that green form as if exudes one to call out in grief, her oneself also breaks up, selects point green ray of light to fly to shoot, had found these purple fragment(s), changes into just likes Vine general green energy Bind comes up, grazes.

Third ray of light also at this moment becomes clear, that is one group of golden-colored ray of light, when Tang Wulin sees it, only thought that the own heartbeat suddenly becomes fierce, intense sad and desolate also along with it floating heart.

That [gold/metal] enlarges before him suddenly, the next quarter, all pictures completely vanished.

The body of Tang Wulin is shivering, mind is shivering, for a very long time is unable to restrain oneself.

Has not known long time, he gradually returned to normal, Life and Ruin, this is Life and Ruin flavor.

That purple as if represents Ruin, green is representing Life, what that golden-colored is ray of light representing?

Ruin and Creation are protecting together what is the photosphere?

Although probably was only very short time, may regarding Tang Wulin, passed a century to be so remote likely.

He can feel obviously in own mind were many anything, but his own also cannot hold. Actually could not clarify to have anything.

Grows the tone, opens eyes slowly. Tang Wulin then surprised seeing, green and purple halo regarding in own body surroundings, is diverging slowly.

His body all normal, felt that during does not have what different place. But in his mind has a marvelous feeling indistinctly. In regards with rapt attention, he discovered with amazement that in own that take shape soon Soul Power vortex center, were just many something.

That is two small luminous spots, one is green, one is purple, they revolve mutually, slow revolving.

Tang Wulin wants to attempt to feel their existence, when his consciousness enters to that green and purple luminous spot surroundings, spiritual appear(ance) short absent-minded, will then unable to see clearly all instantaneously.

Little leans, after the sensation restores, sees as before is that two luminous spots.

This is......

Life and do Ruin bring? But, why can they appear(ance) in the own body? own within the body has Golden Dragon King bloodline, has Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power, but also insufficiently lively?

Most critically, Tang Wulin cannot affirm completely that are actually many these energy in the own body is good is bad.

Somewhat speechless, Tang Wulin shaking the head of gently, then once more opening eyes pupil.

„, You......” this time actually frightened her to jump, because seven eyes been dumbfounded regarding in his surroundings, careful was looking steadily at him.

Besides he has seen six Old Devil, but also were many, this happen to stands in his dead ahead.

„Life Tide, Ruin Tide unexpectedly simultaneously appear(ance), moreover was inspired by you, said quickly that actually you have done what?” The old men asked anxiously.

#844: In the heart has the love

[Say / Way] that Tang Wulin is confused: „My anything has not done! I am only meditation, I do not know what's the matter.” He truly does not know that what's the matter, these that even if the sensation arrived at a moment ago, he does not plan to say.

„Said the process.” Disillusioned Old Devil said.

The Tang Wulin corners of the mouth place reappears to sneer, „you let go by me and my companion, I considered that told you.”

Numerous position Old Devil have all gawked, the obese old man gets angry: „Brat, you are muddled. Knows that respects the elder!”

Tang Wulin he he smiles, „respects the elder? If I have not guessed that wrong, you should be Lazy Old Devil.”

Such remarks, numerous position Old Devil are one startled, looks that the Tang Wulin look also had some Transformation.

Lazy Old Devil inconceivable [say / way]: „How do you know?”

The Tang Wulin show face smiles, „guesses that now looks like, what I guess is right!”

Tang Wulin said: „Receives these many days gradually influencing, how can not select to progress? Let me help your analysis one. Since I passed through front suffering, particularly after suffering of *@ Old Devil, should be passed the quite difficult time. Before you had said to me, initially, you were also Shrek Seven Monsters, regarding this point, I entirely does not believe that but at least the digit, I was note, Seven Monsters, of course was seven people. Five people turned into Old Devil, that another two do not have possibly is the exceptions.”

Looks steadily at that obese old man, Tang Wulin is continue say: „Suffers our is five Old Devil, but you are sixth appear(ance), without doubt, you are also Old Devil, you also agree did not say the own title are anything, my of course will suspect. But flawlessness that your stories spoke, according to my judgment, the entire story should real, you truly in Test we , were training us. Afterward several months, has verified my guess, you started to teach that my knowledge, I have truly learned many good things. However, throughout has not actually relaxed in my heart vigilantly.”

„Front five Old Devil are filling wicked interest Test we, sixth will Old Devil let off us? But even if before my meditation I have not been able to determine all these, after all, that several months of time, you were good to me too, I disappeared to your hostility basically. Until just, after me opened eyes, those who saw was seven people, seven Old Devil, without a doubt, my guess was then correct, you truly were seven people. Such being the case, then, before this Lazy Old Devil you, all that makes have another explanation.”

„That is, you are lulling me. Teaches my knowledge real, story that you told also real, the only issue was your status. You are Lazy Old Devil, all that you made before to let me relax vigilantly, until finally, me has completed study, moreover exhausted of long time, when vigilant relaxes completely, I will naturally put down all vigilance. Then you give me are the most comfortable living conditions, best food, waits for companion this reason. But this all, must guide me to get down all lazily. Perhaps, you must have a look, whether I in this case can also maintain Crystallized Body, whether can also insist cultivate. I said right? Lazy Old Devil older generation(s).”

Is listening to Tang Wulin a series of analysis, numerous position Old Devil complexion somewhat is strange, of course, Lazy Old Devil complexion is actually ugliest.

„Is impossible. At that time I distinct felt your spiritual relaxed thoroughly, the whole person is also so. After one year of suffering and study , the strong person did not have the means at that time maintained calm.” Lazy Old Devil breathless saying.

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, „you said right, I truly completely relaxed at that time. Because does not relax, I fear on spiritual also to unable to withstand. However, I did not worry that own thorough relaxation even lazily will get down. Because, in my heart, has had the same thing to affect me, making me not dare to idle.”

Lazy Old Devil stares, „what is?”

Tang Wulin looks to *@ Old Devil, „*@ older generation(s) should know that in my heart has the love! For my Lover, I must become formidable, must protect her ability. Therefore, I can rest, but rests for well cultivate. Therefore, I started meditation. Now looks like, my guess * does not leave ten. Since many thanks older generation(s) recently training. Does not know that finally this Old Devil older generation(s), actually does want how Test I?”

His vision falls on dead ahead has not seen Old Devil, on the face is having the light smile.

The old men have smiled, gently pats both hands of own to applaud for him, „is very good. Academy has not really elected the wrong person. The current situation makes the hero, will soon face the dangerous in Continent the time, our Shrek really left the Sir talent. I am very gratified. Old man greed(y). You can call me Greedy Old Devil.”

Greedy Old Devil! Really is seven, seven Old Devil. Moreover with similar of Tang Wulin guess, these seven Old Devil many are related with seven Original Sins.

„What do you also need Test my?” Tang Wulin asked.

Greedy Old Devil shows a faint smile, „has not needed. You passed. Good mentality and vigilance, intelligent brains. The following all did not have the significance to you. Your Devil Island taught to finish especially. Congratulates you, your result is among the best. At least is five Hundred Year comes, most outstanding.”

Before Tang Wulin has not gone to ask five Hundred Year, who is more outstanding than own this issue, his whole person also relaxed.

Greedy Old Devil stern [say / way]: „But, before we need you to tell us, on you had what kind of Transformation, simultaneously will have inspired unexpectedly Life Tide and Ruin Tide. Just started is only Life Tide time we also surprised, but when Ruin Tide also appear(ance), was not surprised so is simple. This Transformation will possibly affect the Devil Islands complete islands. Therefore, we need to know the truth of matter.”

Tang Wulin sighed, „was sorry older generation(s), because received you good ’ so ‚ training, let me the first point of society is, do not believe others easily. Therefore, I am unable to judge the outcome that you say now am the truth or the lie. Therefore, I cannot say.”

Greedy Old Devil speechless, audiences Old Devil is also same, they have to plant to lift the stone to pound own the feeling of foot.

Disillusioned Old Devil said: „How do you want agree to tell us?”

Tang Wulin said: That moment that „I and companion leave safely. Said honestly, until now, I do not know own in the reality in the dream. Because, the experience here has too meddlesomely is not real.”

Nightmare Old Devil has selected the eyebrow, „good, you can judge. Then, good, lets your dream, first wakes.”

At the same time was saying, he waves to Tang Wulin. Immediately, a dizziness feeling along with it appear(ance). Tang Wulin only thought that surroundings scenery fast Transformation, the house vanished, the comfortable environment vanished. When the dizziness restores to come, he discovered that own is conscientious, the location place, initially just went to valley that place. But in not far away, he saw his companion.

Ye Xinglan, Yuan En Yehui, Xu Lizhi, Le Zhengyu, Xu Xiaoyan and Xie Xie six people, unexpectedly in not far away, moreover in handling different matters, some of them able to move unhindered jump, some sit cross-legged to sit, on the face the expression varies with.

„Do they immerse in illusion?” Tang Wulin surprised asking.

Nightmare Old Devil said: „real-like and false-like, what is real, what is imaginary?”

#845: Should leave

Tang Wulin hurries to regard with rapt attention, he discovered immediately, Soul Power vortex of own within the body also, that green and purple luminous spot also. Thing that these learn, profound brand mark in his mind.

This illusion was really too fearful, own really might live more than one year of time in the mirage.

„The time speed of flow in illusion, only then one-fourth of outside, therefore you just come here three months of time.” Greedy Old Devil said.

„Your companion have not completed complete Test, they also need some time. I must tell you am, before completing completely Test, words that ahead of time ended, for them is not the good deed. They need the complete process, needs to reconstruct at heart, for example that boy.” Nightmare Old Devil has referred to Le Zhengyu.

Tang Wulin recalls to mind the Le Zhengyu pitiful bitter experience immediately, has a look at surroundings seven Old Devil, in this time heart was believes.

„Good, I told you. First, I do not know Life Tide and Ruin Tide that really you said how were inspired. I am only when finished meditation, suddenly felt that body surroundings Life energy becomes intense. Then starts to see a strange picture.”

At that moment, Tang Wulin in all said that in mirage saw own in detail, in this period, but has concealed finally appear(ance) that two luminous spots in own Soul Power vortex.

In his heart also has vigilance as before, of course cannot all say. But similarly, said these that own saw, he also hopes that can listen to Old Devil analysis, they most understood that on Devil Island Life and Ruin energy person, their analysis without doubt were also most reasonable.

Listened to narration of Tang Wulin, seven Old Devil frowning of as if by prior agreement, as if are with hardship are thinking.

„Without a doubt, purple should be Ruin, what green is Life. Even if also you see in illusion likely is the projection of Goddess of Life and God of Ruin, but makes the place that they can protect have one, that is God Realm. Perhaps, these that you see, why we cannot induce the God Realm reason. This was really too important. I will record in detail, after you who you narrate go back, delivers to Sea God Pavilion, making Sea God Pavilion Master scrutinize.” Greedy Old Devil stern said.

„Good.” Tang Wulin nodded immediately.

Greedy Old Devil said: „Does not know why you will inspire these, did you have other feeling at that time? What is that golden-colored luminous spot?”

Tang Wulin said: „I do not know, when I see that golden-colored luminous spot, thought that the mood fluctuation of own is very big, seems very moved, as if has met feeling of any painful event. A little when looks like initially my Parents suddenly left the feeling.”

Greedy Old Devil nods the head slightly, „this has felt strange, but also very difficult analysis. Like this, you continue here meditation, has a look also to enter that condition once more, feels illusion, here waits for your companion. However, Nightmare illusion, so long as came out you unable to go back, you here waited.”

„Good.” Tang Wulin complies immediately, then he looked to Devour Old Devil, „our these delicious, real? Also?”

„, Has not had. Your boy ate me poorly. Do you know how many good things you have eaten? Here Life energy is so rich, does not need to eat. Your own cultivate goes.” A Devour Old Devil face said angrily that the personal appearance dodged vanishes.

Tang Wulin turns head and looks to Lazy Old Devil, until at this moment, Lazy Old Devil complexion is very ugly, effort wields the sleeves, turns around to vanish.

*@ Old Devil he he smiles, „lazy this attack of fellow receiving may not be really small, your companion are really pitiful. Certainly will be vented the anger by him. greed(y), didn't you plan Test really he? You are in us are fiercest.”

Greedy Old Devil shakes the head, „does not need, only if can erased his part remember, otherwise, will not have any effect. This boy should not be hoodwinked both eyes by greed(y).”

In the Tang Wulin heart the secret unstated criticism, own most likes, but is greed(y)! Likes money since childhood.

Numerous position Old Devil depart in abundance, only remaining Tang Wulin own, companion are still handling the different matters in surroundings. Can see their is well, Tang Wulin also calculates to feel relieved that besides continuing meditation, he cannot find out own also to make anything. Meanwhile, he also wants to feel well, actually that purple and green luminous spot has anything to affect in the own body.

However, is contrary to what expects. This time, he cannot enter depth meditation again, attempt time and time again, cannot feel the function of that two luminous spot.

Soul Power normal cultivate, Soul Power vortex normal revolving, but that green and purple two luminous spots look like with Tang Wulin do not have relations completely, any energy of his within the body has no way to affect that two luminous spots existence.

One month in reality, in Nightmare Old Devil illusion four months of time quick on the past. Other Shrek Seven Monsters six people one by one had eventually concluded their travel of Nightmare.

By Nightmare Old Devil what second was finished illusion is Ye Xinglan, is Yuan En Yehui, Xu Lizhi, Xie Xie and Xu Xiaoyan.

Le Zhengyu is last.

When companion listened to Tang Wulin to narrate when Le Zhengyu bitter experience, Xu Xiaoyan has blushed enough two days, other people actually could not smile. They are afraid. These Old Devil, were really too fearful. They regarding humane Test, arrived at Peak.

Looks at companion, Tang Wulin also has the strange feeling, although here is only four months of time, even if in illusion is just also less than two years, but after passing through these, everybody has grown probably all up. Without a doubt, this is a they life-long unforgettable journey.

Le Zhengyu sobered finally seven days later.

When his body slight(ly) trembles, then the look becomes after the Pure Brightness, first sees is Xu Xiaoyan.

The corners of the mouth shivered, Le Zhengyu took a seat to fall down, „Xiaoyan, I was unfair to you.” The tears almost flowed instantaneously.

The people are the expression are strange, Xu Xiaoyan hurries an arrow step to rush, grasps him, gently is patting his back, „passed, all passed. Your anything has not made the mistake, anything does not have.”

Entire a half hour passes by, Le Zhengyu is gradually restores. Mentioned *@ Old Devil, he hated to clench jaws.

„You should leave.” Light and Shadow dodges, seven Old Devil simultaneously appear(ance) before people. Their expression is various, dissimilar in shape and form. Sees seven people, besides Tang Wulin, another six people reveals a fear all.

Yes! Really was too fearful, here they received too many suffering.

Greedy Old Devil shows a faint smile, „believes that you have remembered here feeling all. Congratulates you, your seven complete graduated normally. You all insisted finally. This is not very easy. As new generation Shrek Seven Monsters, you are qualified. Now, you are going to carry on is last Test. Nobody will deliver you to leave, you need to depend upon own strength. I must remind your am, the following all no longer are illusion, you need own to go facing North Sea Corps. aircraft that of course, you stole before is in illusion has presented. But the process not completely is also false, at least a little I can affirm told you, you in illusion has seen these North Sea Corps military officers, was hates to the marrow of the bones to you absolutely. Good, you momentarily can leave.”

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#846: Shen Xing Nightmare

Le Zhengyu, Xu Lizhi, Xie Xie, Yuan En Yehui, Ye Xinglan and Xu Xiaoyan, six people all relaxed. Finally can leave? Entire two years! Here, they were really sufficed.

Tang Wulin looks at numerous position Old Devil, why does not know, from their look, he saw desolate.

„older generation(s), can you only continuously on Devil Island? Doesn't have what means to make you leave here really? What demand you have, can I help you?”

Greedy Old Devil shook the head, Disillusioned Old Devil he he smiles, „good intention declined with thanks. We are just the energy shapes, once leaves here, without Ruin and protection of Life energy, we will be frightened out of one's wits immediately. Although after arriving here, we that lonely. However, here all also made us have long Life. gains and losses. If, you want, can come back to have a look at us actually. of course, wants to realize a next beforehand experience again, not impossible.”

„Captain, we walk quickly!” Le Zhengyu draws Tang Wulin.

The Tang Wulin corners of the mouth have twitched, then suddenly shouted to clear the way: „Shrek Seven Monsters, stands at attention.”

Other six people have stood with him immediately the body. Tang Wulin serious [say / way]: „Bows!”

......

„!” Shen Xing fierce sat from the bed, big mouth and big mouth is panting for breath.

This does not know that was she many time awakens from Nightmare for the recent several months.

Dreamland that real, she goes to the routine inspection Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell warehouse, has actually encountered the completely unexpected paroxysmal incident. That fellow, that so clear face, he has held under duress her, has threatened Elder Sister. Was bringing on own Sky Flyer 17, finally that bastard unexpectedly directly the own ejection.

The conclusion of Nightmare was the upper air fierce weightlessness feeling, Shen Xing still clearly remembers each time that first own awakened from Nightmare, unexpectedly disgraced incontinence. This is too really unacceptable.

That fellow is genuine existence, he once was grasped in the regiment with his companion, afterward also truly kidnapped aircraft to run away. But, these and own not any relations! own has not had any occurring together with him, why does evil Nightmare is actually own.

What is more strange, Elder Sister also has made similar Nightmare. Tallies with the own dreamland.

Damn and damn! Get lost from my dreamland quickly!

The thump that Shen Xing makes an effort has struck two mattresses, really somewhat could not fall asleep.

Stands up from failure to sit up, puts on the military uniform, before arriving at the mirror, has illuminated the photo. Because the sleep is unsatisfactory, recently she has been hanging the dark pouche. The daytime training has sufficed laboriously, comes back to go right to sleep, this is always her life became a habit. But she wants to sleep now difficultly actually that. Has to be used for meditation many time.

Shen Xing decided to exit to ventilate, ventilates later comes back meditation to be good, at least meditation will not have a dream.

That hateful fellow went to Devil Island, he best not to come back, otherwise, for own Nightmare, must teach him well!

Goes out of Dormitory, Shen Xing flaneries in the base is walking. Although she rank is not high, but is grasping very important supervision duty, the place visited, the soldier of patrol sees her, salutes all immediately.

North Sea Corps adjoins to sea, the sea breeze makes night to become cool. Catches a chill, in Shen Xing heart worried weakened several points.

„Well, how I arrived here to come.” She discovered with amazement that own has arrived at the warehouse in dreamland unexpectedly.

Is storing up Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell that place.

Shen Xing wrinkled frown, „really damn.” She turned around just to walk, actually stopped the footsteps.

Might as well have a look, perhaps, has a look to the place of dreamland, own can also alleviate some. Otherwise, always somewhat could not distinguish clearly is dreamland is the real feeling is really too painful.

Thinks of here, she entered the warehouse without consulting anybody. Is relying on high-grade Identification Card, she rides the elevator to arrive quickly underground.

The soldiers who guards see her, salutes in abundance. Gazes after her to arrive at the warehouse respectfully.

„Did Staff Officer Shen, such late also investigate?” The major who is responsible for the storage management smiles was saying.

Although Shen Xing is very beautiful, but he does not dare to have any improper ambition, but this own Younger Sister of armed forces regimental commander, the status is extremely high. Is gold-plated in the regiment, it is said that will be recalled that side the military headquarters to redistribute quickly.

„Um, has a look.” Nod of Shen Xing not false speech and countenance.

„Good, come, opens the door.”

Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell this and other important warehouses need three keys and special passwords can open large door. Two have the captain of key to be called by the major, in addition the special password, after as well as scanned the retina of Shen Xing. Warehouse large door slowly opens.

Is depositing these many Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell warehouses, itself has air/Qi of invisible withering. Although here not that genuine Super Rank strategic Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. But the value is also huge. Is one of the North Sea Corps most important several warehouses.

Enters the warehouse, the familiar feeling in dreamland arises spontaneously. Because can the dream come here daily, Shen Xing to here familiar feeling also naturally specially will be intense.

Walks in the warehouse, Shen Xing somewhat absent-minded looks at surroundings artillery shell. Suddenly, she stopped the footsteps subconsciously, „here should have four 5th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. How not to have. Leaves the storehouse record to show me.”

She stops the place of footsteps, is just a rack, above artillery shell piles up neatly. But in the Shen Xing memory, here should have four Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell is right. Because she remembers very clearly, in the dreamland, after that bastard held under duress own, once brought own to hide the moment here, therefore she remembered specially clearly.

However, after asking these words, she regrets immediately. That after is the dreamland! own actually in the reality inquired that the matter of dreamland, this may really be......

However, the side has not replied sound to transmit, Shen Xing subconscious turning around looked that is responsible for the major in warehouse to that saw that is actually the shock in his eyes flashing past.

She knows that here does have four 5th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell? This is impossible! Her previous time came to here is the several months ago matters.

Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell according to the category and rank, has strict storage stipulation, cannot change the position casually, only if takes away the service.

„I asked you.” Shen Xing is intelligent, has realized immediately the issue, closely examines rapidly, sounds/voices also becomes severe.

That major hurries to compensate to say with a smile: „artillery shell was taken away to serve, leaves the storehouse to record you to want wait a moment, I must move to take am good.”

Shen Xing said: „Immediately, gives me immediately.”

The major hurries to nod again and again, „you wait a bit, my this goes.” At the same time was saying, he has turned around, under signaled with the eyes to that two captains.

Three people of half steps walk together outward.

„How also to go, making a person go on the line.” Shen Xing shouted to clear the way.

„Good.” The major stops the footsteps, when he has turned around, suddenly, ray of light dodges. Shen Xing only thought that the whole body trembles, the intense feeling lacking in vigilance spreads over whole body each corner instantaneously, her body slowly is also soft but actually.

She stared in a big way eye subconsciously, cannot believe that this was real.

Person who can take the Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell warehouse manager, that must pass through the strict political investigation absolutely, what without a doubt is, at present this having problems, not only he, under his two famous artisans is also so.

complexion of major becomes somewhat fierce, arrives in front of Shen Xing quickly, one has gotten down her front communications device on entraining. Because makes an effort , both were entraining uppermost the Shen Xing military uniform two buttons.

The button falls to the ground, reveals the Shen Xing front to wipe snow white, but this time whole body is lacking in vigilance, called unable to call continually.

The breath of warehouse manager somewhat is obviously rapid, „why, why you can remember that clearly. Even if I, is impossible to remember on each rack have many artillery shell.”

Shen Xing has no way to speak, can only gaze at fixedly him with the severe look.

A warehouse manager face dejected [say / way]: „I do not want, I to know like this resells Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell is the how serious crime. But, I have no alternative but such to do, my family member had been seized by them, my son also in their hands. I do not have the means that I do not have the means. I must walk. Staff Officer Shen, is strange, blames your own. Who makes you mind others'business. I will take away you together, you are own Younger Sister of general, believes that for them will be certainly valuable, this should be able to take to me more advantage. You hold Staff Officer Shen, we must walk immediately, in the evening, informs our fleeing passageway luckily quickly, making them prepare, our leaves.”

------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#847: Also is he

The warehouse manager should restore at this time calmly, he draws from the ground Shen Xing.

At this moment, suddenly, warehouse manager staggered, he only thought that had any thing to go against own in the own under foot. Immediately brings Shen Xing to stagger one side.

Then he and two captains on dumbfounded seeing, in the warehouse ground, the metal(s) square brick raise together unexpectedly slowly, then drills a person from below.

First what appear(ance) is his a pair of arm, shining, above is covering diamond-shaped scales. The weighty metal(s) brick imitates in his hands, if unmistakable, relaxed was shoved open one side, the personal appearance dodges, he jumped.

If normally, warehouse is in charge of first time to start the warning, may at this moment, he just be discovered the secret by Shen Xing, where dares to draw the warning!

„What person?” The warehouse manager drinks lowly at the same time, in the hand lulled rays to shoot toward that golden figure.

Lulls the rays accurate hit, what hit is that person of cross piece gets up the arm that. Under lulling the stimulation of rays, golden-colored scales sends out light halo. That person has flung starting, muttered the tunnel: „A little Ma Susu!”

A terrifying pressure beyond description bursts out from that person, the warehouse manager only thought own faces is not a person, but is terrifying Ferocious Beast is ordinary. Own bloodline as if wanted condense.

Forms leap up from the ground cave entrance, at present one black, the next quarter, warehouse manager anything does not know.

Tang Wulin somewhat surprised looks to lie down in ground Shen Xing.

Although passed was very long, time in illusion is long, but he was one has recognized this once by own in illusion has kidnapped the staff officer.

This is really life where has not met by chance! Has not thought that just left Devil Island, with familiar way (of life) infiltrating here, once more has run into him.

Leaves Devil Island time, Tang Wulin and companion discussed that thought that this directly way (of life) that from underground digs is best. After all, this is most not easily discovered way (of life), so long as entered North Sea Corps, wants to leave on easy many, moreover synthesized the people repeatedly infiltrating North Sea Corps experience in Nightmare, they can judge probably, this warehouse is near from the inland direction, they only need a shorter distance to flee the North Sea Corps control range.

In fact, they have another superiority, that is, did not fear that was grasped.

Had finished Devil Island cultivate, they have not needed to be worried to delay time completely here. Initially they truly had driven away Sky Flyer from here 17, but also only then that was real, surplus all was Nightmare Old Devil simulates with the dreamland. This crime is not small, but by their Shrek Seven Monsters status, the military will inevitably not be what kind of them, at the worst informs the student.

Therefore, in fact they can definitely directly after leaving sea are held directly, however posts-edit on a reasonable point story, can get out of trouble similarly, time that just delays meets relatively long.

What a pity, is not willing to return to Academy by their character obviously like this dirtily, in that case, in Devil Island these many days wasn't suffering Bai Shou? Has studied that many things, must study for the purpose of application is good.

Has not actually thought that a tunnel, saw this kind of major drama.

Formerly in underground, Tang Wulin heard, therefore in such critical moment appear(ance).

Saw that in that dreamland once by own has held under duress Major Shen Xing, let alone, in the Tang Wulin heart really somewhat is unusual. Also greatly admires to Nightmare Old Devil, although he is only the Soul shape, but actually his Spiritual Strength must formidable to what kind of realm! Can control the entire North Sea Corps situation, perhaps by his spiritual stage, subverts entire North Sea Corps not to have any difficulties.

Shen Xing dumbfounded looks at Tang Wulin, she cannot believe the eye of own simply. When her body is completely lacking in vigilance, heard that warehouse manager saying that must take away her, and when gave to the unknown enemy, the mood of her whole person must collapse. Her of course knows that own by enemy was seized , and achievement threatens the Elder Sister hostage to be fearful. Not only her own disaster, even is the entire Family disaster.

In Nightmare, Elder Sister because once own was held under duress to compromise by Tang Wulin, but in the reality, she believes that Elder Sister similarly will also handle the matter that she is not willing to handle for own. Sisters affectionate, nothing more than such as is.

Two sisters grow up together, the sentiment is extremely good, she understood that own Elder Sister, is a gang kisses absolutely does not assist in handling. Critical moment, Elder Sister easier perception.

Once Elder Sister makes the huge mistake for own the words, then, Family definitely will be hit by the devastating disaster. Therefore, in just that flickered, she wished one could dead directly, is not willing to be in charge of Major Chen to carry off by that warehouse.

In each young girl heart the Savior, particularly in desperate is so, who does not hope that has a hero to stand to save own suddenly? What Shen Xing has not thought that this saves the own person, is that own wishes one could to tear to shreds it unexpectedly, has suffered a own several months of fellow in the dreamland.

„It looks like, your situation is not a little wonderful!” Tang Wulin looks at Shen Xing, on the face reveals a chuckle.

The Shen Xing look somewhat anxiously visits him, although is full of the hatred to Tang Wulin, but that after is only the dream, moreover she also clearly knows, the status of front these young people. This also too coincidence, they why in this time direct appear(ance) in warehouse? Now own also in dream inadequate?

Tang Wulin said to companion: „Took off their clothes, starts.”

Escaping......, Takes off the clothes?

Shen Xing pretty face instantaneously becomes a paleness, do they want to do? They and they......

How many minute of desperate once more appear(ance) of just vanished, did this leave the tigers mouth to enter the lair?

Tang Wulin, Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu three people are drawing the warehouse managers and two captains drag one side , helping them undress fast. Yuan En Yehui and Xu Xiaoyan keep off before the Shen Xing body, Ye Xinglan starts to solve her clothes.

The Shen Xing whole person has tarried, saw own fast was strip naked the clothes, time, the human was completely ignorant.

Ye Xinglan general has compared the stature of own and personal appearance, their height is similar, the stature also somewhat resembles.

Under the mask of Xu Xiaoyan and Yuan En Yehui, Ye Xinglan also rapidly took off the own clothes, has exchanged Shen Xing one, and wears the own clothes on Shen Xing.

„Do not be worried that we borrow your clothes. In you have lulled rays, most 20 minutes can return to again normal. These bastards you when the time comes own look that processing was good.” The Ye Xinglan racket the shoulder of Shen Xing, stands up.

Then, she starts on the face of own gently rubs, rubs, while often has a look at Shen Xing. Xu Xiaoyan stands in her behind, starts to handle her and personal appearance same color hair, quick, has made into and Shen Xing exactly the same hairstyle.

When Yuan En Yehui brings the hat, Ye Xinglan puts on, both hands of Ye Xinglan have also put down, Shen Xing dumbfounded seeing another own that animated standing in front of own. Simply is exactly the same, seems like looking in a mirror.

This......

„Good?” Tang Wulin sounds/voices transmits.

„Has handled, but also misses three clothes.” Yuan En Yehui said to him.

The Shen Xing eyeball rotation, saw that three people walked, three people is a military uniform, the warehouse is in charge of Major Chen and that two captains.

----------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#848: Is separated and returns

In the Major Chen mouth resounds Tang Wulin sounds/voices, „first time uses, a little not became a habit, particularly skeleton Transformation, but adapts to slightly. Xie Xie, you asked several people to come, remembers that looked for fat, otherwise Lizhi not good camouflage.”

„Good!”

Xie Xie turned around to go out of warehouse large door, said toward three soldiers who outside not far away value defended: „You and you, have you, your three come, helps to take inventory.”

The following process was simpler, quick, in the warehouse is standing, is Major Chen and Staff Officer Shen, two captains and three soldiers.

But the ground is lying down, is the same seven people, at least looked from the semblance that is exactly the same.

Tang Wulin arrived at side Shen Xing to squat, „you saw our these many secrets, should kill you to eliminate a potential informant?”

The Shen Xing eyeball rotates again and again, she could not speak, was irremovable, but the fear in look was actually particularly explicit.

Tang Wulin laughs, „teases you to play, we walk. Is predestined friends meets again. That warehouse was in charge in one day not to wake, after waiting for you well, processed voluntarily. This time was we have also helped North Sea Corps busy, making you clean up the traitor within, previous time stole away a aircraft matter like this to write off. Walks!”

Then, Tang Wulin stands up, to hand signal that Ye Xinglan makes invitation, seven people, walk toward the warehouse one after another.

Ye Xinglan in short time, grasped the Shen Xing makings basically. Throws out the chest to gain ground, on pretty face brings several points of arrogance, the stride to walk outward.

Left the warehouse, closes warehouse large door again. of course, is only unlatched, how because genuine controls this complex large door they unclear.

Tang Wulin follows side her, whole face compensates to say with a smile: „Staff Officer Shen, your other offended, in this warehouse truly was appear(ance) chaotic, but I will make them reorganize immediately, you could rest assured that quick.”

Ye Xinglan cold snort, „this matter I will report truthfully. You should better before above sends out the survey team handles all, otherwise, the consequence you know.”

„Is and is!” The Tang Wulin again and again name is, during the speeches, the people arrived at the elevator place.

„You please do not bother to see me off. Did not need to deliver.” Ye Xinglan said intentionally.

Tang Wulin hurries saying: „That is how good, we deliver you to come up. Staff Officer Shen, armed forces regimental commander there, you must for our fine talk several!”

Their place visited is a soldier, but among them the dialog is actually flawless. sounds/voices, and Shen Xing as well as that Major Chen not any difference.

Seven Old Devil give them, not only the simple cosmetics technique, has the infiltrating skill. How to change body type, how to change speech and manner, how to change sounds/voices. In having enough deep Soul Power situation, all these are not difficult. Needs quite painful training process that's all. But compares is suffered by numerous position Old Devil, what were these pain considered as?

„Biting” elevator door opens, hand signal that Tang Wulin makes invitation, in walking into elevator of Ye Xinglan first striding bravely forward. Other Tang Wulin and people hurry to follow.

The elevator closes. Fast rise.

In the entire process the people again have not spoken, in the elevator has the monitoring, too much talk leads to error, said that much was inferior did not say.

Quick, the elevator has delivered to them the ground. Is relying on the status sign, they went out of the warehouse with ease. Tang Wulin signaled with the eyes to Ye Xinglan, they have distinguished under one probably , is fast toward one side walks.

After entering a dark corner, Tang Wulin has referred to a not far away military vehicle, that military vehicle as if just went on patrol, is opening toward here.

Ye Xinglan said: „I go.”

„Together.” Tang Wulin has given a hand signal.

Seven people go forward fast, Ye Xinglan walks in the forefront, takes off military officer badge that the front is hanging, „parking.”

The epaulet on her shoulder is the best identification, in addition Shen Xing is famous in the regiment, is the renowned beautiful woman military officer, in the armed forces the rose, driving patrol soldier Captain is a second lieutenant, naturally recognizes her.

The military vehicle stops rapidly, jumped down from vehicle slightly, to Ye Xinglan good military salute, „Staff Officer Shen.”

Ye Xinglan sinking sound track: „Urgent task, we must exit, temporarily requisitions your military vehicles. Immediately leaps the car(riage).”

„Yes!” The second lieutenant complies with one without hesitation.

If there is changed other major, wants to requisition their military vehicles, he will also carry on to above inquired, but Shen Xing but Younger Sister of armed forces regimental commander, is in the dreams in many low rank military officer hearts the sweetheart. The opportunity of this performance does not see, therefore, his without hesitation complied.

The soldier on military vehicle gets out fast, Ye Xinglan gave a hand signal to Tang Wulin, Tang Wulin nodded, the people boarded in abundance, Xie Xie was responsible for driving, on Ye Xinglan the copilot, other Tang Wulin and people sat in behind.

Has not said anything to these soldiers again, the Xie Xie skilled control steering wheel, turns around same place, directly soars the North Sea Corps large door direction to speed away to go.

Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell warehouse.

The eyelash moves, Shen Xing can finally the winking eye, gradually, finger also active. Feeling lacking in vigilance is vanishing fast.

The takes a deep breath tone that she tries hard, stimulation of movement within the body Soul Power stimulates bloodline to operate, the feeling lacking in vigilance vanishes fast.

Struggled to sit from the ground, then she saw lay down in of not far away was strip naked Major Chen as well as two captains and three soldiers. time, has mixed emotions.

The crisis has relieved, but, this time mood was also five senses mixed Chen. She has not thought that fellow in own Nightmare unexpectedly has become the own straw to grasp.

Struggles to crawl from the ground, Shen Xing arrives at the wall fast, effort has pressed down the alarm button.

The ear-piercing alarm sound resounds through the entire warehouse immediately, spread the entire North Sea Corps base.

The Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell warehouse is the regiment heavy, the internal warning directly is most Advanced other. But Shen Xing was very clear, crossed such long time, perhaps that several fellows already ran away.

Tang Wulin their of course left.

Wins victory without firing a shot, has not had any nice fight, is driving the military vehicle, they left North Sea Corps, the military vehicle ran quickly on the High-speed road, fast is far away from the North Sea City direction.

Has saying that the equipment of military vehicle be much better compared with the civil car(riage), not only has the advanced guiding system, but also speed is quick. Xie Xie has arrived at the terminal velocity the military vehicle quickly.

„time was similar, prepares to abandon the car(riage). Arrives at a hiding place the car(riage).” Tang Wulin said to front Xie Xie.

[Say / Way] that Xie Xie some do not abandon: „This car(riage) is really good, if can open to be good.”

Yuan En Yehui ill-humored [say / way]: „Are you silly, made the Mecha regiment of military give us to come several missiles a while you to be comfortable. Quickly, leaves High-speed, finds a place we to get out.”

Next High-speed exits, Xie Xie drove the car(riage), this is small cities, the cities is not big. Looked for woods, drove past the military vehicle. The people fast get out, according to Tang Wulin the position that saw from formerly the guiding system, they dash about wildly in darkness, directly soar the destination to go.

The goal is very simple, is the place that Tang Wulin they support are actually not willing to go, Soul Guidance Train stop station.

Without the transportation vehicle, wants to be far away from North Sea Corps fast is impossible. Tang Wulin does not doubt, nearby quick North Sea Corps will block. They cannot drive military vehicle to continue to hurry along. Therefore, the best means are to ride the public transport means that but in the public transport means that Soul Guidance High-speed Train is quickest one. Therefore, had no alternative.

Is running, they while have relieved Yi Rong on own face, in being away from the Soul Guide Train Station not far place, is acted by a person, buys several clothes to come back, takes off the armed forces extension, changes the civilian clothes, simultaneously after simple change own look, this entered the Soul Guidance High-speed Train station.

Seven people buy a ticket separatedly, buys was recently Class 1 Train. After entering platform, gathers.

Because stopping over station, the platform is somewhat crude, even does not have including the ceiling. The night wind sways, somewhat is very chilly.

Tang Wulin both hands insert the pocket to stand there, in lonely platform only then their several. The appearances of other people are also similar.

„Boss, do you know? I had the feeling that planted to live finally. Isn't our also in Nightmare?” Xie Xie said to Tang Wulin suddenly.

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „I do not know.”

Suffering on Devil Island has made the extremely profound impression for them, their spiritual until now have not been able fully to restore. Especially Le Zhengyu, now also occasionally will become dull.

-------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#849: Shen sisters

Xu Lizhi said: „I completely understood now why we before going, the Academy division commanders were such expression. War God Temple that Senior that we meet is also. Really never wants to return to that place again.”

Yeah, said that can leave, they almost impatiently broke in sea, is far away with quickest speed.

„Actually, Old Devil they are also very pitiful.” Xu Xiaoyan said.

Le Zhengyu complexion changes, „they feel sorry , don't we feel sorry for? We were suffered by them also insufficient.”

„Selects Zhengyu calmly.” Tang Wulin said: „We withstood inhuman suffering, but has to acknowledge that in this several months time, we also had the considerable progress. We grew, were leaving there moment, I genuine felt that own no longer was a child, but turned into the adult.”

„Yes! We grew up.” The Yuan En Yehui chuckle was saying.

Tang Wulin ease [say / way]: „Was right, when by *@ Old Devil Test, had the accident besides Zhengyu, each of you's reaction I saw actually at that time. Is *@ Old Devil looks to me specially. The words said that you do want to know, what reaction each other is?”

The people instantaneously became silent, Le Zhengyu stares in a big way the eye.

Other five people are almost [say / way] with one voice: „Shut up!”

Soul Guidance Train comes, finally gave this chilly small stop station to bring piece of light. Looks at familiar Train, was recalling bitter experience each time, Tang Wulin both hands hug after the brain, first has stepped onto Train.

Finally must go back. Hard times finally passed.

Eventually, he has not said the thing that own of that day sees, good that something did not say.

North Sea Corps.

Shen Yue complexion gloomy listened to subordinates reports, the mood to miss the extreme.

North Sea Corps had the traitor within unexpectedly, moreover is such important post, as the armed forces regimental commander, her Duty-bound Responsibility. What is more important, own Younger Sister nearly degenerated into the captive. This matter, must go all the way with it, how regardless of must eradicate internal traitor within.

„Passes on me to order, immediately launches to purge the motion. The regiment, investigates rigorously.”

„Yes!”

Without a doubt, Major Chen and his partners were eradicated, after inventory, in the warehouse has been short of over 200 Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell. These Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell put together, bombed flat a small city sufficiently.

Shen Xing looks at Elder Sister, until at this moment, her mood was unable to return to normal completely.

„Elder sister, other your pressure was also too big.” Other people exited, Shen Xing also returned to the name of Shen Yue normally.

The Shen Yue brow is tight, „this is not the issue of pressure. Our North Sea Corps unexpectedly by person infiltrating, then, other regiment? Entire Northeast Military District? This matter cannot conceal the truth, must report. Perhaps I will be punished. As for you, I according to rendering meritorious service reporting. After all was you have discovered issue location, moreover prevented these rebels to escape promptly, had about Shrek Seven Monsters these people, I will conceal. Places on the merit you.”

„Elder sister, you? What punishment will you suffer?” Shen Xing somewhat anxiously asked.

Shen Yue is smiling bitterly shaking the head, „does not know that can only be walks one step to look at one. This time matter is too big, perhaps the position of my this armed forces regimental commander must vacillate. Waits for your rendering meritorious service to be approved, I will transfer you as soon as possible. You are also this assuming sole responsibility for an important task time.”

Shen Xing nod of gently. Why does not know, after experiencing the beforehand matter, just when she rested slept, has not had a bad dream again.

Shen Yue has not sent for pursuing Shrek Seven Monsters, for her, does not need to do completely. Because does not have any significance. How even if stressed the Tang Wulin seven people able? Only can make the North Sea Corps interior scandal ferment. With its this, might as well neglect them. Like this is good to everybody. After all, even if celebrating a holiday of Sun-Moon Royal Soul Guidance Master Academy and Shrek Academy is big, that is also the struggle of spirit. But is the military senior official, the lots that she must consider are longer-term.

After two transferring to another vehicle, Tang Wulin and companion were on correct Train, directly soared Shrek City to go. This time, has not come across the rarely seen matter finally, bon voyage.

When Soul Guidance Train steady docking in Shrek City, Tang Wulin own had the feeling that planted to have tears streaming down the face. Has not had Soul Guidance Train of accident, was really too wonderful. Must know, this he may be somewhat with trepidation all the way!

Got out, extension of effort a body.

„Came back finally. We go back to register directly, do you have other matter?” Tang Wulin asked to companion.

Xie Xie said: „I do not plan such quickly to return to Academy, I need the recuperation and recuperation. This playing was too big, I must unable to bear. I plan to go home, for a long time has not gone back. Yuan En you go home with me together. The ugly wife must see the parents-in-law. Whoops!”

Yuan En Yehui works off anger Teng Teng is clutching the ear of Xie Xie, „you said that who is the ugly wife?”

„I ugly, I am ugly. You were most beautiful.” Xie Xie in this aspect never anything moral integrity.

Le Zhengyu to rejoice in other people's misfortunes [say / way]: „Gets what one deserves you. Xiaoyan, you also invited me to go to your family to sit! I not am always ugly.”

Xie Xie gets angry: „Stirring up trouble.”

Xu Xiaoyan „puff” smiles, „good! I am a place come out with Xie Xie, you also together return to Eastsea City with me. I lead you to go to my family to have a look.”

Le Zhengyu and some Xie Xie exclusions stared opposite party one, has not said with the opposite party.

Tang Wulin is laughing in spite of trying not to shaking the head, looks to Ye Xinglan and Xu Lizhi, „you?”

Xu Lizhi looks to Ye Xinglan, Ye Xinglan said: „We return to Academy. The thing of this learning are actually many, I planned that consolidates well. Lizhi is also, this time he harvests many, I must help cultivation of his consolidated own be.”

„Good.”

Tang Wulin said: „One month later, we in Academy all assembled. Then, I planned that practices the coordination with everybody, do you have the dissident views?”

Xie Xie said: „I do not have the issue.”

Yuan En Yehui nods.

Le Zhengyu said: „I do not have any issue. Moreover, Boss I thought that your choice is correct, when has graduated from Inner Court, I planned that enlists in the military with you.”

Xie Xie surprised looks at Le Zhengyu, said: „Has not thought that your patriotism, usually has not looked!”

Xu Xiaoyan said with a smile lowly: „He is because the military uniform is quite graceful. On that day after having worn the military uniform, talked over several times with me.”

Le Zhengyu was discouraged immediately, „wife, you cannot remove my stage!”

Xu Xiaoyan white his eyes, „who is your wife?”

Le Zhengyu smiles, „we shelled peanuts have cooked the cooked rice, can you also not be my wife? I can definitely regard you in that day illusion now am your. After all, *@ Old Devil simulation unusual is good, hey.”

Looks he harbors evil intentions bad smiles, Xu Xiaoyan elegant blushing face, „feeds, in this, you do not go home with me!”

Le Zhengyu hurries to keep silent.

Ye Xinglan said with a smile: „I do not have the opinion, we are a whole, truly should well Joint Training. Moreover, regarding enlistment, some of my also interests. Has seen the North Sea Corps situation, genuine understands that, compared with the army, our individual strength were really too tiny. Although we have not been the serviceman in the future, but I thought that understood the modernized military level is very necessary. After the graduation, I think that I and Lizhi can also enlist in the military.”

--------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#850: Temporarily distinguishes

The Tang Wulin great happiness, can disagreement companion separate, this simply was the wonderful matter.

He turns head to look to Xie Xie and Yuan En Yehui.

Xie Xie is also looking at Yuan En Yehui, without a doubt, this manages strict execution fellow to look at the Yuan En Yehui choice the wife.

The Yuan En Yehui look suddenly becomes somewhat desolate, she shook the head, „I cannot become a soldier, after graduating, I have the important matter to do.”

Spoke these words, she turns around to walk suddenly. Xie Xie is stunned, then apology smiles bitterly to Tang Wulin, hurried to turn around to pursue.

Looks the back that they leave, Tang Wulin mutters the tunnel: „Yuan En as if has any difficulties! But she has not said.”

Ye Xinglan said: „Should be related with her life experience. You did not think that she simultaneously does have two Top Rank Martial Soul to be very strange? Especially Fallen Angel Martial Soul, this itself should be one type is formidable, but may turn into Evil Soul Master Martial Soul. Yuan En initially was the Work Study Student status, looked like, her body should have any secret.”

Tang Wulin said: „They came back, we should look for Yuan En to chat. Regardless of there is any matter, we are a whole. Can help her, bounden.”

„Boss, we also walked.” Le Zhengyu is holding the hand of Xu Xiaoyan, waved to Tang Wulin.

Ye Xinglan asked to Tang Wulin: „We had the destination, you? Why do you plan to go?”

Tang Wulin said: „I want to go to Tang Sect first, then goes to my Senior Teacher there to live in time. The tour of Devil Island, I have many realizing from experience, I want to take a look, can taking this opportunity, rush to 7th Rank Saint Craftsman Rank Blacksmith., That our manufacture Three Word Battle Armor foundation will have if successful in the future.”

Ye Xinglan eye one bright, „have you prepared for?”

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „feeling is a type of very marvelous thing, I currently have this type to feel in any case. As for good, only then tried to know. But has the direction of my Senior Teacher, I thought that should the issue not be big.”

If made other 6th Rank Blacksmith listen to his these words, corona that can perhaps be mad. Which 6th Rank Blacksmith dares saying that the own assault Saint Craftsman issue is not big! Also only then Tang Wulin dares such to do.

Soul Refinement is not easy to complete!

Entrusts with metal(s) Wisdom to entrusting with metal(s) Life is much more difficult.

manufacture Battle Armor, initial time what is most important is the design, is manufacture, forging is rear. But to High Rank Battle Armor time, forging actually became the most important part. Because Battle Armor promotes, first is the promotion in material quality.

The people now are also One Word Battle Armor, only then after the promotion is Two Word Battle Armor Master, they can graduate from Inner Court. Future Three Word Battle Armor, is they whether will become one generation of Elite important indicator.

Ye Xinglan said: „Your foundation has prepared to us, but promotion Battle Armor time, needs our two coordination. One month later you come back, we can start.”

Tang Wulin nods, „this is also I must strive to promote to the Saint Craftsman reason, if there is Saint Craftsman Rank forging ability, helping us promote Two Word Battle Armor to want the easy capital. Your here pressure will also reduce.”

„Um.” Ye Xinglan nodded, although she is the 6th Rank manufacture master, but also has the huge disparity from 7th Rank, at least 2-3 years are impossible to promote. If Tang Wulin can have the Saint Craftsman Rank forging level to coordinate her manufacture Battle Armor as foundation, that success ratio is much higher, the key will be everybody Battle Armor quality will be higher. Now the people win above 50th Rank to cultivate, is this again manufacture Battle Armor time.

„Good, we said goodbye in light of this.”

Left Soul Guide Train Station, three people said goodbye. Tang Wulin goes to Tang Sect directly.

Reason that must go to Tang Sect first, is he planned that Battle Soul Hall has a look, to have task that anything must complete. Left was so long, must report. Moreover, what is more important, now he is One Word Battle Armor Master, has not actually promoted the Battle Member rank of own in Battle Soul Hall. He now or White Rank Battle Member, but by the One Word Battle Armor Master strength, should be able to promote to Yellow Rank Battle Member.

When arrives at Tang Sect General Headquarters, Tang Wulin thinks suddenly a matter, that is own has not worn the Battle Member clothing, the own lots had been detained by Academy, in fact, but should also return to Academy really first one.

Leaves is so long, this matter has forgotten, including Soul Guide Communication Device, own these rare metal(s) anything, all in Academy.

Everybody also has as if forgotten, does not know that Xie Xie on their road thinks does not have.

However since arrived at Tang Sect, advanced has a look.

Passing through the gate, Tang Wulin surprised discovery, Tang Sect General Headquarters were more than former person today. Everybody passes and out, but also is a hurried appearance.

Because usually comes the Tang Sect number of times not to be many, the person who Tang Wulin knows are not many. Is walking forward, suddenly, he saw a familiar face.

Greatly bald, stature grandiose Hall Master Zhao walked from inside.

This Tang Wulin of course recognizes, initially Wu Zhangkong was leading him the time, had seen this.

„Hall Master Zhao.” Tang Wulin respectful salutes to him.

Hall Master Zhao named Zhao Song, Strength Hall Hall Master in Tang Sect Outer Three Halls.

Zhao Song saw that he stares slightly, „you are......”

Tang Wulin in the Star Luo Empire three years, after coming back, has been closing up, therefore Zhao Song also had many years not to see him. He is in the youth development period, once handsome boy turned into stature big and tall slender youth now.

„Hall Master Zhao, I am Tang Wulin.”

„Tang Wulin? Is you!” Who Zhao Song remembered him finally is, immediately said with a smile: „Many years have not seen your boy, were long such high. Good, first did not tell you, I must exit to handle matters. You go, Guo Xiaoxu.” Then, he in a hurry walked.

Guo Xiaoxu is Battle Soul Hall Hall Master, the Tang Wulin immediate superior, initially was he brings in Battle Soul Hall Tang Wulin.

When Tang Wulin arrives at Battle Soul Hall, in Battle Soul Hall the gate opens, inside person unexpectedly is also many. mask from the face, Yellow Rank and Purple Rank Battle Member unexpectedly is many. Moreover there is more than one Black Rank Battle Member.

Tang Wulin searched the probe head, he has not worn the Battle Member clothing, does not know when should go, was actually lifted the hand to block by Yellow Rank Battle Member.

„Who are you? Does not know that Battle Soul Hall is the forbidden area?” Yellow Rank Battle Member sinking sound said.

Tang Wulin said: „Sorry, I am also Battle Member, but has not worn the Battle Member clothing today. Therefore......”

„Are you also Battle Member? Does not wear the clothing is not Battle Member, this regulation(s) you do not know. Quickly leaves here.” That Yellow Rank Battle Member said that in a hurry entered Battle Soul Hall.

Then Tang Wulin but, actually he was very curious what happened, these many Battle Member will arrive at Battle Soul Hall, looked like had about hundred people many, moreover majority were also above Yellow Rank. But he does not have the Battle Member clothing, cannot go in!

When his helpless preparation leaves, in Battle Soul Hall goes out of one person, on this face is bringing mask unexpectedly is red.

Red level Battle Member? Tang Wulin heart big quake, let alone saw, he is listens not to hear Battle Soul Hall also has red level Battle Member existence.

From the Battle Member rank and Soul Ring color match, red level Battle Member should mutually without a doubt compared with Black Rank Battle Member more formidable existence. At present this seems stature not high red level Battle Member, immediately takes to him imperceptibly very big oppression strength.

Tang Wulin hurries to fall back on the one side, making way path. But that red level Battle Member actually stopped the footsteps, in the mouth has sent out light „well”.

„Tang Wulin?”

Listened to the opposite party to call the own name, Tang Wulin to be also startled, „did you know me?”

Red level Battle Member lifts the hand, has lifted mask on own face, reveals a Tang Wulin familiar face. Not is just Battle Soul Hall Hall Master Guo Xiaoxu.

In the Tang Wulin heart is suddenly enlighted, no wonder this is bringing red mask, originally unexpectedly is Battle Soul Hall Hall Master here.

„Hall Master Guo, hello.”

Guo Xiaoxu shows a faint smile, „did you come? Your Battle Member clothing? Was right, heard that you are One Word Battle Armor Master, can change the clothes. Come, happen to I led you to promote the Battle Member rank.” Then, he turns around to move toward nearby Battle Soul Hall work area.

Tang Wulin hurried to follow, asked in a low voice: „Does Hall Master Guo, look like our Battle Soul Hall very busy appearance?”

Guo Xiaoxu sighed one lightly, „Federation had such big matter, can we not be busy? After all, our Battle Soul Hall has taken protecting Federation as own duty.”

Tang Wulin stares, „what important matter left?”

Guo Xiaoxu surprised [say / way]: „Don't you know?”

-----------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#851: terrorist attack

The Tang Wulin forced smile said: „I and companion just came back from Academy military training. Has not gone to Academy with enough time, first came our Tang Sect, does not know that what happened!”

Guo Xiaoxu looked at his one eyes, the sinking sound track: „Ten days ago, Heaven Dou City had terrorist attack, died many people. The Heaven Dou City administration official mansion was razed. The foreign announcement data died more than 1000 people, but in fact, over 4000 dead, the wounded crossed ten thousand.”

„?” Tang Wulin surprised opening mouth.

Heaven Dou City?

He still clearly remembers that Heaven Dou City Chief Executive shouldn't be Mo Lan elder sister's Father? Heaven Dou City encounters terrorist attack, moreover died these many people?

„That Heaven Dou City Administrative official?” Tang Wulin hurries to pursue asks.

Guo Xiaoxu sighed, „died at one's post. Attacks is too sudden, moreover does not have any omen. Altogether 60 5th Rank above Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell were detonated in the Heaven Dou City different places, has created the Heaven Dou City big disturbance. Then does not know fighter aircraft appear(ance) that from where comes sky over Heaven Dou City administration official mansion, has put in 9th Rank Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell, has caused the biggest casualties. This matter has shocked entire Federation. Now Federation enters the 1st Rank garrison condition, dispatched the massive personnel to investigate thoroughly. Our Tang Sect Battle Soul Hall receives Federation War God Temple to invite, coordinates them, participates in the investigation together.”

Listened to the Guo Xiaoxu words, Tang Wulin to hold breath cold air, sudden that too this matter had, moreover was so a disaster. This reminded him of the North Sea Corps Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell robbed matter, hurried to say own in the discovery of North Sea Corps simply.

Guo Xiaoxu more listens to the brow more to wrinkle, „this we have not received the news. It seems like the military blocks off the flow of news. The North Sea Corps Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell warehouse was robbed perhaps is not a case! If some massive Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell flow out, that can be a catastrophe absolutely.”

Tang Wulin said: „Knows which organization now is dry?”

Guo Xiaoxu said: „Knew. Holy Spirit Cult announced that is responsible for this time terrorist attack.”

The Tang Wulin double fist grips tightly, „is Holy Spirit Cult.”

He more than once has had to do with this Evil Soul Master Sect, even barely escapes. Has not thought that actually once again heard had the news about Holy Spirit Cult. Moreover, this Holy Spirit Cult is intense.

Guo Xiaoxu said: „Recently for the six months, Holy Spirit Cult extremely madness initiated repeatedly terrorist attack. Has caused the massive loss. At the beginning, Federation also diligently wanted to press the matter, now had such big matter, could not suppress again. Has not thought that in the surface seems uneventful Federation, was corroded this degree unexpectedly.”

Listened to his expression to fill was discontented and angry, Tang Wulin asked: „Hall Master Guo, you meant, these terrorist attack with Federation itself related?”

Guo Xiaoxu sneers, „of course. How many Holy Spirit Cult can Evil Soul Master have? If no person in power's support. You think they can grow strong is so quick? Without a doubt, has the secret evil behind-the-scenes manipulator. Does not know that this secret evil behind-the-scenes manipulator himself is the Holy Spirit Cult person, has controlled the Holy Spirit Cult person. Behind Holy Spirit Cult has certainly deeper stage existence, we must dig as soon as possible them, otherwise, will only bring many panic. Listens to you to say today luckily, otherwise we have not known that the military also had problems unexpectedly.”

Is the Yellow Rank Battle Member process is very simple from the White Rank Battle Member promotion, Tang Wulin has shown One Word Battle Armor, has Guo Xiaoxu Qin Dian again, he has completed directly the promotion of own Battle Member rank, after exchanging a Yellow Rank Battle Member black robe and yellow mask, he thought immediately is more comfortable, at least will again enter Battle Soul Hall not to be caught up.

„Wulin, you come with me.” Guo Xiaoxu brought Tang Wulin to return to Battle Soul Hall.

„Now our Battle Soul Hall has continued many task from the Federation aspect, searches Holy Spirit Cult according to some clues. You and Holy Spirit Cult have battle experience. I thought that you can also participate in task. This to you is also an exercise. How is it? Is willing to join one to reconnoiter Squad?”

Tang Wulin [say / way] without hesitation: „Duty-bound Responsibility.”

Regarding Holy Spirit Cult, he hates to the marrow of the bones, let alone this Holy Spirit Cult unexpectedly started terrorist attack to kill that many people. Except that wicked does good deeds.

Guo Xiaoxu has completed quickly to the arrangement of Tang Wulin, making him join five people of detection Squad. This Squad is led by Purple Rank Battle Member, including him, four Yellow Rank Battle Member.

According to the Tang Sect Battle Soul Hall interior system, Purple Rank Battle Member is Two Word Battle Armor Master. Yellow Rank Battle Member must have cultivation of One Word Battle Armor Master is, although the population are not many, but fighting strength was quite good.

Moreover, what making Tang Wulin pleasantly surprised is, because the situation is urgent, therefore this time all in view of Holy Spirit Cult searching task, Battle Member accumulated points doubles gives.

This is the big good deed, Battle Member accumulated points can receive in exchange for various resources in Battle Soul Hall absolutely, besides Tang Sect secret arts, various types of rare and precious good things.

For example, Heaven and Earth Treasure that ordinary Tang Sect Disciples can exchange little can see the Ten-thousand Years above rank, generally speaking, Thousand Years placed an upper limit on. But Battle Soul Hall here, has actually concentrated Tang Sect hugest resources, the thing that can exchange wants on not to know many times many. of course, ordinary Tang Sect accumulated points is not good, needs Battle Member accumulated points to exchange.

After all, Battle Soul Hall Battle Member is Tang Sect genuine Nucleus.

Tang Wulin now assault nine Golden Dragon King Seal not anything, resources that but assault following Golden Dragon King Seal, will need in the future even if now looks like by him, is the astronomical figures. Not only is Ten-thousand Years above Heaven and Earth Treasure, but also the quantity is huge. Was not three and four types can solve.

Even if he is close Saint Craftsman stage Blacksmith, felt that the pressure is very big.

He also wants cultivate, cannot the energy use, in forging changes money on, completed Tang Sect Battle Member task without doubt is the shortcut.

Meets the good taboo of this double accumulated points, how can let off?

task that Tang Wulin they receive is the searching Heaven Dou City western suburbs abandoning factory region. Completed the task standard to find the clues about Holy Spirit Cult, according to the reliable information, Holy Spirit Cult some people had appeared and disappeared in that side.

Before that piece abandons the factory , is used to produce rare metal(s), the area is big, afterward because of an explosion accident, causing the deleterious substance to divulge massively, has polluted that lands, therefore was abandoned. This pollution is very difficult to process, until now, the official have not drawn up the effective plan, therefore this lands have also been leaving unused.

Therefore, after receiving task, they also received have specifically been used to isolate the emission qualitative exposure suit. of course, regarding Soul Master, resists emission qualitative ability to by far strong the average person.

Is Purple Rank Battle Member of head stands in the forefront, looks to including Tang Wulin four Yellow Rank Battle Member, said: „Motion immediately starts, waits a minute everybody to debug contact. In this motion, my code number is Purple One, you separately are Yellow One, Yellow Two, Yellow Three and Yellow Four.”

He was saying, while is pointing at four people, what making Tang Wulin somewhat funny is, own is assigned as 3rd. Also is really and three has the fate. But turned into present Yellow Three that's all from original White Three.

„Our simple familiar, I am Assault System Battle Soul Master, you?” Purple One asked.

Yellow One said: „I am Agility System Battle Soul Master.”

Yellow Two said: „I am Cure System Battle Soul Master.” Listens to sounds/voices for the female, and young. Cure System Battle Soul Master can become the chair starts, moreover young, obviously is not very ordinary.

Tang Wulin said: „Assault-Control System Battle Soul Master.”

#852: Tang Sect Combat Car

Yellow Four said: „I am Defense System Battle Soul Master.”

Listened to the words of people, Purple One satisfied nod. Although among Battle Member the status also mutually keeps secret, moreover Soul Master should not inquire each other ability, but at least must know that everybody's excelling direction is anything, will coordinate to be easier.

„Is very good, then, Yellow Three, what degree your can Control be?”

Tang Wulin said: „Vine kind of Control, excels at Bind, controls the audience. And there is a certain attack strength.”

Purple One said: „Good, you are host Control Soul Master of our temporary team. I make the arrow. Yellow Two you treat in behind, Yellow One is responsible for scouting. The Yellow Four whole show is protection Yellow Two and Yellow Three. Understood?”

„Yes.”

The people can become Yellow Rank Battle Member, is elite, the simple exchange arranged task.

„set off!” Purple One rubbish, the big hand wields, five people left Battle Soul Hall fast, on Tang Sect specially is Battle Member preparation Soul Guide Steam Vehicle.

Tang Sect Soul Guide Steam Vehicle all over the body is blue, it is said to commemorate Tang Sect ancestor Tang San. This is not ordinary blue, itself has the color deterioration function, can carry on various camouflage easily. Moreover Tang Sect this type of specially-made vehicles have many other functions.

Because before Tang Wulin, is White Rank Battle Member, has not contacted these Tang Sect high tech. He has seen this Tang Sect Combat Car exchange proportion in the exchange list of Battle Member. Value not poor! Endured compared with Thousand Years spirit items of rare rank.

Purple One drives personally, Tang Sect Combat Car made Tang Wulin feel its advantage quickly, speed was quick, and was steady. Sits in the car(riage), cannot hear any noise. This Combat Car is five positions. Sits can adjust the quite comfortable posture in everyone.

Purple One and Yellow One sit in the front, Tang Wulin and Yellow Two and Yellow Four in the back row. Left Tang Sect General Headquarters, Purple One has been driving Combat Car skilled quickly in the High-speed road, directly soared the Heaven Dou City direction to go.

Has the Tang word logo forefront Tang Sect Combat Car, a on High-speed road, the logo has shone, and sends out similar warning general sounds/voices. The discovery that then Tang Wulin is startled, Tang Sect Combat Car speed promotes continually, the rapidness of speed, even also wants on the strong several points compared with Soul Guidance Train.

Other Soul Guide Steam Vehicle on High-speed road on own initiative give way to traffic, heard the alarm sound naturally the innermost path gives them.

Does this have the privilege? Moreover, can Soul Guide Steam Vehicle be so quick unexpectedly?

Tang Wulin pleasantly surprised. As one person who is called as Soul Guidance Train always to have an accident, if can have such one to be able the High-speed travel, and also has the vehicles of privilege, round trip where simply is not convenient.

„Purple One, this can make others give way to traffic, and overspeed privilege, Tang Sect does Combat Car of our own exchange have?” Tang Wulin cannot bear ask.

Purple One said: „Thinks any good deed. When carries out special task, special approval after Sect, and is good in the Federation report. Our Tang Sect may not have what privilege.”

Although so that's how it is, Tang Wulin somewhat is slightly disappointed, but thinks that this is also reasonable. After all, the Tang Sect Battle Member quantity are not too few, if can the privilege learner vehicle, not be good likely to lead to the traffic accident. Because special task can have privilege to be passable.

Purple One said: „It is not absolute. If you have the special contribution to Sect and Federation, can obtain the Federation reward contributes badge specially, coordinates our Tang Sect Combat Car, can have the privilege actually. of course, this must apply. As far as I know, our Battle Soul Hall has several Battle Member to have such vehicles. After going back, you can inquire the specific demand to the information bank.”

„Thank You (xiexie) you.” Tang Wulin complies with one. This is the good deed! Goes back to ask first said again.

This privilege Tang Sect may have, Shrek Academy also similar possibility. Thinks of here, Tang Wulin remembered own that Yellow Rank Mecha. By own present forging ability, should promote really it. Has the Mecha words, will go into action to facilitate to be many.

The matter that wants to handle is really many! Wipes the light smile to reappear under mask. He likes this substantial feeling.

The Purple One road sense is good, Tang Sect Combat Car continues High-speed to go, compared with being called as Soul Guidance High-speed Train entered the Heaven Dou City range quickly.

The weather gradually faded out, the vehicle speed slowed down, gets down the High-speed road, Purple One has driven Tang Sect Combat Car to enter the Heaven Dou City city limit. Also opened the Combat Car camouflage system, making it quick looks like ordinary vehicles, did not have is so noticeable.

Enters the urban district, the Tang Wulin mood somewhat constrains, by the path, can see many tents and temporary housing, is relying on the keen sense of hearing, he also occasionally can hear some weeping sounds to transmit. Various Federation breakdown lorries also find at everywhere. It can be imagined, this terrorist attack has brought what kind of disaster to Heaven Dou City.

Such existence has surpassed the Twenty-thousand Years Ancient city to undergo so heavily attacks, Holy Spirit Cult was really too hateful.

Purple One sinking sound track: „Weather some late, you had do not excel at the night fighting?”

Nobody spoke.

„Good, we go to that abandoning factory region to search for immediately. Has not known how long must search to be able to find the clue. Earlier starts. Yellow Two, your body?”

„I do not have the issue.” Yellow Two sounds/voices clear replied. She is Cure System Soul Master, therefore Purple One has such asked.

Purple One looked at a vehicle navigation, a revolution of steering wheel, drove on Tang Sect Combat Car an alley, the road was boarding not many, the vehicle speed promoted slowly, fast went in the suburb direction.

Tang Wulin closes both eyes, close eyes maintains mental tranquility. Right hand subconscious according, in the front just obtained on soon Yellow Rank Battle Member badge.

Yellow Rank Battle Member badge itself has certain promotion effect to Spiritual Strength, simultaneously can provide Localization, searching and small range radar multiple functions. The volume is not big, but affects is quite not small, itself also supplements necessary contact, binds the badge insider information.

To Yellow Rank this stage, has Heaven and Earth Difference with beforehand White Rank Battle Member in the treatment obviously.

If White Rank Battle Member is the reserve duty, then, Yellow Rank Battle Member was Battle Soul Hall main fighting strength.

Finally, when the weather is completely dark, Tang Sect Combat Car advances one piece obviously is to abandon region as before., Can see the workshop take shape shadows by far.

Without any light existence, gloomy, but bleak/desolate. The car(riage) advances this region, has a cloudy and cold feeling to raid the heart imperceptibly.

Purple One stops Tang Sect Combat Car, said in a low voice: „Inspects communications device.”

The people hold down separately own badge, according to serial number order, 11 checkups.

„Communication is normal, gets out.” Purple One told one, first to get out, simultaneously has turned off all headlights.

The people get out successively. After getting out, that cloudy and cold feeling particularly was also obvious.

Purple One looked at surroundings, said: „Yellow Two, you with Yellow Four one group, Yellow One and Yellow Three, I, we are divided into four teams, disperses searching. Has any discovery to report immediately. If discovers Evil Soul Master, do not act rashly, first greeted the teammate. Remember, all give priority to own safety. Understood?”

„Yes!”

This piece abandons factory region obvious area not to be small, in their each individual hand blueprint, Purple One spreads out own blueprint, has divided the searching region above. His own searching most deep place.

„Motion.”

Purple One waves toward Tang Sect Combat Car, sees only on his finger ring ray of light to dodge, received Tang Sect Combat Car, then toward abandoning the factory goes.

Tang Wulin own also storage ring, inside huge spatial can direct load bearing Mecha, but also kept Academy before military training.

Yellow One also fast submerges in darkness, Tang Wulin looked at a own map, toward assigned direction barrel.

In the eye the purple aura glistening, does not need any lighting attachment, relies on Purple Demon Eyes he also to see the surroundings situation clearly. Purple Demon Eyes was almost Battle Member necessary Tang Sect secret arts.

Purple One had not confessed that desirably everybody must wear the exposure suit, is in itself is confident to them, everybody has Battle Armor, Battle Armor is easier-to-use than any exposure suit.

Tang Wulin had not felt that any illness, his own Golden Dragon King bloodline is formidable, ordinary deleterious substance where may invade his body!

Fast vanguard, Tang Wulin walks, while is feeling surroundings all, simultaneously opened the miniature radar function on Yellow Rank badge.

This miniature radar he is a first use, can search to observe 100 meters in diameter range, 100 meters range all turns into the three-dimensional shape, presents in his spiritual sea. It is said the design inspiration came from initially Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao Spirit Eyes Soul Skill Spiritual Detection. of course, compared with Ice Spirit Douluo, the investigation range wanted small many.

#853: Bai to come?

The miniature radar supplementary heat energy survey, searches to observe to the Life body especially sensitively, is easy-to-use.

After Tang Wulin opening radar, but continues to pour into Soul Power, in mind immediately appear(ance) stereoscopic view within diameter hundred meters range. surroundings is the worn-out factory and equipment. Feels very bleakly.

Said is searching, is relying on the miniature radar, so long as actually walks the factory region, even if completes foundation searching.

Tang Wulin barrel, in the meantime, he marches forward while Control the own Soul Power seal pore and own aura, falls to the ground very dexterously, as far as possible does not send out any sounds/voices.

This collecting rest/breath technique is he in the Devil Island study, from Disillusioned Old Devil there. A infiltrating most important point, must keep the enemy from discovering own. The collecting rest/breath technique of Disillusioned Old Devil is exquisite, not only can restrain own aura, but also is relying on Soul Power and Ruin energy blends mutually, Control, can barrier get down including the own body temperature. Can avoid searching of heat energy detector to observe.

Tang Wulin is also studies for the purpose of application now, therefore, even if some people carry on to search to observe with various types of detectors now, is unable to discover that has sealed up own aura and Soul Power completely as well as changed him of body temperature.

Disillusioned Old Devil had told Tang Wulin at that time, Life of human only then one time, no matter, must with own biggest is vigilant facing having the threat of possibility appear(ance). Because, perhaps once the appear(ance) fault, does not have the possibility of regret. Because, the human died.

Regarding the guidance of Old Devil, because there are beforehand all sorts to suffer, Tang Wulin remembered specially clearly. Therefore, he will collect the rest/breath technique to use at this time, simultaneously own also covert personal appearance as far as possible, quietly advance. The miniature radar energy fluctuation on badge was also used Soul Power by him as far as possible conceals.

Collects rest/breath technique Tang Wulin is quickest of middle school of Shrek Seven Monsters, because his Spiritual Strength is strongest, Spirit Abyss Realm Spiritual Strength stage, can complete to collect various Control that the rest/breath technique must well.

Quick, Tang Wulin ended a big region on searching, not any discovery. Perhaps is because the emission qualitative reason, this place does not have including the snakeworm mouse ant. Seriously is a deathly stillness.

„Entre region searching finished, had not discovered.” In the ear communications device transmits Purple One sounds/voices.

„East district searching finished, had not discovered.” Then is Yellow One.

Tang Wulin presses communications device, said: „West district searching finished, had not discovered.”

Yellow Two sounds/voices transmits, „Southern District is in searching.”

Purple One said: „Yellow One and Yellow Three, you to Southern District convergence Yellow Two and Yellow Four, after I goes to the North area to search for the element, converge with you.”

„Yes!”

As Captain, Purple One very natural has undertaken many work loads, in Battle Soul Hall this is regulation(s), everyone can very natural execution.

Tang Wulin marches forward toward Southern District fast, was quick he to rely on Yellow Rank badge Localization equipment to find Yellow Two and Yellow Four two people. Yellow One compared with him first to one step. Agility System Soul Master will be always quicker.

„It looks like, anything does not have!” Yellow One somewhat disappointedly said.

According to the stipulation of this task, needs discover that is task completes, otherwise, can only receive one-third rewards.

Yellow Two shows a faint smile, „hopes that Purple One can take to us the good news.”

„Um.” Tang Wulin nods.

At this time, the face under his mask is slightly frown, although anything had not discovered in beforehand searching, but he actually felt that some are not right. He and Evil Soul Master combat multiple, in addition the sensation is keen, imperceptibly, he can feel that in this workshop has a bewildered constriction, making him very uncomfortable.

time is not long, the form comes together fast, the Tang Wulin four people of subconsciousness make the defensive gesture, simultaneously examined badge.

Is Purple One.

Purple One moves sideways to fall before them, „not any discovery. This piece abandons the factory to be completely empty. The heat energy survey does not have reaction.”

Yellow One said: „We what to do? Bai to come?”

Purple One thinks that said: „Also can only so. Infers from the common sense, Evil Soul Master started such big terrorist attack, should already draw back was far. Will not keep nearby Heaven Dou City. Moreover here also already by military searching a time. Also has not discovered anything.”

Yellow Two helpless light sighed one. Yellow Four has not spoken, Tang Wulin has not spoken.

After Purple One thinking moment, said: „Was good, we remove.” Cannot continue to stay without any discovery here. Carries on the exploration through Battle Member badge is very reliable, the badge miniature radar has not discovered anything, even if they stay here again, same suffices to discover any thing very much difficultly. Only then returned first says again.

„Hum......” in this time, suddenly, a low wail is resounding.

Five people simultaneously reaction comes, toward that weeping sound transmits instantaneously, but the direction looks. In this jet black night, in this worn out factory, hears to have the weeping sound to transmit suddenly, the feeling that immediately after making them be in violation , the fine body hair stands erect all.

Tang Wulin is calmest one, on Devil Island, compared with many that this rarely seen matter he saw.

„What person?” Purple One shouted to clear the way fierce at the same time, turned on the own Battle Member badge miniature radar. But what made him be startled, with the miniature radar of his over 300 meters investigation range, has not discovered any Life body existence unexpectedly.

„Hum......” weeping sound as before.

Tang Wulin brow slightly wrinkle, has thought of anything indistinctly.

Four surroundings sudden weeping sounds ring out, as if some countless people in sob. The weeping sound reverberation, the surroundings factory as if becomes is not normal, a time ghost numerous, various equipment that these abandon as if lived, is swinging gently.

„Everybody was careful!” The Purple One sinking sound shouted to clear the way, simultaneously released own Martial Soul. Entire seven Soul Ring raise from his, impressively is Seven Rings Soul Saint level Elite.

Without doubt, Battle Soul Hall when arranges task is very careful, each Battle Member regarding Tang Sect, regarding Battle Soul Hall is most precious. Therefore, although is only a searching group, has provided Battle Armor Master of Seven Rings Soul Saint rank. Seven Rings Soul Saint adds on Two Word Battle Armor, making him be have in the past the ordinary Titled Douluo level strength, can handle facing most dangers easily.

Yellow One, Yellow Two and Yellow Four also respectively released Martial Soul, all was Five Rings cultivates is, Yellow Four fell back on behind, the back to Yellow Two, Yellow One and Tang Wulin in the both sides, Purple One in the front line, take shape a standard cross battlefield.

On Tang Wulin also releases Soul Ring, two yellow, three purple. Five Soul Rings seems with other three Yellow Rank Battle Member does not have what difference.

Camouflage Technique! Or is Soul Ring Camouflage Technique. Comes from Nightmare Douluo.

Soul Master distinguishes the strength most direct method is to look at the Soul Ring quantity and color of opposite party, the different colors represent the different age limits to cultivate are. Meanwhile, Soul Ring is also easiest to expose a Soul Master strong and weak.

In view of this, Nightmare Old Devil taught to Tang Wulin Camouflage Technique, fused, Control through strength of Spiritual Strength and Ruin mutually, the line of sight of distortion person. Or is makes ray of light that his own Soul Ring ray of light refracts have Transformation. Thus changes the Soul Ring color that in other people vision sees.

Although this Camouflage Technique does not have any actual combat function, but actually very practical. Especially after Tang Wulin had Child of Nature that rarely seen green-gold Soul Ring, tenancy of Camouflage Technique also had the effect.

At least he now looks like, is different from ordinary Soul Master.

„Hum......, Hum......, Hum......” weeping sound became even more sad and shrill, listened to make one be afraid in the ear.

-------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#854: Spiritual Illusion

[Say / Way] that Purple One lets somebody cool off or calm down: „Plays tricks, comes out!” At the same time was saying, his right hand to airborne one finger, does not see Soul Ring to start, one group of white light have shot up to the sky. The white light group concentrates not to be loose, straight rushes to 50 meters upper air suddenly to explode, changes into white halo, tiny particle Bi Xian who the surroundings ground shines.

Very strong Soul Power controls ability. The Tang Wulin heart shakes, really worthily is Purple Rank Battle Member. His clearly is control Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power starts, compared with using Soul Skill saves Soul Power, played the illumination the effect. It looks like the momentum is very big, but consumption Soul Power is in fact minimal.

In the ground anything does not have, in their field of vision range, even if through Purple Demon Eyes, has not looked at why not assumes the post to the place.

Purple One sinking sound track: „Follows me.” At the same time was saying, he walks toward outside quickly.

Without doubt, this strange Transformation is appear(ance) in the factory range, they must leave here first better adapting.

„Hum......, Hum......, Hum......” wail resounds once more, the surroundings air also starts becomes cloudy and cold.

When Purple One brings four Yellow Rank Battle Member are wanting to leave the factory region first, surroundings spatial immediately starts the fierce distortion, is unable to take one's bearings. All people have a dizzy feeling.

The inexplicable sense of fear and spiritual pressure immediately just like tide general to rush.

What is more important, until now, where they have not discovered the enemy.

Purple One sinking sound track: „Spiritual Illusion, may be excels at the spiritual ability enemy. It is not able to contact General Headquarters. Everybody has been careful, should not be separated.”

In this time, he was discovering that on Vine Bind the waist of own, subconscious turning head looked, sees hand signal that Tang Wulin gives.

In illusion, the enemy who after most fears separates forcefully, is lost the contact. The Tang Wulin prompt release Blue Silver Emperor, has solved this problem.

The wail is getting more and more sad and shrill, the surroundings illusion just likes galloping-horse lantern generally rotator fast, Purple One has tried attack, but his attack falls into the illusion just likes the clay ox entering the sea vanishes without the trace immediately generally.

Purple One has not acted rashly again, falls into enemy huge illusion range, this time heart sank to the valley. illusion of this range, is not ordinary Soul Master can release, this is similar to Domain general existence. But in Domain of enemy, wants to difficultly. Moreover, the opposite party obviously is pointed has sealed up their communication ability, is unable to contact General Headquarters and reinforcements.

In this time, the Purple One ear has been transmitting Tang Wulin sounds/voices, „Purple One, I am Yellow Three, I have the means to solve illusion temporarily. When I melt illusion, you lead us to use quickest speed to clash.”

„Good!” Had not inquired how Tang Wulin melts illusion, at this time, stable mentality showing of Tang Sect Battle Member without doubt.

Tang Wulin sounds/voices also resounds in several other companion ears, the next quarter, he said in a low voice: „Three, two and one!”

With three countdowns, body tightening of people as if by prior agreement. Tang Wulin body fiercely, five Soul Ring do not seem any Transformation, may in fact actually cut became Golden Dragon King four bloodline ring of light.

„Raising” earthshaking roars to resound, all has covered all wails instantaneously.

The terrifying roar is deafening, huge Golden-colored Dragon Head as if shoots up to the sky, surroundings illusion immediately is similar to air bubble general to shatter, in an instant the factory as if returned to normal.

Did not need Tang Wulin saying that Purple One jumped, simultaneously both hands entrained own Blue Silver Emperor, relied on cultivation of Seven Rings Soul Saint stage is being, led the Tang Wulin four people simultaneously to jump, flushed away toward outside fast.

Obviously, this sudden Transformation surpassed that to hide the enemy in hidden place is unexpected. Their speed incredibly fast is also incomparable, saw that must run out of the factory region.

„” A sad and shrill incomparable pitiful yell suddenly resounds. Before they will soon run out of the factory, a giant head from underground drilled suddenly.

This head reaches as high as ten meters, in the both eyes of Skeleton head braves quiet green flame, opens mouth, huge green flame has covered toward the Tang Wulin five people.

Without any feeling of ignition, but five people actually simultaneously felt that Soul transmits the fierce pricking. As if in that flash, their mind fire of Soul burnt got up.

What Little Thing is this?

The Purple One tian item roars, in eyes purple light suddenly to launch, revolved Peak Purple Demon Eyes, at the same time, Battle Armor rapid upturns since his body, a pair of Wings opened in the back, has blocked positive all green brilliance. Is protecting behind four people.

Stuffy snort along with it resounding, the Purple One footsteps staggered, his whole body is covering tan Battle Armor was contaminated by that purple brilliance unexpectedly.

Yellow Two drinks one tenderly, the pure white brilliance falls on Purple One together, „Spiritual Heal!”

Her judgment is accurate, this green brilliance without doubt is direct attack spiritual sea. Really, Purple One green flame reduced several points. However, flame of that huge Skeleton blowout actually from all directions spread to come, covers directly to them.

Yellow Four drinks one lowly, body Fourth Soul Ring Great Release of Rays of Light, at the same time circular shield turning round revolving, after shield appear(ance), is in itself covering a strange Armor piece, these Armor pieces disperse rapidly, changes into screen to protect the people.

Meanwhile, people own Battle Armor has dressed on, strengthens the defense strength.

In the Purple One mouth exudes one to roar, Sixth Soul Ring sparkle. This time, the people know finally his Martial Soul was anything.

With resonant named, a purple great hawk soars, from the sky opens pair of wings, fierce flapping forward, the purple energy storm has swept across the front hundred meters scopes instantaneously.

Purple Jade Divine Eagle, very formidable Flight Class Soul Beast. At this time Purple One displays, is own sixth Soul Skill, Divine Eagle Heavenly Dance.

Divine Eagle Heavenly Dance can release the amethyst storm, this spiritual and physical dual attack storms present range attack, can simultaneously the enemy of attack wide scope.

The purple storm and that huge Skeleton green brilliance assault in the same place, reluctantly blocked that brilliance unable to continue assault unexpectedly again on the people, cannot launch to counter-attack.

This flickers, the people understand that intercepts their enemies, the strength above them. Including the human had not seen that they fell into so the inferiority.

At this moment, in five Battle Member, calmest instead is Tang Wulin. Experienced that many on Devil Island, other did not say, only mentality, he was far the ultra average person.

Not eagerly act , when Purple One and Yellow Four they resist opposite party attack, Tang Wulin carefully is observing that huge Skeleton head.

He discovered that when that huge Skeleton emits the green brilliance, under Skeleton, as if green halo of desalination unceasingly to its direction collection in the past, looked like from all directions absorb anything was resembling.

Sees this, has affirmed the guess of Tang Wulin.

Third ring of light sparkles once more, „raising” Golden Dragon Roars resounds once again.

The green brilliance that in the Skeleton livestock spouts drags slightly, seems the trend of not having weakened, but if carefully looked that will discover, in the ground collected past pale green halo actually to vanish in frightening of Golden Dragon Roars.

At this moment, Tang Wulin fierce vertical leaps from flank, in the right hand golden light (Jin Guang) dodges, Golden Dragon Spear fell into the palm. Dazzling golden light (Jin Guang) blooms from him, the flinging arm without hesitation, Golden Dragon Spear changes into the golden-colored cold electricity to be together ordinary, center perpendicular incidence that Skeleton forehead position.

From starting Golden Dragon Roars to flinging Golden Dragon Spear, the free time who this entire process just twice blinks.

Giant Skeleton also came under the instantaneous influence of Golden Dragon Roars obviously, among the Golden Dragon Spear moment arrived at its forehead dead ahead.

green light covers along with it appear(ance), the flash when but it and Golden Dragon Spear lance point contact, the green light covers is penetrated instantaneously, Golden Dragon Spear dodges not to have.

Puncture, Bone Pierce and Devour, this is Golden Dragon Spear supplements Three Great properties. Tang Wulin Golden Dragon King Seal breaks through stage every time, will enhance stage regarding the control and understanding of Golden Dragon Spear.

Then after huge Skeleton was hurled into by Golden Dragon Spear, unexpectedly is directly vigorously led goes backward but actually. The green brilliance in mouth also spurted to airborne.

Leaps to resound the resonant dragon roar sound on airborne Tang Wulin, in the midair immediately appear(ance) together golden light avatar, Golden Dragon Soars!

---------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#855: formidable

After Tang Wulin ejects Golden Dragon Spear, immediately stimulates to movement Golden Dragon Soars, arrived at the side of that huge Skeleton head directly, the right hand has wielded outrageously.

Five Daoist priests reach seven meters dark-gold blade edge glow to dodge not to have, from one side dividing maliciously on that huge Skeleton. ear-piercing chaffing sound and to shatter sound along with it resounding. time, the green light scatters in all directions to flutter about, innumerable brilliance suddenly to launch.

The Tang Wulin both arms protect alternately before the body, the golden-colored halo gable lives in the body of own, a nose oven falls to the ground. Simultaneously a right hand move, [gold/metal] flies to shoot to return together, falls starts, establishes the distinguished merit impressively Golden Dragon Spear.

Let alone Yellow One, Yellow Two and Yellow Four, even if Purple One, staying that at this time also looked.

Tang Wulin from the eruption to chopping into pieces that Skeleton head, the entire process is just several times breathes time. Then brought Skeleton of huge puzzle to them on such to shatter. Simply is inconceivable.

„Walks quickly!” Tang Wulin gave a loud shout, shakes awoke people. The people hurry to dash about wildly to come, ran out of the factory district with him.

Strange saying that left the factory district, that terrifying pressure vanished without the trace immediately. Behind does not have the enemy to pursue unexpectedly.

Purple One waves the arms about, Tang Sect Combat Car flies to shoot, his vertical leaps, boards, the people also drill into the car(riage). The accelerator, leads their lightning to fly to shoot instantaneously generally, speeds away to go toward the old route.

In factory district.

The form reappears together quietly in the distant place, seems is already the 40-year-old middle-aged person, body glittering two yellow, two purple, three black Seven Soul Rings. The right hand is grasping handle jet black staff, staff above has green light fog take shape photosphere.

This time he, complexion seems is very ugly and gloomy.

„Broke my Biting Demon Skeleton unexpectedly. Perhaps the Tang Sect person will come quickly, could not attend to other, immediately collects all ghosts that can collect, we left immediately.”

„Yes!” surroundings flies a big piece of dense and numerous Skeleton head, in the eye pupil of each Skeleton head glittering green flame, but these Skeleton want slightly were many, their rapid flies to shoot to go toward all around.

Tang Sect Combat Car High-speed goes, people Battle Armor of flashes through with flowing light takes back vanishes in abundance to within the body does not see.

Yellow Four cannot bear surprised looks at Tang Wulin, „Yellow Three, do you achieve? A moment ago that simply was too graceful. Unexpectedly directly that Skeleton making blasting. heavens! You were too simply good.”

Tang Wulin said: „It is not I am fierce, is that Skeleton you have not imagined is so strong.”

Purple One had just completed the report to General Headquarters at this time, after leaving the factory region, the communication immediately became normal. Listened to the Tang Wulin words, he turned head, asked to Tang Wulin: „Said that is what situation?”

Tang Wulin said: „At that time these weeping sound appear(ance) time. We had not discovered that anybody's trail, this means that weeping sound is not the Life body sends out. Some time ago, I just had seen some strange situations. Therefore, I bold guess, these weeping sounds come from resentful spirit(s), resentful spirit(s) in this factory.”

„According to our task, our time carries out the task goal factory, had had the major accident, deleterious substance revelation, certainly dying many people. The person who then, these were driven to death after suffering an injustice has possibility take shape resentful spirit(s). These resentful spirit(s) should naturally vanish, but if after handling of person with high aspirations, they long-time existence will perhaps get down. For example Evil Soul Master!”

„Therefore, when we are unable to discover when weeping sound origin, I am then bold the judgment am resentful spirit(s), originally the factory died resentful spirit(s) of these people. Later illusion, should also be these resentful spirit(s) inspires.”

„Control resentful spirit(s) needs Spiritual Strength obviously, moreover is very huge Spiritual Strength. We the enemy do not know where hides. To run out of the tight encirclement, must first solve enemy's Control to resentful spirit(s), therefore I used that sounds/voices Soul Skill, in the roaring sound, the sound wave added on spiritual dual to frighten really to let resentful spirit(s) appear(ance) short out-of-control, therefore we can run out outward. Then comes that huge Skeleton head, the itself attack strength is very strong, but I noted at that time, had many halo collections under it in the past, frightened our resentful spirit(s) to be very similar to before. Therefore, I guessed again that the energy source of that giant Skeleton head is resentful spirit(s) in factory. If I guessed that correct, then, hides the enemy in hidden place is very possible not to have us to imagine I formidable, he borrowed resentful spirit(s) in factory, will therefore become that strong.”

Here, Tang Wulin has stopped, „is in itself not strong, Skeleton that he released naturally likely had the flaw in the defense aspect. I used this to fire in bursts the attack, after interrupted first resentful spirit(s) input has ruined it. When we clash later not to have pursuing troops appear(ance), should verify my guess. Hides the enemy in hidden place is not truly formidable, beside the factory, he not necessarily is our matches.”

Listened to Tang Wulin analysis, in Tang Sect Combat Car suddenly became peaceful.

Long time, drives Purple One to say slowly that „really what you enter with us is a factory?” When said these words, in his sounds/voices some distinct anguished flavors.

He is this line of Captain, is, when facing the danger, he actually cannot discover that the enemy genuine goal and assessed at that time the situation. If were not Tang Wulin has given the correct judgment, and at crucial moments strove to turn the tide. They likely fell into there.

Yellow One, Yellow Two and Yellow Four also likely are looked that Monster looks at Tang Wulin generally.

fighting strength is an aspect, this analysis ability was really too fearful.

Tang Wulin scratches the head, in the heart actually somewhat thinks otherwise, he thought these that own makes are very normal! Will these companions so be why surprised?

His of course does not know, passed through Devil Island after a series of teaches especially, he became with before is different, power of observation and adapting ability, degree of firmness wait / etc.. All stage of far ultra average person, even if Tang Sect Battle Member is also same. Towering that reveals accidentally, sufficiently shocked companion.

After Tang Sect Combat Car enters the urban district, stopped, waits for subsidiary troops' arrival. time is not long, appear(ance) that two Black Rank Battle Member are quietly.

They and Purple One exchanged simply, Purple One said the judgment of Tang Wulin, he has not snatched the merit, narrated then situation completely realistically.

Two Black Rank Battle Member applauses after looking at Tang Wulin, immediately vanishes in the dim light of night.

„Why do we go now? Purple One.” Yellow One asked to Purple One.

Purple One said: „Here waits. After waiting for the result to come out, returns again. Also is good to determine whether we have completed task. Everybody tired has been able rest a while in the car(riage), I am responsible for the value defending.”

He in shocking in Tang Wulin ability simultaneously, in the heart also fills guilty. If not striving to turn the tide of Tang Wulin. Perhaps this time they lost in a big way . Moreover the aspect of likely being annihilated. If so, as the team leader, he can hardly absolve.

Tang Wulin arrives at side Purple One, wanted to say anything, Purple One actually shook the head to him, „was all right, did not need to comfort me. I rejoice very much your such teammate. Also realized that on resisting the Evil Soul Master path, we have are insufficient. After going back, I will try hard to make up insufficient these.”

Tang Wulin compares the thumb to him, worthily is Battle Member!

Today's situation Purple One deals with not the ideal reason to be various, one is too sudden, another is did not know about Evil Soul Master. In addition itself insufficiently calm. Is lacks resists Evil Soul Master experience.

#856: Pavilion Master direction

But these do not affect his outstanding, resists Evil Soul Master to have heavy responsibilities, the performance of Tang Wulin to him is not the small stimulation, so long as is also living, Battle Member certainly unceasingly will progress.

Yellow One, Yellow Two and Yellow Four also walked, expressed gratitude to Tang Wulin.

Factory that side situation is unknown, the thoughts that everybody has not rested, can only wait for here silently. To quick dawn, two Black Rank Battle Member returned, has brought the news.

Evil Soul Master in factory all left, the judgment of Tang Wulin is correct. There Evil Soul Master has truly used resentful spirit(s) in factory. Meanwhile, the place bottom deep place under factory also has a altar. From the service condition in altar. The people who not only resentful spirit(s) in factory by sacrificed and refined, in this terrorist attack died, many Soul were also guided the past to perform sacrificed and refined by these Evil Soul Master through the altar.

This news made the people heart heavy, in the meantime, two Black Rank Battle Member also announced that their task completed.

In view of the fact that in task completion process the prominent manifestation of Tang Wulin, the complete reward of this task, Tang Wulin is alone half, other surplus four person differences.

This does not have the means to modestly decline, higher authority Battle Member has decided that the subordinate can only comply with. Moreover, the Purple One four people also feel a heartfelt admiration.

This task is the double several points, in addition was alone half, Tang Wulin absolutely is the harvest is rich. However, this motion has also cast a shadow in his heart, because of his clear seeing, wildness of Holy Spirit Cult.

By the Federation strength, is at a loss to Holy Spirit Cult unexpectedly, the attack had such long time. Unexpectedly had not found Holy Spirit Cult this motion the main force. This time with great difficulty some clues, but Evil Soul Master was withdraws calmly. If nobody helps them, that nobody believes absolutely. The Holy Spirit Cult internal channel absolutely is quite fearful.

Purple One opens Tang Sect Combat Car to return to Shrek City, has handed over task, after receiving accumulated points, this temporary Squad also along with it dismissal.

Tang Wulin has not received task again, but returned to Academy directly. First went back to bring back the own thing to say again. Then he also plans to go to Heaven Dou City, goes to Senior Teacher there.

This time completes task time, he has known, that side Blacksmith Association has not received affect of large explosion, is unfortunate was lucky.

Shrek Academy all as before, Tang Wulin returns to Inner Court, first arrives on Sea God Island, report.

Has not waited for him to mount Sea God Island, he surprised seeing, on the Sea God Island shore is standing a person.

white-clothed, crosses the hands behind the back to stand, on the handsome face is leading light cold meaning, sees Tang Wulin to come, has not revealed the surprised color, instead beckons toward him.

Tang Wulin tip of the toe on water surface, Control personal appearance steady falling in shore, then immediately respectful bows to salute, „Old Yun.”

Yes, this in shore is not others, is Shrek Academy Present Generation Sea God Pavilion Pavilion Master, Sky Raising Douluo Yun Ming.

Yun Ming nods the head to him slightly, „you come with me.” Then, turns around to walk toward Sea God Island.

Tang Wulin hurries to follow.

The surface looks that Yun Ming as if has not walked quickly, but Tang Wulin actually running that wants All-Out to go to can follow his step.

Sea God Island is not too big, the time of a while, Tang Wulin arrived at Sea God Pavilion with him.

Enters Sea God Pavilion, Yun Ming has not stayed in the hall, but steps onto the staircase. Tang Wulin follows somewhat curiously in him behind, looks at surroundings all.

Regarding Sea God Pavilion, he cannot say absolutely familiar, but to here curiosity is actually many. This seems the area is not too big, leans on the log cabin that on Golden Tree constructs, is on entire Douluo Continent one of the most authoritarian places!

Yun Ming brings Tang Wulin to arrive at Sea God Pavilion Third Layer, enters in a spacious room.

In the room anything decorates does not have, but has two rush cushions in the ground.

Yun Ming own sat down on inner rush cushion, has referred to the opposite rush cushion, „sat.”

Tang Wulin sits down according to the word, in heart surprised at the same time , is very curious. Was Old Yun formerly was waiting for me in the shore?

Regarding Yun Ming knows that he comes back him not to be accidental, takes cultivation of Old Yun as, so long as perhaps he steps into Shrek City that to flicker, Old Yun can know.

„Has the Na'er news?” The Yun Ming sinking sound asked.

The Tang Wulin heart slightly shocked, is actually smiling bitterly shaking the head, Na'er or Gu Yue, a news does not have!

Yun Ming said suddenly: „Your take shape Soul Power vortex?”

Tang Wulin visits him surprisedly, then nodded. Although he has not been definitely able to understand Yun Ming that stage, but can see own already take shape Soul Power vortex, this is the what kind eyesight, as if the body of own can be completely understood by his look.

Yun Ming brow slightly pressed, seems pondering anything.

Enough after long time, once more opens the mouth saying: „Can have the issue?”

Tang Wulin shook the head, „had narrated with Teacher(s) is the same, Soul Power vortex is very normal, but why I will not know in this rank on appear(ance) Soul Power vortex. As if before should be Seven Rings, appear(ance).”

Yun Ming said: „Soul Power vortex in fact and rank irrelevant, is only related with the Soul Power congealing thick degree. After Soul Power compresses to the certain extent, because itself more and more close solid state, but pure solid state Soul Power is actually nonexistent, Soul Power that therefore, this being approximate in solid state must by special situation existence, that revolves.”

„Simply speaking, if you have one cup of very thick chocolate, when you do not go to manage it, makes its natural places there, it quick on condense into pieces, or is one cup of thick saltwater, you do not go to manage it, quick will have crystals settles down below. However, when your unceasing carries on stirring to them, lets they are in revolving throughout time, they can maintain at the liquid condition. But such liquid has high potency at the same time is even.”

„Soul Power is also so, after your Soul Power is the certain extent, oneself naturally will adjust Soul Power, simultaneously will be guiding their take shape vortex. This is a Soul Power cultivate process naturally. Knows that the Soul Nucleus formation has the qualitative change. Soul Power vortex itself has very strong attraction, attracts Soul Power of your within the body, has very strong hauling to outside Heaven and Earth Elementary Forces, making your cultivate be able to be twice the result with half the effort. Takes your Five Rings to cultivate to can take shape Soul Power vortex be very rarely. In the past, I am 59th Rank time take shape. Later, is almost the same to 60th Rank 60th Rank to 70th Rank cultivate speed and 50th Rank.”

Listened to Yun Ming these words, Tang Wulin to Soul Power vortex immediately some brand-new understanding, moreover he discovered with amazement that this Sea God Pavilion Master Old Yun is directing own unexpectedly. Is he 59th Rank take shape Soul Power vortex? That said that can also surpass him in this aspect own?

Although in heart surprised, all that but Tang Wulin said Yun Ming record firmly sincerely, this may be is honored as now the direction of world first person! overwhelming majority Soul Master is for a lifetime impossible to have such opportunity.

Yun Ming visited him to perceive, continued saying: „Then you cultivate routinely and that's the end, has Soul Power vortex to make foundation, your cultivation for quick that can promote. If there is any issue, can come Sea God Pavilion to look for me.”

„Yes. Thank You (xiexie) Old Yun.” Tang Wulin respectful saying.

Yun Ming look somewhat complex visits him, „I am a very perceptual person, therefore, because of the Na'er matter, I do not like you.”

Tang Wulin stares, but he also can only respond with smiles bitterly. Regarding Na'er, in his own heart has been full of feeling sorry?

Yun Ming continues saying: „But, stemming from is Academy considered that I should not such do. This time, you are very good because of the Devil Island military training effect. I obtained the news that that side has spread. Your result has even surpassed overwhelming majority older generation(s).”

Tang Wulin has not spoken, is this is praising me?

Yun Ming has stopped, seems is considering any matter, but he has not set firm resolve eventually, beckoned with the hand, said: „You go.”

„Yes.” Tang Wulin hurries to stand up, salutes after Yun Ming once more, turns around to depart.

Looks the back that he leaves, Yun Ming sighs one lightly, has rubbed the brow of own.

One side of room door shoves open, Holy Spirit Douluo Ya Li walked from inside, she arrives at behind Yun Ming, gently rubs to pinch the shoulder for him.

„Can't decide? This child is very outstanding, temperament or ability, endure greatly duty.”

Yun Ming shook the head, „I do not like him. Has a look again.”

Ya Li sighed one lightly, „do not push him was too far!”

-----------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. Since thank everybody continuously support.

#857: Ancestral Master selection and broadcast

On the Yun Ming face reveals a light smile, „this I was not worried, not only he Academy Shrek Seven Monsters, is Tang Sect Battle Member. My this time regulation(s) that is to violate Academy sets, is increasing some Test to him. Plans the conference to inform, supplements Tang Wulin is to prepare Sea God Pavilion Ancient. However, the news must to the outside surface, including to Tang Wulin own.”

„Yes!”

Yun Ming stands up, holds on wife's hand, „actually, I very much will also anticipate to visit him also to be able in the future Creation what kind of miracle. All previous Sea God Pavilion Master must experience innumerable wheting to shoulder the heavy responsibility finally.”

Ya Li shows a faint smile, „I like this child very much, I believe him certainly. According to Academy regulation(s), can complete Devil Island completely Test, can become Sea God Pavilion Ancient. way (of life) that if can break the record completes Test, then, is the next generation Sea God Pavilion Master successor. His result is obvious to all.”

Yun Ming shows a faint smile, „I have discretion.”

Left Sea God Pavilion, Tang Wulin somewhat is bewildered, Sea God Pavilion Master Old Yun arrives at shore edge joint own personally, to direct own how many Soul Power vortex the methods of cultivate? He can feel that Yun Ming somewhat starts to speak but hesitates, but does not know that actually he must say anything.

However, Old Yun as if accepted own to a certain extent, this finally is a good deed.

Tang Wulin returned to the own dwelling first, brings the thing of own depositing on the body, then arrives at the log cabin that Scarlet Dragon Douluo Zhuo Shi lived.

„Ancestral Master.”

Zhuo Shi is exposing to the sun Sun in the courtyard, had repaired to this is, has not needed frequently cultivate, more actually senses Heaven and Earth, needs the instantaneous sudden enlightenment to make the breakthrough to be possible.

Zhuo Shi visits him to arrive, is not surprised, shows a faint smile, said: „Did Pavilion Master look for you?”

Tang Wulin curious [say / way]: „Did you know?”

Zhuo Shi said with a smile: „He looks for you are very normal matter. Come, sits the little while to Ancestral Master here.” At the same time was saying, he has referred to own position.

Tang Wulin arrives at side Zhuo Shi to sit down, Zhuo Shi said: „Talks about your trip of experiences.” Then, he has closed both eyes.

It is not good to conceal to Ancestral Master Tang Wulin of course anything, immediately, he spoke the companion trip of bitter experiences of own and in detail. From being called as Soul Guidance High-speed Train has an accident, facing formidable Evil Soul Master, arrived again afterward arrived at North Sea City as well as said in all line on Devil Island having in detail. Had not mentioned finally own comes back to participate has the Battle Member motion about Tang Sect.

Zhuo Shi has closed one's eyes to listen to him to narrate, said finally until him, again opening eyes pupil.

Sighed one lightly, Zhuo Shi said: „The Continent peace as if arrived at the end. Our generation was old, in the future changed Continent, to protect Continent task is the matters of your young people.”

Tang Wulin visits him surprisedly, „is Ancestral Master, so really serious?”

Zhuo Shi sinking sound track: „Will only think you are more serious . The Federation high level had some problems, some people of flagrant starts started the Federation interior battle. Superficially, Federation is uneventful, but in fact, the internal struggle was intense. But this Heaven Dou City matter, is outside one time of internal struggle manifests. Mo Wu as Federation Member of Parliament, he is the important successor who a clique trains, actually falls in this Holy Spirit Cult the lower part of the body of surprise attack, this has caused a Federation internal contradictions about intensification. Which side politician although cannot reach an agreement and Holy Spirit Cult has the relations. But what without a doubt is, good that such Holy Spirit Cult can hide, Federation actually takes Evil Soul Master Sect not to have the means that above does not have protective umbrella this is impossible.”

„Tumultuous times as if soon appear(ance), not only Federation had problems, I heard, Spirit Transferring Pagoda also has issue appear(ance). Even that side Star Luo Empire, the Green Skeleton organization as if obtained anything to support, promoted with the Star Luo Empire official war continually. As if entire Douluo Star becomes is not peaceful.”

The Tang Wulin brain is rotating unceasingly, pondering. But, he discovered that own is confused, since all, he has been only a Shrek Academy student, too had not understood the Continent situation that what are more is only assiduous cultivate.

Zhuo Shi said: „You have not needed to think now many, genuine involves in this, but must wait till you to graduate after Inner Court. However, you remember, is the head of Shrek Academy this generation of Shrek Seven Monsters, your Duty-bound Responsibility. Since Shrek Academy has been neutral, but this aims at the Continent peace period. Once appear(ance) might subvert Continent, brings the fatal threat to the general publics existence, Academy also same decisive act . Do you understand my meaning?”

Tang Wulin nods the head slightly, without a doubt, Shrek Academy counts Ten-thousand Years inheritance, has the ingrained status on Douluo Continent, the Academy outstanding graduating cadets have almost in the major influences, once Academy calls from a high place, strength that can summon absolutely is very fearful.

Zhuo Shi lifts the hand to hold down the shoulder of Tang Wulin, „, the pressure will be getting bigger and bigger, the tour of this Devil Island you will meet genuine to understand to your advantage in the future. I hope that you can achieve the pressure to be bigger, power to be bigger. Come, you recently cultivate some issues, said including the Golden Dragon Nine Styles issue.”

Tang Wulin has treated in the Zhuo Shi log cabin in the evening, after the direction of Zhuo Shi, recently appear(ance) some issues completely will be solved.

In the evening he kept on Sea God Island.

He lives, in Gu Yue leaves in his log cabin, sits in the bedside, looks at the out of the window bright moonlight, in the mind reappears this that tender face, as if can feel her flavor.

Front silver dragon scales under shining of moonlight, is reflecting the gentle brilliance, that night, sleepless.

The second day very early in the morning, Tang Wulin left Academy, yesterday he had said to Zhuo Shi, he will arrive at Heaven Dou City one month, follows Divine Craftsman Zhen Hua to continue to study forging.

His forging level arrived at very important bottleneck now, once he can complete Soul Refinement, will then enter another realm in the forging aspect, as now forging youngest 6th Rank Blacksmith, once breaks through, he has the infinite possibility in the forging aspect.

Left Academy, Tang Wulin had not gone to the Soul Guidance High-speed Train station to ride Soul Guidance Train. He really has feared to Soul Guidance Train now, particularly has feared from Shrek City to Heaven Dou City this. On this Train, he does not know that has had many matters. For own, for the safety of others other passengers, he decided that own does not sit Soul Guidance Train to be quite good.

Arrived at Tang Sect, Battle Soul Hall, Tang Wulin has exchanged bright Tang Sect Combat Car with own accumulated points directly.

On that day after riding Combat Car, he is also has only one in mind to this Little Thing, speed did not say quickly, and was stable. Only is a pity does not have privilege, various facility also far ultra ordinary vehicles that but so, on the vehicle provides.

As for his Mecha, has taken carry back, later promoted on. But Mecha is different from the automobile, control of Federation to Mecha is strict, especially now is very special period.

Tang Wulin Battle Member accumulated points are quite many, exchanges Tang Sect Combat Car also some surplus. Combat Car had also been admitted in own storage ring by him. Went out to release.

Different with Tang Sect Combat Car that day rode, what this exchange was one has three rows of seats, can most ride Tang Sect Combat Car of eight people, speed did not have on that day that rapidness, but the cross-country performance was actually much better.

The Shrek Seven Monsters seven people, many seat, naturally leave her......

-----------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#858: wisdom presses the disturbance

Drives to start off, the Tang Sect Combat Car camouflage system opens, vehicles surface take shape dark blue paint surface, seems like black under the gloomy ray, only then under the sunlight, will present for sapphire generally profound luster. This blue was called the water silicon metahewettite to be blue by Tang Sect, withdraws from a mineral substance. Itself anti-corrosive, but can also increase the metal(s) degree of hardness. Some Mecha will also choose this material quality as the exterior painting.

Tang Sect Combat Car under driving of Tang Wulin on the High-speed road, went in the Heaven Dou City direction with lightning speed once more.

own the feeling of driving and going by car is also different, Tang Wulin discovered that this Tang Sect Combat Car opened not to say very steadily, moreover controlled extremely good, can achieve a condition of person car(riage) body very much easily.

Although speed is quick, but actually very much has confidence. Has only used less than two hours of time, the Heaven Dou City guidepost already was by far in sight.

Does not know that Battle Soul Hall does have to hold these Holy Spirit Cult Evil Soul Master. The bitter experience of that worn out factory made the Tang Wulin heart heavy. More is understands to Holy Spirit Cult profoundly, more can feel them to the society's harm to Federation. These fellows, must sooner eradicate are really good!

Has gotten down the High-speed road, Tang Wulin familiar turning the main road, expunges to the Heaven Dou City urban district direction. Was similar to the day before yesterday situation, by path many disaster victims, but could see that they obtained the official placement, the quantity reduced.

Perhaps the reconstruction must carry on very for a long time, after all destruction serious of that moreover this time matter nature is extremely bad. Thinks that should also ignite in entire Federation to the heart of Holy Spirit Cult sharing a common hatred.

At the same time is thinking, Tang Wulin drives to enter in the urban district, the order in urban district is good, was only the police vehicle quantity of patrol obviously are much more than past.

Police vehicle really useful, will not be attacked. In the Tang Wulin heart sighed one darkly, but there are always to compare not to have, at least can make the people steadfaster.

Heaven Dou City Blacksmith Association is Blacksmith Association General Headquarters, Tang Wulin arrives at the nearby the car(riage), turns in a small lane to stop, gets out, receives the car(riage) with storage ring, then walks toward Blacksmith Association.

Just now gets to the entrance, he stopped the footsteps, is not he does not want to go, but is Blacksmith Association large door is stopped up at this time unexpectedly watertight.

„Hands over the murderer, hands over the murderer!” The entrance, at least over a thousand people stop up there, call of madness. Some agitated people also take the stone to throw toward Blacksmith Association.

Before Association gate, has pulled up yellow line, inside has the police to keep the order, but is very obvious, they somewhat could not block the agitated people.

Tang Wulin surprised asked people in surrounding to ask knows, the trouble of Blacksmith Association was big.

Demonstrated according to the investigation monitoring, before the Heaven Dou City bitter experience attacks, these detonate in the Fixed Installed Soul Guidance Artillery Shell terrifying member, the place that at least several finally go is Blacksmith Association.

Heaven Dou City such Metropolis, the Soul Guidance monitor is almost found in the main block. Therefore sees very clearly.

Although currently did not have any evidence to show that Blacksmith Association is related with Holy Spirit Cult, but, these videos were revealed by the person with high aspirations. The Heaven Dou City excited people looked like found immediately proclaimed the drain port to be common, looked for Blacksmith Association.

Blacksmith Association General Headquarters had been besieged good several days, now can only be large door shuts tightly. Without a doubt, the prestige of this matter to Blacksmith Association has had the enormous attack.

The Tang Wulin brow is tight, he believes to Senior Teacher absolutely. Blacksmith Association is how possible to have relation with Evil Soul Master. Moreover, is monitoring video recording easily known by the people? At least before not having the findings should not put.

The calm judgment, this people frame Blacksmith Association obviously intentionally!

Tang Wulin still clearly remembers, the assassination of that Senior Teacher bitter experience. Without a doubt, that assassination should be related with Holy Spirit Cult. As Continent only Divine Craftsman, without a doubt, Senior Teacher in the situation , by Holy Spirit Cult not being used, absolutely is their eye-sores and thorns in the side, is then quick except it.

The people mostly are follow, especially thoses lost family member's people, wanting Control to live in the mood not to be truly simple. Especially now the Heaven Dou City administration building is blown up directly, almost all Advanced city Administrative officials are annihilated, the newly arrived officials handled this accident to be badly battered, who had the thoughts to help Blacksmith Association clarify!

In the situations of these issues, the pressure that Blacksmith Association bears will be getting bigger and bigger.

To be what to do good? In the Tang Wulin eye is revealing the color of thinking, since own came, has faced this issue. If that wants the means to help Senior Teacher.

He does not have to enter Blacksmith Association eagerly, but one side falls back on the common corner, is observing silently.

The people that here gathers have over a thousand fully, moreover is agitated, for a very long time does not go. It seems causes trouble not only also a day. That side Blacksmith Association, many glasses were destroyed.

Is the goal that then, they cause trouble what?

To handle a matter, first wants calm analysis, this is Lazy Old Devil gives Tang Wulin. His original words are, in this world the most intelligent people is a dead beat, because only then the dead beat will find out these to save the method of time and work.

Comes across the matter, doing things recklessly processes, can only be wastes time and energy, only then looks for the accurate goal, strikes to subdue, can time-saving reduce effort, has many time to handle other matters, for example, has a long lazy sleep.

Without doubt, Tang Wulin does not approve regarding the Lazy Old Devil words completely, the method of but regarding him working has actually studied.

Before having traded, his perhaps really anything means that only cannot be go in look for Senior Teacher first, asks the Blacksmith Association present situation.

But this time he, actually compared with initially calm many, stand in the common place, the vision the people that causes trouble from these 11 has swept.

Relies on Spirit Abyss Realm spiritual to cultivate is, very much easily he can observe a person unusual is careful. What he first does is the resolution, has Soul Master separately in the crowd.

Answer negative, in the people of causing trouble, Soul Master does not have, is the average person.

But he has not given up in light of this, but continues carefully to observe. About after dozen minutes, Tang Wulin discovered that in people that these cause trouble, is very distributing several leaders evenly.

Whenever the people clamored some stops that and made time, they can always voice at the right moment, raised one once more *.

Altogether 16 such people, they very even branch in these over a thousand people of regions. Tang Wulin also discovered through the careful observation that on these person of ears is bringing communications device, is very advanced miniature communications device.

This Little Thing value Tang Wulin is very clear, at least will not be the average person can afford or will buy.

In summary, perhaps these characteristics put out one to come unable alone to prove anything, but if gathers in the same place, can prove a lot.

Let alone, Tang Wulin did not need the extremely detailed evidence.

Turns around to depart. Moves toward by the street gloomy place.

„Hands over the murderer, punishes Blacksmith Association!” The people are shouting loud.

„Blacksmith Association Association President comes out, gives us a confession!”

„The Blacksmith Association people should on the guilotine. Your these damn Evil Soul Master......”

Various types cursed angrily the sound continuously.

At this moment, suddenly, the form cuts into the crowd together like lightning. His appear(ance) was really too quick, invisible strength released from him, the place visited, the people were pushed all one side.

yellow cape and yellow mask. The front is bringing Tang Sect Yellow Rank Battle Member badge.

Lifts the hand, he held one to yell the ominous people.

Does not wait for people reaction to come, he bellows suddenly, „where runs!” At the same time was saying, his Soul Ring ray of light shine in abundance, enough eight, two yellow, two purple, four black. The extremely powerful imposing manner erupts from the body along with it.

Huge blue-gold Vine howl just like Mighty Dragon generally, first shoots up to the sky, then drills into the crowd, goal 11 Bind that will see formerly solidity.

Although people over a thousand, but at this time actually because the shock loses one's voice to call out in alarm.

„Tang Sect Battle Soul Hall arrests the Evil Soul Master Holy Spirit Cult scoundrel, everybody does not use startled.” In Tang Wulin sounds/voices contained some Golden Dragon Roars spiritual deterrent effects, one people called out in alarm the sound pressure.

Inside police also fast ran, when but they see dressing up and front of Tang Wulin Battle Member badge as well as Soul Ring, stops the footsteps, has not approached again.

---------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#859: Six big Elite

Although Continent Soul Guidance Technology highly is now developed, the Soul Master status had been inferior before Ten-thousand Years, was so lofty. But on Douluo Continent, Soul Master is noblest profession, this point has not changed after all.

Everyone awakens Martial Soul when six years old, all the hope and was praying own can become Soul Master. Most people turn over to disappointedly, but in their mind, the Soul Master status stands one's ground steadfastly throughout.

When side them, sees with one's own eyes Eight Rings Soul Douluo stage Soul Master appear(ance), when feels his formidable strength and dignity, time besides feeling to be startled, fear, what are more is curious and frantic.

Must know, High Rank Soul Master is not easy to see! This is Eight Rings Soul Douluo, in entire Continent Soul Master can arrange on number existence. Moreover, at present this Soul Master the great strength of strength, not only Soul Douluo is so simple, is he Tang Sect person, Tang Sect Battle Member?

Tang Sect Battle Soul Hall, is not everyone knows, as long as is person who knows, is clear, Federation War God Temple, Tang Sect Battle Soul Hall, this is on Continent the illustrious Soul Master association, the overall strength is quite formidable.

Moreover Twenty-thousand Years of Tang Sect able to move unhindered on Continent, has the extremely positive status, the initial Tang Sect ancestor, one generation of person outstanding Tang San, are now Spirit Transferring Pagoda founder Ice Spirit Douluo Huo Yuhao, all stems from Tang Sect.

Compares in Soul Master, Tang Sect has some mysterious nature and noble feelings. Therefore, when Tang Wulin indicates the status, the resentfulness of people innermost feelings these cause trouble turned into the complex mood.

„Why you and you catch me. We are look for Blacksmith Association to ask for an explanation. Even if you are the Tang Sect person, you cannot falsely accuse the good person.” Was stressed that person in hand also to try to argue by Tang Wulin.

„He is Blacksmith Association sends radically. Everybody do not believe him.” Compared with far place, by Blue Silver Emperor Bind the scoundrel is also clamors.

Tang Wulin sneers, „why I told you to catch you quickly. First, I must ask everybody, anyone of you knows the person who in my hand grabs.”

Although these several people were clamoring, but how Tang Wulin to be dazzling by Eight Soul Rings that Camouflage Technique released, people are not excited.

Stands said in Tang Wulin side not far away people: „Did not know. A little unfamiliar.”

Tang Wulin sinking sound track: „These several people, a moment ago made ominously. Heaven Dou City met with the disaster, is the times of ten thousand numerous disaster relief, they actually instigate everybody to come to cause trouble. Right, scoundrel who these launch the attack truly once had been to Blacksmith Association, but everybody thinks calmly that they come Blacksmith Association to mean they are the Blacksmith Association people? The scoundrel does not know that has to monitor this type of thing in our Heaven Dou City? We push toward front again, supposed that these scoundrels have been to the dining room, has lived in Hotel, the dining room and Hotel are their connivances. Perhaps everybody also has to do business, where if they have been to your, means you and they are one group?”

These people who „I hold, incite everybody mood intentionally, in this need the moment that works as one resisting natural calamities difficultly, to rebuild one's homeland. What mentality are they such will do?”

At the same time was saying, Tang Wulin holds in that person of ear to pinch in the own hand, uncovers miniature communications device to come, „everybody has a look, this is anything, this is miniature communications device, is not very expensive, 30,000 federation coin(s) one sets. Moreover this type is the Advanced model, anti-jamming ability is very good, should add in 50,000 to 60,000 federation coin(s). Excuse me, as an average person, you needs this type of thing? You can begin personally, in these person of ears that since I grasp looks, look has this communications device.”

The people that also the public sentiment was roused to action become somewhat are immediately noisy, some busybodies had found communications device from these person of ears quickly, and has lifted up high high.

„Has, has, seems is the same.”

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, the general situation has decided.

„They instigate everybody to come to cause trouble, his heart may execute, in my opinion, they most have the possibility and scoundrel are one group. Then, I give the police them, I believe that after they carry on the careful interrogation, certainly will have the result. Heaven Dou City was hit by a such serious disaster, I know that everybody is very sad, but for this reason, we should not make the kissing painful enmity quick matter of!”

At the same time was saying, Tang Wulin restrains Soul Ring, simultaneously beckons toward the police, with the help of people, the person of looking ashen gathered these several.

„, I am not a scoundrel, I am not a scoundrel. Some people to me money, let me these words, leading everybody to cause trouble.” A willpower not firm rioter collapsed finally.

Everyone knows that what if was determined as this terrorist attack scoundrel to be going to face is anything.

A person collapses, immediately, other people also start willpower to become less crowded. The surroundings people are in an uproar.

The matter developed this degree, the Tang Wulin goal has also achieved, while the police handled this matter time, he withdrew from the crowd quietly, from one side bypassed, arrived at the Blacksmith Association back door directly, simultaneously has dialed the Zhen Hua telephone.

The telephone sound gets up, the ear hears the Zhen Hua frank laughter, „knows that is your boy, when learned camouflage, looks you released Eight Soul Rings time, but also really frightened me to jump.”

„? You know that I came!” Tang Wulin surprised [say / way].

Zhen Hua said with a smile: „Your this boy! Good, first came to say again. I have made the human meet you.”

The free time who spoken, the back door opens, inside goes out of the person who seems somewhat familiar actually cannot name the character. Tang Wulin hurried.

In his heart some surprise, listen to sounds/voices from communications device slightly, the Senior Teacher mood is not as if bad! Outside noisily becomes this, what reaction doesn't he have? This mentality may really be good.

Rides the elevator, arrives at the Zhen Hua location floor directly. Enters the Zhen Hua office, Tang Wulin had a scare.

In the Divine Craftsman Zhen Hua office may, not only a person, six people, besides Zhen Hua, Tang Wulin are quite familiar, that is his another Teacher(s), Innate Body Sect Sect Master Mu Ye.

Sees Tang Wulin to walk, Mu Ye cannot bear ridicule saying: „Your this brat, comes back to go bad our good deeds. Visits you to release Blue Silver Grass, I have not recognized you to come.”

„Teacher(s), Senior Teacher.” Tang Wulin somewhat cannot feel the brains.

Besides these two, moreover four person two male two females of sitting, seem are the appearances of middle-aged person.

And a middle-aged person somewhat helpless [say / way]: „Good fishing motion, has not then incurred.”

Fishing moves, Tang Wulin understands suddenly that surprised [say / way]: „These people, below causes trouble, is you arranges?”

Zhen Hua loses says with a smile: „That, we are actually not bored. But is thwarts that's all. Holy Spirit Cult asked some average people to cause trouble, the goal nothing but directed me, after I exited, found the way to attack me again. But can be sent to sneak attack my person, thinks in Holy Spirit Cult can some status. Our is coordinating them to act in a play. When waits for the people to rush to our large door mouth, even bursts, is I should exit. Was makes your boy destroying. Others see a Soul Douluo rank Soul Master appear(ance), even to cope with me, definitely will change the plan.”

--------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#860: Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo

Listened to the Zhen Hua words, a Tang Wulin face forced smile, this ginger is old spicy! The own book thinks processing was very attractive, has not actually thought that this is Senior Teacher they give a snare under Holy Spirit Cult cloth.

On the Zhen Hua face smiling face restraining, „this time matter is serious. Has not thought really that Holy Spirit Cult these people are unexpectedly bold to this degree. Wulin, does your boy this go is such long time, how Academy sends military training that you go to?”

Tang Wulin works as these many people not to say many, is only fluent: „Also very has the harvest. This just did not come back to come to see you.”

Zhen Hua nodded, „comes, I give you to introduce.” At the same time was saying, he points at the opposite two middle-aged female saying: „These two from War God Temple, are War God Temple Present Generation War God.”

Tang Wulin has not known nothing regarding War God Temple now, War God Temple altogether 18 War God, this is War God Temple mainstay existence. 18 War God all are Titled Douluo rank Elite. Directly by the designation of Federation Parliament. It is said above 18 War God, War God Temple also has the apex strength, as for is any Tang Wulin is not clear.

Two middle-aged female look does not have any specially outstanding place.

Under the introduction of Zhen Hua, Tang Wulin knew that their called Tang Liyue, called Zhu Xuan.

Tang Liyue title Ice Moon, Zhu Xuan title Dawn Cat. Truly is two Titled Douluo.

Zhen Hua aims at a middle-aged person again, said: „This came from Spirit Transferring Pagoda Heavenly Saint Douluo Xu Shengqun.” Introduced this time, Zhen Hua obviously compared with before introduce that two War God Temple female War God want serious many.

Tang Wulin hurries saying: „Your Excellency hello.”

Xu Shengqun has a relish looks at Tang Wulin, nodded to him.

Zhen Hua said with a smile: „Brother Xu is now one of the Spirit Transferring Pagoda Four Great Spirit Transferring Envoys.”

The Tang Wulin heart shakes, regarding Spirit Transferring Pagoda he War God Temple understanding were more , the organization of Spirit Transferring Pagoda is very strict.

At first, Federation Parliament establishes, actually has profited from the Spirit Transferring Pagoda high-level pattern.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda has 36 elders, initial time holds an office by all influence. But on Continent is getting more and more important along with the status of development and Spirit Transferring Pagoda of time. Gradually, Spirit Transferring Pagoda own take shape an independent individual.

For all this, present Spirit Transferring Pagoda as before is the discussing official business group comprised of 36 elders handles the important matter.

Above discussing official business group, several high levels, includes Spirit Transferring Pagoda Pagoda Master, two Vice Pagoda Master as well as Four Spirit Transferring Envoys . This complete 42 people, are all high levels of Spirit Transferring Pagoda organization.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda on the other hand is a very democratic organization, even if Pagoda Master cannot act in a self-serving manner, but Pagoda Master has a vote veto, this point is fiercest. Vice Pagoda Master and Spirit Transferring Envoy(s) everyone has two tickets voting rights, is next to the Pagoda Master three tickets. Each discussing official business group elders have a ticket. Whenever there is the important matter must decide, is the time of collective voting.

Two Vice Pagoda Master and Four Great Spirit Transferring Envoys must have the enormous contribution to be elected regarding the Spirit Transferring Pagoda organization besides itself, what is more important, they are representing the Spirit Transferring Pagoda peak strength. At least is also Super Rank Douluo above stage existence.

In other words, front Heavenly Saint Douluo Xu Shengqun, purely in cultivation for on, but must surpass Innate Body Sect Sect Master Mu Ye. How as for synthesizing fighting strength to be unknown.

The Zhen Hua vision changes last, from his look, Tang Wulin even saw the respect. By Zhen Hua one generation of Divine Craftsman Continent status, meets appear(ance) to respect this expression unexpectedly, in front of him this status on Continent meets venerates?

Not only he, even if in his Mu Ye, in the vision falls when finally on this, revealed a complex look similarly, from his look, what Tang Wulin saw was the fear.

Without a doubt, Zhen Hua or Mu Ye, on Continent are the characters who the stamping the feet all sea shivers, can let them so, it can be imagined this was what kind of existence.

That middle-aged person figure is slim, look is handsome, a little he and Tang Wulin look like very much, has the a pair of very attractive eye, the look is gentle, the eyelash is very long, although seems is about 40 -year-old ages, but as before has actually been full of the mature charm of middle-aged man.

Sits there, as if no what powerful aura to reveal, at least was inferior that front several are so noticeable, but when the Tang Wulin vision falls on him, actually cannot help but will be attracted by him.

Zhen Hua said: „Wulin, this said with some of your origins.”

„Has the origin with me?” Tang Wulin surprised [say / way].

That middle-aged person shows a faint smile to him, reveals a words tooth, „my own introduced own. I called Zang Xin, we were Tang Sect.”

Zang Xin? Regarding Tang Wulin, this name is without doubt strange. Must say that only and he has the place of things in common, possibly is the name gesture comparison......

Zhen Hua said: „Senior Zang is Tang Sect Douluo Hall Vice Hall Master, title Excessive Love (passionate).”

„cough cough.” Zang Xin hears the title of own, immediately coughs two. Resembling is somewhat awkward.

Zhen Hua hurrying syllabic final, somewhat awkward [say / way]: „Sorry, I forgot you not to be willing to mention your title.”

This time Tang Wulin has not actually noted the sense organ of Zang Xin to own title, was been completely shocking by the Douluo Hall three characters.

The Tang Sect internal structure he was clearer, Inner Three Halls and Outer Three Halls, his own is in Inner Three Halls, Battle Soul Hall member.

Inner Three Halls , in descending order , are Worship Hall, Battle Soul Hall and Law Enforcement Hall. But above Outer Three Halls, Tang Sect also most highest authority location, was Douluo Hall.

It is said that only then Worship Hall Worshipped has to rise into the Douluo Hall possibility. Douluo Hall Hall Master is Present Generation Tang Sect Sect Master.

At present this, unexpectedly is Tang Sect Douluo Hall Vice Hall Master, that also means that he is Under One Person, Above Ten Thousand!

After going to Star Luo Empire, Tang Wulin is very clear, not only Tang Sect has the pivotal status in Douluo Continent, is even higher than on Douluo Continent in the Star Luo Continent status.

Zhen Hua formerly to the name of Xu Shengqun was Brother Xu, but to the name of this Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo Zang Xin was actually Senior Zang, the difference between this may be big. Without doubt, this Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo age does not seem that young like the surface.

„Yeah, blames Hall Master, in the past must have a such title to me, this is really loses disgraced for a lifetime! Wulin, you do not need to call me any Your Excellency, do not call my title. You called me Old Zang to be good.”

Amiability that this Douluo Hall Vice Hall Master could not say, on the face throughout was the happy expression glistening, but Tang Wulin does not dare so, to hurry the respectful [say / way]: „Tang Wulin has seen Vice Hall Master.”

Zang Xin shows a faint smile, first meeting, gives you a small gift. At the same time was saying, he lifts the hand, a small thing flew toward Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin hurries to receive, falls starts, is a circular small sign, small sign manufacture is fine, the interior has Soul Guidance Method Array existence obviously, the outside seems is also very beautiful, side is blue side is red, both sides inscribe Tang word.

„Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark!”

Including Xu Shengqun, other five Titled Douluo lose one's voice to call out in alarm all.

That two females, Ice Moon Douluo Tang Liyue and Dawn Cat Douluo Zhu Xuan looks the color of envying, even somewhat is unable to restrain oneself.

Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark? Even if Tang Sect Disciples, Tang Wulin does not know that this is any existence. But he is intelligent, immediately bows over 90 degrees, respectful [say / way]: „Many thanks Vice Hall Master grants.” He does not dare to call Zang Xin is Old Zang.

Zang Xin said with a smile: „Not anything, this is Hall Master makes me give you. I also deliver favor done at little or no cost. You obtain, is you earns.”

„Hall Master? Does Hall Master also know me?” Who Tang Sect Present Generation Douluo Hall Hall Master is, let alone Tang Wulin, even if many Titled Douluo does not know. Only then Continent genuine stands in peak few talented people knows this mysterious Hall Master status.

Zang Xin said: „Is taking Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark, when you have free time comes to Douluo Hall, how naturally some people will tell you to use. Remembers that received, if lost, you missed this chance.”

„Yes.” Tang Wulin respectful complies with one, then arrives at Mu Ye and Zhen Hua behind stands firm, here without doubt is an elder, where has the share that he sits.

Zhen Hua said with a smile: „This time is thinking has Senior Zang to assume personal command personally, can perhaps fish the strip big fish to come, has not actually thought that was destroyed by Wulin accidentally. Was inferior that we have lunch first. Mu Ye, wanted to be laborious you.”

„Good.” The Mu Ye words are not many, comply with one, then shot a look at Tang Wulin, „boy, comes to overcome the hand to me.”

-------------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#861: secret?

Looks that Mu Ye brought Tang Wulin to enter the kitchen, on the Zang Xin face has revealed a smile, „some Innate Body Sect people have straightened out finally . Moreover the luck was good.”

Zhen Hua said with a smile: „I am also very accidental, has not thought that Tang Sect so regards as important to Wulin. Said honestly that this child I also favors. I listened to Mu Chen saying that he already soon close Saint Craftsman stage. This time, I estimated that he must consult the knowledge in this aspect to me.”

„Saint Craftsman? He how old?” Xu Shengqun surprised saying.

Zhen Hua proud [say / way]: „This child is advantageous. If Continent will again certainly leave one to be able in the future Heavenly Refinement Blacksmith, then, belongs to him.”

What does Heavenly Refinement mean? People is clear. Zhen Hua is boasted embarrassed Divine Craftsman said.

Tang Liyue and Zhu Xuan look at each other one, two female eyeground deep places have ray of light to flash through.

Appearance that Zang Xin always smiling, „Tang Sect to his attaching great importance, will only imagine you are bigger. Therefore, please trouble everybody, do not have his idea.”

His saying of course was not to Zhen Hua said that Blacksmith Association and Soul Master itself did not have what conflict place, but complemented one another. But was actually not true as Spirit Transferring Pagoda and War God Temple.

Tang Liyue said with a smile: „Senior Zang, you cannot doting parent! Our War God Temple is always not exclusive. He is Tang Sect Disciples, can join War God Temple is the Federation potency.”

Zang Xin smiles, actually shows neither approval nor disapproval.

Xu Shengqun wanted to say anything, but looked at smiling Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo, has not said eventually.

Although he is Spirit Transferring Pagoda most top layer one of the six people, does not dare to have in the face of this slightly dissolutely. Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo sounds to be only Douluo Hall Vice Hall Master, but is Spirit Transferring Pagoda high-level he is clear, this and Douluo Hall Hall Master also did not have much difference. Similarly stands in this world most peak man.

Spirit Transferring Pagoda Pagoda Master had said that on Continent, the match who he most is not willing to face is not Shrek Academy Sky Raising Douluo, but is Tang Sect two big Hall Master, obviously his appraisals to these two Hall Master was lofty.

Kitchen.

Closes, Mu Ye complexion as if relaxed several points, suddenly lifts the hand racket to the shoulder of Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin knows that he must do, of course will not dodge, whatever the palm of Mu Ye falls on his shoulder.

On the shoulder sinks, a great strength transmits instantaneously.

Compared with Zhen Hua, Tang Wulin longer time has not seen Mu Ye actually, comes back after Star Luo Continent, he has not seen own this Teacher(s).

Mu Ye stares slightly, he had considered that Tang Wulin strength will grow, strength that therefore this palm uses is not small, but, Tang Wulin actually does not have least bit reaction, he has not thought completely.

Tang Wulin smiles.

The Mu Ye eyebrow selects, on the face reveals the faint smile the expression, according to the palm actually suddenly thrust augmentation of Tang Wulin shoulder.

Tang Wulin is washing the potato, „can Teacher(s), peel?”

The corners of the mouth of Mu Ye twitched, in the heart have actually been full of the shock, even if were Strength Type Soul Master of Soul Saint rank, under strength function that in own just exerted, could not certainly withstand, but own this disciple was actually imitates, if safe. Is this possible?

Has not continued again, because he saw floor appear(ance) of Tang Wulin under foot the fissure, catches up again, perhaps the Tang Wulin person is all right, this floor actually must unable to withstand.

„Brat, what good thing you have eaten, how does strength grow these many?”

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, „Teacher(s), this is the secret. However my strength already already over 100,000 jin (0.5 kg). Moreover my own has the feeling, as if has still been growing.”

Is Innate Body Sect Sect Master, in body intensity, Mu Ye is always fills proud, although he until now cannot break through to the Super Rank Douluo level, but he has confessed that by the body intensity, own sufficiently and Limit Douluo compares favorably. But, looks that front this Five Rings cultivates for about disciple, his some are not self-confident, develops according to Tang Wulin present speed, perhaps soon, he can surpass own in the body strength level.

„Young fellow, you are fierce. Waits a minute me to teach your head-family the law of building up body, your strength such, must meet allocate to be good.”

„allocate?” Tang Wulin surprised looks at Mu Ye.

Mu Ye light [say / way]: „You have 100,000 jin (0.5 kg) strength, then, you, when does not approach the match, how many can display?”

Tang Wulin said: „Must throw in light of the weapon, or is coordinate Martial Soul and Soul Skill and so on has certain effect.”

Mu Ye shook the head, „strength is in itself also energy part, your bloodline Soul Skill is also good, own Martial Soul Soul Skill, does not conflict with it. Present you, look like have treasure mountain actually not to know that spatially how to unearth. But our Innate Body Sect the law of building up body, is helps you unearth this treasure mountain. However, you cannot be infatuated with the feeling of strength, Soul Power cultivate is basic. So long as there is enough formidable Soul Power, cultivate other will be again twice the result with half the effort. Teacher(s) was extremely in rigid as well as afterward too many energy will place to study on Mecha in own strength in the past, is unable to break through Super Rank Douluo stage to the present.”

„Yes.” Tang Wulin earnest nod, Mu Ye these words absolutely are his heart-to-heart talk, Tang Wulin from his look knows that this matter was big to his influence.

In fact, the Mu Ye young time is Innate Body Sect one generation of talents, is honored as possibly achieves predecessor stage existence. But afterward follows the growth of strength, because the division commander has not achieved such stage, to his direction on appear(ance) some issues, in addition his own hobby was extremely widespread, this lost the cultivate Soul Power best opportunity. Otherwise, by his talent, has possibility assault Limit Douluo that level.

Mu Ye is processing the food, while continues saying: „Before that Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo you, hasn't seen?”

Tang Wulin shakes the head.

Mu Ye said: „Tang Sect is really speechless that I have not thought that they so will attach great importance to you. If there is an opportunity, hits to relate with this. He the status in Tang Sect is extremely high, in fact, every so often, even if some Douluo Hall Hall Master not necessarily he speaks to be effective. He gives your Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark is a big chance, must hold surely.”

Tang Wulin curious asking: „Teacher(s), actually Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark is any thing, why your probably very shocking as.”

Mu Ye sinking sound track: „Tang Sect is time-honored, wants remote many compared with our Innate Body Sect. When Tang Sect ancestor Tang San overawes Continent, Tang Sect has discovered land of treasures. Said accurately that is that Thousand Hands Douluo Tang San discovery. This land of treasures is very covert, moreover it is said is the institution, poison is layer on layer densely covered. But in land of treasures, is actually breeding numerous Heaven and Earth Treasure, is most Top Rank existence. The genuine situation I am not specially clear. But so long as you know that Tang San and Huo Yuhao these two can obtain the advantage to be enough from this land of treasures greatly.”

Tang Wulin hear of his saying, were so heavier regarding the Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark curiosity several points, but is very obvious, Mu Ye does not know about the truth.

Mu Ye said: „After you go back, can use Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark as soon as possible, I believe that has the direction of this Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo, you will not miss. Was right, do not walk with him is too near.”

Tang Wulin somewhat cannot feel the brains, previous minute of Mu Ye also makes own be on good terms Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo, how the latter minute also said that makes own not walk with him is too near?

The Mu Ye look is somewhat strange, body sends out gentle energy, him and Tang Wulin gable, has isolated all of outside.

„You know that what the title of Tang Sect Present Generation Douluo Hall Hall Master is?” Mu Ye asked.

#862: Unexpected breakthrough

Tang Wulin shook the head, how he possibly knows that Tang Sect Douluo Hall Hall Master is always most mysterious existence.

Although renewal most quickly he present is Battle Member, but also falls far short from the Tang Sect high level.

Mu Ye said in a low voice: „Title No Love (heartless), No Love (heartless) Douluo Cao Dezhi.”

Tang Wulin this is first time hears Tang Sect Present Generation Douluo Hall Hall Master, is the Tang Sect Sect Master name, time stared in a big way the eye.

„Associates to what?” In Mu Ye eye ray of light glittering.

Tang Wulin shakes the head at a loss, No Love (heartless) Douluo? Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo?

Mu Ye said: „[Say / Way] is No Love (heartless) actually feels emotion, Excessive Love (passionate) hated since old times idle. In legend, Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo and No Love (heartless) Douluo, cough cough. Did not need me to say again.”

Tang Wulin stared in a big way the eye instantaneously, „did you mean? Their two both male?”

„Ehm!” Mu Ye has selected the eyebrow, „may not mention this matter except for this room to anybody, this to Tang Sect is one of the maximum secret.”

Tang Wulin only thought that the whole person is not good, Douluo Hall Hall Master No Love (heartless) Douluo and Vice Hall Master Excessive Love (passionate) is Douluo pair of? This......

„Teacher(s), is your this news reasonable?” Tang Wulin asked to Mu Ye.

„It is not reasonable!” Mu Ye principle saying of of course.

A Tang Wulin almost blood spurts, „was not reasonable you to add that you did not fear......”

Mu Ye said with a smile: „My this did not tell you . Moreover, since there is a legend, of course not rumor, some these definitely views. For example, as far as I know, No Love (heartless) Douluo and Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo have not gotten married, they are one generation of big energies, liked their outstanding females being many. Doesn't have them to like? Is, these two relations have been good, the earlier time common wanderer world, was Tang Sect has performed the distinguished service. The title so is also ambiguous.”

Tang Wulin relaxed, said: „Your this is makes groundless accusations.”

Mu Ye smiles, „Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo is forgiving in all directions, No Love (heartless) Douluo does not have the scandal. Legend Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo game world, to cover him and relations between No Love (heartless) Douluo. specific I am not how clear, they are not in any case normal.”

Tang Wulin coughs, has the topic about elders, good of his many mixing. Moreover he could also see, Mu Ye said these, malicious intent. After all, Innate Body Sect and Tang Sect earlier book is the competitive relations, but along with the time passage, Innate Body Sect potential, but Tang Sect even more is formidable, had already spread out.

Mu Ye cook truly formidable, in addition food excellent, table of sumptuous lunches have suspended quickly.

Zhen Hua invited the numerous positions to take a seat, without doubt, Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo Zang Xin sat the seat of honor, in the people, was his status is highest.

Tang Wulin takes the junior, naturally accompanies respectfully end the place. Looks that in a good vegetable his heart of table darkly to shout to be a pity, these many elders, he cannot let loose made chewing motions greatly quickly. Only can be looks dry greedyly.

Zhen Hua does not know where from looked for one bottle seemed the liquor of outside wrapping unusual vicissitudes, gave everyone personally but actually one cup, included Tang Wulin.

„My this bottle of Dragon Blood Wine history was glorious, had not hated with drink, initially a friend gave to me. Today happen to please appraise.”

The liquor fluid presents for the amber brown, has the light delicate fragrance to flutter faintly, this type of fragrance is unusual, is a little similar to the sandalwood, likely is the garden fragrant fragrance.

In front of Tang Wulin one cup, he has not drunk, immediately the big feeling is curious.

„Senior Zang, fellow good friends, I respect everybody.” At the same time was saying, Zhen Hua carries cup.

Zang Xin shows a faint smile, takes up front wine class, „Dragon Blood Wine, good thing! I also had many years not to drink. Um, smelled like that is Scarlet Dragon dragon blood. Strong mellow, itself has thick fire element essence. To dispelling yin cold evil qi, strengthens own courage vigor to have helps very well. Moreover, makes up Pure Yang greatly.”

Hears makes up Pure Yang these characters greatly, besides Tang Wulin, several masculine Titled Douluo revealed the smile of understanding.

Zhen Hua raises up the thumb, „Senior Zang is really an expert, please.” At the same time was saying, his own in the liquor the cup tosses down first.

Dragon Blood Wine? Tang Wulin curious looks in front cup the liquor fluid, saw that other people have drunk, he was one has also drunk.

Dragon Blood Wine entrance sweet and pure, but is strong, Tang Wulin only thought that steam wells up above instantaneously, the firing line breaks in the lower abdomen of own together.

Whole body all pores in completely have opened in an instant as if, on the handsome face surges immediately two lump of red, at present is also piece of mold hu.

Good fierce liquor! Good comfortable feeling.

He only thought that at this time own body extend opened completely, the skeleton, channels or bloodline and skin, have plants is burnt to console the feeling.

Whole body steam Teng Teng, the skin surface are quickly many have wiped to blush.

Looks at Titled Douluo again, is actually side, if safe.

Without doubt, this is the disparity of strength, takes cultivation of Tang Wulin as, energy that in this Dragon Blood Wine contains was extremely rich, is unable instantaneous absorb.

But also at this moment, suddenly, Tang Wulin hears own within the body transmits „clang” a resounding, within the body Qi and Blood on madness surges. His whole person body one stiff.

Went bad!

Truly has had problems, the issue is, his Ninth Layer Seal, broke.

Dragon Blood Wine leads Tang Wulin has been suppressing bloodline aura, under the ascension, one flushed Golden Dragon King Ninth Layer Seal suddenly.

In fact, Tang Wulin did not know about Dragon Blood Wine, otherwise he will not drink.

Dragon Blood Wine itself of course is the thing of big making up, Zhen Hua takes it naturally is also the good intention, but this Little Thing must look that is who drinks.

Tang Wulin drinks, the nutritious effect naturally has. But don't forget, his within the body was flowing Golden Dragon King bloodline, although Scarlet Dragon was also True Dragon, but quality and rank and Golden Dragon King bad was too far.

Golden Dragon King bloodline feels Scarlet Dragon bloodline to enter, how can not the violent anger? Although Dragon Blood Wine was drunk to digest absorb, but Golden Dragon King bloodline is one gets up on Frantic, Ninth Layer Seal that Frantic Golden Dragon King bloodline aura facing already creakied, naturally clashes.

Previous quarter Tang Wulin or the cheek are red, next one flickers to be centered on his body, the energy fluctuation of Frantic bloomed. Skin surface instantaneous courage Golden Scales, has covered his entire cheek as well as the body piece by piece instantaneously.

Golden Dragon King 18 Seal, after first eight opening, on Tang Wulin can, when does not use Golden Dragon Body the majority was covered by golden-colored scales. But this ninth Seal, final scales will make up neat.

Strong bloodline aura to rush, the low and deep dragon roar sound also transmits in Tang Wulin bloodline fluctuation. Chair instantaneous to shatter under his body, sits falls to the ground.

At this moment, Tang Wulin anything could not attend , can only be makes an effort Power Control to make the body of own to sit cross-legged to sit.

This was he already had assault Ninth Layer Seal ability, can stand firm oneself at crucial moments. Otherwise, if like former assault Seal, perhaps already painful pouring on the ground.

Numerous position Titled Douluo also had a scare, Xu Shengqun surprised [say / way]: „The Zhen Hua brother, your this potency of alcohol is a little strong! This child......”

Zhen Hua is also the surprised color, looks in the Tang Wulin heart to fill puzzled, „should not! Although the Dragon Blood Wine effect is very good, but by the Wulin physical quality, withstanding should an issue not have, how can appear(ance) this situation, be his cultivation to achieve tranquilly, soon will break through? Also is not right! His Soul Power should just achieve shortly after 50th Rank, the distance next big bottleneck also has very big disparity.”

„It is not Soul Power.” Zang Xin arrives at side Tang Wulin, both eyes narrow the eyes, „should be similar to the breakthrough of ability, but is actually not Soul Power, but is bloodline aura Transformation of his own within the body. Very overbearing energy, but is also very strange, agrees with his oneself completely.”

Mu Ye also arrives at side Tang Wulin, regarding the Tang Wulin situation, that he most understands, understands that was his within the body that and Dragon-Type approximate bloodline appear(ance) Transformation. To come to be inspired by Dragon Blood Wine.

But takes cultivation of Zang Xin as, had not said that his present situation has the danger, wants to come not to have the too major problem.

, The Tang Wulin condition is gradually tranquil gradually, seems truly greatly has not obstructed.

Zang Xin shows a faint smile, „was good, we continue to eat meal, when we finished eating the food, perhaps he restored.”

Tang Wulin felt at this time Golden Dragon King Essence is similar to the blowout blooms in within the body generally, after the whole body last part of places golden-colored dragon scales covers, in his skin surface as if take shape a special energy circulation, the feeling of greatly somewhat growing continually.

------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued..)

The quickest renewal correct novel read, please visit

Please collect the home station to read the newest novel!

#863: Dual cycle

Since continuously, Tang Wulin bloodline energy, although is formidable, but actually needs to eat massive food as the supplement, whenever uses time, will consume massively, once consumes completely, he will also fall into the weak condition.

The renewal may this time feeling actually start most quickly becomes different, that surge turbulent bloodline energy starts a take shape marvelous circulation in his skin surface, this circulation and circulation of Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power in channels does not conflict mutually, instead in originally existence channels strength of slowly absorb some bloodline to skin surface layer.

Under the skin is of force circulation bloodline, in channels is the Soul Power circulation, when this two strip in unceasing Transformation, some strange reaction also started appear(ance).

First is, Tang Wulin the ratio of Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power operation was smoother before, runs speed to start to speed up obviously, the Soul Power vortex revolution is even more smooth, in the process of High-speed revolving, the vortex most under acme starts to have some clear ray of light glittering,

Then after is the strength of bloodline was separated alone, the revolution also similarly becomes smooth, what is more important, in generating process, strength of take shape bloodline a marvelous circulation, manic gradually becomes affable, meanwhile indistinctly has bloodline aura to promote continually. When looks like cultivate Soul Power Soul Power will grow is the same.

Two circulations from initial jerky to transfers gradually round pleasant, the two as if mutually do not disturb, but each other also has the subtle relation, one outside, one in *** Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power of department grows continually, the strength of exterior bloodline is vigorous, just like long stream grand river rolling unconsciously.

Nine Golden Dragon King Seal indistinct fluctuation that broken leave golden-colored halo, is consolidating the bloodline aura circulation of his outside body, making Tang Wulin have the feeling of being reborn.

In his spiritual world, he also similarly feels that golden-colored Mighty Dragon as if soars, baseless conjecture on his spiritual sea, from Dragon's Head to Dragon's Tail, altogether nine golden light (Jin Guang) ray of light glittering, ominous prestige illustrious. That is terrifying aura beyond description, as if must all break open the entire world.

Tang Wulin also first time feels to come from the stubbornness in Golden Dragon King energy, that stubbornness, dominates in all above, dominates in the feeling of head of myriad life form. As if all should submit to before it, before is not, that deep sleep feeling.

In his sensation, Golden Dragon King bloodline in within the body as if lived, genuine changed into Golden Dragon King, has greatly able to move unhindered opens and closes, the indignance of looking disdainfully world, even there are to plant to run out of the feeling of his body.

In this moment, even if no explanation of Old Tang, Tang Wulin also finally understands why Old Tang will say, Seal Golden Dragon King bloodline 18 Seal latter nine and front nine were entirely different.

Compared with Golden Dragon King how Golden Dragon King of deep sleep can with consciousness, wants to continue energy in absorb Golden Dragon King Seal in the future, as if must yield this Golden Dragon King be gradually good, danger that these must face, what kind terrifying.

Tang Wulin holds breath cold air, heart has the intimacy. However, he can also feel obviously, compared with Golden Dragon King latter nine Seal and front nine, wanted not to have the several fold obviously solid. In other words, he wants to break through following Seal very difficulties, but similarly, energy in that Seal wants to also similarly very difficulties.

Words as the matter stands, will at least give him not the small opportunity. Has sufficient preparation time.

After Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power and Golden Dragon King bloodline energy revolves 49 sidereal revolutions, respective return. Mysterious Heaven Skill Soul Power condenses in Soul Power vortex in Dantian, but the strength of that Golden Dragon King bloodline finally condenses in the Tang Wulin chest locates, as if also changed into vortex, golden-colored vortex, but this vortex in his chest surface.

Sits even can see in people who by the table eats meal that the Tang Wulin chest place has shone, golden-colored halo are blooming from there outward, the clothes somewhat cannot block.

Tang Wulin aura also in the unceasing promotion, he is Five Rings Soul King, the people present all are one generation of big energies, but these positions can actually be able to feel greatly, transmits from him oppresses the strength, that of course possibly is not the oppression on Soul Power, but came from the pressure in bloodline.

„This boy of bloodline aura, but must above you! I refer to is not energy in bloodline, but is bloodline origin aura.” In the Zhen Hua eye is greatly bright, said to Mu Ye.

Mu Ye also looks the strange color, „I can feel that has not thought that his bloodline can also evolve unexpectedly continually, I think that his bloodline was opened by me completely, now looks like, just just started that's all. Present he, is genuine shows oneself really me the time. bloodline aura becomes the circulation, was interesting.”

Excessive Love (passionate) Douluo Zang Xin both eyes narrow the eyes, mutter the tunnel: „Becoming the circulation, this means that his bloodline aura has the possibility like Soul Power, condense becomes is similar to Soul Nucleus existence. In the Tang Sect ancient book, but also never has Soul Master appear(ance) such situation. On this child, actually part of bloodline belongs to Soul Beast? You should know that cultivates Soul Beast cultivate to Ten-thousand Years for later, may leave to belong to Soul Beast Soul Nucleus in within the body condense, their Soul Nucleus are more came from in bloodline, with the difference of our Soul Master. Once the Soul Beast death, this Soul Nucleus will change into Soul Ring, most formidable or special Soul Nucleus, will also affect their skeletons, thus appear(ance) Soul Bone.”

Zhen Hua suddenly serious to Zang Xin and various humanity on the scene: „Numerous positions, I have a request, hopes that the numerous positions can keep secret for my this Master Nephew, I do not hope that he was taken away by Federation, treats as test sample.”

Zang Xin shows a faint smile, „this you have considered thoroughly actually, has changed others or possible, he is not good. He is our Tang Sect person, not only that also will be our Tang Sect must enter the Worshipped palace in the future even is the Douluo Hall successor. Let alone, do not forget, he is one of the Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters. Will Shrek Academy allow some people to treat as test sample with him?”

At the same time was saying, his vision seems very natural on the scene has swept from Spirit Transferring Pagoda and War God Temple several faces, does not have any imposing manner to bloom obviously, but that several are actually in the heart imposing. Without a doubt, Zang Xin these words representative is not his own, but is entire Tang Sect.

„You also leaked said that he was also our Innate Body Sect person, was my being in direct line disciple.” Mu Ye somewhat proud saying.

Zang Xin shot a look at his one eyes, gave a calm smile, not to say anything again.

Said honestly, some Mu Ye headaches, he even somewhat angry stared Zhen Hua one, if not Zhen Hua Dragon Blood Wine, Tang Wulin is also insufficient to expose so in front of these many Elite, this exposition, is without a doubt disadvantageous to him. He is thinking with any means that can turn in the future Tang Wulin, becomes Innate Body Sect successor Sect Master. Because Tang Wulin cultivates to now also fall far short, he does not have worries. But he stares at now by Zang Xin, naturally entered the Tang Sect high-level field of vision, Zang Xin formerly had given him Tang Sect Ice and Fire Mark, let alone also discovers on him now special location. Later wanted to strive for his difficulties.

Zhen Hua is actually the innocent appearance, in the heart is actually very happy, own this Master Nephew just like hidden dragon in deep pool, once runs out, likely soars. What is rarer, this child temperament is stable, grows along with the age, not only not arrogant, instead was calmer. In his heart truly also somewhat regretted, if presents not to have War God Temple and Spirit Transferring Pagoda these today, was naturally better.

The people liquor over three patrol, Tang Wulin grows the tone finally, has opened both eyes slowly.

Within the body aura restrains, all changed normal, that flash when but his eyes opened, the people clearly saw, in his eyes, the bright flashed through.( To be continued..)

The quickest renewal correct novel read, please visit

Please collect the home station to read the newest novel!

#864: Being well-prepared

That ray of light is quite radiant, including Zang Xin, in people eyes appear(ance) instantaneous absent-minded.

The renewal does not have anybody to see most quickly that opens binocular that flash in him, the pupil is not the circular of average person, but raises up, the a pair of eye pupil presents for bright golden-colored.

ray of light dodges, the eye pupil also returned to normal. Tang Wulin only thought that all the limbs and bones are all happy, has exhausted strength.

Although this time broke through ninth Seal, but he has strength to turn time of feeling. Really was too carefree.

„Awoke to eat meal.” Zhen Hua said with a smile.

Tang Wulin hurries to crawl, somewhat embarrassed [say / way]: „Senior Teacher and Teacher(s), older generation(s), sorry, I do not know......”

Zang Xin beckoned with the hand, „was good, this is your chance. Eats meal, but, Dragon Blood Wine do not drink.”

Tang Wulin awkward smiling, this takes a chair, has eaten.

Because before people, pays attention to him, eats are not many, had repaired to their this is, too does not need to absorb energy through food. Tang Wulin actually not so, as before, how regardless of cultivates to promote, he has not reduced regarding the hope of food, under one made chewing motions greatly quickly, was healthier immediately, after all, these food may be the good things today!

Has eaten meal, other people said goodbye one after another, only remaining Zhen Hua and Mu Ye two people.

Zhen Hua said to Mu Ye: „Behind you lines up! But my Master Nephew looks my.”

Mu Ye snort, „control has eaten to provide lodging, I worry.” Then, he has patted the shoulder of Tang Wulin, walked without consulting anybody, only remaining Tang Wulin and Zhen Hua two people.

Zhen Hua sighed one lightly, „Wulin, you may know that today you are working as the surface breakthroughs of these many people, to you, but half congratulations half sorrow!”

In the Tang Wulin heart moves, „Senior Teacher, did you mean?”

Zhen Hua said: „I, Mu Ye and Zang Xin older generation(s) does not matter, in some sense, you are our people, we look forward to your talent different to report. But War God Temple and Spirit Transferring Pagoda that several, although is our allies, but from some significance, there is competitive relations. of course, I am only Blacksmith, I am do not matter, but, even is Innate Body Sect may be not true regarding Tang Sect and Shrek Academy. War God Temple invites the thoughts that you join to be perhaps more, but Tang Sect not necessarily is actually willing to put you to go. This involved gambling between high levels.”

„of course, you have shown your potential before people today, definitely will make Tang Sect attach great importance to you, War God Temple and in the Spirit Transferring Pagoda high-level field of vision also meets appear(ance) your form. Looked how you will develop in the future. However, you remember a few words, how regardless of the future, you must how choose, most important is own must be formidable enough. Depends upon other people's strength, sizes up the situation no doubt importantly, but anything was inferior important that own itself comes formidable. Only then own has enough formidable strength, can be in an impregnable position.”

„Yes.” In Tang Wulin heart imposing. Actually he knows these since childhood, Father had said to him, in this world, can definitely trust, and forever relies on, has own.

Zhen Hua shows a faint smile, „you do not need too to be worried that after all you are now young, the potential is matter, whether to change into the strength the potential is different matter. Let alone you behind have Shrek Academy. Moreover, you are Blacksmith. If you can soon break in Saint Craftsman stage, then to any side absolutely was scarce resources. Is higher in the forging aspect achievement, very good conceals ability in your other aspects, to you is also the protective function. Therefore, this time, you stay here, I listened to your Teacher(s) to say your situation, since you were in the Half-step Saint Craftsman situation, then, this time did not break in the Saint Craftsman level, I will not put you to walk.”

Looks cunningness that in the Senior Teacher eye not minces, Tang Wulin also smiles, whatever, Senior Teacher is also hopes own to be able in the forging aspect upper formation building. After all, looks like in Divine Craftsman, what but also there is compared with a forging more important matter? But in fact, to own, can break through in the forging aspect, truly is very important.

At that moment, Tang Wulin lived in Blacksmith Association General Headquarters, every day follows Zhen Hua to study forging.

Those who stem from him to be unexpected, Zhen Hua had not taught how he carries on Soul Refinement, but unravels general, is improving him each detail in forging, although Tang Wulin has done very well, but Zhen Hua actually can find some slight defects in his forging process. Then is makes him carry on various metal(s) Harmonizing Refinement, making him feel metal(s) properties slight Transformation in Harmonizing Refinement.

Tang Wulin spiritual cultivated to already to enter Spirit Abyss Realm, in addition this breakthrough, strength of Soul Power and bloodline had not the small growth, Soul Power has repaired for because unexpectedly the bloodline energy peeling rushed to 54th Rank directly, the strength of bloodline was also suddenly to increase, he in forging, not only stepped up the own forging level, controlled strength that own increased gradually.

, He completely immersed in this forging world gradually, has forgotten time of outside, the entire sentiment invests.

„Did you break through?” Mu Ye pursues asks.

„Yes!”

„Did you break through really?” Mu Ye asked again.

A Tang Wulin face speechless looks at Teacher(s), „Teacher(s), your this asked more than 20! Real, or you ask Senior Teacher.”

The Mu Ye corners of the mouth twitched, „does not use, I believe you. But, 20-year-old Saint Craftsman, this, makes people somewhat be hard to accept!”

The Tang Wulin corners of the mouth outlined attractive curve, „may this be the fact.”

In his heart can not be unhappy? Yes, last night, he finally broke through.

In fact, he became 6th Rank Blacksmith had more than four years of time, compared before, speed of this breakthrough was not absolutely quickly.

However, in the Blacksmith world, spanning of each big stage, is extremely difficulties.

From Thousand Refinements to Spirit Refinement, from Spirit Refinement to Soul Refinement, not ill natural moat is ordinary. Every time steps forward big realm, in the forging world, is as for in entire Continent, the influence to be entirely different.

Saint Craftsman and Master Craftsman treatment, differs hundred times. Soul Refinement and Spirit Refinement price spread is also so!

What Spirit Refinement gives metal(s) is Life, metal(s) after Spirit Refinement, is similar to Plant, but Soul Refinement gives metal(s) is actually Wisdom. Wisdom that although at first waits, but made metal(s) learn the ponder, disparity, was huge.

Therefore, when Mu Ye knew that Tang Wulin finally completed the breakthrough yesterday, finally after forging has succeeded his first block Soul Refinement metal(s), questioning that today keeping, is actually this fact.

But Zhen Hua absolutely does not have appear(ance) today, but Mu Ye is completely conceivable, that will cause the what kind excitement.

Grows the tone, Mu Ye said: „Your this boy, but also is really......”

Tang Wulin blinked, „Teacher(s), you did not say that can teach me some Innate Body Sect secret arts? When we start.”

Mu Ye has smiled suddenly, „becomes Saint Craftsman is very self-satisfied? Snort, is quick I to make you know self-satisfied the consequence before me.”

Tang Wulin hit to tremble smartly spirit, immediately recalled initially on the ship oppressive the desire immortal by that wanted. However, he is quickly calm, because, he passed through Devil Island military training! What also has more painful than suffering that seven Old Devil bring?

Not only Old Devil suffer their bodies, what is more important suffers their Soul, that is most fearful.

„Your physical state, differs from our Innate Body Sect passing cultivate Martial Soul. On the other hand, I am willing your Innate Body Martial Soul induction to be bloodline. But has the cultivate law about bloodline, Innate Body Sect does not have. Therefore, I teach you, is how the body of Control own. You have strength spatially, is actually not able Control, then, regardless of your strength is strong, impossible genuine to control its mystery. Innate Body energy is so. The human body innumerable mysteries, how stimulate Innate Body, how to control Innate Body, how when uses Innate Body energy to display the geometrical multiple mighty energy, these are I must teach you.”

„Thank You (xiexie) Teacher(s), when do we start?”

„Now!”

Tang Wulin stopped over in Heaven Dou City for one month, finally returns.

Had Tang Sect Combat Car, he was will not sit Soul Guidance Train, always auspicious omen others Train how was not good!

When he drives to return to Shrek City, already compared with time that initially and companion agreed late five days. However Shrek Academy Inner Court are not many regarding the request of disciple. Gives them many spatial. Is Present Generation Shrek Seven Monsters is so.

-----------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued..)

The quickest renewal correct novel read, please visit

Please collect the home station to read the newest novel!

#865: On together

This month, the harvest of Tang Wulin is without doubt huge, breaks through Ninth Layer Golden Dragon King Seal, strength of separation Soul Power and bloodline, enters step Saint Craftsman, controls Innate Body.

The renewal is quickest

Short one month of time, for him, is more like the beforehand several years of accumulations releases all.

From initially went to Star Luo Empire to the present, had more than four years fully, in the four years, Dragon Burying afterward studied on Devil Island, for him, is a process of accumulation. Is well-prepared, Heaven Dou City one month, he genuine understands that actually own had how ability of degree.

Returns to Inner Court directly, returned to that once own and Gu Yue small log cabin. He is even anticipating, is Gu Yue came back, or at least leaves behind the word in the small log cabin to him, even if has one to believe to be also good.

In the log cabin had a light dust, in addition, not many anything.

When Tang Wulin enters the log cabin next one flickers, in he bright eyes were many several points of desolate. She has not come back eventually, disappears without a word eventually.

Actually may be what kind of pressure, makes you so cruel-hearted unexpectedly? She likes own obviously, is actually that departure resolutely.

Na'er, Na'er where?

Tang Wulin only thinks the heart intermittent stabbing pain.

Knowledge that in Academy, should study he no longer was short, what are more is needs the accumulation and cultivate of time, unceasing promotion. But his some are unable to sink the heart to come.

But, wants to graduate from Inner Court, needs to become Two Word Battle Armor Master is first good. Two Word Battle Armor Master, the normal request, above Soul Power 60th Rank, Battle Armor completes.

Tang Wulin subconscious gripping tightened fist, this coming back, own also this and companion together, diligently assault Two Word Battle Armor Master. After becoming Two Word Battle Armor Master, he must complete the own desire, makes own diligently more formidable, then seeks for Parents, seeks for Na'er and Gu Yue.

The takes a deep breath tone, is smelling the room familiar flavor, he dejected abandoning in own heart. He was 20 years old, ten years ago, Parents departs, he arrives at today step by step, has faced many hardships, but he actually step by step walked. He is very strong, wants strong many compared with the average person, the innermost feelings pain was pressed in a flash, he always told own to be hopeful. So long as own becomes formidable, certainly will be then good in the future.

Opens already entire one month of closure Soul Guide Communication Device, poured into some Soul Power to imitate the energy for it slightly, Tang Wulin has dialed the Ye Xinglan Soul Guide Communicator number.

„Wulin?” Ye Xinglan sounds/voices transmits, she as before is as before is so tranquil.

„Um, is I, I came back. Did everybody come back?”

Another side of Soul Guide Communication Device transmits Xu Lizhi sounds/voices, „Boss, you came back finally, we also think that you were missing. Comes back well, where are you at? Everybody came back, we look for you.”

Tang Wulin said: „I in Sea God Island, you come.”

Shrek Seven Monsters has to enter the Sea God Island privilege. This is other Inner Court students does not have.

time is not long, when that familiar face appear(ance) in front of own, on the Tang Wulin face revealed heartfeltly the smiling face.

Although is only one month does not see, sees them again, in Tang Wulin heart warm. At least, side own also has these good companion.

„Well, Boss, how I thought that you is a little different!” The Xie Xie movement is quickest, first arrives at side Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin shrugs the arm, „what has not to be different?”

Xie Xie brow slightly wrinkle, „is different. With my Teacher(s) words, is in the feeling different, this is the sixth sense.” Speed Hall Hall Master Liang Xiaoyu is his Teacher(s), Liang Xiaoyu has told him, as Agility System Battle Soul Master, the sixth sense is important. The formidable sixth sense can make him have quickest reaction speed.

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „Do you want to know?”

In the Xie Xie eye reveals to be vigilant the color immediately, he and Tang Wulin knew that time is longest, most understands him, when Tang Wulin smiles most temperate, generally is thinks the bad idea the time.

„Does not think!” Xie Xie shaking the head without hesitation.

„I think, me to think.” Le Zhengyu has collected grinningly. His spiritual as if thoroughly restored from the shadow.

Tang Wulin has a look at him, has a look at Ye Xinglan again, as if their this month also had not small Transformation! It looks like, among them the issue has been solved.

„Boss, you do not need to visit her. I went to her home, then also led her to go to our home. Our Parents has approved. Momentarily can marry. However after we prepare and other strengths become the strong point, said again.”

Marriage? Heard these two characters absent-minded, Tang Wulin slightly.

Xie Xie flies rapidly a foot, kicks on the Le Zhengyu buttocks, „do you love to talk about somebody's most vulnerable points? Our is forms a pair, when you Boss such do reach an agreement? Are you oppressive dog you do know? Boss as unmarried dog already very pitiful, have you been able like this? I do not do, you said that is Yuan En? Yuan En, you , if willing to marry me, regardless of when me. Now is also good.”

„You sufficed!” Tang Wulin ill-humored [say / way]: „This month, I achieved mastery through a comprehensive study some beforehand accumulations. Therefore you will feel somewhat differently. Everybody all assembled, we in Training Field to island tried the hand. You on together.”

Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu look at each other one, in the heart have doubts.

„On together? Boss did you determine?”

Without doubt, they approve to the Tang Wulin strength, but he is missing that three years of Soul Power to cultivate for the promotion after is not many, but the strength of people, has dominated above him many. On the individual strength, is very as before strong by strength of Tang Wulin bloodline, is, if two pairs one, they do not think that is also not the Tang Wulin match. After all, they were also not initially.

Practicing of Devil Island, everybody is separates basically, moreover what are more is Test spiritual and Soul. Are not many to the individual strength influence.

The Le Zhengyu corners of the mouth place reveals a smiling face, „good! Boss, that such settled.”

Xie Xie smiles, „is also good and be also good. That tries.”

Tang Wulin looks at the appearance that in their eyes harbors evil intentions, the brow selects. It looks like, they are very as if confident!

Xu Xiaoyan covering the mouth chuckle, quietly has given a hand signal to Tang Wulin, Tang Wulin suddenly, why the Le Zhengyu confidence so was then full.

But is he to own confidently? What is more important, he also wants to feel, present own, can actually be what kind of degree.

Training Field on Sea God Island on a hill, here ban uses to numerous position Titled Douluo, therefore is absolutely solid, will not have any problem.

The Tang Wulin seven people step onto Training Field one after another in high spirits, Xu Lizhi opened Training Field Guard Screen to the one side. As Food System Soul Master, when the team compares notes, obviously does not have his anything matter. He and Xu Xiaoyan was looking in the line at the same time.

Xu Xiaoyan Control System Soul Skill is the heaven defying kind, has words that she participates, which side regardless in is unfair one kind.

of course, two pairs one similarly is in their opinion unfair. Everybody in same stage, cultivates to be higher, in fact the disparity should slightly be more right, therefore, including Xu Xiaoyan, everybody basically does not favor Tang Wulin.

One pair two, that is must have the absolute disparity to win. Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu two people, although bickers frequently, may their relations be in fact good, the coordination absolutely is also tacit, assault agility, resists Tang Wulin, should the issue not be big.( To be continued..)

The quickest renewal correct novel read, please visit

Please collect the home station to read the newest novel!

#866: Soul Emperor Le Zhengyu

Let alone, Tang Wulin is breaking through, they have not been idling! Devil Island after is very big to the Le Zhengyu attack, but when he walks gradually after the shadow, surprised discovery, own in Soul Power or the Spiritual Strength aspect, had the enormous promotion.

The renewal is quickest

On the Tang Wulin face reveals a light god only, both hands joint hold in the front, look at opposite Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu. In the surface smiled is richer.

Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan also draw back in the one side, Yuan En ask to Ye Xinglan: „Xinglan, you thought that who can win?”

On the Ye Xinglan rare face reveals a smile, „you such asked that didn't favor Xie Xie?”

Yuan En Yehui said: „That but is actually not, by me to their understanding, Xie Xie and Zhengyu joint words, the opportunity should be very big, after all, their cultivation for there, moreover everybody each other was too familiar. However, I also similarly understand Wulin, initially, he was bringing First Grade and we hit, wins one victory after another, this fellow seemed the gentle breeze drizzle, may in fact black belly very much, did not fight the uncertain war. If meets the difficult time, association goes against in the forefront. In the imposing manner, Zhengyu and Xie Xie are not his match. Therefore, finally who can win is very difficult to say. However, comes back after Devil Island, in fact we each other do not have, understood. Especially to Wulin, after all, he was so long that side Star Luo Empire, after coming back, has not listened to him to say actually to have met anything in that side.”

Ye Xinglan said with a smile: „That has a look, if the gambling, I also believe that Wulin will win.”

Yuan En Yehui surprised [say / way]: „Why?” Her many somewhat hesitates, may look at the Ye Xinglan expression, clearly has the absolute confidence to Tang Wulin.

Ye Xinglan shakes the head, „why I do not know, is a feeling. You carefully look, Wulin aura, is really as if different from before, Xie Xie sixth sense was right. Actually as to have anything not to be different, makes us wait. Wulin asks them to compare notes today, should not be is aimless.”

„Um.” Yuan En Yehui nods, their vision also as if by prior agreement falls on the scene.

Xu Xiaoyan cracks into a chuckle, „I make referee, did you prepare?”

The range of summit specially is not big, 300 meters in diameter, regarding the fight of Five Rings Soul King rank, this range book being insufficient makes them display completely, because has strong to ban that Control their energy is not leaking, did not matter.

Tang Wulin nods, Xie Xie smiles, „Boss, we will not show mercy! I still remember now, initially our first meeting time you hit the appearance that me flies. I very much bear a grudge.”

„?” Tang Wulin faint smile visits him.

Xie Xie turns head to look to Le Zhengyu, Le Zhengyu snort, „had felt relieved that I want to win his thought that is more rigid than you. Do not be a drag on my on the line.”

„!” Xie Xie has given the hand signal of despising to Le Zhengyu, „who drags whose hind leg is uncertain, Xiaoyan, we prepared.”

Xu Xiaoyan said with a smile: „Good, that starts!” At the same time was saying, he makes an effort to wave.

Le Zhengyu almost with the instance that she makes noise, has been similar to arrow dart overran toward Tang Wulin. Without any gaudy, is frontage hardly clashes, one has pulled open distance between him and Xie Xie.

„Hey, you wait / etc. I, what you cannot understand are the coordination!” Xie Xie is unsatisfactory, but his start was obviously slow, falls behind Le Zhengyu many.

Le Zhengyu in the instance of running out, body burst out the unprecedented imposing manner, Soul Ring raised from his rapidly.

Four purple two black, right, Six Soul Rings! Entire six.

Before Xu Xiaoyan to the hand signal that Tang Wulin gave, was six.

21-year-old Le Zhengyu, in short several years time, fully showed strength of his one generation of talents, successfully became Six Rings Soul Emperor level Elite.

Initially, to protect Xu Xiaoyan, he has displayed Holy Angel [lineage/vein] bloodline talent ability Sacrifice, thus has consumed the own Life strength large scale, in fact, after using Sacrifice, to Holy Angel [lineage/vein], had a special help. Sacrifice divine skill, can make their full senses deep meaning between Life Flame and Sacred Flame, regarding Holy Angel [lineage/vein], although has consumed their Life strength large scale, actually can also make them experience Sacred bloodline aura in shorter time profoundly, better promotion.

Later Devil Island a series of Test, making Le Zhengyu oneself fly to enter suddenly courageous, what is more important, there, his absorb very huge Life energy, when own Sacrifice Life energy that consumes supplemented, meanwhile made his own Life energy sublimate, this was his background, today dares challenge Tang Wulin also to believe background that own can win.

In some sense, although Le Zhengyu had the intense shadow on Devil Island, may in fact, he obtain benefits there biggest, spiritual and Soul Power double harvest.

Some time ago, after obtaining Xu Xiaoyan family's approval, he has completed the breakthrough finally, one step strided in Soul Emperor stage, became in High Rank Soul Master, had had Two Word Battle Armor background.

Six Soul Ring, four purple two black, this absolutely is Soul Ring matching of most Top Rank. Radiant Sacred Flame ascends from him. First Soul Ring shines, behind a pair of pure white wing appear(ance) with him at the same time, Sacred Light fell on own together.

Sacred Light, the attack and defense has both, Le Zhengyu is very clear, Sacred Light attack Tang Wulin will not have any effect, but attaches in oneself, is actually to his effective amplification. The a pair of pure white wing was exaggerated golden-colored instantaneously.

Holy Sword along with it appear(ance), sword tip(s) glittering, golden-colored halo spreads, making his whole person really just like Angel Descends common.

A back pair of wings racket, Le Zhengyu from the sky is similar to together golden light (Jin Guang), before arrived at the Tang Wulin body, directly slanting above position, back huge Angel phantom flashes before baseless, both hands grasp the sword, a sword of being outspoken cut to Tang Wulin.

This sword seems simple, but actually unified his first, second and fourth, Three Great Soul Skill. Angel Descends before attack blooms flickers the release, all engagements as wonderful as the summit. It can be said that this struck to promote his fighting strength 120%.

Tang Wulin that moment of Le Zhengyu starting has not moved, stands in as in same place, even own Martial Soul does not have the release continually, but be with smile on the face looks that Le Zhengyu clashes to own.

Until Le Zhengyu flaps pair of wings accelerates the time suddenly, on his face revealed surprised.

But at this moment, before his body, suddenly resounds „biting” a light sound.

A handle illusory dagger does not have appear(ance) of omen before his body, moreover just stabs in his front. What hit is the right chest, on the other hand is not the critical right chest.

But when, that dagger stabs his chest instant, resounds crisply, is actually not able the little advance half minute.

Dagger of course possibly is not Le Zhengyu, the illusory form congealing reality, on the Xie Xie face has filled slightly inconceivable.

Is this possible?

When Le Zhengyu opens Angel pair of wings, that prestigious brilliance completely has covered following Xie Xie, but according to the former Xie Xie program, he completely was backward, let alone also had the sudden acceleration of Le Zhengyu. It looks like, he should not appear(ance) be here right.

May complete attack is actually he, although is only Shadow Dragon Blade, but actually fully gathers the strength in the attack process, unprecedented strikes. All imposing manners and attack strength, are stabbing Tang Wulin that flickers to erupt.

But the feeling of Xie Xie, own Shadow Dragon Dagger actually likely stabs the mountain that has towered palatially, is unable to enter the slightest.

Has saying that he and Le Zhengyu coordination is quite tacit, all people think Le Zhengyu attack should arrive at first time, first completes attack is actually Xie Xie.

In fact, Xie Xie has not thought own can strike the accomplishment, so long as this attack can attract the Tang Wulin attention, destroyed his defense and fight rhythm is enough. Le Zhengyu Storing Power strikes to flicker will arrive.

But, what regardless of he has not thought that meaning that Tang Wulin has not resisted, his Shadow Dragon Dagger cannot take to him unexpectedly any injury.

When he saw when smile that the Tang Wulin corners of the mouth place reveals understands that Tang Wulin has to discover him, but has not planned defense.

Also at this time, Tang Wulin finally moved, his right foot however stamps courageous, with the low and deep dragon roar sound, the terrifying fluctuation strength made 30 meters in diameter range in centered on him, as if entire spatial caved.

Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth!

But is this original Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth?

---------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued..)

The quickest renewal correct novel read, please visit

Please collect the home station to read the newest novel!

#867: Pulls out instantaneously flies

Eight Golden Dragon rise straight from the ground, each over five meters, what terrifying was spatial twisted, Le Zhengyu only thought that spatial madness of that distortion was tearing the body of own, making him have to release many Sacred Flame to resist, in the meantime, his Holy Sword also completely cut in the vacancy, declined radically on Tang Wulin.

The renewal is quickest

Xie Xie in close-range, is in itself Agility System Soul Master, directly was flushed by the fluctuation whole person, the whole body is lacking in vigilance.

Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu after all are Shrek Seven Monsters, although simultaneously does not faint from fear right, but their reaction also absolutely are enough quick. They as if by prior agreement, released own Battle Armor in first time.

The Battle Armor rapid turn over, covers the whole body, resists Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth mighty energy, but Tang Wulin has not planned to give them obviously such opportunity, sees only his personal appearance half revolution, the right leg wields like lightning, eight Golden Dragon that airborne raises are ordinary just like all rivers run into sea, drills into his right leg instantaneously, then in the people eyes, on appear(ance) huge Dragon's Tail, has swept away.

Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu can do, after is puts on Battle Armor, All-Out defense. Then their bodies are similar to artillery shell generally are rumbled to fly, distant flies beyond hundred meters, hits on Guard Screen. Splashes two dazzling halo.

This......

This!

This?

Le Zhengyu and Xie Xie were perplexed. On the Xu Xiaoyan face smiling face freeze, Xu Lizhi stared in a big way both eyes.

Yuan En Yehui and on Ye Xinglan face expression also in instantaneous stiff.

Is this possible?

In their eyes, this was unable to describe with the miracle simply.

Two!

Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth and Golden Dragon Swings Its Tail, are ability in Golden Dragon Nine Styles. But such two, Tang Wulin even does not have the release including Martial Soul.

Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu had been rumbled to fly.

Is they do not coordinate tacitly? Is their attack not formidable?

It is not.

Tang Wulin ability is extremely overbearing, the overbearing two people of bases do not have the opportunity.

Falls to the ground following screen, Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu think the whole body Qi and Blood tuck dive all, although Battle Armor has blocked the overwhelming majority attack strength, but the feelings of some of their actually as before whole body worns out and aching, hurry to transfer Soul Power to restore diligently.

Has not been injured, is, just that two, actually the ratio was injured also makes them shock.

By an enemy two, pull out instantaneously flies.

This simply......

When, his changed was so formidable? Just that flickered, they also had before, is when facing initially Monster Academy that Dragon King Long Yue. Mountain Dragon King once took to them to oppress the strength like this, but that time Mountain Dragon King Martial Soul was formidable, surmounted their stage, the Martial Soul also crush.

But present Tang Wulin, has Five Rings obviously! In cultivation for on not compared with them. But that terrifying oppression strength, was ordinary just like the mountain at this time, the oppression comes.

At this moment, Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu understand suddenly, own two people, unexpectedly with him already no longer on same stage.

„Comes again!” Tang Wulin low and deep sounds/voices simultaneously resounds in their ears.

Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu have put on their Battle Armor at this time, after simple controlling one's breathing, they simultaneously body.

With is Shrek Seven Monsters, can they not have the heart of viing for supremacy?

Xie Xie soars, swings the body in a flash, the body revolves in airborne High-speed, gets up with the dragon roar sound, on him ascends immediately together Golden Dragon Light and Shadow, Fifth Soul Ring Great Release of Rays of Light, is his fifth Soul Skill, Light Illusory Dragon. In that Light Illusory Dragon shadow place, dragon of nothingness is partly visible, Shadow Illusory Dragon.

Had formerly lesson, this time comes up, he used own strongest ability, Double Dragon Transformation.

In the Le Zhengyu hand Holy Sword points to the sky, drinks one coldly, meaning of the Frantic erupts immediately from him, back Angel phantom enlarges instantaneously, his Soul Spirit Little Angel also along with it appear(ance) in his shoulder, together radiant golden light (Jin Guang) soars, tiny particle Bi Xian who entire Training Field shines upon, huge golden light (Jin Guang) drops from the clouds, is refracting suddenly, this diameter has three meters giant light beam fully, instantaneously on Devour front Xie Xie Double Dragon Transformation.

„,” In more spirited dragon roar sound, Double Dragon Transformation brings that Angel's Fury intense Sacred Light to drill suddenly, the prestigious imposing manner made in entire Training Field all become a piece of distortion.

Two big One Word Battle Armor Master simultaneously display Top Rank Soul Skill, by Angel's Fury amplification Double Dragon Transformation, formidable of its mighty energy, even if Two Word Battle Armor Master does not dare the frontage to meet hardly.

But has Tang Wulin stands in same place moved as before, but the look became dignified several points.

His courageous however takes a deep breath tone, the whole person as if became along with the movement of inspiration inflates, within the body Soul Power vortex High-speed revolved, the Qi and Blood vortex reversion of chest place revolved, whole person body surroundings has covered [gold/metal] white two color halo, piece by piece golden-colored dragon scales reappearing naturally in his skin surface, four golden-colored ring of light regarding in body surroundings.

„Raises”

When Tang Wulin this Golden Dragon Roars roars, saw only his surroundings Qi and Blood surge, the body of whole person in instantaneous empty melted all over the body unexpectedly, but changed into huge Golden Dragon Head, unequalled cruel aura burst out. As if he really incarnation is Golden Dragon King is at this moment common.

Xie Xie Double Dragon Transformation under this Golden Dragon Roars, unexpectedly instantaneously became illusory, even if there is Angel's Fury in addition to hold, unexpectedly also had the sign that must break up.

At this moment, Tang Wulin appears, both hands by body, regelation heavy extrusion, Golden Dragon Ascends The Heavens!

Formerly the huge dragon head again congealing reality of empty, in a flash changed into 30 meters in length golden-colored Mighty Dragon outrageously, with that Double Dragon Transformation maliciously hit together.

Spirited dragon roar, calls out in grief general dragon roar, resounds through entire Training Field.

Distant place observing people, all for it discoloration.

But appear(ance) that at this time, by Training Field, several forms also been quietly, has included Scarlet Dragon Douluo Zhuo Shi and Blazing Dragon Douluo Feng Wuyu this Double Saint Dragons old two.

When Feng Wuyu looks Tang Wulin this type Golden Dragon Ascends The Heavens promotes, was startled stares in a big way the eye, „old thing, was this your Scarlet Dragon Ascends The Heavens?”

Although Zhuo Shi in the eye similarly is also revealing the color of shock, actually immediately sticks out chest, „clothing refuses to accept!”

Feng Wuyu turned head to look at his one eyes, immediately discovered his look was not right, „took, this was not your incurs radically. After improving. I do not believe you unable to feel shivering of bloodline.”

Truly, takes cultivation of their two big Titled Douluo as, at this time under Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Roars and Golden Dragon Ascends The Heavens, unexpectedly in trembling, moreover is quite intense, that is in one sense of fear from bone, even if in their eyes, Tang Wulin in Training Field, has a palatial feeling.

At this moment, Tang Wulin vanished suddenly, the whole person looks like in airborne transforms golden-colored Mighty Dragon once more, but moves sideways, flew high to fly to formerly the Nucleus place of collision.

His right arm finds out, wields void, Golden Dragon Claw rises suddenly against the wind, changes into a diameter to surpass five meters huge dragon claw racket to fall outrageously, the dragon claw claw finds out the dark-gold light blade edge sharp, this claw lays out instant, surroundings spatial changes into black suddenly, is ordinary just like the black hole. The terrifying attracting customer interest erupts from that black hole, two forms explode Nucleus to locate immediately appear(ance) from that all was covered under this claw.

Golden Dragon Soars and Golden Dragon Solitude Destruction Claws Divine Dragon Nine Styles.

„Bang”

Two forms simultaneously fly upside down, this time did not fly to the same direction, but flew respectively to two directions, Le Zhengyu was better, the back a pair of wing forwarded the counter- volume, the own gable, but in flying upside down, but in process, feather ** the piece flew to fall.

----------------------------------------

Welcome everybody to join our own prestige and Platform. Prestige - increases friend - search public number, searching Tang three few, has first of v authentication is.( To be continued..)

The quickest renewal correct novel read, please visit

Please collect the home station to read the newest novel!

#868: He already so formidable?

Another side, the Xie Xie appearance was frigid, two huge wounds from the right shoulder to the left thigh place, Battle Armor were cut unexpectedly completely.

Renewal most although quickly that Battle Armor is relying on the itself Spiritual Alloy Top Rank quality in fast Self-Restoration, but Xie Xie actually also directly lost fighting strength, falls on the ground, cannot stand again.

Tang Wulin drops from the clouds, falls in the ground, exudes one to thunder, the audience, is silent.

Yuan En Yehui moves sideways, rushed to side Xie Xie, has hugged from the ground him, inspects his physical state.

When the next quarter, she gains ground, in the eye the color of shock is rich. Xie Xie seems the appearance is frigid, may in fact a wound by, Battle Armor clearly not be cut, has revealed inside Innate Body, has not actually damaged including the clothes, but was sealed up bloodline and Soul Power. Tang Wulin formerly that formidable attack, unexpectedly can strength Control to so subtle stage, simply be the strange its technique.

Nobody will think that he just that was the having no way wound to Xie Xie, in fact, if his All-Out to go, perhaps the body of Xie Xie had been cut to pieces.

Le Zhengyu falls to the ground, does not feel better similarly, Battle Armor was also appear(ance) three huge breakage wounds, only compared with the Xie Xie strong point was, his Battle Armor has excelled in defense strength, has not damaged completely.

After falling to the ground, his whole person was ignorant, in just that flickered, facing Tang Wulin lays out that claw time, he only thought that the body of own was attracted absorbs there, wants to dodge cannot achieve. Only can stiffly shoulders. But his Holy Sword cannot play any defense to affect, first time crushing under that terrifying Golden Dragon Claw, then other people have flown upside down. If not All-Out defense, perhaps he and Xie Xie are also similar. Moreover he can also feel obviously that Tang Wulin that claw, does not have All-Out completely. What is more important, he has not put on Battle Armor! This simply......

When, did he unexpectedly become so formidable?

In other Shrek Seven Monsters six people of feelings, this time Tang Wulin, already completely with them not in a category, but has not seen in one month, this seems like reborn simply, is more like dragon soaring through the nine heavens is ordinary, shows has surpassed toward strength. Even if were Le Zhengyu has promoted Six Rings stage, is Soul Emperor, may before him, not have the least bit opportunity as before.

Le Zhengyu understands, only if own uses that Sacrifice stunt, perhaps can also spell to spell. May so, he also think that the opportunity is not big.

Was this disparity also too rather big?

Racket of Yuan En Yehui after on Xie Xie has rubbed several next, Xie Xie then awakes to turn around. Then his body is shivering unexpectedly unceasingly, enough after several seconds, returns to normal.

„You how?” Asking of Yuan En Yehui doubts.

The Xie Xie forced smile said: „bloodline frightens, was too fearful. Before Boss just that Golden Dragon Roars and entirely different, my bloodline has submitted to directly, the entire body sluggish such as fills the lead to be common, does this also hit? When Boss already formidable in this way?”

At this moment, in the people eyes, Tang Wulin that just dropped from the clouds, looked like trades simply has resembled personally. The personal appearance no longer is slender tall and straight, but is big and tall palatial, even if they once faced Mountain Dragon King Martial Soul owner Long Yue the time, seems also mediocre, moreover Long Yue has also been short of Tang Wulin that essence reserved brilliant feeling. Only then Long Yue under madness condition as if can compared with the present Tang Wulin imposing manner.

Transformed, he transformed, hidden dragon leaps out of the deep pool, soars.

Tang Wulin looked at both hands of own, was feeling just to the utilization of strength, to the utilization of body, as well as to the control of own each point of strength, coordinated the sensation of Spiritual Strength to match with searching to observe. This feeling is wonderful.

Because besides breaks through Golden Dragon King Ninth Layer Seal to make the strength of his Qi and Blood complete, Innate Body Sect that to various body Control as well as to spiritual Control Method, played the crucial role.

Like such that Mu Ye said that had strength spatially, the application of genuine will not be useless, without a doubt, Tang Wulin initially has controlled now has applied ability of strength of own Soul Power and Qi and Blood. Within the body two vortex High-speed revolve, involves and complements one another mutually, the beforehand consumption quickly restores to come.

„I try.” The form dodges, Ye Xinglan arrived in front of Tang Wulin, facing strong Tang Wulin, she, not only does not have the half minute to be timid, instead fighting intent is soaring. This is she, no matter, would grasping the nettle. Her road, wants unceasing challenge Elite, breaks through in assault limits.

„Good! Yuan En comes together.” Tang Wulin also beckons to Yuan En Yehui.

Without a doubt, Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan, are stronger than Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu.

Yuan En Yehui stands up, the stride arrives at side Ye Xinglan, what making Xu Lizhi surprised was, Ye Xinglan had not opposed unexpectedly. Can see from this point that she confessed was not the present Tang Wulin match.

Xu Xiaoyan has licked red lips, arrives at side Le Zhengyu, said: „Starts!”

Ye Xinglan lateral steps forward one step, then the whole person concentrates to stand there is motionless, but in this flash, her body surroundings ray suddenly became gloomy, as if all rays were attracted by her body absorb, extremely sharp sword intent jumped to shoot from her, made Training Field Guard Screen appear(ance) the intermittent ripples.

sword intent that but that spreads continued the flash to converge the past like her top of the head above, will not affect others, but such condensation, sword intent was also more fearful.

Ye Xinglan has closed both eyes, she has not released Martial Soul, looks like stands there meditation. But the Tang Wulin expression, obviously compared with formerly dignified many.

Yuan En Yehui one step steps forward, keeps off in front of Ye Xinglan, the personal appearance rises suddenly, shows her Great Titan Ape Martial Soul.

The both arms lift by the body, pair of Giant Hammer(s) appear(ance), this Giant Hammer(s) initially Tang Wulin gave her baseless, when facing the fight of Evil Soul Master was once incomplete, afterward looked for other Blacksmith to help after Yuan En Yehui, patched. This was the steelyard weight of Mecha use as if unable to see any weight in her hands.

The Yuan En Yehui look concentrates, Battle Armor rapid turn over on, cover in which her whole person, the imposing manner rise suddenly instantaneously.

Tang Wulin this time has attacked on own initiative, the tip of the toe in the ground, the human generally flushed just like artillery shell, carefully looked that can see from his High-speed form, his body while assault since, the right arm receives backward, grasps to hold turned into a fist, from the sky has completed the Storing Power movement.

Yuan En Yehui steps forward once more one step, similarly is assault, dual hammers brandishes horizontally, this she does not have any to keep the hand, because of her very clear Tang Wulin strength.

„Bang” both sides collide suddenly in together, even if is relying on the a pair of steelyard weight, in addition own Battle Armor amplification, under this pure strength meets the tough head-on with toughness, the body of Yuan En Yehui by flying upside down of Tang Wulin fist bombardment, like formerly Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu, hit directly on Guard Screen of distant place.

The Tang Wulin body from the sky stagnated, back Golden Dragon Light and Shadow flashes before, Golden Dragon Soars for him in the airborne two acceleration, dashes to Ye Xinglan.

Also at this moment, Ye Xinglan moved, her right hand lifts, empty grasps after the own brain, Star Divine Sword appears, sword light instantaneous glittering that the bolt of white silk also resembles together, all rays were all attracted in that flash absorb, in all person fields of vision, sees in jet black spatial, together radiant starlight instantaneous flash, but.

„Clang!”

Tang Wulin drops from the clouds, by a Ye Xinglan sword interception, this is also in today's comparing notes process, some first people can block his offensive directly.

The Ye Xinglan whole body megascism simultaneously, Battle Armor takes possession, the personal appearance dodges, sword tip(s) is radiant, has covered his body.

The Tang Wulin both arms get up in the body front trail, treadon Ghost Shadow Perplexing Track, speed incredibly fast of whole person are unexpectedly incomparable, in illusory glittering brings a series of afterimage.

Although Ye Xinglan Star Divine Sword is fast, actually falls on the vacancy, is unable to lock his personal appearance.

Yuan En Yehui from the distant place ball, two groups of Air Artillery simultaneously the bang to Tang Wulin, contains his personal appearance, at the same time, she has also completed own Gigantic Demon Titan Transformation, grasps dual hammers, drops from the clouds, falls behind Tang Wulin, around with Ye Xinglan launches the potential of converging attack.

Xu Xiaoyan stands side Le Zhengyu, said in a low voice: „Has a look at others, Sister Xinglan and Yuan En do not have you to be so weak.”

Le Zhengyu showed the whites of the eyes, „is not we are weak, is Xie Xie that fellow is weak. He has coldly by the heart and gall that Boss that dragon roar deters, cannot display fighting strength to come, otherwise, my where will defeat that miserably. Is useless including sixth Soul Skill. Moreover, I just may have the strength of again war.”

------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.( To be continued..)

The quickest renewal correct novel read, please visit

Please collect the home station to read the newest novel!

#869: terrifying Tang Wulin

„Raising” at this moment, spirited dragon roar resounds once more, Golden Dragon Roars.

Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan do not have Dragon Clan bloodline freely, but under Tang Wulin this roars, is the whole body trembles as before greatly, the body simultaneously became slow.

The Tang Wulin right foot stamps, Golden Dragon Roars meets Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth, surroundings spatial twists instantaneously, immediately the led whole person in shivering stagnates in his close-range Ye Xinglan.

But she cultivates for truly is in people are next to Tang Wulin, while feeling not good, on Battle Armor point starlight puts greatly, releases Guard Screen promptly. Therefore, her shivering has continued the flash, relied on tyrannical sword intent to melt. But also at this moment, eight Golden Dragon leapt up, all flew to following Yuan En Yehui. Tang Wulin while Ye Xinglan sluggish at the same time, arrived at her.

Right hand Golden Dragon Claw wields outrageously, place visited, spatial piece of to shatter, to shatter spatial appear(ance) attracts the customer interest naturally, attracts is pulling the body of Ye Xinglan.

On Star Divine Sword selects, Ye Xinglan has completed Body and Sword Unity without enough distance sprint unexpectedly.

„Bites!” A series of crisp whining noises resound from the sword claw interface point unceasingly. Then can see the disparity, each collision, Ye Xinglan freely already as far as possible displays own sword intent, may by Tang Wulin oppression unceasing retreat, the strength aspect, their disparities really be too big.

The Tang Wulin personal appearance reverses, the right leg sweeps away, in the spirited dragon roar sound, huge Dragon's Tail appears, Golden Dragon Swings Its Tail.

The skillful aspect, Tang Wulin is not excels, way (of life) simple and crude that he uses, broken by the strength. I do not compete sword intent and sword technique with you, uses most pure strength to suppress you.

Ye Xinglan but, can only be Star Divine Sword transforms innumerable sword tip(s), explodes with the strength draws back, as before likely was actually flown to exit to resemble by the Golden Dragon Swings Its Tail bang.

Tang Wulin Golden Dragon Swings Its Tail leads the body to fling horizontally, simply has not gone to look that was shaken Ye Xinglan that draws back, the right arm raises, Golden Dragon Solitude Destruction Claws!

Before was Le Zhengyu and Xie Xie two people facing his Golden Dragon Solitude Destruction Claws, but this time, actually just solved Golden Dragon Shakes the Earth that eight Golden Dragon Yuan En Yehui alone to face.

terrifying huge dragon claw is bringing to shatter void attracts the attraction to drop from the clouds, Golden Dragon Fearful Claw sharp. This absolutely is in Tang Wulin Divine Dragon Nine Styles at present most formidable attack.

To change body Fallen Angel dodges was impossible, on Yuan En Yehui Sixth Soul Ring Great Release of Rays of Light, dual hammers previous gathers in the body, the both legs stand on Training Field just like taking root general, a diameter achieves ten meters great hand suddenly appear(ance) from him, that great hand makes a fist shakes Tang Wulin that huge Golden Dragon Claw hardly.

Right, Yuan En Yehui is the same with Le Zhengyu, broke through Six Rings, incarnation Soul Emperor.

„Bang” Tang Wulin and Yuan En Yehui simultaneously the body megascism, to shatter of grasping of Golden Dragon Solitude Destruction Claws and Titan in each other collision, unexpectedly is evenly matched.

But must know, Yuan En Yehui to block this strikes, itself has the Battle Armor amplification, Titan's Power, Vajra Titan and Gigantic Demon Titan Three Great amplification, in addition sixth Soul Skill.

However, has blocked Tang Wulin finally directly most strikes, cold star already instantaneous appear(ance) behind Tang Wulin.

After Tang Wulin right hand fierce flings, together [gold/metal] horizontally in the back, is Golden Dragon Spear, at the same time, his One Word Battle Armor: Dragon, in instantaneous upper body.

Yuan En Yehui and Ye Xinglan have striven to excel after all Xie Xie and Le Zhengyu, without Battle Armor, wants to defeat them not to be really easy.

Yuan En Yehui Sixth Soul Ring continues ray of light to bloom, the right hand hammer to airborne throws, grasping of appear(ance) Titan, holds Giant Hammer(s) once more directly, flies high to pound to fall.

Concentrates in his back Ye Xinglan body, Fifth Soul Ring blooms, the whole person changes into one to sparkle instantaneously the blazing ray of light stars, terrifying incomparable sword intent is locking his whole body.

Two big Elite All-Out to go, seemed can suppress Tang Wulin finally.

The Tang Wulin takes a deep breath tone, the whole person as if entered in a special state, his eyes becomes exceptionally bright. Saw Giant Hammer(s) near body instant, whole body Battle Armor suddenly becomes is similar to mirror surface common brilliance.

„Bang” Giant Hammer(s) shoots, Golden Dragon Tyrant Body.

Whole body ray of light rapidly glittering at the same time, in his hand Golden Dragon Spear punctures. Greeted Ye Xinglan fifth Soul Skill, Stars Sword!

„Biting”, when that ear-piercing collision resounds, Xie Xie, Le Zhengyu, Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi discoloration distant place, covers the ear all, Le Zhengyu keeps off before several other people fast, pair of wings opens, Sacred Light blooms, flickers below, assault wave already but outrageously.

Ye Xinglan stuffy snort, personal appearance explodes draws back at the same time, fresh blood has spurted.

The Tang Wulin eye dew apologetic color, the personal appearance rotation, Golden Dragon Spear sweeps away, Golden Dragon Swings Its Tail sweeps away in another shape, Yuan En Yehui assault flew.

Puts on Battle Armor Tang Wulin, strength gives people an irresistible feeling, was really too strong.

Xu Lizhi rushed to side Ye Xinglan, fast forces in her mouth Restoring Stuffed Meatbun.

Ye Xinglan eats up Restoring Stuffed Meatbun, compares the thumb to Tang Wulin.

Tang Wulin has also caught up fast, „is sorry Xinglan, your sword intent is too strong, my Control does not live.”

Ye Xinglan said with a smile: „All right, this fights satisfies a craving very much. Actually, you received strength finally, otherwise, concentrates strength of you and Yuan En two people through Golden Dragon Tyrant Body, this (spear|gun) I cannot block.”

Tang Wulin truly was as far as possible received strength, strength that but Golden Dragon Tyrant Body borrowed, in addition his own strength extremely formidable. Then injured Ye Xinglan.

The people gather, Xie Xie cannot bear say: „Boss, how you suddenly became such strong. Xinglan adds Yuan En is not your match.”

Tang Wulin said: „Was good at controlling to own strength, then my bloodline also had further regained consciousness. Actually you are also because does not know that my promotion, otherwise, I want to win am not easy. of course, you are an exception.”

Xie Xie smiles, „this has not related, next time on the side of I and you, not only not affected, instead has increased? I thought that our two hit their five not to have the issue. I am and you have stood on one side.”

„Didn't boast to die?” Le Zhengyu ill-humored [say / way].

„Refuses to accept to try!” Xie Xie self-satisfied standing side Tang Wulin, the flavor that somewhat bullies the weak by relying on powerful connections greatly, making the people smile.

But after Tang Wulin slightly makes the ponder, said: „Can try. Xinglan, are you good?”

Ye Xinglan said: „I do not have the issue, you really trial?”

Two pairs five two were different from just one pair, although Xu Lizhi not anything fighting strength, but his Steamed Stuffed Bun was not small to everybody amplification, regarding the Shrek Seven Monsters mature team, everybody coordinated tacitly, to increase a person like this extremely every time, fighting strength was the geometrical multiple promotion. Let alone also had Xu Xiaoyan Power Control.

Ye Xinglan and Yuan En Yehui add Le Zhengyu Three Great Assault System Battle Soul Master, two Six Rings Soul Emperor, have in the enough auxiliary situation in behind, Tang Wulin and Xie Xie two people want to block are not easy.

Tang Wulin firm nod, „tries. Today and everybody compares notes, mainly to thoroughly understanding your current conditions, then, we must start Two Word Battle Armor manufacture. I planned, when our Two Word Battle Armor manufacture, forging this aspect brings a pleasant surprise to everybody.”

Xie Xie curious [say / way]: „What pleasant surprise?”

Tang Wulin shows a faint smile, „I broke through.”

The people shake, almost blurted out, „Saint Craftsman?”

Tang Wulin is not good to conceal to companion of course anything, is smiling nod.

---------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket.

#870: Solidization Soul Skill possibility

The people look at each other in blank diamay, Xu Xiaoyan is calls out in alarm said: „heavens! Boss, you will have this one month to close up next time again can promote the strength the good matter certainly to lead us massively! Saint Craftsman, Soul Refinement? To say that you can build Three Word Battle Armor metal(s) to us?”

Tang Wulin said with a smile: „Also was short, after all I just entered this stage, but also needs time to improve. Moreover, even if can build for everybody now, you have more than enough. Does not have Seven Rings to cultivate is, not having Martial Soul avatar to take foundation, possibly has not used Battle Armor that the Soul Refinement metal(s) manufacture becomes. Therefore, we cannot aim too high, completes our Two Word Battle Armor. However, has Soul Refinement to take the background words, I planned to everybody Two Word Battle Armor time, completes at least four metal(s) Harmonizing Refinement, lets our Battle Armor far ultra same level stage level. Two Word Battle Armor besides Wings, but can also Solidization Soul Skill, moreover not by Martial Soul limit Soul Skill. You can think clearly, best is we each other can, mutual portray.”

Behavior Solidization Soul Skill, can through Battle Armor special Nucleus method, any Soul Skill Solidization, the Soul Skill might cultivate with Soul Master for as well as Battle Armor itself related, of course, to Three Word Battle Armor time, this Solidization Soul Skill can be many.

For example, Tang Wulin Soul Skill can Solidization on Xie Xie Battle Armor this. This need has the Soul Master All-Out coordination of Soul Skill to be good.

„Boss, I wanted Solidization you a moment ago ability of that claw.” Xie Xie immediately saying without hesitation.

Tang Wulin laughs in spite of trying not to immediately, beauty that „you think, first did not say my is the bloodline Soul Ring technique, now has not known to be able Solidization, even if, you do not have my strength and my Golden Dragon Fearful Claw take the amplification. To you, that is not quite suitable. In you, has Yuan En strength to be able to display my Golden Dragon Solitude Destruction Claws majority of mighty energy, can consider Solidization. of course, but must in Solidization, the attempt whether to use my this bloodline Soul Ring technique.”

Tang Wulin continues saying: „I estimate or have the opportunity . Moreover, Spiritual Alloy metal(s) species are more, the itself supporting capacity is also bigger, our Solidization Teacher(s) some Soul Skill are not impossible. Below Seven Rings, should be able to choose. But should better with Soul Skill that own own ability agrees with mutually, such amplification effect will be best.”

Two Word Battle Armor and One Word Battle Armor completely are two concepts, strict, after must wait till Two Word Battle Armor, is genuine Battle Armor Master. of course, Tang Wulin their this Spiritual Metal One Word Battle Armor was exceptional.

At this time, Le Zhengyu and Yuan En Yehui broke through Six Rings, completely had load bearing Two Word Battle Armor foundation, Soul Power of other people also differed not many.

Xu Lizhi is especially excited, if he can have Two Word Battle Armor, so long as Solidization easy-to-use attack kind of Soul Skill, is qualitative leaps to his strength absolutely, can fight finally.

„Was good, we hit again, everybody All-Out to go. Only by doing so, what can make me see clearly your following Battle Armor most to need is anything.” Tang Wulin smiles was saying.

Although now they are not suitable to use Soul Refinement metal(s) manufacture Battle Armor, but has Soul Refinement background, Tang Wulin completes four types self-confidently is five metal(s) Spiritual Alloy issues is not even big. of course, when manufacture Spiritual Alloy, but must consider that everybody wants Solidization Battle Armor Soul Skill properties.

This had Super Rank Blacksmith advantage location when manufacture Battle Armor. To behind, the function of Blacksmith was more important.

Changes into the ordinary Blacksmith words, completed Spirit Refinement to be very reluctant, but Spirit Refinement has been able manufacture Two Word Battle Armor. May be able be imagined regarding the Battle Armor Soul Skill supporting capacity. Some many Two Word Battle Armor because of own qualitative issue, do not even have means Solidization Battle Armor Soul Skill.

Reason that Zhen Hua shakes Continent, all parties must to him the face, because of Battle Armor to the later period, Four Word Battle Armor want to complete Peak, needs this Divine Craftsman All-Out to go.

If Tang Wulin now emits the wind, said that own is Saint Craftsman, then, wants to make money in Shrek Academy, absolutely was the easy matter.

Feng Wuyu is Titled Douluo, is not good to do, but he is young, Soul Master of course is willing to work with him.

Xie Xie moves sideways, arrived at side Tang Wulin, arrives really took two pairs of five times, he somewhat was worried that said in a low voice: „Boss, are we good? My Battle Armor has not replied to complete, perhaps I could not help you be too many!”

Tang Wulin shot a look at his one eyes ill-humoredly, „is the strength of spirit a little good? Yuan En may look.”

Xie Xie smiles, „has your me to be confident! Boss, come, making them know that the flower like this is why red.”

The Le Zhengyu eyebrow selects, „who makes whom know that the flower like this is why red has not said.”

Both sides retreat, two pairs five, the quantity is disparate.

Yuan En Yehui, Ye Xinglan and Le Zhengyu three people before, Xu Xiaoyan and Xu Lizhi two people., Five people directly have put without hesitation on Battle Armor.

Tang Wulin Battle Armor has not escaped, facing five companion, his expression also became very serious. This war may not be relaxed like before.

Xu Lizhi started to recite the incantation, Steamed Stuffed Bun manufacture come out unceasingly, Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun and Puncture fork gets a swelled head, Hard Crystal Bun, looks at such, is preparation every.

Tang Wulin gives a loud shout, „starts!” He cannot wait for Xu Lizhi to complete Steamed Stuffed Bun, in that case, their opportunity did not have.

Personal appearance suddenly to dodge, Tang Wulin flushed, Xie Xie moves sideways, hid in him behind vanishes.

This time Tang Wulin, felt obviously in own behind sharp air/Qi in unceasing is increasing sharply, moves Storing Power? This fellow formerly lost to own, the primary cause also is really came from in bloodline!

Since with Yuan En, Xie Xie is never together lax, not being able to withstand that in fact, his fighting strength original non- today displays.

Becoming the allied force, the feeling of Xie Xie also and formerly faced Tang Wulin time was completely different, because no longer is hostile, he feels Tang Wulin bloodline fluctuation to make own bloodline obviously extremely stimulated, moves the Storing Power process usually to be much quicker.

Although the strength of his bloodline cannot increase the strength directly, but bloodline is exuberant, can actually make his own strength display 120%.

This was the disparity. Let alone, Tang Wulin also has to be able simultaneously to strengthen their ability.

Even if facing five people, Tang Wulin is as before unprecedented, the whole person looks like Mighty Dragon, is showing the fang to the match.

At this moment, ray of light suddenly appear(ance) in his front road which must be taken. In Tang Wulin heart one startled, body shifts instantaneously, does not allow to send in the middle changes the position.

Star Wheel Ice Chain quietly appear(ance), if he is slow a racket, must be lived by Star Wheel Ice Chain Bind, that tenable anchorage effect, will make absolutely his imposing manner plummet immediately. Even if so, because fends, the Tang Wulin charge imposing manner weakened several points.

Yuan En Yehui has filled Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun to the own mouth, welcomed. In the Le Zhengyu hand Holy Sword condenses once more, Holy Sword lifts up high, Trial of Light drops from the clouds together, chops Tang Wulin.

Five pairs two, they have the absolute superiority, before fight way (of life) also nature, was different.

Yuan En Yehui eats up Bloodthirsty Bean Paste Bun not to calculate that the backhand catches Xu Lizhi with Hard Crystal Bun that the Tang Sect Hidden Weapons technique throws, is squeezes in the own mouth, the whole body shone crystal luster immediately, defense increased.

Star-time Chains also in this are their five people links, a five body.

The Tang Wulin corners of the mouth twitched slightly, were many Xu Xiaoyan with Xu Lizhi, is really is different! If two pairs three, he has the absolute assurance to win, but two pairs five, completely were not that a matter.

After Xu Xiaoyan has released Star Wheel Chains with a smile, toward Tang Wulin one finger, Tang Wulin subconscious has made fending, but this time is anything has not actually occurred.

Xu Xiaoyan spits the tongue to him, a winning smile of face is sweet.

Tang Wulin both eyes narrow the eyes, suddenly, before his left leg cross, the right arm to behind unbends, Golden Dragon Spear changes into together the golden-colored lightning, directly soars Xu Xiaoyan direction suddenly to launch to go.

Must know that now Tang Wulin strength can describe with terrifying absolutely, in addition his own Battle Armor amplification and Golden Dragon Body amplification. The Golden Dragon Spear itself terrifying destructive power, treats as to throw the spear to project, its mighty energy, even if Seven Rings Soul Saint, must facing be earnestly good.

--------------------------------------

Asked the monthly ticket and recommendation ticket. Told everybody a good news, our «For Your I Am willing To deeply love the Entire world» soap opera approximately in April starting. It is expected that can meet with everybody at earliest at the end of this year.